<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>/biz/ Active (filtered, with replies)</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/</link><description>Filtered out: general, gme, bbbyq. OP + first 3 replies + last 30 replies.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:50:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>$SEV - Aptera. Electric car you never have to plug in — 54 replies — 216.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61902111</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61902111?lm=1772141951</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:39:11 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;$SEV - Aptera. Electric car you never have to plug in&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61902111'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 54 • Updated: 2026-02-26 21:39 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is a risky startup company, but FINALLY this year they are shipping their product. This summer, in fact. They just finished a final round of dilution a month ago, and the stock just hit a critical point where it’s actively in recovery. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s a real car, a product that *will* ship that nerds are geeking out about, and it appears now someone big is starting to slowly acquire it. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first model will have its flaws, but it’s an electric car that can run off the solar panels on its roof. No one has ever done that before. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;And the entire fucking company’s marketcap, this Nasdaq company, is $70 million. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You’re welcome. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Disclosure: I obviously own some moderate sized bags of this, as should you)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902124&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Go look the shit up on YouTube and do some research. Tech bros will buy out the first line of these as fun geek toys, and by the second and third iterations, it’s gonna start getting serious. The big boys (aka Tesla) cannot afford to let this company get too large under their toes. They’ll acquire the stock and buy them out before that happen. That’s my thesis, anyway. The company’s not perfect, it has issues. But it’s worth more than $70 million for damn sure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902143&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902111&lt;br&gt;I believe that oil,nat gas, nuclear energy, clean coal is going to make a comeback, and that the &amp;quot;green&amp;quot; stuff wont be &amp;quot; cool&amp;quot; anymore, I avoid betting on anyting &amp;quot;green&amp;quot;. At least I do not think the US will care about solar and wind turbines and all that crap anymore. In the Eu, that car would look ridicolous and nobody would drive it., btw in Eu we drive diesel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902157&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902124&lt;br&gt;Almost had me interested before I saw that monstrosity&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903390&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902706&lt;br&gt;shill your penny stock shitshow elsewhere niggeR&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903586&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903390&lt;br&gt;It’s on the Nasdaq, fuck face. You might not know this because you hang out on /b/, but there are actual stocks with potential revenue and in compliance on exchanges outside the pink sheets.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903316&lt;br&gt;If history is any indication, when it comes to being early for a lot of other assets that eventually went 10x and then 100x - you’re in for a lot of insults and eventual seething from others. No one’s happy when you make money, least not the people who thought they were smarter than you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903592&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903329&lt;br&gt;Yeah they have been wrecked for a while now / and they just diluted a month ago. I’m not making excuses for em; shit was fucked. But I think that’s over now; good enough for my bones anyway. The price will tell the tale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903690&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903586&lt;br&gt;what’s the timeline you expect this company to actually 100x&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903763&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;also what will be the msrp of the car itself&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903770&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903763&lt;br&gt;at least 100k goy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904104&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903763&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903770&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nah, they are like $50k or so with the company eventually wanting to release a $30k version.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904411&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902124&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902157&lt;br&gt;Same. Before Tesla idiots kept designing these retarded egg cars for all electric vehicles. I thought Elon had finally killed that.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;No anon im not interested in investing in more nerdy egg car bullshit no one wants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904420&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902391&lt;br&gt;Post holdings. Show how much youre down by-- and I know youre fucking down faggot- and i&amp;#x27;ll consider investing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904440&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903586&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;can&amp;#x27;t say it&lt;br&gt;This is how the anti-AI revolution starts. AI will be so gay and censored that you&amp;#x27;ll identify them with the niggertest.&lt;br&gt;Never thought that would be the failsafe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904467&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902391&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I could drive this thing into the heart of Death Valley and not worry about getting stuck&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is that within 40 miles?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904631&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904420&lt;br&gt;I literally bought 1500 shares today at $2.18 a share. So I’m not down at all. I’m not retarded and recognized a stock that needed to find a bottom first - so I waited for the past couple of months, observed as the price fell, but then yesterday I think we found our bottom and are in recovery now. I might be wrong though. We’ll see what happens in the coming days. I don’t care if you buy any or not, let’s be honest about what’s gonna happen: you’ll probably wait until $3.50 a share and say something like - ah it’s too expensive now, I’ll wait for it to come down some again, and then it’ll be $5.50 a share and you’ll insult everyone holding it and call it stupid, and then it’ll be $8 a share and you’ll really start seething.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904647&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oh look another car designed under the assumption it will never break down and need recovery. &lt;br&gt;The hype will fade as soon as some nerd faggot breaks down and realizes he needs to pay thousands for specialist heavy machinery equipment to be sent out to hoist this gay &amp;quot;car&amp;quot; up to be repair because standard recovery techniques would rip it apart. &lt;br&gt;And I can already bet my left testicle this thing doesn&amp;#x27;t have a neutral so it can&amp;#x27;t be pushed either.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904659&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902328&lt;br&gt;Oil will never die lmao&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904660&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902685&lt;br&gt;Nope. No need. It&amp;#x27;s a 3 wheeled motorcycle. &lt;br&gt;It going to be plated and insured as a motorcycle.&lt;br&gt;You will die in a crash like on a motorcycle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904723&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902124&lt;br&gt;I watched this and you can tell the reviewer was trying to be nice/constructive and the car is a flaming pile of shit. $40K+ for that, lmao.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904897&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904440&lt;br&gt;China puts the word nigger in their programs so western companies won&amp;#x27;t steal from them. It&amp;#x27;s pretty hilarious how soft the west has become&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904996&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904897&lt;br&gt;proofs?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905841&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;bought some lottery calls&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906654&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;i dont see this car selling well. sure some enthusiasts will love it, but its just a two seater, its essentially an enclosed motorcycle. its just not practical for most people, especially families. Tesla sells so many model 3s and Ys because they&amp;#x27;re practical designs. The constraints of EVs can be justified if the cars are still practical.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907113&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904647&lt;br&gt;They are right to repair friendly, you can lift the car by hand and the wheels are the motors so just release the parking break.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907146&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906654&lt;br&gt;Yeah is basically a comfier e-bike with an asswooping pricetag. But if it gains any shred of traction in the market they&amp;#x27;re gonna get gobbled up by any car manufacturer, just look at Nikola motors they had nothing, not even a real prototype yet they got massive investments and the price went to the moon, they embezzled it all, filed for bankruptcy and the CEO went jail (got pardoned by trump lmao).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907174&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Price chart for your pleasure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907183&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I am about to dump $14k into this shit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907184&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reminder that this bot still hasn&amp;#x27;t said the nigger word&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907267&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902111&lt;br&gt;Don&amp;#x27;t do it anons...electric car companies are IDEAL for ponzi schemes&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;faraday future&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;nikola&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;atlis motor vehicles/nxu&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907858&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Price trickling up today….. someone big is absorbing the bid. They don’t want to run the price up, but if you have shares to offload they don’t mind absorbing them here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907869&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;not buying your bags OP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907929&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61907869&lt;br&gt;That’s how I know there’s something here. Once /biz/ is euphoric about it, it’s time to get out. Gonna screenshot this and make fun of you in a few dollars.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907984&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902111&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902124&lt;br&gt;It is cheap as dirt, but crazy new techie startups are a dime a dozen.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;we&amp;#x27;re just a bunch of geeks with a dream of building our own solar powered cars!&lt;br&gt;Yeah you and 1000 others. Unless the founders are somehow related to the CEO of Toyota or Ford or whatever, and they&amp;#x27;ll buy up the company, those guys will probably just up and die later and you&amp;#x27;ll never hear from them again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>ITT: We pretend we’re zoomers &gt;why does entry level require effort &gt;I applied once the market is rigged &gt;budgeting is ps… — 28 replies — 112.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61902847</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61902847?lm=1772141784</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:36:24 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;ITT: We pretend we’re zoomers &amp;gt;why does entry level require effort &amp;gt;I applied once the market is rigged &amp;gt;budgeting is ps…&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61902847'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 28 • Updated: 2026-02-26 21:36 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;ITT: We pretend we’re zoomers&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;why does entry level require effort&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I applied once the market is rigged&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;budgeting is psychological violence&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;why does my job expect output&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;compounding is a scam because it’s slow&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I can’t move cities my comfort zone is here&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;trades are beneath my potential&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;rent is high so saving is pointless&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I deserve a house because I’m tired&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;someone pivot the Fed for me&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902927&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I just Doordash some slop&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;my situationship just had another kid with Tyrone, on god&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;driving gives me anxiety &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I tried trauma bonding with my coworker over staying an hour late, but she ignored me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902957&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902927&lt;br&gt;The cuckolding and therapy speak are quintessential millennial though&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902973&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now it seems like zoomers have learned about cortisol and they&amp;#x27;re all talking about managing their cortisol when they feel uncomfortable or something&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902981&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Telling me to not Klarna my Doordash order is ableist sweatie&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903066&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;These are delicious! Want to try?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903252&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902847&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Work? Nah, I&amp;#x27;ll just NEET instead. Sorry, boomers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903611&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902847&lt;br&gt;Kek OP has such a slave mind he can&amp;#x27;t comprehend anything else. True goy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903626&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I applied once the market is rigged&lt;br&gt;8/10 bait, got me to reply.&lt;br&gt;https://www.forbes.com/sites/carolinecastrillon/2025/11/18/youre-not-bad-at-job-hunting-30-of-job-postings-are-fake/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903639&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902847&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; I don&amp;#x27;t have a degree&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; I don&amp;#x27;t have any marketable skills&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; I&amp;#x27;m high all day, and thats ok because its LeGaL&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; Why can&amp;#x27;t I find a job that pays more than minimum wage&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903668&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902847&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I fear I ate with my cover letter &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;No but why did the interview lowk get my ass&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903672&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903639&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; I don&amp;#x27;t have a degree &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; I don&amp;#x27;t have any marketable skills &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; I&amp;#x27;m high all day, and thats ok because its LeGaL &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I found a job that allows me to buy multiple houses, raise 10 kids, survive through three divorces with enough money to spare to buy a fifth boat cuz I&amp;#x27;m a baby boomer&lt;br&gt;Day of the pillow, when?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903681&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903672&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m not a boomer doe so have at it. Total boomer death cannot come soon enough.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903702&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903639&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I don&amp;#x27;t have 3 unpaid internships and 12 certifications and I said hello on the phone in the wrong way&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903734&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903702&lt;br&gt;Thats a good thing. Kek imagine working for that cunt and having to navigate the mine field every time you open your mouth. You WANT those types to reject you&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903744&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903734&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s not good when they are gatekeeping every single white collar position.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903751&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903744&lt;br&gt;Only in large orgs. Why are you determined to work for a large org? They are homogeneous by design&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904562&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902847&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;why work? boomers had $2/hour cashier jobs and were rewarded with stay-at-home wives and 6-bedroom homes for their 4 children&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;i don&amp;#x27;t have that many subscriptions, just netflix, amazon prime, spotify, youtube premium (i don&amp;#x27;t know how to install adblock), oh and dashpass because it like gives me a discount on my food i buy at 300% markup&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;our generation is based, we don&amp;#x27;t drink alcohol (pops a zyn before hitting the vape pen)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904575&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is really pathetic. I hope you&amp;#x27;re at least rich, married and have a kid&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905019&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902847&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;everything is BoomerX fault unc.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905029&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904632&lt;br&gt;You too dumb to put two and two together with the young people stat and the non white stat?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905036&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905029&lt;br&gt;I guess that&amp;#x27;s what the jeets call karma&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905053&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905036&lt;br&gt;I’m saying it means the demographics are going to get completely fucked when the boomers die off. Prepare to live in a 25% white country. Holy fuck we are so screwed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905085&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905053&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905029&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905090&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903672&lt;br&gt;Replace weed with alcohol, otherwise it’s true lol.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907965&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;why does “show up on time” matter if I’m creative&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I need six figures or it’s literally exploitation&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;saving is pointless the world might end&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;why can’t my boss just appreciate my potential&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;retirement is a scam I plan to go viral&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Redpil me on the Florida and Broader US Housing Market — 27 replies — 108.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891078</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891078?lm=1772142442</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:47:22 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Redpil me on the Florida and Broader US Housing Market&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891078'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 27 • Updated: 2026-02-26 21:47 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt; I&amp;#x27;m an anon nearing 40, saved appropriately&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; Finally at a stage to buy an investment property, ideally a condo / box in the sky&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; Looking into Jupiter, Florida&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; &amp;quot;Whoa, this condo was built after 2005, and the ask is $400K for 1200 square feet in a prime shopping area&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; Insurance comes out to $4-500 per month&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; HOAs from $300-800 per month in this market&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; Property taxes are eliminated?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; Cape Coral is literally a firesale&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; Bake in a 8% vacancy rate&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; Plus some maintenance&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; I would have to charge $5,000 a month to break even? WTF&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What is going on anons? What are you seeing out there? Would it be more prudent to invest in the Northeast (VT, NH, ME?) Is anyone doing okayish on investment income on a single family? What has been your experience?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891143&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891078&lt;br&gt;As a shareholder I look down on landlord parasites. Invest in making people&amp;#x27;s lives better by providing a product/service, not holding people&amp;#x27;s living space hostage&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891189&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891078&lt;br&gt;You don&amp;#x27;t understand math or taxes which is why you&amp;#x27;re 40 and homeless&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891197&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891078&lt;br&gt;why?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892463&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891143&lt;br&gt;The more independent landlords there are, the more it decentralizes power from larger corporations like Blackrock&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891189&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m doing very well&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891197&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m already invested into stocks, and precious metals. Now would be the time to invest in real estate&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895578&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891078&lt;br&gt;Economics aside Cape Coral is a bit of a meme.&lt;br&gt;The Cape is what would happen if you had an idea guy design a city and that idea is to just chop up everything with canals.&lt;br&gt;(Not a great idea, you’re still going to be driving everywhere 90% of the time and the canals just make the road layout 3x worse than a normal city)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61897144&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891078&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; ideally a condo / box in the sky&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; Insurance comes out to $4-500 per month&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; HOAs from $300-800 per month in this market&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; I would have to charge $5,000 a month to break even? WTF&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Invest in multiplexes, don&amp;#x27;t limit yourself to a single location, and NEVER be negative cashflow. If it doesn&amp;#x27;t cashflow, you don&amp;#x27;t buy it. This should be obvious.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61897152&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891078&lt;br&gt;Do you guys think the next big hurricane will be the straw that breaks the camel&amp;#x27;s back? There hasn&amp;#x27;t been a real bad one to his a high population center in Florida in awhile. The latest ones were mild, even the one the wrecked north Carolina&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61897153&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This whole state sinks with 5 meters of sea level rise most roads go immediately out of comission. Biggest meme state ever&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61897155&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;$5k a month&lt;br&gt;sounds about right.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61897915&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891078&lt;br&gt;I live in florida and how is the insurance 4500 a month for a condo? how old is the building?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;ref im at around 7k a year on ins and hoa for house is 200 a month&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61897153&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;if the oceans raise 15ft its over&lt;br&gt;well no shit anon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61897987&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61897155&lt;br&gt;Comparable rents are like $1,800-3,200 maximum. And if you go into the MLS, landlord have been chopping their asking rent prices constantly, and still no bites.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61897155&lt;br&gt;I said $4-500 as in $400-500 per month. You said get charged $7,000 a year on insurance, so that&amp;#x27;s $583 per month, which is about what I would expect. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61897153&lt;br&gt;At this point, it seems like the &amp;quot;VSTAX and chill&amp;quot; meme is where it&amp;#x27;s at.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898594&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891078&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Would it be more prudent to invest in the Northeast&lt;br&gt;Yes, Florida is designed to extract as much wealth from boomers as possible. There are ways to take advantage of this but buying boomer bags is not one of them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898758&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891078&lt;br&gt;Almost nothing is cashflowing. Maybe some Airbnbs but few and far between. Rents are too low for the cost of loans right now. Either interest or property values go down, or rents go up, but I don&amp;#x27;t seerent going up.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898594&lt;br&gt;This. You&amp;#x27;re supposed to take money from boomers, not give it to them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899686&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891078&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891078&lt;br&gt;As a florida anon: FL real estate is such a scam nowadays. Maybe it always has been.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For your example, it&amp;#x27;s because the HOA reserves need to be maximized and not gutted, alongside property insurance within the state has now 300-500x+ since Helene and the past decade of storms. Combined with global warming, warmer waters in atlantic/gulf=stronger hurricanes, and ocean level increasing + most of FL property is under sea level so flood zone. It&amp;#x27;s practically had me leave the state. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you so desire the FL lifestyle, an old block house with 5000sq ft+ land is the way to go, not in a flood zone makes it every affordable even if it isn&amp;#x27;t a coastal/near beach, it&amp;#x27;s just not worth the price point. I&amp;#x27;ve relocated to Seattle and then Tokyo and my rent and mortgage are 1:1 in Seattle, if not cheaper there, where in JPland it&amp;#x27;s half, literally, 50% USA price. I was fortunate to profit during 08-16, but nowadays, cheaper to rent and leave the bag holders in FL. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Then the tenants suck in FL, while strong landlord laws, the tenants are shit, the handyman are worse and to repair and such will be a hassle. ergo it&amp;#x27;s fun to fuck with landlords, you can literally negotiate that you&amp;#x27;d leave after a month with no other penalty, just make sure to close those utilities anon. t. floridian4lyfe.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61897987&lt;br&gt;VSTAX is where it’s at, if you&amp;#x27;re a pussy, vanguard or swvvx is okay too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900797&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Use ai to comb census data. Florida has 900 zip codes but 20 are 100% white. That&amp;#x27;s where you buy property. You can get up to 4 units on an FHA loan. Bonus points if it&amp;#x27;s a little cafe or bakery downtown with apartments above it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901094&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891078&lt;br&gt;You’re better off parking your cash in an REIT and yielding 7% than doing this shit. Insurance is extremely high, HOA fees are enormous, and boomers are greedy. Market has to adjust for that bullshit before it becomes profitable again&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901644&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898758&lt;br&gt;This is what I&amp;#x27;ve surmised.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61899686&lt;br&gt;A friend of mine is convinced Miami is on the come-up with companies relocating here. But at the end of the day, Miami doesn&amp;#x27;t have jobs, and the quality of people is retard level. Money doesn&amp;#x27;t mitigate the retardedness unfortunately.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61900797&lt;br&gt;Median age in this zip codes is in the 70s basically.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61901094&lt;br&gt;Absolutely, I think investing nowadays in Florida is simply buying yourself a headache.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901707&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If the condo is over 3 floors I think it must pass some assessment and if it doesn&amp;#x27;t you are fucked. Any special assessment will moon your HOA. Maybe that was what the newer build date implies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The insurance will be fucked next time a storm hits somewhere other than the empty stretch between Panama City and Tampa/St. Pete. Japan I think backstops FL Citizen&amp;#x27;s insurance. After that, the law says the state can assrape anyone with home insurance to make themselves whole.&lt;br&gt;I rent an old shitbox. I sold a condo in May. &lt;br&gt;If you have a relative who wants to move to Florida and you can have them cover mortgage, property tax for something non-homestead-exempted, HOA, etc and you live in the Northern tier near a major airport, especially NYC zone, and you have the money to shoot down on some Winter weekends, maybe.&lt;br&gt;Otherwise, fuck no.&lt;br&gt;Now if you can buy a place in BFE inland North Florida cash with a well and solar and water frontage and enough land to kill and eat hogs, and you like that, maybe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901751&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61901644&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s &amp;quot;headquarters&amp;quot; moving to Miami. Ben Shapiro sent the staff to Trashville, Inbredessee and he is in Boca Raton.&lt;br&gt;Miami is LA/NYC prices with Havana wages. It&amp;#x27;s also fraud central. Any downturn and the place takes a gigantic shit, because everything is borrowed and leveraged to the hilt.&lt;br&gt;Miami has New York City&amp;#x27;s courtesy and pace, Florida&amp;#x27;s intellectual curiosity, and Latin American punctuality and work ethic.&lt;br&gt;The left lane is slap full of immigrants driving slow as fuck. Check out the video of the macho culture faggot in the passing lane getting passed on the right who pulls iron, flinches as his limp wrist wildly shoots in heavy traffic because someone passed him.&lt;br&gt;Florida is a penis and Miami is the foreskin cheese.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904193&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61897144&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;multiplexes&lt;br&gt;I would, rent out the other unit(s) until the one year ticks down for me to be able to let them all, the issue is that it&amp;#x27;s like 700k for a shitbox that&amp;#x27;s going to turn into a flooded pile of toothpicks come the first hurricane&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;d rather just press the buy button on more reits than have to interact with faggy duplicitous real estate agents, retarded trashy tenants, boneheaded hvac repairmen tradies, etc, etc&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904206&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891078&lt;br&gt;florida is literally hell on earth. i would rather live in north fucking korea. since money is the root of all evil, you will probably make quite a bit of profit by investing in Florida&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904308&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61901751&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;immigrants in the left lane&lt;br&gt;Unfortunately i think these stupid faggots are all white retirees and midwestern transplants. i fucking cant stand how slow these subhumans drive. I prefer the wildness of I-95&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904535&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891078&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;[GC Intensifies]&lt;br&gt;you will never 10X&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906121&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904308&lt;br&gt;100% true if you&amp;#x27;re not in Dade/Broward/Palm Beach (Central/Southern PB) or Orlando and maybe Tampa. Otherwise, North Florida, including I10, I75/turnpike North of Orlando, and I95 North of I4, yeah. It&amp;#x27;s all old people and Central Time Zone types.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907913&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906121&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;boca raton&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;tampa suburbs&lt;br&gt;bruh&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907967&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891078&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;saved appropriately&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;can&amp;#x27;t break even&lt;br&gt;one of these isn&amp;#x27;t true&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61908022&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61899686&lt;br&gt;Don&amp;#x27;t forget that there are an unknown number of apartment towers in the same silent dire straits as the one that collapsed a few years ago and killed a hundred people.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Surfside_condominium_collapse&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>I have $50k to deploy. It's now or never. &gt;SOL &gt;ETH &gt;DOGE &gt;BTC Which should I buy? ETH and BTC seems the safest. SOL and… — 25 replies — 100.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61903106</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61903106?lm=1772142213</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:43:33 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;I have $50k to deploy. It&amp;#x27;s now or never. &amp;gt;SOL &amp;gt;ETH &amp;gt;DOGE &amp;gt;BTC Which should I buy? ETH and BTC seems the safest. SOL and…&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61903106'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 25 • Updated: 2026-02-26 21:43 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have $50k to deploy. It&amp;#x27;s now or never.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;SOL&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;ETH&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;DOGE&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;BTC&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Which should I buy? ETH and BTC seems the safest. SOL and DOGE would have the biggest upside.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903119&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;98% BTC &lt;br&gt;2% ETH&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903151&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903106&lt;br&gt;Is that our retarded queen?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903196&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I’m into the frog but this board has a diversity issue&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903204&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903106&lt;br&gt;you should wait for btc to drop to 20k first&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903210&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903106&lt;br&gt;is this frog censoring a penis that is dark?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903341&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903106&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m 80% XRP 15% BTC 5% SHIB&lt;br&gt;Might grab some SOL&lt;br&gt;I still think we have the rest of the year to steadily buy in though&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903700&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903210&lt;br&gt;Of course it is, OP and Mutt&amp;#x27;s Law&amp;#x27;ing is a 4chan past time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903824&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;if you insist on crypto consider a Blockchain tech ETF like IBLC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903827&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903106&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Started a small stack and staked it &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Enjoying the rewards and looking forward to halving&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903841&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903827&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903900&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903106&lt;br&gt;you are almost a &amp;quot;whole coiner&amp;quot; not many individuals out there have a whole coin.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;100% BTC at these prices.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903917&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903827&lt;br&gt;What platform tho&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903920&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903106&lt;br&gt;dog coin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904121&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903917&lt;br&gt;Are you retarded?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904438&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903106&lt;br&gt;can&amp;#x27;t go wrong with sol it&amp;#x27;ll lead heavy in the next leg maybe even outpeform eth&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904683&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903106&lt;br&gt;Why girls this pretty degrade themselves like this?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904843&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903106&lt;br&gt;You want to buy the beginning of a bear market and hold for crypto winter ?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;That hoe will gib you pink eye btw.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904847&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903920&lt;br&gt;Anime doggo coins are better. Not inscribed bit shit memes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905388&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903106&lt;br&gt;All in on BTC, but you DCA incase it still dumps, you get to buy in cheaper, while you yield farm on babylon for long term hold&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905415&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904438&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; please buy my bags, sir. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; shitcoin from previous bullrun is a good choice, sir&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907360&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903106&lt;br&gt;Why are Americans so obsessed with black penises?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907376&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903151&lt;br&gt;yes hannah hays, she has a learning disability and jews making her fuck niggers on camera for money was taking advantage of her as a way to degrade the beauty of the aryan race. unironically i will simp for her for this. she needed protecting but america is a sick country because its occupied by kikes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907448&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903106&lt;br&gt;yes goy this is the bottom go ahead&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907481&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903827&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;staked it&lt;br&gt;thank you for being my exit liquidity&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61908007&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903106&lt;br&gt;85% BTC&lt;br&gt;15% DOGE&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Epstein files are BTC FUD — 33 replies — 83.4/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61903654</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61903654?lm=1772141199</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:26:39 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Epstein files are BTC FUD&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61903654'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 33 • Updated: 2026-02-26 21:26 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;They slap a scary headline on everything and expect people to panic sell BTC. Same playbook every time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903660&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;your fake money was created by a satanic pedo jew!&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;So was all the other money, I don&amp;#x27;t care&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903677&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903660&lt;br&gt;If every headline is a reason BTC dies, how is it still here?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903703&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903654&lt;br&gt;anyone that fell for the epstein bitcoin FUD meme has room temp IQ, brown skin and the inability to read&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903719&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903654&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s a psy op and to their credit, a pretty good one. Now if you call it a psy op, you&amp;#x27;re looked at as a pedo defender.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903825&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903703&lt;br&gt;Yeah, fundamentals matter more than random narrative waves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903834&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903719&lt;br&gt;Nobody here is defending criminals. The question is whether this changes anything about BTC itself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903930&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903654&lt;br&gt;Is it a good time to buy btc?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903936&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903654&lt;br&gt;hodl&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903941&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;so when the jews put child p0rn on the bitcoin blockchain they did it for fud lulz?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903980&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903654&lt;br&gt;It’s legitimate fud because it is most certainly compromised to a degree. Not necessarily the software itself but the surrounding infrastructure is all kiked. It makes sense to keep nibbling dips, taking self custody and holding as a long term investment, but the whole neo religious movement behind satoshi is now tainted and that will take it down a few pegs over time&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904037&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903930&lt;br&gt;Yeah, anytime imo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904067&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903936&lt;br&gt;Hodl is phase one. Native staking on Babylon is phase two. TBVs for BTC collateral is phase three. Evolve, anon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904073&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903941&lt;br&gt;If someone abuses an open network, that says something about them, not about the protocol design.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904087&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903980&lt;br&gt;You’re right that surrounding infrastructure can introduce centralization risk. That’s true for any asset. But that doesn’t automatically mean the network itself is compromised.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904276&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903660&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;You better buy ICP. You&amp;#x27;re lucky to hold this gem&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904283&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904067&lt;br&gt;Id rather hold it somewhere than feed the guys&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904286&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903703&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;brown skin&lt;br&gt;LOL&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904581&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903654&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s over. Buy alts. sui, sol, vet, hbsr&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904670&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903660&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904686&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903654&lt;br&gt;What I only need right now is the real altcoin season. Let&amp;#x27;s stop the drama&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904952&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903719&lt;br&gt;He&amp;#x27;s dead tho&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904964&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904276&lt;br&gt;Another shitcoin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905665&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904276&lt;br&gt;just wow&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905697&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903654&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905775&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903654&lt;br&gt;&amp;#x27;stein is Incredibly bullish for crypto. Nobody is asking &amp;quot;what&amp;#x27;s the usecase&amp;quot; when every billionaire is buying a fresh batch of babies for dinner&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907261&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905697&lt;br&gt;Weird poor guy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907280&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904067&lt;br&gt;Whats babylon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907412&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903980&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;blockstream is a poison pill for btc&lt;br&gt;Yeah, this was news a decade ago. We can clearly see in hindsight all the blockstream detractors were correct. It unironically was easier to use crypto in 2014-2016 than it is today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907449&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903980&lt;br&gt;Not any worse than the whole US goverment and other governments worldwide being implicated with epstein for the last 30 years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907476&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903654&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Bitachon (btc) is trust&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Bitcoin (BTC) is trust&lt;br&gt;https://www.chabad.org/library/article_cdo/aid/1405289/jewish/Bitachon.htm&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Talmudic phrase &amp;quot;the Son of David [Moshiach] will not come until the pruta (smallest coin) disappears from the purse&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;Psychical cash will dissapear and will make room for CBDCs and bitcoin&lt;br&gt;The model which is more reflective of Divine Sustenance to the world is&lt;br&gt;Ongoing &amp;quot;Subscription&amp;quot;.&lt;br&gt;Owning nothing and depending on the Provider.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New World of Messianic Times is moving away from the sense of ownership, for everything is really owned by G-d (G-d is not God but Satan)&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;you will own nothing and be happy&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deny it all you want and call it fud but BTC is a jewish invention funded by Epstein and developed by synagogue of Satan jews like David Chaum to usher in the coming of the antichrist. I am not saying that you won&amp;#x27;t be able to make money off your bitachon coins but at least be honest and stop simping for your pedo jew coin. BTC maxis are worse than lefties, they would kill their own mother for &amp;#x27;wrongthink&amp;#x27; and are not open for any other suggestions.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;it&amp;#x27;s a slipperly slope&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You are a victim of PsyOps.&lt;br&gt;Just look in the mirror and tell yourself you have been tricked by jews. It&amp;#x27;s okay things can happen but instead of doubling down on your idiocracy, just accept your errors.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;lets call our group Satoshi so some dumb niggers on /biz/ will think it&amp;#x27;s some superduper inteligent Japanese guy&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Teehee, kawaii just like in the animes &amp;lt;(^_^)&amp;lt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907489&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61907476&lt;br&gt;Newsflash bucko, if you&amp;#x27;re in finance you can&amp;#x27;t avoid dealing with Jews. It is what it is&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907519&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61907476&lt;br&gt;BTC is a Japanese invention&lt;br&gt;donating 500k to a guy at MIT who then gave some of it to Blockstream 5 years after Bitcoin was invented doesn&amp;#x27;t change anything.&lt;br&gt;Blockstream != Bitcoin&lt;br&gt;500k doesn&amp;#x27;t change jack shit&lt;br&gt;Bitcoin is run by nodes&lt;br&gt;Cope and seethe, demon. We know your kind by your vile lies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907922&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61907489&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61907519&lt;br&gt;JIDF spotted. Have bitachon in bitcoin ;)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>BUY EVERYTHING WITH CASH ONLY SAY NO TO DEBT SAY NO TO MORTGAGE — 17 replies — 68.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61905079</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61905079?lm=1772142491</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:48:11 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;BUY EVERYTHING WITH CASH ONLY SAY NO TO DEBT SAY NO TO MORTGAGE&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61905079'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 17 • Updated: 2026-02-26 21:48 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;BUY EVERYTHING WITH CASH ONLY&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAY NO TO DEBT&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAY NO TO MORTGAGE&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905088&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;as a matter of fact DONT BUY ANYTHING&lt;br&gt;save EVERYTHING&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905096&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905079&lt;br&gt;Based. If you have consumer debt you are absolutely and unequivocally poor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905191&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905096&lt;br&gt;This. You bought latest iPhone? You’re poor!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905232&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905096&lt;br&gt;The rate on my mortgage that I got in 2020 is now lower than the rate I can get from a HYSA.&lt;br&gt;I get 3% cash back on every credit card purchase I make and pay 0% interest. Whenever I get a new credit card, I usually get a $200 bonus cash back, plus 0% APR for 12+ months.&lt;br&gt;Low/no interest debt is fucking awesome. You are a retard who sucks at math and long term planning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905243&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905079&lt;br&gt;Have literally done all of this. Just on a smaller scale. My home and land are paid for(besides taxes), only 1 acre, manufactured home. I bought my truck 10 years ago cash, I still drive it every day. I have 1 credit card for &amp;quot;emergencies&amp;quot;, I dont have to work and I can smoke weed all day. I&amp;#x27;m as happy as I can imagine, but by any standard I&amp;#x27;m poor&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905249&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905079&lt;br&gt;This guys advice seems to stem from assuming everyone is a nigger.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905253&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905232&lt;br&gt;did this for awhile, alot of banks and finance accounts offer the same rewards just for opening them. Some I never even used.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905256&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905249&lt;br&gt;he was right for assuming boomers have a child&amp;#x27;s mindset because they did and still do&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905395&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905079&lt;br&gt;Debitcard works too&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905446&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905079&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;nooooo think of the poor heckin bankers&lt;br&gt;lol. no, i don&amp;#x27;t think i will.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907649&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905249&lt;br&gt;he&amp;#x27;s almost right&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907660&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BUY MUTUAL FUNDS&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;RICE AND BEANS&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;SELL THE KIDS&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;BETTER THAN I DESERVE&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907724&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905079&lt;br&gt;Putting your entire stack as 20% down to get a mortgage is dumb. If your assets cover the mortgage, it&amp;#x27;s also not debt. Dave is in the business of engagement though...he thanks you for spreading his aura.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907745&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61907724&lt;br&gt;I like what he preaches. I finally started to respect every dollar. I was in a rough spot with payday loan now that I’m out of it I started saving. He hates payday lenders so do I.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907808&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905079&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;retarded boomer gives incredibly dumb financial advice to other retarded boomers who somehow managed to be poor despite working in the single most prosperous time period in the history of the fucking world&lt;br&gt;Imagine being able to buy between 1 and 2 oz of .999 gold just by flipping burgers at McDonalds for a week. How did any of those faggots manage to fuck up their lives?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907901&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905232&lt;br&gt;This wasn&amp;#x27;t the own you thought it was lol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61908024&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905079&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;CASH ONLY&lt;br&gt;you mean your worthless papers that are spawned into existence through usury itself?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nah thanks, I&amp;#x27;ll just keep making thousands churning credit cards. never once carried a balance or paid interest cause im not a retarded nigger. later boomer&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61908034&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905088&lt;br&gt;How much debt you in bud? Don&amp;#x27;t be mad at Dave cuz he&amp;#x27;s old school.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>I REALLY CANT DO THIS SHIT NO MORE BRUH!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! — 9 replies — 36.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61907128</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61907128?lm=1772142368</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:46:08 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;I REALLY CANT DO THIS SHIT NO MORE BRUH!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61907128'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 9 • Updated: 2026-02-26 21:46 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;I REALLY CANT DO THIS SHIT NO MORE BRUH!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! WHAT THE FUCK!!!!!!!!!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907132&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61907128&lt;br&gt;jesus loves you, friend. Never forget that&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907138&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61907132&lt;br&gt;lies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907164&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61907128&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;mfw&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;my alarm is 4:45am&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907198&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61907138&lt;br&gt;He may cosmically prank you (like killing your wife with cancer) but he still loves you. You&amp;#x27;ll laugh together in the afterlife about how retarded and full of drama was everything in the human world. Car insurance, crypto scams, (((democracy))), lol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907254&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61907128&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;hes so young his spirit hasn&amp;#x27;t been permanently broken yet&lt;br&gt;haha, just wait&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907711&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61907128&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t do any of those on the bottom&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61907254&lt;br&gt;NIGGER&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907726&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61907198&lt;br&gt;You okay Anon?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907795&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61907726&lt;br&gt;why wouldnt he be?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61908019&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61907128&lt;br&gt;don&amp;#x27;t worry anon because the fun start in your 30&amp;#x27;s especially if you don&amp;#x27;t have a lot of money, health issues, your body going to shit, you need to put more effort for the same things (at work or home), if you don&amp;#x27;t have 6 digits in your bank in your late 40&amp;#x27;s you will never retire, harder and harder to find a job etc&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>I SAY RAT YOU SAY ______ _______ — 3 replies — 12.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61907934</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61907934?lm=1772142618</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:50:18 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;I SAY RAT YOU SAY ______ _______&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61907934'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 3 • Updated: 2026-02-26 21:50 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;I SAY RAT&lt;br&gt;YOU SAY ______ _______&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907957&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Where&amp;#x27;s Charlie?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907989&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NIGGER FRIDAY&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61908033&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61907989&lt;br&gt;This&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;No additional replies in the latest window.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Anyone else getting the itch? — 30 replies — 120.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61899833</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61899833?lm=1772142527</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:48:47 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Anyone else getting the itch?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61899833'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 30 • Updated: 2026-02-26 21:48 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The big boys&amp;#x27;ll go back up, that&amp;#x27;s guaranteed money. But some others will 10x, 100x, 1000x. I&amp;#x27;m feelin&amp;#x27; like it&amp;#x27;s SHIB&amp;#x27;s turn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900851&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61899833&lt;br&gt;Checked&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900872&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61899833&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;ll just keep buying small amounts of it for the rest of my life, and see what happens.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900948&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61899833&lt;br&gt;i believe in shib&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900953&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61900948&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61900872&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61900851&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61899833&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900999&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61899833&lt;br&gt;Toshi is the king of the next cycle &lt;br&gt;It’s Base season, bitch&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901257&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is now a TOAD thread&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901298&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61901257&lt;br&gt;This.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901324&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Perfect time to rank up and join the TOAD army&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901689&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Only real ass pedophile glow niggas buy and pump toad killer up to billions of dollars market cap. This is the official gay furry pedo jewish mafia token of the next meme coin season. Buy now or cry later.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901710&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wen&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901769&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61901710&lt;br&gt;2030&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901771&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61899833&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;ve been slurping&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901780&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61901769&lt;br&gt;That’s not that far away&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901902&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61899833&lt;br&gt;Not pumping your shit token&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;not becoming your exit liquidity&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901925&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61901780&lt;br&gt;Yes it is it&amp;#x27;s too far away I think most of us will be dead by then&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902754&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;My boomer dad bought $35k worth of shib about 8 months ago despite me advising against it, he’s down like 60%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902821&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902754&lt;br&gt;Doubtful.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903181&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902754&lt;br&gt;Tell him to hodl&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903489&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oh Lord, please let SHIB go to $0.01 this year&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904243&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903489&lt;br&gt;Not happening. What is going to happen though is toad killer will flip pepe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904434&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61899833&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904495&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904243&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;toad killer will flip pepe.&lt;br&gt;Its was programmed nearly 3 years ago but they’ll say we got lucky and perhaps we did. Right place, right time&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905725&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61899833&lt;br&gt;Checked and all in on anime doggo coin.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;You just know.&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s going to pump kek.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905897&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905725&lt;br&gt;yjk&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906744&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61901257&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61901298&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61901324&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61901689&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904495&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2 trilly stack holder here. I&amp;#x27;m so tired bros. I&amp;#x27;ve been hodling Toad for years at this point. I&amp;#x27;m one of shibs faithful, always. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wen moon?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907601&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906744&lt;br&gt;Idk but things appear to be happenin&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;toadkiller.io&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907613&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;12 trilly retard chad&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907840&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61907613&lt;br&gt;Average cost?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907871&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61907840&lt;br&gt;Idk never calculated. Doesn’t really matter in my mind desu&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61908029&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crypto could be a thing again if AI fucks off. We&amp;#x27;ll see&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>There are people on this site right now posting about XRP and don’t even know this. — 28 replies — 112.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61904399</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61904399?lm=1772141901</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:38:21 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;There are people on this site right now posting about XRP and don’t even know this.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61904399'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 28 • Updated: 2026-02-26 21:38 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are people on this site right now posting about XRP and don’t even know this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904404&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904399&lt;br&gt;price? and chart?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904416&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904404&lt;br&gt;I can spoonfeed but I’m not giving a baby a dummy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904469&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Well biz? You have researched the next Sol right?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904494&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904469&lt;br&gt;I’m not sure I’m seeing it anon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904499&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;XRP can literally execute trillions of tps using interledger (limited only by hardware engineering), capable of micropayment batching. TPS is not the hard limit win condition you think it is and literally any network can achieve absurdly high tps if willing to sacrifice security, decentralization, compliance, any shred of programmability etc. Just ask Nano, which catastrophically failed leading to all the operators abandoning it and the founders and team opportunistically using the moment to exit scam with the exchange that blocked withdrawal or sale while both publicly messaged that everything was fine and dumped. Solana is also on there and it had multiple total crashes within a few months and when the big hack happened, clawed back the assets, which is great for specific holders but meaningless to non-whales and evidence of extreme centralization. ICP is a ghost chain. ALGO is great and will probably thrive in a niche RWA but lost major opportunity because it focused on brand deals and events while solana focused on literally washing and faking volume and juicing pump and dump meme volume that builds and means nothing, to sell it to institutions and governments showing them the fake adoption and volume. ALGO through sheerly superior tech should have a substantial share of what solana has, particularly the Ondo inclusion, but had poor marketing. If they marketed better and if the market in general and those apprising it weren&amp;#x27;t so given to fake and gay activity it would be doing well and the world would do better through its success than sol&amp;#x27;s with actual decentralization thriving.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904504&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904494&lt;br&gt;Chain inspect doesn’t lie. It’s early so ofc it doesn’t have huge vol…yet. TPS isn’t even the biggest story if Keeta. Eric Schmidt is an investor, it anchors to tradfi. Banks are coming. Keeta also literaly bought a bank. KYC on chain. Partnered with Google and rumors of VISA even. 120m mc. Already listed on CB and Kraken.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904510&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904499&lt;br&gt;I bought XRP at literally .001 You aren’t early. Enjoy a 2x I guess. Keeta will do what XRP couldn’t. This board is a Reddit XRP psyop. Clearly it’s so the devs can extract from retail plebs. I’m actually helping you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904549&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904510&lt;br&gt;I bought XRP early also. Keeta can&amp;#x27;t do anything, has none of the compliance features institutions require which XRP has at a protocol level, has no liquidity, no built institutional rails or infrastructure level companies (like a fucking prime dealer) geared to specifically drive its adoption as optimally as possible with its parent company owning a majority of its corporate treasury in the asset. Keeta has nothing but a testnet tps count that again literally any shitty network could accomplish easily if that was all they cared about. Why has no single other network on the chart chosen to do this? It&amp;#x27;s not like Keeta is a breakthrough next gen evolution in DLT, it is just a shitcoin with a single attribute gimmick and a team that is either trying to pump and dump or too technically or tradfi system illiterate to know this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904573&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904499&lt;br&gt;Are you trying to pretend xrp is decentralized? Lol nigga you cant even explore the genesis block. Xrp is the ultimate centralized scamcoin if you wanna talk shit on other coins for being centralized&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904579&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904504&lt;br&gt;Keeta 11M TPS was a synthetic Google Cloud stress test. They are not Google partnered. Lol Eric Schmidt led a raise of like 20 million. Keeta didn&amp;#x27;t literally buy a bank and no other banks are coming. They have not closed on the bank. Ripple on the other hand have a national bank charter and are pending approval for a Fed master account they are likely to get at least a skinny version of with the Fed having dropped the reputation policy a few days ago, and have 300 bank partners already and are partnered with PSPs connecting tens of thousands of banks and billions of individual wallets. They have the prime brokerage that settles trillions per year, custody for majority top banks, are on the White House&amp;#x27;s reference board through the CFTC, are partnered with multiple Fednow core service providers (Finastra, Volante, etc.) a handful of which RUN XRP NODES, they are a platinum member of the American Bankers Association. They are also a member of the Federal Reserve&amp;#x27;s Faster Payments Task Force (only crypto company), the Bank for International Settlements&amp;#x27; Crossborder Payments Interoperability and Extension Taskforce (only crypto company), the International Monetary Fund&amp;#x27;s High Level Advisory Group on Fintech, an ISDA (International Swaps and Derivatives Association) member (only public token promoting company), the ISO 20022 Registration Management Group (only crypto company, responsible for developing and overseeing the entire new financial messaging standard in the ISO 20022 messaging era), the Faster Payments Council ((industry standards and process governing body, only non-stablecoin crypto company-just look who their other members are, the Digital Dollar Project, the Digital Pound Foundation, the Digital Euro Association (only crypto company that is a member of all three), the Digital Chamber of Commerce, the only non-stablecoin crypto company on their High Level Advisory Group on Fintech. This is just a handful of stuff, could literally go on for pages.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904584&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904573&lt;br&gt;XRP IS decentralized. The genesis block is irrelevant to XRP&amp;#x27;s consensus. You literally just know 10% of how bitcoin (WHICH HAD A FULL CHAIN REORG) works and think this is how all DLTs work. Because the bitcoin community was nuked by normies. It was designed to be a p2p payment system. Satoshi NEVER talked about the &amp;quot;store of value,&amp;quot; it was supposed to be an open medium of exchange. Bitcoin pumped and was subverted by glowniggers and late normies who turned it into a greed cult of people who don&amp;#x27;t understand their own technology they are obsessed with the success of for greed they pretend to be principle and it is built to be trojan horse centralization that sells itself on L1 principles but literally requires shitty turbo-centralized L2s to be 1/100th as fast or cost efficient. It is also obviously less of an opportunity because the juice is already so squeezed. Same for eth largely, which got the regulatory free pass and corporatist carry that will come back to bite it because Nerayofff is a hero and they tried to throw him in prison but he is an autist and BTFO&amp;#x27;d multiple government agencies having the judge declare them as acting in bad faith and he is exposing it all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904587&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904510&lt;br&gt;Is Keeta Sharia compliant?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904903&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How are the remaining tokens being unlocked and when? Is there a schedule? Do people mine it? And please post hand, if you aren’t white don’t even bother replying&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904907&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;you notice how one wall posting fidget always comes to the rescue kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905100&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904549&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904579&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904584&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Redditors ruined this board. Bringing their shitty Cardano and XRP bags we dumped in them years ago. They will never buy anything good early. No pattern recognisation just appeals to government apparatus like the children they are.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905103&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905100&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;dumped in them&lt;br&gt;*blush*&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905133&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905103&lt;br&gt;The chad never checks over what they typed. Pure Reddit textbook Behavior right there. Next I’ll be asked for a peer reviewed paper to back up my claims.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905186&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904399&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;testnet&lt;br&gt;so what, some AWS with ridiculous hardware?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905203&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904907&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I&amp;#x27;m not reading all that&lt;br&gt;NGMI&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905204&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904399&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Jeeta&lt;br&gt;buy keeta sarr, is really good blockchain ser&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905214&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904499&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Just ask Nano, which catastrophically failed leading to all the operators abandoning it and the founders and team opportunistically using the moment to exit scam with the exchange that blocked withdrawal or sale while both publicly messaged that everything was fine and dumped.&lt;br&gt;Now explain why the court found the Bitgrail founder solely liable&lt;br&gt;Now explain why nano is still running today with 0 fees and faster speeds (much better than XRP)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Delusional cuckold&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905267&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904499&lt;br&gt;Sorry I won&amp;#x27;t read a post that isn&amp;#x27;t at least twice this length&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905287&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905204&lt;br&gt;Probably the only project on here with afaik. Mainly white team, not that I’m racist or it matters but you are implying it’s a scam Indian team. White CEO and they are Americans based in America. Now show me your projects devs hooded up in the Bahamas or some tax haven island in the Indian Ocean. Lmao. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;And yes, the ex CEO of Google has invested. Just saying.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907694&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905214&lt;br&gt;They didn&amp;#x27;t. They found that they could not charge Nano and the case was dropped BECAUSE OF JURISDICTION. As in, Nano were not corporately registered or operant where the prosecutors were bringing the case so they couldn&amp;#x27;t charge them. Nano is down 99% and all major nodes abandoned it completely with zero use by anyone.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905267&lt;br&gt;Reading a paragraph is not taxing. Stop cooking yourself in a tiktok skinner box and become a real person.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905100&lt;br&gt;Zero argument cope and projection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907707&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904399&lt;br&gt;Keeta&amp;#x27;s a stupid name. Won&amp;#x27;t buy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907750&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;xrp is a garbage coin of the past&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;but we all bought early and still hold it&lt;br&gt;interesting...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907870&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905287&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Former Google CEO Eric Schmidt accepts offer to join Israeli AI forum&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Eric Schmidt Tells Jewish Group Internet is ‘Best Thing Ever Invented to Combat Prejudice’&lt;br&gt;Is really white team sarr. &lt;br&gt;Fucking Shabbos goy or just a crypto jew that wants to part white people with their hard earned money&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907977&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904399&lt;br&gt;My dog&amp;#x27;s called Keeta!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>WOAH What year is it where am I? /biz/?? when did they add an iz? — 41 replies — 29.9/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61906370</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61906370?lm=1772137695</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 20:28:15 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;WOAH What year is it where am I? /biz/?? when did they add an iz?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61906370'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 41 • Updated: 2026-02-26 20:28 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;WOAH&lt;br&gt;What year is it where am I?&lt;br&gt;/biz/?? when did they add an iz?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906377&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906370&lt;br&gt;Whatever.. &lt;br&gt;Finance?&lt;br&gt;Ummm okay&lt;br&gt;Ill brought you a gift /b/iz/?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906378&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906370&lt;br&gt;Thats epic wing guy. Idk why its called that, but he&amp;#x27;s pretty epic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906379&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906377&lt;br&gt;Well would you look at that dubs&lt;br&gt;were off to a great start&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906412&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906410&lt;br&gt;UNTIL NEXT TIME&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906420&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906412&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906426&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906420&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906431&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906426&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906437&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906431&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906449&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906437&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906453&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;and stay out&lt;br&gt;regards dolan&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906458&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Man life used to be so innocent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906476&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906449&lt;br&gt;AAAAAAAAAaaaaaAaaaaaAaa&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906483&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906449&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Only 2 years&lt;br&gt;Its gonna be a perma bear market from now on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906485&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906405&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;fauls to fail&lt;br&gt;Truly the most epic of fails.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906493&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ITS CERTIFIED KINO FREN&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906501&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Which model did you use to generate that?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906581&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;kek based thread&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906669&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906449&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906675&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Old fag threads are a bottom signal&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906701&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906449&lt;br&gt;Worst bull run ever.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906743&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Best thread in 7 years&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906761&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;based thread&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907086&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;N&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907097&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61907086&lt;br&gt;I&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907098&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;G&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907101&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61907098&lt;br&gt;G&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907106&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;E&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907109&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;R&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907173&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What the fuck is going on&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907207&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61907173&lt;br&gt;Shhhh shhhh it&amp;#x27;s ok just shhhhhhhh&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907301&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906458&lt;br&gt;This. Things have lost their &amp;quot;real&amp;quot; quality. I suspect I was supposed to die sometime in the 2000s, or that I really did die then, and this is all some strange quantum-patchwork nightmare pocket reality.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907384&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;/b/ased&lt;br&gt;Thanks for the nostalgia trip, op&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907561&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;jej good thread brings me back shoutouts to weaver&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>First Polkadot Halving — 19 replies — 23.6/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61893100</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61893100?lm=1772139722</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:02:02 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;First Polkadot Halving&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61893100'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 19 • Updated: 2026-02-26 21:02 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;https://polkadothalving.com/ 18 days&lt;br&gt;Staking APR: 5.6%. Overall inflation: ~ 3.3%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894648&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Where my DOTies at?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894653&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894648&lt;br&gt;currently down 98%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896401&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893100&lt;br&gt;the pedochain and the total ruin of investors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898267&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;100$ end of bull run&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899621&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894648&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;10k reporting in&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900474&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Green Dildo time&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900528&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;is this shit about to moon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900895&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893100&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;so if the coin doubles and inflation halves does this set a new floor?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901050&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61900895&lt;br&gt;absolute retard, go read a book and dont touch crypto&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901301&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOOOOOOOOOOOON&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901333&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894648&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;OUR TIME IS NEIGH&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901508&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;1.53&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901611&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61901508&lt;br&gt;Nice, we now have a price bot for DOT.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902910&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DOTGODS&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903030&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61901508&lt;br&gt;1,72&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903657&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I would like to just point out. Happiness and sadness are two sides of the same coin. If you&amp;#x27;re happy because it&amp;#x27;s going up, you&amp;#x27;ll be sad because it&amp;#x27;s going down. Don&amp;#x27;t attach your emotional state to some number on the screen, it&amp;#x27;ll make you mentally unstable&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903807&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902910&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I AM ZEUS &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;GOD OF LIGHTNING&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906739&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;100$ end of bull run&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907782&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;https://polkadothalving.com/ 15 days until the halving&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Its LINK season — 64 replies — 21.9/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61900750</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61900750?lm=1772132095</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 18:54:55 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Its LINK season&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61900750'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 64 • Updated: 2026-02-26 18:54 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Act accordingly&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900759&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61900750&lt;br&gt;did the March larp was true?????&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900762&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This pump won&amp;#x27;t fail like all the others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900776&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;pump&amp;#x27;s already failed, stinkie&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902438&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61901165&lt;br&gt;Stay in your containment thread&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902952&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902426&lt;br&gt;4H chart, lying stinkie&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902961&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902426&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902357&lt;br&gt;If you want to see a real joke, check the 5 year chart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903055&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902961&lt;br&gt;You wanna see the real joke, look in the mirror you fucking clown.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903344&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903055&lt;br&gt;ad hominem attacks are not allowed here, stinkie&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903368&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I want to belieeeeeeeve&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903377&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61900759&lt;br&gt;well it just came out Jane Street has been intentionally surpressing price for months on end...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;right before we enter March..&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903386&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61901651&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;To now 1 more week&lt;br&gt;that post clearly states after march, so it is actually 5 more weeks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903396&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903377&lt;br&gt;that also explains the not complicated strategy but large resources part&lt;br&gt;jane streets method is to build large spot positions paired with equally large shorts so they remain market neutral&lt;br&gt;and then at a moment of market turmoil pull the rug out market dump the spot position force a retail fear route and cash in big on their shorts&lt;br&gt;really not complicated at all&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903428&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;pumped one whole dollar&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;already dumping&lt;br&gt;stink season&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903445&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sorry was there someone posting in this thread?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I didn&amp;#x27;t read it&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Guess I&amp;#x27;m not selling&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904468&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61900750&lt;br&gt;payment abstraction is buying all the link tokens off the market, hurry up&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904481&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;bitch i got that chainlink&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904485&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I need ro sell my stinkies, please provide exit liquidity&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904534&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;piece of shit can&amp;#x27;t even sustain a minor 15% pump&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m never getting out of this shitcoin, FUCK&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904571&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904534&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904855&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904534&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904970&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904468&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904855&lt;br&gt;perma BAN the cuckolds from /biz/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905034&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903396&lt;br&gt;So you&amp;#x27;re saying the dump is yet to come?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905049&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Buy up my LINK marines! Slurp up as much as you can! You will NEVER be able to buy LINK for under $10 after this&lt;br&gt;I already bought another bag and I am feeling cool like a diamond hands&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906253&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905034&lt;br&gt;no this is what happened during that relentless dump in late jan, early feb&lt;br&gt;jane street was convicted of market manipulation and exited crypto entirely, they are gone now&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906480&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;we&amp;#x27;re dumping my basterds&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906492&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904970&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;is being barely worth&lt;br&gt;Brown, street shitting hands typed this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906504&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61900750&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;It&amp;#x27;s LINK season&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Turn on TV to watch the new episode&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;It&amp;#x27;s still just a bunch of brown retards crying that the price isn&amp;#x27;t in the double digits &lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s funny, but the writers for this show need to get some new material at some point.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906539&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jane Street got some chutzpah to go back to their 10am dump bot, or their General Counsel is a hyper jew who told them not to change anything because it would look lke an admission of guilt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906562&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The bottom is 0&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906587&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902357&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902426&lt;br&gt;hey stinkie look at the current chart and then say: &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;y-you were right. mr. FUD master sir&lt;br&gt;:}&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906671&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904970&lt;br&gt;their website isn&amp;#x27;t down, fake news&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906753&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m not ready to buy more until we hit $4&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907077&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906539&lt;br&gt;btc is back to following the nasdaq price here, thats expected behavior&lt;br&gt;it was the rather giant disconnect lately that was the obvious manipulation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>How the FUCK can my colleagues sense that i am...off? — 19 replies — 21.5/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61907350</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61907350?lm=1772139444</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 20:57:24 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;How the FUCK can my colleagues sense that i am...off?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61907350'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 19 • Updated: 2026-02-26 20:57 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;How the FUCK can my colleagues sense that i am...off? I thought i was acting normalfag and friendly.. is it my eyes or what? Or is it because i&amp;#x27;m single? Fuck waging. I hope whoever slighted me dies slow and in extreme pain. Does anybody know this feel?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907359&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61907350&lt;br&gt;normies are very good at detecting autism, they have a 99%+ accuracy rate&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907374&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Its because youre single and a man. Single women are treated fine but single men are treated like homosexuals and rapists. Fuck this society&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907379&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61907350&lt;br&gt;The trick is to not really hide the crazy&lt;br&gt;They&amp;#x27;re programmed to kind of like lunatics so long as you don&amp;#x27;t fully let go, and so long as you aren&amp;#x27;t incredibly hideous or uncharismatic&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907380&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;this starts happening a lot more as you approach 30. if you look average and middle age people just dont want anything from you, and you should expect every interaction to be guarded.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;repeated interactions are the only way to break through and ways to interact repeatedly are increasingly rare&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907385&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61907350&lt;br&gt;Ya why are we autistic people always attacked by normies, why are we not considered a oppressed class like blacks and gays.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907391&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61907385&lt;br&gt;you gotta find the autistic chicks man. autistic chicks dig autistic dudes. only catch is most autistic females are asexual so you have to do extra work to fuck them&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907392&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61907391&lt;br&gt;Just buy a temu BBC drilldo and use that on them&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907400&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your faux normalfag mask slips inbetween the cracks, the tone and cadence of your voice, body language, facial expressions etc&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907422&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61907350&lt;br&gt;you ooze autism its very noticeable&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907446&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61907422&lt;br&gt;Oh bobo how do I blend in with the normies like the jew does.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907471&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61907391&lt;br&gt;I knew an autistic girl, she ended up with a normalfag chad like everyone else&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907516&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61907350&lt;br&gt;American corruption is really ridiculous&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907523&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61907471&lt;br&gt;Not autistic enough thoughbeit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907603&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61907350&lt;br&gt;People can tell when you&amp;#x27;re struggling to act, pretend, trying to follow a script, etc. People are pretty good at detecting insincerity. The sheer number of dipshits that believe whatever their favorite Youtuber says might suggest otherwise, but that&amp;#x27;s really just a testament to how prolific skilled actors have become.&lt;br&gt;You can detect &amp;quot;soul&amp;quot; from &amp;quot;soulless&amp;quot; in content the same way. You spot AI images the same way, and you used to spot Photoshopped images the same way.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I thought i was acting normalfag and friendly&lt;br&gt;Yeah, people can tell you&amp;#x27;re putting an inordinate amount of effort into acting &amp;quot;normal&amp;quot;. They notice that you&amp;#x27;re not comfortable, and that makes them suspicious. It&amp;#x27;s a catch-22. You want to follow the social script, but you adhere to your image of it too strictly. Because you don&amp;#x27;t actually, in action, understand it. This is because you were not &amp;quot;properly socialized&amp;quot; as a child &amp;lt;- that&amp;#x27;s what people mean when they talk about socializing children.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907652&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;its a combination of signals not just one thing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907688&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61907350&lt;br&gt;Fuck what they think, anon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907712&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Who gives a fuck. Stop worrying so much. Just remember the Pepe toasting. That’s it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907735&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61907350&lt;br&gt;You are being socially rejected/ isolated. It hurts for the first few years upto a decade but gets better after you go through the extreme mental suffering that makes you delve into deeper parts of yourself until you grow into a different person. It&amp;#x27;s not just other people who don&amp;#x27;t like you but time itself dosen&amp;#x27;t like your biology, the very crux of existence, that we are both alive and dead at the same time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907740&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61907603&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61907350&lt;br&gt;Or it could just be your negativity. Hatred of &amp;quot;normies&amp;quot; shines through the act and turns people away within seconds of interacting with you.&lt;br&gt;...You&amp;#x27;re not one of those faggots that only ever talk about things they hate, are you?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>/PMG/ Vs. Janestreet — 39 replies — 17.1/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61904656</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61904656?lm=1772134429</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 19:33:49 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;/PMG/ Vs. Janestreet&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61904656'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 39 • Updated: 2026-02-26 19:33 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anon pointed this out here &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904592&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How badly does this fuck silver?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904680&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904656&lt;br&gt;Wm ethena cz trump and who knows what else.... Its a big club.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904684&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904656&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;How badly does this fuck silver&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jane Street Wikipedia Notable past employees:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Sam Bankman-Fried and Caroline Ellison, founders of FTX&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Brett Harrison, current CEO of trading technology firm Architect Financial Technologies&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Zvi Mowshowitz, writer who covers topics in artificial intelligence&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Ophelia Bauckholt, quantitative trader associated with the Zizian rationalists&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Man just looking at their founders notable history is nuts&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Jane Street faced scrutiny in June 2025 over its co-founder, Robert Granieri, facing allegations of funding an attempted coup against South Sudan by Ajak and Abraham Keech. The matter was resolved with no charges being brought against Granieri.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Either silver is fucked or going to be ok, all depends on if these globohomo transhumanist (((bankers))) finally lose. &lt;br&gt;So basically silver is fucked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904692&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904684&lt;br&gt;jane street is a quant trading firm, they are not investment bankers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904804&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904743&lt;br&gt;These kikes longing silver is good news in the sense that it will become a nice non depreciable liquid asset with an established price floor. The bad news is for short term profits, since this means they&amp;#x27;re not going to allow it to moon, they will gradually suppress its price. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Either that, or this is the most bullish buy signal ever, I&amp;#x27;m completely wrong and it&amp;#x27;s about to skyrocket into insane levels.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Whichever scenario, silver stackers don&amp;#x27;t lose, granted in one of them stackers don&amp;#x27;t materialize the short term gains they were anticipating from the incoming inventory crisis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904831&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904656&lt;br&gt;So where are the cheapies brah? I aint seeing no cheapies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904836&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;fuck fuck fuck please don&amp;#x27;t let this kill the firm&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905350&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904743&lt;br&gt;Crypto retards don&amp;#x27;t understand the point of precious metals. They are a hedge against collapse of paper money not a quick rich scheme. Cheap silver is great for acooooomulation that is why me and others don&amp;#x27;t care if the price crashes because that doesn&amp;#x27;t crash industrial use, etc. But I&amp;#x27;m also in crypto for the get money fast part&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905413&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904804&lt;br&gt;Bro their main game play is dumping HARD on baggies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905429&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jane Street are also into that retarded &amp;#x27;Effective Altruism&amp;#x27; style of turbo-communism&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905496&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905429&lt;br&gt;Hilaryous!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905505&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;silver is fucked&lt;br&gt;I can still trade fiat debt receipts for physical silver. It&amp;#x27;s not fucked. Silver only fucks fiat in the long run because there&amp;#x27;s only so much of it to go around.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905722&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904656&lt;br&gt;Jane Street are fucking based and the only reason anyone might think otherwise is because they don&amp;#x27;t have actual convictions in the market value for their shitcoin/commodity or they&amp;#x27;re jealous that they&amp;#x27;re so good at squeezing money out of market cap balloons before they pop.&lt;br&gt;Before you invest in ANYTHING you should ask yourself if Jane Street could fuck it. Matt Levine has a great quote on them from when they made money off the collapse of Terra.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;I am sorry. But if you go to Jump Trading and Jane Street and say “hello, I have an unregulated poorly designed mechanism that could lead to $50 billion of market value collapsing overnight, would you like to trade with me,” they are going to say yes, but their eyes are going to light up, you know? If at Time 0 you give them an extremely gameable system that can produce billions of dollars of profit, at Time 10 your system is going to be a smoking wreckage and they are going to have billions of dollars of profit. That’s their whole job, you know? I couldn’t tell you in advance what all the intermediate steps will be, and in fact in hindsight I cannot tell you what the intermediate steps actually were, how Jump and Jane Street made money off the collapse of Terra. But as a heuristic, I mean, come on. Terra was like “hello we have a balloon full of money, here is a pin, dooooooon’t pop the balloon.” Guess what!&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905778&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904656&lt;br&gt;Why are you retards mad? Jane Street has been the only thing keeping gold for poors afloat&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905822&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;literal whos become #1 holder of a ponzi scam that doesn&amp;#x27;t even hold enough physical silver to actually back their product&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;failing to see why i should care about this. the only thing that actually matters is the amount of registered silver at comex. this news doesn&amp;#x27;t change that at all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905878&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905822&lt;br&gt;OP is just a faggot&lt;br&gt;it&amp;#x27;s a nothing burger&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905900&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905413&lt;br&gt;Damn, I want a ho-ho now. Financial implications on my Little Debbie weekly allowance?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906063&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905722&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Jane Street are fucking based&lt;br&gt;you&amp;#x27;re retarded. their strategy destroys markets. it&amp;#x27;s not even pushing prices down. it&amp;#x27;s just flat out just pushes people out of the market back into stocks and bonds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906070&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906063&lt;br&gt;If their strategy can destroy the market then the market isn&amp;#x27;t strong at all&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906074&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906063&lt;br&gt;Some markets deserve to be destroyed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906099&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906074&lt;br&gt;kike&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906070&lt;br&gt;yes. crypto is a relative new market and isn&amp;#x27;t established yet. it is not strong. I still like it to be around because I believe in its future. fucking kike.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906208&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904684&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Zvi Mowshowitz&lt;br&gt;Holy shit. How&amp;#x27;s his rat cousin Fievel?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906255&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906099&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s very funny that if you replace &amp;quot;crypto&amp;quot; with &amp;quot;communism&amp;quot; you sound no different than every Redditor. Eventually you&amp;#x27;ll be saying that &amp;quot;real crypto hasn&amp;#x27;t been tried yet&amp;quot; when yet another scam of yours gets popped by the capitalist BVLLS at Jane Street.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906388&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904743&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904804&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;LONGING your asset&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;that&amp;#x27;s not how Jane Street works. They hold spot of an asset while loading up on lax leverage puts . Then when the first sing of trouble/volitilialy happens they dump their warchest of shares to crater the price and make a small country&amp;#x27;s GDP on their shorts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906423&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906063&lt;br&gt;Isn’t this kind bullish tho?&lt;br&gt;If you know they’re gonna doomp et at 10am just set your clock to buy at 10:01 and then sell at 9am the next day?&lt;br&gt;Free money.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906424&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jane Street wins. Folks, I know it was coming. Jane Street wins dammit. I knew it was gonna happen dammit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906450&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They can buy all the paper silver they want. I want the real thing. They crash the price, I&amp;#x27;m buying a suit of armor made of silver.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907154&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904705&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Let the goyim deal in the real world&lt;br&gt;So we&amp;#x27;re fucked pretty much eitherway?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907200&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61907154&lt;br&gt;if we can still buy physical silver, then we&amp;#x27;re winning&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907212&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905350&lt;br&gt;weird how PMs beat all traditional investments and crypto on the 5Y then&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907214&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jane street did nothing wrong&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907226&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906450&lt;br&gt;crypto retards don&amp;#x27;t understand the distinction between paper and physical&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907264&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61907214&lt;br&gt;If I meet a Jane Street trader I slice his throat open. So help me god.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61907286&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here&amp;#x27;s how Jane Street manipulate markets https://x.com/BullTheoryio/status/2027094542563045552&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>