<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>/biz/ Active (filtered, with replies)</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/</link><description>Filtered out: general, gme, bbbyq. OP + first 3 replies + last 30 replies.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 05:51:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>how do you guys cope with the fact that OF egirls are making tens of millions a year? — 69 replies — 187.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889270</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889270?lm=1771997351</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 05:29:11 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;how do you guys cope with the fact that OF egirls are making tens of millions a year?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889270'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 69 • Updated: 2026-02-25 05:29 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;how do you guys cope with the fact that OF egirls are making tens of millions a year? this shit is really unbelievable man i am seething so hard holy fuck&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889273&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I literally just don&amp;#x27;t care. Nobody will ever love them and I can also make 10 million without displaying my butthole for the world to see&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889278&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s only like top1% creators making millions&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889279&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889273&lt;br&gt;i didnt care too for so long but now im starting to care fml its just so unfair.. Not only are they extremely hot they also get to make 20MM a year for years scamming with bikini pics on OF&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;its just so unfair i feel like crying&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893140&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889830&lt;br&gt;everyone compares themselves to women, they are people too after all not some different species&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893380&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Start an only fans account.&lt;br&gt;Show the world your talent.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;My a PBJ using your dick to spread the stuff.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Profit.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Don’t give up until you try.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893392&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Make a PBJ!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Edit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893415&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889279&lt;br&gt;nigga are you stupid, hot girls have always had ez mode, any girl with looks + little brains can hustle money like crazy. I knew a waitress 2 years ago working in a shitty diner that was finessing 3-4 boomers, I remember one time a boomer literally handed her a $3,000 check, no sexual favors or anything, just sweet talk, this chick was spending 5-10,000 dollars a month on clothes and was driving a brand new Jeep luxury model&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893458&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;I know a money laundering scheme when I see one&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893483&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892313&lt;br&gt;Fucking kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893517&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;At least i can coom out of the leaked photos of these e-prostitutes, i can&amp;#x27;t cope with the fact some teenage faggot like barron trump (or Eric i don&amp;#x27;t know who&amp;#x27;s is who in that family of pagan gods worshiper faggots) make billions just because he was born in the &amp;quot;right&amp;quot; family.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893555&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I have never paid for porn or whores in my life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893557&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;the same way I cope with dude getting paid millions to play with balls, I don&amp;#x27;t care. it&amp;#x27;s not me and it doesn&amp;#x27;t impact me, so why should I give a shit?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893569&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;99% of them are making like 20 bucks a month lmfao&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893631&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889354&lt;br&gt;I met a girl who was a friend of a friend of mine at a party when I was younger and she literally handed me a business card with her OF address on it. I didn&amp;#x27;t realize what it was at first but the second I read it I blurted out &amp;quot;What the fuck is wrong with you?&amp;quot; without thinking and she got super offended. I&amp;#x27;m pretty sure I was the first person she handed it to that actually said anything negative about it by the way she reacted, which is very bizarre to me. It&amp;#x27;s kind of crazy how common this shit is.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893680&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;Like everything in the world of money being born a woman was a gamble&lt;br&gt;You just lost it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893688&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t think about women at all anon. They are the worst investment you can make in life&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893708&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889282&lt;br&gt;this right here. tons of people play sports, statistically, 0.000001 get paid well. Image stretching you butthole for a year or two and then finally coming to the conclusion it would have been both easier and more profitable to work a mcjob. add in its a clear red flag so they wont ever get a quality man.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893748&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893140&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;t. tranny&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894411&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889273&lt;br&gt;cope, if i can show my penis for millions i would flex on them hoes bro while being paid.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894435&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s all fake. Yet another demoralization psyop. You really fell for that? LMAO&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894538&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892313&lt;br&gt;You remind me of an anon who was here years ago. Fuck I forget his name but he made like 2k a month selling burping videos. He ended up caving and doing full blown hog cranking after telling anons he was only doing burp fetish shit.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t respect it but I kind of admire the journey desu. Once you&amp;#x27;re on the highway to being a degen there&amp;#x27;s really no off ramp&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894578&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t cope because I don&amp;#x27;t care, but be proud of never contributing to it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895418&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894538&lt;br&gt;Just tell the truth, it was you lol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895453&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;You reek of envy and it&amp;#x27;s pathetic.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;waaaah I&amp;#x27;m unhappy because some people have it better&lt;br&gt;Grow up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895459&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t care. I cannot control it therefore I do not care. They can make 10000 Gorillions every second and I wouldn&amp;#x27;t care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895475&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s upsetting not because I&amp;#x27;m envious but because I pity them. Even the successful ones that are making money I imagine aren&amp;#x27;t happy or fulfilled.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895479&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ai will solve this and make chuds rich at the same time&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895520&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;why does OF cause so much psychic damage to anons? you know guys can make an OF too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895541&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;I guess those egirls are just that much smarter than you, because anyone with millions of dollars compared to a broke bitch must be smart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61897746&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;fart&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899392&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;i dont even think about it, life is unfair, this is far from being one of the unfair things that matter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899395&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889298&lt;br&gt;i see car washes close down all the time, this is some boomer thinking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899410&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For your OF to be successful, you have to be popular elsewhere first. OF is where you take your already dedicated audience for financial support in exchange for token nudes. Whores starting with OF and 0 exposure elsewhere, like camsites, will end up in the 90% majority who make nothing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Tried selling my silver today &gt;spent 20 dollars on gas just to get to the only dealer that accepts bullion in my area &gt;p… — 22 replies — 88.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61893298</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61893298?lm=1771998561</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 05:49:21 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Tried selling my silver today &amp;gt;spent 20 dollars on gas just to get to the only dealer that accepts bullion in my area &amp;gt;p…&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61893298'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 22 • Updated: 2026-02-25 05:49 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tried selling my silver today&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;spent 20 dollars on gas just to get to the only dealer that accepts bullion in my area&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;pawn broker says they only pay 90% of spot price, including a 12% processing fee&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;IRS also collects 28% in taxes&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;pawn broker laughs and tells me the next town over 100 miles away has pawn shop&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;might aswell try&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;halfway there, spending another 20 bucks on gas, my back left tire blew out&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;didnt have a spare&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;call towing company which ended up costing hundreds of dollars&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;had to buy two tires just to not mess up wheel alignment&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;And i thought crypto fees were abhorrent&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893318&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893298&lt;br&gt;You fell for the holding physical meme. I am PM ETFs and can sell for spot in click of a button&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893323&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893298&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893166&lt;br&gt;Samefag. Cope and seethe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893429&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893298&lt;br&gt;You don’t sell physical unless you actually need the money to buy something else. It’s not an investment. It’s insurance&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893472&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893429&lt;br&gt;it&amp;#x27;s an investment that has paid off more than stocks tho&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893477&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893318&lt;br&gt;no you can&amp;#x27;t lol. silver ETFs are like $10 below spot&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893485&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;the 2026 panda coin is pretty cute. might get some &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;in before it&amp;#x27;s fake cuz chinks hurfdurf&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893516&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893298&lt;br&gt;you weren&amp;#x27;t supposed to want to ever sell it&lt;br&gt;did you get the latest COVID vaccine booster?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893951&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893298&lt;br&gt;Youre supposed to sell to a real person. Fuck institutions, fees, and the (IRS)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893968&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893298&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Be me &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;European &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;200 dealers in a 200km radius &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Go to dealer with 3% spread for buying and selling &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Sell for 99% of spot as long as it&amp;#x27;s anything remotely tradeable like a Panda&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Don&amp;#x27;t pay taxes (like most Europeans below the Main river)&lt;br&gt;Wtf is your problem? They&amp;#x27;ll even pick it up if you ask.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893992&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893298&lt;br&gt;what a dumb boomer LARP. just use the internet to sell your silver like you use it to tell lies on a mongolian basket weaving board, retard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894003&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893298&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Tried selling my silver today&lt;br&gt;First mistake.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;spent 20 dollars on gas just to get to the only dealer that accepts bullion in my area&lt;br&gt;Have you tried not living in Alaska?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;pawn broker says they only pay 90% of spot price, including a 12% processing fee&lt;br&gt;So they pay 2% over spot...Nice&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;IRS also collects 28% in taxes&lt;br&gt;Common misconception that precious metals are taxed at 28%. The reality is that you owe tax according to your income bracket which means that if you make around $60k per year you only owe 12% on precious metals capital gains. If you make $600k+ per year then yes you will owe 28%.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;halfway there, spending another 20 bucks on gas, my back left tire blew out.&lt;br&gt;What does this have to do with silver?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;didnt have a spare&lt;br&gt;You make $600k per year and you can&amp;#x27;t afford a spare tire???&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894008&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893516&lt;br&gt;SILVERMARINES&lt;br&gt;NEVER SELL&lt;br&gt;ONLY ROCKS&lt;br&gt;FOREVER&lt;br&gt;NO FOOD &lt;br&gt;NO HOUSE&lt;br&gt;NO CAR &lt;br&gt;JUST SILVER&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894081&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893298&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;sold the bottom&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;struggles with simple tasks&lt;br&gt;Classic frog poster.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894082&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894008&lt;br&gt;this but unironically&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894105&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894003&lt;br&gt;It’s an Israeli making up a story, or a dumb faggot white retard nigger making up a story.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896846&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893298&lt;br&gt;how do you even silver physical silver do you go to one of those cash for gold spots or what?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61897078&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893298&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;Trust me! Bullion dealers won&amp;#x27;t buy your metals at spot price! NO DON&amp;#x27;T TRY IT YOURSELF, just believe me!&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Another day of jews and bankers lying trying desperately to convince people to exchange their actual physical value for paper nothingness because they&amp;#x27;re running out of physical silver.&lt;br&gt;*yawn*&lt;br&gt;Got anything new?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899403&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893298&lt;br&gt;What are you going to cry, crybaby?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;waaaaa nobody works for freeeeeeeeee&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;i&amp;#x27;m the only one who works for moneeeee&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;also fuuuud&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899440&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894081&lt;br&gt;frog posters are fucking dumb&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899447&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61899440&lt;br&gt;smarter than cat posters tho&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899453&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893477&lt;br&gt;If I bought the silver etf at the same percentage below spot then I&amp;#x27;m golden u retard&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899470&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893298&lt;br&gt;but you still made over 200% because you bought it at $20 right&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>My company's VDI has been down for the entire day from morning to night. — 49 replies — 54.4/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61898325</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61898325?lm=1771995437</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:57:17 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;My company&amp;#x27;s VDI has been down for the entire day from morning to night.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61898325'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 49 • Updated: 2026-02-25 04:57 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;My company&amp;#x27;s VDI has been down for the entire day from morning to night. Apparently started since the day before in Asia. Nobody can login and we probably lost millions in dollars.&lt;br&gt;Its still not fixed.&lt;br&gt;Tfw all our IT got outsourced to jeets in kolkata&lt;br&gt;Not going to say my company name so i dont get subpoenad to death but its pharmaceutical&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898346&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898325&lt;br&gt;I fucking hate VDIs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898354&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898346&lt;br&gt;I have no idea what even vdi is but none of our lines could run because we couldnt login to SAP. What a fucking waste of time and it impacted every single one of our factories globally. Nobody could do shit or even communicate through teams&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898373&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898354&lt;br&gt;The best part is none of us could contact IT since we couldnt login and our VP had to call kolkata lmao. I looked at the stocks and nothing happened so i guess no one is aware. What a disaster.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898556&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898537&lt;br&gt;What do you think link posters are?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898558&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898556&lt;br&gt;Jeets most likely&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898565&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lmao, whats with the fucking JEETs in this thread? Pissed we all you you fucking suck at your jobs? OP isnt a one off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898574&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898565&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;terminally brainwashed by the most transparent wumao spam&lt;br&gt;This website should have died a long time ago&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898593&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898414&lt;br&gt;If it makes you feel better, I see this situation occurring on a much more regular basis soon. I’m clairvoyant schizophrenic&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898598&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;tap card on printer to try to photocopy shit&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Cant login to printer&lt;br&gt;Aight&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898608&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898598&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Failed to validate user&lt;br&gt;Id take a pic but i fear the subpeona&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898630&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898608&lt;br&gt;just get to the roof and jump&lt;br&gt;at least the vultures have something to fill the space between ads for the next 12 hours until its forgotten&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898631&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898593&lt;br&gt;Yeah but i didnt think it would happen to us cause we arent a tech company. We manufacture pharmaceuticals. This is beyond retarded&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898634&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898598&lt;br&gt;Who was the smart guy who approved this outsourcing of EVERYTHING to jeets?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;And what is the size of his golden parachute? Can he buy a luxury yacht with that money?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898654&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898634&lt;br&gt;The ceo hasnt changed in years though. Hes a fat guy with white hair&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898677&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898654&lt;br&gt;Im seething&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898734&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898677&lt;br&gt;At least i can still login to email with phone.&lt;br&gt;Whats the solution to the jeet problem&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898751&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898325&lt;br&gt;Is it a private equity backed company?&lt;br&gt;I really hope so.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898760&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;only have half a dozen emails about the IT outtage instead of the usual 50 over emails&lt;br&gt;Maybe the jeets arent so bad after all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898764&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898751&lt;br&gt;Its not&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898768&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898764&lt;br&gt;Bummer. I hope PE fags lose all their money.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898770&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898768&lt;br&gt;Its on the swiss stock exchange&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898790&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alcon?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Looks like it already dumped after hours, so no insider trading for me, unfortunately.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898950&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898790&lt;br&gt;If i get into legal trouble because of you id be upset&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898958&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898950&lt;br&gt;But no i have no comments on this. No company or companies can sue me for libel for i have not named any entity that was affected or no part can sue me for leaking sensitive insider info for it is non identifiable information that could be anyone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899045&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898950&lt;br&gt;I just dumped the info in this thread into Gemini and ChatGPT and both were able to figure it out, sorry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I hope you don&amp;#x27;t get in trouble though.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899055&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61899045&lt;br&gt;No this is all larp. There has been 0 issues with any company. Its all fake. Carry on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899057&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61899055&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899068&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898325&lt;br&gt;The management team is always impressed with the savings from enslaving jeets and then this is what happens. Turns out no money was saved and instead you&amp;#x27;re looking at a large financial loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899072&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61899068&lt;br&gt;They will save even more money after firing OP for being white and a snitch&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899087&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;how can a medical device company lose millions in a few hours of glitchy computer? are they that large that few hours of salaries are that much? or do they, like, sell their stuff non-stop 24/7 and a little delay is a disaster?&lt;br&gt;i understand if, like, the regional natural gas distributor shuts down mid-winter and a whole state is freezing. or a payment processor like visa has stopped and nobody can buy shit. but alcon?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899106&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61899087&lt;br&gt;He mentioned every production line being down for 2 days globally. Definitely a couple million in lost revenue every hour its down. Pharma is a lucrative industry&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899110&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61899106&lt;br&gt;Its probably still down but i cant find anything on the news&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899346&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kek i thought i might find something here &lt;br&gt;Imagine firing 50 americans and outsourcing it all to India only to lose billions&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Why didn't LINK hit ATH during the bullrun? — 10 replies — 40.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61897419</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61897419?lm=1771997870</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 05:37:50 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Why didn&amp;#x27;t LINK hit ATH during the bullrun?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61897419'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 10 • Updated: 2026-02-25 05:37 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why didn&amp;#x27;t LINK hit ATH during the bullrun? It couldn&amp;#x27;t even reach previous ATH...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61897479&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61897419&lt;br&gt;Because sergay won&amp;#x27;t stop selling. Why don&amp;#x27;t you people understand this? He&amp;#x27;s diluting the supply. He&amp;#x27;s neutralizing pumps for his own gain. He&amp;#x27;s getting rich while you&amp;#x27;re sitting there with your finger in your ass wondering wtf is going on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61897580&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;still holding link&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61897582&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61897479&lt;br&gt;because LINK marines are cuckolds who worship a fat Slavshit. They brag about losing money while Sirgay becomes a multi billionaire. Pure cuckoldry&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61897590&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61897419&lt;br&gt;what bullrun?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As soon as LINK hit $30.0000000 market crashed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61897598&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61897419&lt;br&gt;It did break ATH marketcap.&lt;br&gt;So many new tokens flooded the market.&lt;br&gt;Why would you expect it to go higher in absolute terms?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61897600&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61897590&lt;br&gt;coping linkie schizo detected&lt;br&gt;no, link does not le secretly control le crypto market cuz it&amp;#x27;s le secret GOD TOOOKEEN&lt;br&gt;go fart in your pillow, dumb stinkie&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61897602&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61897590&lt;br&gt;This&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;There was no bullrun, even king shitcoin barely made any progress&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898612&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61897419&lt;br&gt;nobody believes in crapto anymore, they realized it&amp;#x27;s literally just a pnd ponzi scheme for institutions, scammers and insider traders to extract wealth like criminals with zero consequences&lt;br&gt;this is probably the last run where you&amp;#x27;ll see crapto this high&lt;br&gt;btc isn&amp;#x27;t even the original technology satoshi envisioned anymore, the writing was on the wall&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898673&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61897419&lt;br&gt;Link is dead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899436&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61897598&lt;br&gt;Translation = tokenomics suck. They can print it out of thin air.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>I was watching the State of The Union address and just found out about Trump Accounts. — 9 replies — 36.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61898955</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61898955?lm=1771998096</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 05:41:36 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;I was watching the State of The Union address and just found out about Trump Accounts.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61898955'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 9 • Updated: 2026-02-25 05:41 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;I was watching the State of The Union address and just found out about Trump Accounts.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Newborns in America basically get $1000 for free from the US treasury (funded by private contribution btw) in a tax-free investment account. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Being a millennial is a humiliation ritual at this point. They had to suffer through 08 then Biden, meanwhile gen-alpha Thadbabbies get $1000 just for being born that could mature to $100k by the time they&amp;#x27;re 18.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898977&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;millenials are tough and resilient, we have sub human low iq retards beneath us and oligarch greedy faggots above us. yet here i am rich as fuck from letting the goyim deal in the real world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898986&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maybe it is a soft UBI rollout?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898995&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;how you get dat&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899073&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I read the writing on the wall in high school and I&amp;#x27;m also not a good trader so I just joined the Army. Soon I&amp;#x27;ll retire and collect a free mortgage payment for the rest of my life, work another job and collect 2 retirements, TSP, and social security in my twilight years. I never once worried about money or housing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899212&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898955&lt;br&gt;They forgot to mention that the account will be automatically drained and sent to Israel when the child turns 18&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899250&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898955&lt;br&gt;real talk why cant us millennails sue the govt for unequal discrimination and get our $1,000 accounts too&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899415&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61899212&lt;br&gt;Dood pls! Stop being realist!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899430&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898955&lt;br&gt;they&amp;#x27;ll be lucky if they can buy a hamburger with that when they collect in 2044.&lt;br&gt;ss and medicare are totally insolvent, we are fucking BROKE and they spend like 2T more every year than they bring in.&lt;br&gt;you have no fucking idea how bad it&amp;#x27;s going to get.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899444&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I have a Biden baby and a trump baby so sadly I only get one funded trump account. You can make an account for older babies but you don&amp;#x27;t get $1k. Also some rich people have publicly stated they&amp;#x27;ll fund trump baby accounts too based on whatever their own criteria is, as well as a handful of employers.&lt;br&gt;I heard it&amp;#x27;s part of filing taxes this year, idk. The $100k projected value at maturation is based on contributing the maximum $5k/yr. Supposedly at 18 it&amp;#x27;s limited to educational expenses and buying a house until they reach 30(????). Which is good because that would be really annoying if your kid got $100k and bought a gaming laptop and a base model Ford mustang&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>ENTIRE PUMP RETRACED FUCK THIS PIECE OF SHITCOIN — 2 replies — 8.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61899435</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61899435?lm=1771998388</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 05:46:28 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;ENTIRE PUMP RETRACED FUCK THIS PIECE OF SHITCOIN&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61899435'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 2 • Updated: 2026-02-25 05:46 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;ENTIRE PUMP RETRACED FUCK THIS PIECE OF SHITCOIN&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899438&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;silvers mooning before that 5k insta moon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899461&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61899438&lt;br&gt;Where will this shitty return to normal bounce back to 60$?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;No additional replies in the latest window.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>/smg/ - BUT WHOSE SIDE IS HE ON??? edition — 311 replies — 82.7/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61896953</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61896953?lm=1771985144</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 02:05:44 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;/smg/ - BUT WHOSE SIDE IS HE ON??? edition&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61896953'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 311 • Updated: 2026-02-25 02:05 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;Some helpful links to numb the pain&lt;br&gt;https://findahelpline.com/&lt;br&gt;https://www.nvidia.com/refunds/&lt;br&gt;https://www.whitehouse.gov/refunds&lt;br&gt;https://jlingz.com/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Educational sites:&lt;br&gt;https://www.investopedia.com&lt;br&gt;https://www.khanacademy.org/economics-finance-domain&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Financial TV Streams:&lt;br&gt;https://www.newslive.com/american/cnbc.html&lt;br&gt;https://www.livestreamy.net/bloomberg/&lt;br&gt;destiny.gg/bigscreen&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Charts:&lt;br&gt;https://www.tradingview.com&lt;br&gt;https://www.finscreener.com&lt;br&gt;https://www.portfoliovisualizer.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Screeners: so you feel like in the movies&lt;br&gt;https://finviz.com/&lt;br&gt;https://etfdb.com/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Gambling:&lt;br&gt;https://www.optionsplaybook.com/options-introduction/&lt;br&gt;https://www.optionsprofitcalculator.com&lt;br&gt;https://optionstrat.com/&lt;br&gt;https://www.optionistics.com/quotes/option-prices&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Pre-Market and Live data:&lt;br&gt;https://www.investing.com/indices/indices-futures&lt;br&gt;https://finance.yahoo.com/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Calendars&lt;br&gt;https://www.marketwatch.com/economy-politics/calendar&lt;br&gt;https://www.earningswhispers.com/calendar&lt;br&gt;https://www.cmegroup.com/trading/interest-rates/countdown-to-fomc.html&lt;br&gt;https://www.mortgagenewsdaily.com/data/building-permits&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Boomer Investing 101: so zoomers with meme stocks can outperform you&lt;br&gt;https://www.bogleheads.org/wiki/Getting_started&lt;br&gt;https://www.sec.gov/search-filings&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Misc smg:&lt;br&gt;https://www.financialjuice.com/home&lt;br&gt;https://finance.yahoo.com/trending-tickers&lt;br&gt;https://market24hclock.com/&lt;br&gt;https://www.dividendchannel.com/drip-returns-calculator&lt;br&gt;https://brokerchooser.com/&lt;br&gt;https://www.chathamfinancial.com/technology/us-market-rates&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Previous smigger thread&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895463&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896959&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61896953&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895463&lt;br&gt;Should I take the ~90k i saved my first year practicing law for a down payment and try to make it? Just all in every trade? What would the strategy be? I just don&amp;#x27;t want to do this shit forever. I have like 360k invested currently and if I stay at home the next 5 years and dump it all in etfs I could probably fuck off to SEA or south America. I just want to accelerate that.. Who needs a fucking house any way&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896961&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; currents&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896969&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dont make the thread political&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898228&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61897999&lt;br&gt;How 2 buy if market close?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898232&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898228&lt;br&gt;After hours innit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898234&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898228&lt;br&gt;Check the extended hours toggle&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898236&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898179&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;down from IPO&lt;br&gt;Wow&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898241&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898179&lt;br&gt;I think it&amp;#x27;s because uber eats is eating their lunch! *Winks at you and grabs your arm and gives you an Indian rugburn and then noogies your stupid ass head and laughs at my own joke*&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898243&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61897999&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Based IREN Chad! Almost certainly over $100 by the end of the year.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Easiest way to a 3 X in a while.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898253&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61897999&lt;br&gt;i just bought 1k worth and am down $2. why the fuck did i listen to you&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898254&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crypto exchange Kraken has launched trading of tokenized equity perpetual futures on its regulated derivatives platforms, allowing eligible non-US clients to trade 24/7 leveraged exposure to major US stock indexes, gold and individual companies including Nvidia, Apple and Tesla.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;24/7 leveraged exposure to major US stock indexes, gold and individual companies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898258&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898063&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;dunking on blacks while humble-bragging&lt;br&gt;very based mr newsom!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898270&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;i seriously need the market to dump to trigger my buy limit. i can withstand the volatility unlike you redditors&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898287&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOGLE&lt;br&gt;O&lt;br&gt;I&lt;br&gt;L some moar during EXT hrs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898292&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898287&lt;br&gt;*BOGLED&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;i&amp;#x27;m definitely not telling u NIGGERS to buy NATGAS bc it is waaaaay 2 dangerous 4 NIGGERS u have 2 gno how2 and i have a lot of dry powder 4 way moar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898310&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898179&lt;br&gt;citrini research made a hit piece that mentioned them&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898314&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898254&lt;br&gt;Erm... don&amp;#x27;t you need a license or something from the government to be a brokerage?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898337&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Any alternatives to TradingView? That shit site turned into burning garbage over the last 5 years. It&amp;#x27;s nothing but jeet AI spam and jeet mods izzatfarming together. Had a jeet threaten to dox me and the little swarthoid cunt is still not banned but they banned me for calling the Fed stupid.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898339&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I bought NVDA calls yesterday and sold them for 12% profit today :)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898358&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898292&lt;br&gt;I heard the hot blonde CEO of HGRAF will be opening her gas plant for business fyi&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898362&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898314&lt;br&gt;what are they gonna do about it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898372&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;he didn&amp;#x27;t buy oil tanker calls before the strikes on Iran tonight&lt;br&gt;Never gonna make it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898378&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;sumitomo metals is carrying my portfolio like no tomorrow&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898388&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898339&lt;br&gt;Nice play&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898396&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898358&lt;br&gt;She could just release the gas stored in her lips and power an AI data center that figures out how to correct the errors in the mutant fish genes and moon AquaBounty stook.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898399&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898378&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898404&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I have a weird feeling that the trump pump returns tonight. Dare I say, we&amp;#x27;re so back?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898420&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898418&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898418&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898418&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898464&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898404&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898759&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898147&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898774&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I just hit 6 figures for the first time&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898802&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898774&lt;br&gt;kick ass, BLESSED&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898809&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898774&lt;br&gt;Nice work anon. You&amp;#x27;re gonna make it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>TESLA IS FUCKED — 53 replies — 70.4/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61896337</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61896337?lm=1771995968</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 05:06:08 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;TESLA IS FUCKED&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61896337'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 53 • Updated: 2026-02-25 05:06 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s over for Elon omg&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896387&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61896337&lt;br&gt;elon shmelon&lt;br&gt;eot&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896395&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Teslas are not for e*ropeans&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;They are for gujaratiCHADS&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896411&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61896337&lt;br&gt;Here in hungarystan there was a fucking big jump in byd sales the past year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896616&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla is in the tech industry, not in the car industry. You&amp;#x27;d have to be a double digit IQ redditor to not understand this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896618&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61896337&lt;br&gt;The chinese manufacturers haven&amp;#x27;t taken over 90% of european market share yet just because they are taxed to shit. The european car companies are fucking dead and I say this as someone from a family that&amp;#x27;s only ever owned european cars. &lt;br&gt;Anyways. Elon antics aside, Tesla is an american company that makes cars primarily for Americans, and that type of business has never been successful in Europe. Even Ford who ran a European branch in England making cars like the Fiesta and Focus has been losing traction for a while now and other brands like Chevy which used to be somewhat common 20 years ago are completely gone now. &lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t think it will impact the stock price a lot though, since that&amp;#x27;s pricing tesla as a space robot company that&amp;#x27;s going to colonize mars using catgirls, not a car company.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896623&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61896612&lt;br&gt;China is 10x better than the west now&lt;br&gt;cost of living very cheap, everyone owns their own place&lt;br&gt;Much cleaner and safer&lt;br&gt;Cities actually desirable places to live/work&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s like what the west used to be 80 years ago before ZOG ruined it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896630&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61896623&lt;br&gt;China can only become decent like Japan and then america and Israel will just collapse it like they did to Japan with Plaza accords.&lt;br&gt;America is gonna cap Korea in the knees too, Korea is becoming too rich.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896631&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61896618&lt;br&gt;Chinks leap-frogged USA in tech race due to the indian gypsy infestation. Go to any tech company in USA and there will be a common sight, entire floors packed with smelly stinky indians all pretending to work, it is all performative. Chinks are now far beyond US tech, their robots are a generation ahead, no way to catch up, it would take decades and mass removal of indian scammers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896645&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61896623&lt;br&gt;kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896705&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61896337&lt;br&gt;tsla is not a car company. future of finance. trump won. seeth harder trannycel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896712&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61896616&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;tesla is not in the car industry&lt;br&gt;well, not for much longer it isn&amp;#x27;t&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896718&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61896600&lt;br&gt;Apparently, building stuff in China is just cheaper&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896722&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61896337&lt;br&gt;Europeans can&amp;#x27;t afford Teslas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896818&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61896705&lt;br&gt;imagine throwing away not only your huge successful democrat subsidy corporation, but also your entire good reputation with smart people, so moron dogs like this bark your praises until the news tells them not to&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896832&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61896818&lt;br&gt;smart people lol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896884&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61896832&lt;br&gt;woof&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896893&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61896337&lt;br&gt;Good riddance. The sooner he becomes irrelevant, the better.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896907&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61896818&lt;br&gt;he won the game and is just goofing around in the post-plot open world sandbox&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896910&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61896718&lt;br&gt;Yea&lt;br&gt;Everything is 4-5x cheaper in china&lt;br&gt;Thats a multiplier across the whole economy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898015&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61896608&lt;br&gt;Lol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898105&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61896337&lt;br&gt;sweaty tesla is not a car company its a hyperloop on mars company, those metrics are irrelevant to valuation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898110&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61896337&lt;br&gt;how are BYD batteries after 3 or 5 years&lt;br&gt;asking for a friend&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898831&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61896907&lt;br&gt;He won 3 decades ago&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898833&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61896337&lt;br&gt;Tesla isn&amp;#x27;t just a car manufacturer dude&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898840&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61896596&lt;br&gt;Explain why the revenue for Tesla won&amp;#x27;t increase.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898844&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898833&lt;br&gt;Well car manufacturing is just the only thing that made them money.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898939&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898833&lt;br&gt;Biggest cope&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898943&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61896337&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;d have to be insane to spend new car money on cheap Chinese garbage. Imagine going into debt and making payments on a piece of shit from Temu that broke three years ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899305&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898943&lt;br&gt;They mog most overpriced garbage on the market&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899309&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61896337&lt;br&gt;Ming hao!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Soon lal ppls in de world driving Chinese car ! Many ppls wanting Chinese &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I trust family life to Chinese electric vehicle !&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899349&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61896337&lt;br&gt;lol once again China brags about learning how to copy the White Man&amp;#x27;s invention. They are eternally behind. Niggas still can&amp;#x27;t innovate and its sad.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899365&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61899349&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61899309&lt;br&gt;China won kikes lost simple as&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>is there any hope for chainlink? one thing i've noticed is that this is no longer a chainlink board. there's like 5 link… — 10 replies — 40.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61899134</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61899134?lm=1771998111</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 05:41:51 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;is there any hope for chainlink? one thing i&amp;#x27;ve noticed is that this is no longer a chainlink board. there&amp;#x27;s like 5 link…&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61899134'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 10 • Updated: 2026-02-25 05:41 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;is there any hope for chainlink? one thing i&amp;#x27;ve noticed is that this is no longer a chainlink board. there&amp;#x27;s like 5 link threads MAX these days. it really feels like it&amp;#x27;s ogre. wtf are we looking forward to? swift?? someone give me some hopium and make it the good stuff. is anyone even here??? am i shouting into the void....&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899145&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Niggerlink.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899148&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;SEC Hires Chainlink Lawyer In Pivot To Tech Led Regulation&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;as new legal chief&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899161&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;NPC chart looking compressed&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;sideways grind&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;sideways phases often precede volatility&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;volatility can go both ways&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;still doing great&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899168&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kevin Warsh knows the future is on chain. And he knows LINK is the gold standard for smart contracts. Jerome knows it too but is too weak to shake things up. Expect big things when Jerome&amp;#x27;s out. Unironically hold the fucking line marines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899181&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61899134&lt;br&gt;Remember lad, the chains you link in life are the ones you hold in death&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899241&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hold the line marines, 2 more weeks and then we make it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899248&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61899134&lt;br&gt;The only hopium left for stinkies is The Ropium&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899295&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s the Bulgarians&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899306&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What are you crying about? Slurp the cheapies while confidence is low. You have a once in a lifetime opportunity to become rich beyond your wildest dreams and you are complaining. Amateur! You don&amp;#x27;t deserve to be wealthy!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899445&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61899306&lt;br&gt;Make sure to buy more tokens so Sergey can give the money to his HR roasties.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Wut Gud out of Pumped Dead Coins? — 22 replies — 16.1/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890886</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890886?lm=1771993761</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:29:21 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Wut Gud out of Pumped Dead Coins?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890886'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 22 • Updated: 2026-02-25 04:29 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;HBAR - seems to actually do something, though I am not sure what. Something about Lemon and all the crypto problems being solved - nobody uses it though. Least embarrassing price action on list&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALGO - tranny dump already happened, was leading DiFi platform and was pretty decent for dApps. Dead now that all of that is dead.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;ICP - muh Caffeine app builder and distributed compute. Only &amp;quot;real&amp;quot; token to do a 1/1000x (2k -&amp;gt; $2)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;LINK - honestly, I am not sure what LINK does, something about oracles and sending JSON objects&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;GOLD - more gooder if Iran bombed?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;XRP - I don&amp;#x27;t know what XRP does, is it like a replacement for USDC for replacing FedWire? Banks aren&amp;#x27;t ready to adopt it yet and still use USDC. Also not sure what it does.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;???&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Serious question though, which of these or similar can pump?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Also, if you want to tell me what they do, I would genuinely appreciate it. I only really understand ALGO and ICP.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890916&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890886&lt;br&gt;definitely not QNT&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890935&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890886&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;tfw no clussy&lt;br&gt;Also&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;LINK - honestly, I am not sure what LINK does, something about oracles and sending JSON objects&lt;br&gt;We&amp;#x27;re still so fucking early&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891060&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Banks are adopting Ripple atable coins. Not CRP. Although there is an option to ise On Demand Liquidity which replies on XRP. Obviously this is supplemental at best and can&amp;#x27;t supplant transferring actually USD available.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891937&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890886&lt;br&gt;Imo buying across any mix of the following will be solid longterm:&lt;br&gt;XRP, QNT, CC, XDC, ALGO (possibly dead, but in quantum age may shine for sake of superior tech), DAG, HBAR, XLM, SUI, SEI, APT, FLR, ONDO, NOM, ADA, HYPE, SOL, POL, ATOM, DAG, AAVE, DOT, VET, ZRO, RED, HYPE.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here is a pretty good rundown of the XRP use cases at present from specifically Ripple&amp;#x27;s operation perspective:&lt;br&gt;https://ripple.com/insights/institutional-defi-on-xrpl-scaling-real-world-finance-with-xrp-at-the-core/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891947&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891060&lt;br&gt;Ripple&amp;#x27;s whole strategy is (just like RLUSD launching on Eth and moving to XRPL) to meet the liquidity where it is and move it to the XRPL. Multiple banks already use XRP but many cannot until Clarity passes. XRPL optimizes using XRP and minted assets autobridge using it between different stable coin or minted asset issuances etc.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891961&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890935&lt;br&gt;Link doesn&amp;#x27;t do ANYTHING. It has ZERO utility and no one who invests in it even understands it, they just hear names that CLL has fireside chats with and presume this translates to token value despite it not doing so. The coin exists as a literally unnecessary rent seeker fee insertion. It doesn&amp;#x27;t solve efficiencies or have a basis for use, it is literally just specific jewry&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892018&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890886&lt;br&gt;A LUST PROVOKING VIDEO?!?!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;FUCK YEAH!!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892452&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890886&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;bitches will dress like clowns and dance like retards and will make 5 or 6 digits monthly while you wage like a slave for almost nothing&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;i am in Hell&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892733&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890886&lt;br&gt;Most of those chains are kinda dead now that DeFi and Dapps are old news, but there are--supposedly--a dozen or so council member use cases being worked on by Hedera council members, some of which are transferable, so could be adopted by other enterprises. That seems interesting. Repsol and Fed Ex are recent members and all new members are required to have a use case they are working on, and supply chains and energy tracking seem good fits for DLTs. Will take a looooong time, though, of course. &lt;br&gt;I really don&amp;#x27;t know if crypto has another pump-n-dump fad like NFTs, DeFi, Dapps etc left in it. It really might just be the long wait for mainstream institutional adoption (another reason why I rate Hedera over most others).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892748&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892452&lt;br&gt;She is top 10% in looks genetically, 1% via not being fat and knowing how to appeal professionally.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If she were a male, she would be benching 315 for reps at sub 8% BF, running 3 miles in 18 minutes at 6&amp;#x27;1 with a 130 IQ and working a 200k+ job, and that&amp;#x27;s without connections.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some people have it easy, but it isn&amp;#x27;t gender-related. Average women get discarded at 35 at best. It&amp;#x27;s brutal.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891060&lt;br&gt;So is that Ripples&amp;#x27; value prop? As mentioned, I do see banks trying to do wires via USDC (and then convert back to USD on both sides). Is XRP pretty much offering that. Thread was serious insofar that I really want to understand what each of these coins is trying to supposedly do. ALGO is the clearest for me (distributed apps), but that whole market died.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891937&lt;br&gt;Going to go read this, brb.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891937&lt;br&gt;Any preferences in that list - that&amp;#x27;s a long-ass list and I am maybe vaguely familiar with half at most.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892764&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892733&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I really don&amp;#x27;t know if crypto has another pump-n-dump fad like NFTs, DeFi, Dapps etc left in it&lt;br&gt;That was the real issue with this cycle, there was no hype. Just Bitcoin-led, muh instituional adoption, zero other narrative.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893117&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892748&lt;br&gt;It is a long list sort of intentionally so that I am not shilling anything. I think 99% of crypto will be valueless and a lot of it is reaching the runway end in the next year or two, especially with clarity, but a few dozen will thrive and emerge at minimum and of those I think are strong, this list if bought across in a diverse way, I think would more or less guarantee if crypto succeeds you do very well also.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893214&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892452&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Blame it on the whore instead of the worthless simps&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Andrew Tate style &amp;quot;men&amp;quot; are so incredibly fucking gay.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894845&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;it would be fun to fuck a chick dressed like this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894974&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894845&lt;br&gt;Yeah I always wanted to dress as a clown&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895078&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;not a single coin does anything&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;you know how when you go to a convenience store and all the different scratch-offs have different names but they&amp;#x27;re all exactly the same thing? fancy packaging for what appears to be different themes but all designed to trick you out of your money&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;thats what altcoins are, there are no exceptions, and everyone in the market understands this by now&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895159&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890886&lt;br&gt;honestly, its way more bearish that prediction market coins aren&amp;#x27;t up bigly&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895162&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891947&lt;br&gt;why would banks use rlusd or xrpl as a bridge currency when they can just atomically swap stablecoins? Theres no nostro-vostro in crypto, underlying assets can be sold anywhere instantly at any time, even automatically via smartcontracts or even put into liquidity pools for any overhead&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896947&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895162&lt;br&gt;XRP is natively used on the XRP in cross minted asset swaps at a fraction of the cost and speed of off or cross ledger settlement with basically bottomless on demand liquidity so that low volume corridors don&amp;#x27;t get blown out and weird continuous markets don&amp;#x27;t need to be developed for an efficient universal system. XRP also has none of the risk inherent in smart contracts, is completely counterparty-less and using ILP the whole thing can scale to literally trillions of tps with fees paid in any currency, capable of micropayment batching. XRP is less risky, has no counterparty or contract risk and scales liquidity regardless of the currency pair instantly with no need to establish liquidity between the currency pairs let alone specific issuer walled garden tokens (USDC vs. USDT vs. RLUSD vs. every other national etc. stablecoin) and costs less and finalizes faster. Literally every single reason they would be considering is better done this way, with a few frictions as technically possible with current DLT and zero middlemen unless they choose to have them, completely decentralized, being able to atomic swap on ILP through their own chosen structure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61897000&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895078&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;jeet can&amp;#x27;t read solidity&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899146&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890886&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;ICP - muh Caffeine app builder and distributed compute. Only &amp;quot;real&amp;quot; token to do a 1/1000x (2k -&amp;gt; $2)&lt;br&gt;imagine thinking someone would rather host icp rather than an ai model. companies are lining up to make new data centers for ai when icp is wasted rack space&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899278&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Friend&amp;#x27;s been tossing me this SKR stuff.&lt;br&gt;Says to hold. &lt;br&gt;Cheapie price, only 2 cents right now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Reminder: Palantir will be over $250 a share by the end of the year — 18 replies — 15.6/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61898276</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61898276?lm=1771994529</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:42:09 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Reminder: Palantir will be over $250 a share by the end of the year&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61898276'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 18 • Updated: 2026-02-25 04:42 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;That&amp;#x27;s a +100% return from its current price. You can run from it, you can hide from it, but the AI job apocalypse is coming and it will be powered by PLTR. This is your fate, make your time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898281&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Palantir is ponzi business that depends 100% on a bankrupt layer 1 ponzi. Bankrupt treasury, the company dies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898297&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898281&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Bankrupt treasury&lt;br&gt;Lol, lmao even, that&amp;#x27;s not possible anon. You&amp;#x27;re going to be eating cold beans from a can and counting how many 9mm rounds you have left before that will happen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898304&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898297&lt;br&gt;Its already bankrupt and the old methodology of just shoving it under the rug, kicking the can and broadcasting over the dead one-to-many propaganda channels of the 20th century and its equivalent missing link shit on the internet to &amp;quot;just trust the state&amp;quot;, isnt working anymore.&lt;br&gt;The auction clock hits 16:59 on the 13 March 2026, bid to cover 0.32&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898322&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898276&lt;br&gt;Hasbro is also up 20% YTD, featuring black Bard and Thorin soon in the Hobbit Magic the Gathering set&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898324&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898304&lt;br&gt;hahahaha, he still thinks metal exchanges have to deliver. have you learned nothing since covid? the game has no rules, only the pretense of rules to keep you playing. enjoy losing it all on shiny boomer (paper) rocks, kek.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898345&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898324&lt;br&gt;Au contraire; the communist political party circus lacks two essential means to enforce policy — fear and/or trust; and since the failed bail outs covered up with a weak ass chinese sars propaganda operation utilizing outdated 20th century one-to-many broadcast methodology it hasnt become better. It has become worse and worse each month.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898356&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898322&lt;br&gt;Should I be longing TMNT on 10x leverage??&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898365&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898356&lt;br&gt;Nobody wants TMNT, UB sets are hot garbage if not tied into a fantasy IP. Buy more Lorwyn boxes if you can find them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898369&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898356&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;trying to shill with an &amp;quot;I&amp;quot; statement&lt;br&gt;AHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA&lt;br&gt;its just pathetic at this point to watch peer-2-peer advertisers perform the dance of the 20th century&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898381&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898365&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;please be nostalgic&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;boomerX was nostalgic&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;nostalgia sells&lt;br&gt;AHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA&lt;br&gt;there is nothing to be nostalgic about. The future is great, because the future is dead&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898484&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898345&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898369&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898381&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Now set the bot to &amp;quot;full schizo&amp;quot; and have it spam AI threads with nonsense to kill engagement&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898494&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898484&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;hahahaha I am going to social signal by calling an authentic anon bot&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The outdated methodology says it works&lt;br&gt;Nigger, you are social signaling only to yourself&lt;br&gt;I tell you again Pete, its time to end your life. You were never smart, you got lucky being present at the tail end of a ponzi and mistook it for your own genius, normal faggot&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898535&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sure but tomorrow it dumps&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898676&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898494&lt;br&gt;Surely this is an authentic anon, he said the gamer word&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898912&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898369&lt;br&gt;Sadly just a wee consumer-bot, not ro-bot. I admire your dedication to sniffing out shilling&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898968&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898276&lt;br&gt;top signal&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899307&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898968&lt;br&gt;elaborate&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899318&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898276&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reminder: You are funding a company whose technology is being used to surveil and control American citizens. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;...you greedy, ignorant piece of shit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Mac minis are the new ASIC miners — 49 replies — 12.4/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61893434</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61893434?lm=1771984424</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:53:44 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Mac minis are the new ASIC miners&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61893434'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 49 • Updated: 2026-02-25 01:53 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mac minis are like the ASIC miners except they do actual work instead of mining bitcoin for no reason.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893585&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893434&lt;br&gt;What are people even doing with their 50 mac mini AI agents?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893611&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893585&lt;br&gt;Its like a team of 50 indians&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893612&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893611&lt;br&gt;Just imagine the sound of 50 echoing good morning sirs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895196&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895191&lt;br&gt;Create asset bubbles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895198&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895191&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895251&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895191&lt;br&gt;What do You actually do?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This message was written by:&lt;br&gt;50 macs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895338&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893611&lt;br&gt;imagine the smell&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895344&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895338&lt;br&gt;jej is make me laugh&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895377&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893611&lt;br&gt;minus the shitting?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895732&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895163&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;even then, a properly set up PC inference workstation with real GPU&amp;#x27;s will beat the macs token times by a fair margin &lt;br&gt;Not at the same price&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895740&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895377&lt;br&gt;Plus they can work 24 hours a day&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895338&lt;br&gt;Apple shouldn&amp;#x27;t actually produce smells because it&amp;#x27;s considered a premium product&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895757&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895191&lt;br&gt;Glorified googling program. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I’ve tried to use AI to diagnose some tricky health issues I’ve had and while it did help at first, I’m pretty sure it eventually tried to kill me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895762&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895732&lt;br&gt;If it was &amp;#x27;the same price&amp;#x27; people would choose the faster option, aka notMac. The problem with the cheap option here being - again - you can cool GPUs and they are somewhat designed to be ran at high temps for extended periods. Mac Minis weren&amp;#x27;t and aren&amp;#x27;t. And these retards are going to fry their Mactrash, abusing them 24/7 as retarded AI agents.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895788&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;you really don&amp;#x27;t need a mac mini, old Lenovo Thinkcenters work perfectly fine and you get get a used one with 32GB of ram and 2 TB of disk space for like $200-300&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I have been using a few with Unbuntu installed to run a bunch of agents on an isolated Vlan at home. (These things are honestly security risks, don&amp;#x27;t give them access to your home network or personal info)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895820&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895757&lt;br&gt;chatgpt is useless now, its a glorified yes man. You can actually trick it into giving horrific advice. Which puts it at the level of a 32 year old life coach, nothing more. Gemini is a good tool if you can get a local unit to run, great for helping map and document trades. But nothing more than that, if you really needed something to bounce ideas off of it isn&amp;#x27;t that. But that is all you can expect out of it, a really good calculator. It&amp;#x27;s when people expect it to be a thinking breathing human is when problems arise&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895868&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895788&lt;br&gt;And what model can you on 32gb ram? Thinkcentres dont have dedicated gpu do they?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895888&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895868&lt;br&gt;no one is running the actual model locally, this is for running the agent and all its tools, most people are running API calls off Openrouter&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895922&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895888&lt;br&gt;These ARE running local models, that&amp;#x27;s the entire point of using MacMinis and unified RAM. Whether the Minis will survive the experience, is another issue entirely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896004&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895757&lt;br&gt;Interesting. &lt;br&gt;Mine kept saying im trans. Kek! &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; sadface.jpg&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896011&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894156&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;give the mac mini all of my personal info, financial data, passwords, internet browsing history etc.&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s a personal computer. It already has all of those things.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896031&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895820&lt;br&gt;Yes that’s pretty much it. Although it did help me diagnose leaky gut issues and initially helped with some supplements, but then it started telling me to basically OD on magnesium and electrolytes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896090&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894238&lt;br&gt;Rent it to people that are scared of running it locally or too stupid to figure it out.&lt;br&gt;Stuff like this https://seafloor.bot/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896126&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Basically in the future everyone will have their own personal agentic AI, and these people are hosting them while its still hard to get it set up.&lt;br&gt;This isnt a sustainable business model tho, because its only a matter of time before soke big company like google starts doing it with infinitely more success because they actually have all the data from everyone, so the AI assistant will come out of factory already knowing you better than you know yourself.&lt;br&gt;But it will be profitable probably for a 1 or 2. I dont see this stuff getting released by a big company before its tested enough to ensure most of the nightmarish stories being reported about openclaw have a close to 0% chance of happening.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896174&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893434&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;they do actual work&lt;br&gt;how much money has your agent made?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896193&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895922&lt;br&gt;No they aren&amp;#x27;t. They&amp;#x27;re just a bunch of iToddlers who can&amp;#x27;t into Raspberry Pi or Linux.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896922&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61896126&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;knowing you better than you know yourself&lt;br&gt;it&amp;#x27;s actually pretty hard to personalize large language models, so dont expect the same behaviour as you have from your tiktok or youtube algorithm&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896954&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;this is pure retardium. the minis are not running shit. they can&amp;#x27;t run any models, and anyways open models are not worth running, they&amp;#x27;re dumb as rocks&lt;br&gt;openclaw uses api to run, claude because it&amp;#x27;s the only one that can do shit. the fattest claude (the only able one) can burn hundreds of $$$ per day. and you don&amp;#x27;t need a mac mini for it. you can just run it on the cloud or in a virtual machine. it&amp;#x27;s really lean on resources - you just need to pay a lot of money for the api&lt;br&gt;dumb. all of it is just dumb&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896995&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895757&lt;br&gt;Must be a canadian llm, MAID GPT.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61897015&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61896193&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s the same software. If you can&amp;#x27;t into linux then you definitely can&amp;#x27;t into macos. Both start up into a first class GUI and both require you to drop to the command line to install LLM shit because that&amp;#x27;s how the software works. Ollama front ends not withstanding.&lt;br&gt;Hell, raspi clusters are easy mode because it far easier to find a prebaked recipe you can copy/paste to get it all running whereas mac users have to deal with retards hardcoding paths and cuda bullshit into their workflows.&lt;br&gt;That said there is some retardation going on with the mac buying. Macs are the sane choice because they are the absolute cheapest way to get more than 64GB with GPU access to that pool. Your 128GB of DDR5 and a xeon doesn&amp;#x27;t compare. Buying a joblot of 16GB mac minis is defeating the purpose though.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61897157&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895163&lt;br&gt;correct&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895732&lt;br&gt;wrong. AMD GPUs out on price to performance ratios for AI as long as you have enough IQ to configure rocm kernel&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61897160&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61897157&lt;br&gt;*AMD GPUs win out&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898771&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61897157&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;ll believe it when I see it. A PC with enough VRAM on the GPU to beat mac, I don&amp;#x27;t think it works. Plus that pc has to do offloading.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>The War with Iran — 21 replies — 10.6/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61895849</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61895849?lm=1771991542</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 03:52:22 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;The War with Iran&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61895849'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 21 • Updated: 2026-02-25 03:52 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;A geopolitical risk premium is priced-in to all parts of this market right now.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We see a 3 different potential scenarios:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. US makes deal with Iran: Stocks rise, commodities fall&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. US does &amp;quot;one-time&amp;quot; strike with Iran: Brief volatility which ends with stocks rising, commodities falling&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. US enters prolonged war with Iran: Stocks fall, commodities rise&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our positions win in 2 of the 3 scenarios outlined above, which we believe are more likely than #3.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If the US truly is setting up for a long war with Iran, then this would be highly bearish for equities, bullish for crude and gold.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why don&amp;#x27;t we think this is the case?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump wants $2/gallon gas and wants to be the &amp;quot;Peace President.&amp;quot; None of these objectives are obtained in a prolonged war with Iran, particularly with mid-term elections on the horizon.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;That is our current mindset on how we are approaching this market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895853&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I also have a club for those interested in the stock market, where I publish all paid premium content, as shown in the attached photo. I will save you time and hundreds of dollars on subscriptions, which you will get practically for free.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895951&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;bump&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895972&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895853&lt;br&gt;Please feel free to ask any questions you may have ;)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895984&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895849&lt;br&gt;Yea there’s almost no chance Trump invades Iran. It’s less popular than operation Iraqi freedom or Afghanistan. There’s also already a mutiny happening with the troops, the US economy is already in recession and even normies are wising up to Israeli influence over the government. An invasion would completely destabilize the country domestically even worse than the Epstein files&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896103&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895849&lt;br&gt;Totally normal volume spike&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896104&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895849&lt;br&gt;I see three possibilities happening in the future&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I win the lottery&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I have to split the lottery&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I do not win the lottery&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;our positions win in 2 of 3 of the scenarios outlined above, which we believe are more likely than #3 (only 33.3333% of the options)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61897009&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why does it matter what orange tard wants? USA is owned by Bibi and his tribe and burgers will die for Israel, with a smile on their face.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61897173&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895849&lt;br&gt;TACO is a PEDO&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61897299&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;bump&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61897321&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895853&lt;br&gt;Guys, join the club!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61897364&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;bump&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61897439&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895984&lt;br&gt;Israel always gets what they want from Trump.&lt;br&gt;Bet on it, Iran will be either hammered from the skies or invaded by ground forces.&lt;br&gt;American men will deploy to Iran either as special forces, CIA/Green beret deep cover, or as US army infantrymen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898183&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;bump&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898225&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895849&lt;br&gt;in case you haven&amp;#x27;t noticed the US economy likes war. what happens when the threat of war hovers over our heads indefinitely? markets go up. maybe through mid terms? &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;If the US truly is setting up for a long war with Iran, then this would be highly bearish for equities, bullish for crude and gold&lt;br&gt;you didn&amp;#x27;t read the assignment get out&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898233&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;bump&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898812&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895984&lt;br&gt;Texas and Florida want the war.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898836&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895849&lt;br&gt;2.5. Iran gets curb stomped (again) but ground forces are intact. Popular uprisings flare up but it ends up a Syria thing and goes on forever. Doesn&amp;#x27;t effect the US though and shipping routes remain open. Iran is surrounded by enemies. Kurds take the chance to set up shop in the NW. Afghanistan maybe takes some turf in the east. Recent US visit to Azerbaijan and Armenia probably were to get them to accept refugees secretly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898865&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898812&lt;br&gt;They will get it during the next civil war&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899086&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898225&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The war in the Ukraine is our fault&lt;br&gt;Slavs love war, they fight for fun over there. They&amp;#x27;ve been doing it for thousands of years, like pale Arabs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899112&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jannies do your fucking job&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899158&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895853&lt;br&gt;Whats your angle? you get my data?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>&gt;days away from the bottom of the current BTC bear market &gt;RSI more oversold than 2022 and 2018 &gt;"crypto is dead" invoke… — 17 replies — 9.4/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61892571</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61892571?lm=1771992147</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:02:27 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;&amp;gt;days away from the bottom of the current BTC bear market &amp;gt;RSI more oversold than 2022 and 2018 &amp;gt;&amp;quot;crypto is dead&amp;quot; invoke…&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61892571'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 17 • Updated: 2026-02-25 04:02 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;days away from the bottom of the current BTC bear market&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;RSI more oversold than 2022 and 2018&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;crypto is dead&amp;quot; invoked incessantly more than ever&lt;br&gt;comfiest slurp of my life&lt;br&gt;2018 slurp bought me a car&lt;br&gt;2022 slurp paid off my student loans &lt;br&gt;2026 slurp about to buy me a house&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892579&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There&amp;#x27;s no need to rush in. DCA maybe, it could go lower. This thing takes the escallater up and the elevator down.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;t. sideliner&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892591&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892579&lt;br&gt;I keep fresh powder and buy orders lower down anyway&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892618&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892571&lt;br&gt;was the top really 420 days ago?? time flies!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892627&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892618&lt;br&gt;look at the top left&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892643&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892571&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;BTC Outperforms gold&lt;br&gt;maybe but it doesn&amp;#x27;t say what&amp;#x27;s going to happen against the usd&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892655&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892618&lt;br&gt;top for btcusd was in oct 2025, he is using a btc gold chart&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892661&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892618&lt;br&gt;no, OP is a cock sucking faggot as always&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892627&lt;br&gt;okay if that&amp;#x27;s the game you wanna play, then based on this chart, it&amp;#x27;s not going to surpass ath in terms of gold next cycle. it looks like it&amp;#x27;s not even gonna reach old ath&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892673&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892643&lt;br&gt;give me one good reason why I should go off the USD 4 year cycle instead of the Gold 4 year cycle?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892696&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892661&lt;br&gt;all it shows is that the gains over gold have been dampening as time goes on, which makes sense as the asset matures and becomes less volatile. Your assumption can&amp;#x27;t be made until the next ATH is under the previous in terms of Gold.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892711&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892673&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;give me one good reason why I should go off the USD 4 year cycle instead of the Gold 4 year cycle?&lt;br&gt;If you&amp;#x27;re mainly positioned into gold right now, then none&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892727&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892673&lt;br&gt;Because going by your chart it doesn&amp;#x27;t seem like a gold 4 year cycle, the recent one was shorter&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892732&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892711&lt;br&gt;To some degree, yes.&lt;br&gt;Money printer is about to brrrr, 0% chance fiat outperforms both Gold and BTC anyway, so it&amp;#x27;s a ridiculous concern.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892745&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892732&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Money printer is about to brrrr, 0% chance fiat outperforms both Gold and BTC anyway, so it&amp;#x27;s a ridiculous concern.&lt;br&gt;Oh I was talking about short term like next 2-6 months&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894165&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892571&lt;br&gt;Don&amp;#x27;t confuse outperforming gold for going up against the dollar.&lt;br&gt;Gold could very well go down right now WITH bitcoin. It is topping, after all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896811&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892571&lt;br&gt;you have no idea how over things are do you. this isn&amp;#x27;t one of your &amp;quot;cycles&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61897196&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61896811&lt;br&gt;If I got 10$ everytime I heard that I&amp;#x27;d be a multi billionaire by now. Let me guess? This time it&amp;#x27;s different? This time it&amp;#x27;s not like the last times?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899194&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892571&lt;br&gt;slurp le dip&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>no no NO NO NO NO-AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA — 13 replies — 7.3/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61898732</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61898732?lm=1771992235</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:03:55 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;no no NO NO NO NO-AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61898732'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 13 • Updated: 2026-02-25 04:03 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;no no NO NO NO NO-AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898763&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;another scam pump no doubt&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898805&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898763&lt;br&gt;It’s design is to liquidate both sides but theirs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898884&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898732&lt;br&gt;who the fuck printed that candle? Saylor? God?&lt;br&gt;it&amp;#x27;s bigger than my cock at full mast.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898904&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;was that the bottom bros? what if it never goes back down&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898908&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898904&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;what if it never goes back down&lt;br&gt;i&amp;#x27;ll finally fulfill my dream of buying and owning a human.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898971&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;legit trumps first year. holy shit am i the only one that sees forced volitily for rich to buy at bottom?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899036&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s already reversing&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899043&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61899036&lt;br&gt;we are leveraged we are long&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899058&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Too much hopium in this thread. Lmao&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899070&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61899058&lt;br&gt;I hope it goes down but it won&amp;#x27;t&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899125&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;literally dumping already&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899172&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;friend checks NPC market cap&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;says “still relatively small”&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;small caps have room&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;especially with consistent activity&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899195&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;piece of shit already retraced everything&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>