<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>/biz/ Active (no generals, context, ticker-first, exploding)</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/</link><description>OP + first 3 replies + last 30 replies. Ticker threads boosted. Exploding threads flagged.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 02:55:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>[TICKER | EXPLODING 896.0/hr] /BBBYQ/ - Bath Barron Edition — 224 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61803438</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61803438?lm=1771209712</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 02:41:52 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;/BBBYQ/ - Bath Barron Edition&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61803438'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 224 • Updated: 2026-02-16 02:41 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;BBBYQ&lt;br&gt;TOKENS.COM&lt;br&gt;TZERO&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;WAGMI&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61803541&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WAGMI&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61803630&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Look at them go!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61804731&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;pp, if i don&amp;#x27;t get anything for my canceled shares, i&amp;#x27;m going to find you and kick you in the balls&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855003&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I dont care.&lt;br&gt;I dont cafè&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855287&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855003&lt;br&gt;This goes to show you just how dumb and disingenuous the silly shillies are. You can ask Goldberg whatever the hell you want but he is not obligated to give you a truthful answer when M&amp;amp;A is involved. He wouldn&amp;#x27;t tell you so this is completely useless. &lt;br&gt;This still does not solve the CUSIP Conundrum. Words only get you so far, but right here right now in 2026 there are open Bed Bath and Beyond stores and the company that operates them is not even using the Overstock/BYON/BBBY CUSIP. They issued new securities in October using BBBYQs CUSIP. &lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s already proven 100% fact that a reverse merger of the BBBYQ shell has already occurred with BBBY. There is zero counterargument. &lt;br&gt;Overstock, BYON and BBBY all kept them same CUSIP. So why now does it suddenly switch? Occams Razor solves the puzzle: BBBYQ shell reverse merger has already occured and the details are not in any known docket.&lt;br&gt;BBBY mystery has been solved by yours truly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855551&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855003&lt;br&gt;Mayhaps DK-Butterfly and DK-Butterfly1 are different entities. As per the Jake DD.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855610&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855551&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s just a typo, bro. For some reason, when writing out DK-Butterfly. I, too, will accidentally add on a -1 for no reason. This speculative theories are bizarre-1. See! Haha, I did it on accident just now. I can&amp;#x27;t even believe I did that LOL&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855697&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855003&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Sent from my iPhone&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856432&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855697&lt;br&gt;I dont care&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857014&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hallo?&lt;br&gt;When BBBY return? &lt;br&gt;I dont care&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857266&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857014&lt;br&gt;BBBY is trading now. BBBYQ was canceled, and no longer exists. If you had BBBYQ when it was canceled you lost that investment, it can never be returned. Anyone who says BBBYQ is coming back is a scammer or mentally ill.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857313&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855287&lt;br&gt;What mental illnesses are you diagnosed with?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857321&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857266&lt;br&gt;I dont care of loss my Money.&lt;br&gt;I dont read your shit post.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857369&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;where we&amp;#x27;re you when your shares we&amp;#x27;re cancel?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;me I&amp;#x27;m at house&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;wife come home and say &amp;quot;no bbq sauce&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;it does not matter&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;sauce is not the main for me to eat&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;she ask if I&amp;#x27;m eat without, I say yes&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I&amp;#x27;m love it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857512&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857369&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Michael Goldbergenstein say from iPhone&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;share are cancel&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;No&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857528&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857512&lt;br&gt;Yes, share are cancel. Shorts are also cancel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857530&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853518&lt;br&gt;BBBY and gme sagas have been incredibly illuminating for me&lt;br&gt;I always thought that it is at least *possible* for rational actors to creatively misunderstand evidence disproving legacy conspiracies like flat earth&lt;br&gt;but for meme stocks it&amp;#x27;s all completely dry corporate and legal documents explicitly formulated in such a way that there&amp;#x27;s nothing to misunderstand&lt;br&gt;meme stocks gave me a new understanding of the strength of people&amp;#x27;s delusion&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857546&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857528&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857530&lt;br&gt;What do you guys think about DK-Butterfly&amp;#x27;s CUSIP matching the new BBBY warrants?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What do you guys think about GME needing to recognize a loss on a security they never sold?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What do you guys think about Gustavo Arnal being murdered in cold blood for helping RC?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What do you guys think about there being no final decree yet?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I bet you have a lot to say about it on a Sunday morning don&amp;#x27;t you?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857565&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857313&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;There is zero counterargument.&lt;br&gt;I am sorry. But there is no answer to the CUSIP Conundrum. What else am I to believe other than the thesis that CH11 for BBBYQ would end in a transaction. We now have evidence that this transaction took place. You just don&amp;#x27;t like that I harp on it and won&amp;#x27;t let it go. &lt;br&gt;You are just a grumpy wumpy seethy weethy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857577&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857546&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;What do you guys think about DK-Butterfly&amp;#x27;s CUSIP matching the new BBBY warrants?&lt;br&gt;This is quite intriguing indeed! By my best calculations, it appears that BBBYQ shell has reverse merged with BBBY. This is the only way possible the warrants would use the wrong CUSIP. &lt;br&gt;This would be like filing your taxes and you suddenly misusing the wrong social security number when filling out the paperwork. The bankers that help underwrite these securities are not guessing and using the wrong CUSIP. When the investment bankers helped in creating these warrants for distribution, at that very moment the controlling interest of BBBY was BBBYQ. It&amp;#x27;s 100% proven fact. It&amp;#x27;s a fact because we can literally check the CUSIPs right here right now. We can also go into Bed Bath and Beyond stores right here and now. We also know what a Butterfly transaction is. It&amp;#x27;s exactly what happened in this CH11. There is still much more to come!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857602&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857565&lt;br&gt;There is an answer, you just refuse to accept it because of your mental illness. Anyone who held BBBYQ at cancelation will never get anything for it, that was a 100% loss that is unrecoverable. &lt;br&gt;There are also some that know this, yet try to tie the old BBBYQ to the warrants in order to pump and dump them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857791&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;mental illness&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857968&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857602&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;There is an answer&lt;br&gt;What is the answer? You sure do a lot of seething about some pretty basic logic here. I am doing, with 100% Grade-A proven facts that A + B = C and you are having a meltdown about it. You have three options:&lt;br&gt;1 - State the obvious. Reverse merger already happened. Towelkings win. &lt;br&gt;2 - State a logical explanation why the wrong CUSIP is being used on warrants in the context that we&amp;#x27;ve been postulating for YEARS that this restructuring ends in a transaction. The evidence supports our thesis.&lt;br&gt;3 - Be a grumpy wumpy seethy weethy. &lt;br&gt;Those are your only options, and no, being a seethy does not solve the CUSIP Conundrum. If you can&amp;#x27;t solve the conundrum then that means we have our Cusip Confirmation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858165&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857968&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;CUSIP Conundrum&lt;br&gt;There is no Conundrum, the CUSIP of BBBYQ no longer exists as it was canceled.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858182&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ken griffin LOL&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858188&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858182&lt;br&gt;KEN GRIFFIN &lt;br&gt;LOL&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858201&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858182&lt;br&gt;KG is down 97.5% on GME? Damn, shoulda been long lol.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858219&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;hahahahaha can&amp;#x27;t believe mentally ill bagholders who lost all of their money still here. they lost their money because someone on the internet told them to buy a dead company stock. how about i tell you to suck my dick. would you do it? BBBYQ = dead company, dead stock, bankrupt. BBBY = new company. if you are too stupid to understand this, there&amp;#x27;s no light for you, keep coping until 2100, no refunds. you shouldn&amp;#x27;t have gambled your hard earned money. if this continues, i&amp;#x27;ll start threads about my roulette losses and demand that casino pay me back, because casinos ASSIP-6 starts with the number hit on roulette. KEK baggies. you guys are literally living in the dream world. reading your cope on reddit and here, gives me schadenfreude.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858250&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858219&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;rage posting about a stock he doesn&amp;#x27;t own&lt;br&gt;but why?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858863&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858250&lt;br&gt;empathy for fellow man maybe?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858996&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858219&lt;br&gt;The money will be refunded x1000 at least maybe twice that. You can&amp;#x27;t argue with the value it brings. That&amp;#x27;s just math.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859061&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858250&lt;br&gt;They are very empathetic anon. Please give up and stop nooticing. Please, it&amp;#x27;s for your own good. We care about your sanity and safety. Plz&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859101&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858219&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;uses reddit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>[TICKER | EXPLODING 160.0/hr] WTF — 40 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61854357</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61854357?lm=1771210132</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 02:48:52 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;WTF&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61854357'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 40 • Updated: 2026-02-16 02:48 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHY IS CHINA DUMPING TREASURIES FOR GOLD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854363&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854357&lt;br&gt;for treasuries to match gold they have to pay now at least 10%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854376&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854357&lt;br&gt;Schizo fear mongering youtube take&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;the dollar is dying! The yuan is here!&lt;br&gt;in realty&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;no one wants to trade in yuan because they all know china keeps it artifically low so you&amp;#x27;re going to get useless paper so they are instead using gold in their trade instead of dollars and will keep their currency weaker than the dollar for exports&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854416&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854357&lt;br&gt;Idk, idc.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855186&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854357&lt;br&gt;Because ching chong ping pong&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855237&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854357&lt;br&gt;Their position in US treasuries is part of keeping the dollar strong vs their currency, so they can export more goods here. If people here are soon to be unemployed, due to AI doing total white-collar death, there will fewer people to buy their goods. Japan, China, and other exporters have less incentive to buy US debt if the US consumer base dries up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855282&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump bullied China during his first term, and as a result we had Covid. Trump bullied China again in his second term, and as a result we have the death of the usd.&lt;br&gt;Play stupid games, win stupid prizes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855397&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854357&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;gold&lt;br&gt;real and straight&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;fiat&lt;br&gt;fake and gay&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855471&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854357&lt;br&gt;Same move as when puccia shifted its reserves to gold before 2022. Only to burn that gold anyway lmao.&lt;br&gt;If you don&amp;#x27;t understand this means invasion of real China by Chyna in 2027, I don&amp;#x27;t know what to tell you.&lt;br&gt;Buy your DDR5 right now, you won&amp;#x27;t believe how cheap it is right now compared to what it will be next year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855553&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855282&lt;br&gt;Yay! Fuck this fake and gay economy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855589&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The chinese age is coming. Kushner and other high level jews are teaching their kids chinese for a reason, they are ready to slaughter a spent America on a sacrificial altar to buy their position within the Pax Sinica.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855600&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854357&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Why is China dumping nigger kike American dollars for real money&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855645&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855589&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;to buy their position within the Pax Sinica.&lt;br&gt;You think the Chinese are having anything to do with these satanic fucks? Theres a reason China is arming Iran to the teeth with missile tech and advanced radar systems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855682&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855645&lt;br&gt;China does not care about your satanic panic. They are godless materialists. They see jews and want to emulate them so they can be rich and powerful too. Sell this line to MAGAtards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855688&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854357&lt;br&gt;They know we&amp;#x27;ll default on our debt to them when Taiwan kicks off next year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855692&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855589&lt;br&gt;Unlike the founding fathers, the Chinese are at least aware of the menace.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854357&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;US leverages the power of the dollar to ass fuck Russia as a response to the invasion of Ukraine&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;States decided to start unwinding US reserves in favour of gold&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;US is getting perilously close to having unsustainable debt due to rollover into higher interest rates, and the only way out will be printing dollars.&lt;br&gt;Hmmm, I wonder why.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855695&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854357&lt;br&gt;zoom out&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855854&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855692&lt;br&gt;It doesn&amp;#x27;t matter when your state relegion is just another jewish denomination. Christianity has been aware of jews 2000 years before chinese communist&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855978&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;lol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856018&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854357&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;After Biden&amp;#x27;s confiscation of Russia&amp;#x27;s entire foreign exchange reserve parked in treasuries, China got a wakeup call so they are getting the fuck out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856103&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855645&lt;br&gt;The Chinese unironically believe that they are more than a match for the Jews and so they do not feel the need to import Jewish bankers unlike every European power ever.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856133&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;gee I can&amp;#x27;t imagine why anyone wouldn&amp;#x27;t have faith in US treasuries&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856146&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854376&lt;br&gt;Even the Chinese don’t trust the yuan. They also don’t trust the dollar. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;That’s why they are buying gold.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856178&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;My birthday is literally June 11. I normally don&amp;#x27;t mention it but it&amp;#x27;s weirding me out that a lot of big events happen on that date. It&amp;#x27;s like it has occult significance or some shit since June is Gemini and 11 is the &amp;#x27;twin&amp;#x27; day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856201&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China is known for the quality of their metals.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;aka chinesium steel&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856299&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856719&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bruh&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857428&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854376&lt;br&gt;China hasn&amp;#x27;t relied on currency devaluation since the 1990s. They had a hard peg to the US dollar until 2005 and a soft peg since then.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857432&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854357&lt;br&gt;So that they can get dumped on and become a nation of bag holders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857453&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854357&lt;br&gt;They are preparing for war.&lt;br&gt;A large part of Russia’s war chest is gold and they’ve done a lot of war work to try and smuggle more gold out of africa because the gold they do have isn’t enough to fund the war.&lt;br&gt;China is trying to accumulate while they can before they invade.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857475&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855645&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; Theres a reason China is arming Iran to the teeth with missile tech and advanced radar systems.&lt;br&gt;If Iran has received Chinese weapons, then the Iranians are doing an extremely good job of hiding them. There is no evidence that China has been supplying any meaningful quantity of armaments to Iran.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;China sold Iran a few semi-obsolete Hong Qi 7 air defense systems 20 years ago, and more recently a few Shen Nung low-power counter-drone lasers. Essentially nothing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857497&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857453&lt;br&gt;Are they planning on sinking the US carrier fleets by overloading them with gold?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859068&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lol Kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859114&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854357&lt;br&gt;you guys know there&amp;#x27;s a very limited amount of gold to buy, right? You cannot physically buy even a small fraction of US treasuries in gold.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>[TICKER | EXPLODING 145.4/hr] Money doesn't buy happiness — 41 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61855335</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61855335?lm=1771209525</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 02:38:45 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Money doesn&amp;#x27;t buy happiness&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61855335'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 41 • Updated: 2026-02-16 02:38 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;When you make it you&amp;#x27;re still gonna be a virgin incel. The only difference is you&amp;#x27;ll have $10 million in the bank that you won&amp;#x27;t even spend since your only hobbies are 4chud and pirating PC games.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855344&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855335&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;that you won&amp;#x27;t even spend since your only hobbies are 4chud and pirating PC games&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Not true, there&amp;#x27;s a lot of hobbies that I put on hold because I couldn&amp;#x27;t afford a house. I need land in a place without neighbors who complain about noise and open fires.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855348&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855335&lt;br&gt;Stupid sexy chud.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Also OP, HOOKERS. You fucking demoralising faggot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855354&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855335&lt;br&gt;what a fine young gentleman&lt;br&gt;the one with glasses needs to practice more, though&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855465&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yeah well 10k sure would make me a lot more happy than I am now, my friend died this morning, plus I&amp;#x27;m broke and it&amp;#x27;s raining.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855473&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855461&lt;br&gt;you know nothing about me faggot. he&amp;#x27;ll never see 4 million again in his life I guarantee it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855484&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855335&lt;br&gt;it&amp;#x27;s interesting how some people look like they just aren&amp;#x27;t meant to be dancers&lt;br&gt;bless that dude for trying though&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855533&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855335&lt;br&gt;I an incel who only ever banged 7 hookers (thank god no STDs) but having 10 million would very much better my life. I don’t care if I still can’t get a gf, at very least I can be comfy and take care of my parents and help my nephews and nieces.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Also if I really wanted to I could just be upfront with a bitch and make an arrangement where she gives me kids and I provide for her if I wanted children of my own&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855543&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855335&lt;br&gt;Money definitely buys happiness when I was rich I had a great diet and workout regimen now that I am back to wage cucking I am a alcoholic cocaine addict&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855547&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855335&lt;br&gt;Fuck he&amp;#x27;s good&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855550&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;you just KNOW this girl fell for the dancing chud&lt;br&gt;look at her face and how much she is smiling by grinding herself all over him&lt;br&gt;this chud did the impossible&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855561&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855335&lt;br&gt;White rizzler goated with the sauce while shanequa thirsts for that bwc&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855727&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;QUIRKED UP WHITE BOY WITH A LITTLE BIT OF SWAGGER&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855728&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855335&lt;br&gt;Try buying food with happiness, retard.&lt;br&gt;You sound like a retarded cunt, who everyone else is talking care of.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855740&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855335&lt;br&gt;Money might not buy happiness. But it ends unhappiness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855746&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855335&lt;br&gt;get back in the fucking cage, wagie&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855754&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855335&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s true. Sometimes I get down about work and money. But at the end of the day I have a roof over my head, food in the fridge, and a girl who loves me and sucks my dick on command. Just having those three things makes me a rich man. Happiness is a mindset.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855775&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;My father just died one year after he retired from ALS. He was extremely jewish with his money, and never did anything fun. Now my mom has it all. You need to cultivate something along the way. Everyone thinks they will live to at least 80 even though that probably won&amp;#x27;t be the case. Don&amp;#x27;t waste your life waiting for the moment you are imagining will turn it all around. It might pass you by forever&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855784&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855775&lt;br&gt;ngmi&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855799&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855775&lt;br&gt;ngmi&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855804&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855561&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;That nigger bitch is vile&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856107&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855335&lt;br&gt;but with a nice pc and a comfortable chair&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856663&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855335&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t care about being a extra virgin incel, all I care about is escaping the hell that is wageslaving. Let me read books and play video games and go for long walks and the rest of the world can fuck off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856683&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855356&lt;br&gt;7 figures to 5 is rough. I&amp;#x27;ve done 7 to 6 to various extent multiple times and am back to 6 now again, thought I was in multiple 7s a few months ago. I just feel there&amp;#x27;s more to come but of course knowing what I know now, I have regrets. But investing in retrospect is the easiest thing ever.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856924&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855804&lt;br&gt;You don&amp;#x27;t have to repeat the same thing twice in one sentence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856941&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855335&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Laughs in going to a country with a debased and devalued currency&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lol nigger&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856948&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855335&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;When you make it you&amp;#x27;re still gonna be a virgin incel.&lt;br&gt;Correct, and I&amp;#x27;m happy with that&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The only difference is you&amp;#x27;ll have $10 million in the bank that you won&amp;#x27;t even spend since your only hobbies are 4chud and pirating PC games.&lt;br&gt;Correct, but I won&amp;#x27;t have to work.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t get it, are you trying to demoralize or lift me up?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857249&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855335&lt;br&gt;If I had 10 million I would spend all day fucking s tier hookers. I would have sugar babies. I would go to Japan and use brothels like hotels. I would have cute barely legal twinks on my dick 24/7 dressed in their school uniforms. Why the fuck would I be a virgin incel. Money buys everything.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;hurrrrrrrrr but no affection not real love hurrrrrrrrrrr&lt;br&gt;Ok? I don&amp;#x27;t care. Who is happier, the wageslave brokie with a gf or a multi-millionaire on a yaht? If you think it&amp;#x27;s the wageslave, it&amp;#x27;s because you&amp;#x27;re retarded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857275&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857249&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;a multi-millionaire on a yaht&lt;br&gt;you mean a yak ?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857310&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;dire you can buy a woman but whaf abouf her feelings&lt;br&gt;What a cuck&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857371&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GO STEVEN&lt;br&gt;GO STEVEN&lt;br&gt;GO GO GO&lt;br&gt;GO STEVEN&lt;br&gt;OOOOO&lt;br&gt;OOOOO&lt;br&gt;HITTEM WITH THAT&lt;br&gt;OOOO&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857386&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855335&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m on year long holiday with my GF. I solded some Bitcoin , stonks in 2024 and 2025. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;money does buy happiness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857401&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855356&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I was up almost $4 million dollars in 2024 and I fully roundtripped back down to low 5 figures&lt;br&gt;How can be possible?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859095&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857401&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;put 35k into memecoin at average of $4M&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;memecoin goes to $500M&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thats how&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;if i still held it i would have about $90k, but I sold it to go trade other stuff and lost a chunk of it essentially round tripping me all the way back down to what i originally invested in 2024&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>[TICKER | EXPLODING 96.6/hr] Thread 61856070 — 28 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61856070</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61856070?lm=1771209496</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 02:38:16 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Thread 61856070&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61856070'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 28 • Updated: 2026-02-16 02:38 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;We all make fun of elderly people and call them retarded boomer faggots when they fall for an obvious Indian scam...but...what if WE are the retarded boomer faggots? Think about it. What do you even know about the economy? You think your bank is making you win money for free with compound interest? Your credit card gives you cash back and you feel you&amp;#x27;re defeating the system? Lol. This whole world may be a gigantic Indian call center and we are all boomer retards being scammed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856079&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;whoa&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856086&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856070&lt;br&gt;boomers are extra retarded though. No way when I&amp;#x27;m 70 will I fall for even 1% of the stupid ass shit those lead brain-damaged retards do&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856089&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856070&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856091&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856070&lt;br&gt;Have you seen how many tards on this board have been scammed by coins that literally advertise that they are scams?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;That&amp;#x27;s even more retarded than boomer faggots who are usually are mentally declining due to age and still have some modicum of faith in people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856126&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856070&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;You think your bank is making you win money for free with compound interest?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How do you see it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856130&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856086&lt;br&gt;No but you will fall for a shitload of the new social engineering scams specifically designed to target the new generation of elderly folks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856727&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856070&lt;br&gt;Oh I&amp;#x27;m just as fucking retarded as many boomers out there, I have no doubts about that. It&amp;#x27;s just that our skillsets are different so instead of gift card fraud, I fall for digital currency fraud. I also have no idea what a carburetor is but I remember my dad used to always bitch about his...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856921&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856070&lt;br&gt;I fell for the &amp;quot;leave your parents or you will never fuck&amp;quot; scam. Thanks Jews.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857128&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856070&lt;br&gt;My mum (marm) almost just fell for another &amp;quot;added hydrogen&amp;quot; scam water filter that is being reviewed by the gaurdian (a uk newspaper) but with &amp;quot;h2&amp;quot; infront of its normal web address. Not many mainstream newspapers use standard emojis for their articles but this one does apparently.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857241&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856070&lt;br&gt;The price of everything you buy has embedded exorbitant credit card transaction fees. Credit Card cash back? You&amp;#x27;re too dumb to realize that&amp;#x27;s from your pocket in the first place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857251&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856130&lt;br&gt;Maybe we are victims of these new social engineering scams right now, I&amp;#x27;m afraid to think what I&amp;#x27;m doing with my oney and who i give my money to, lol. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856727&lt;br&gt;your dad fell for the carburator scam, lol. Being a victim of scams is in your genes, bucko&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857257&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856070&lt;br&gt;Nah boomers are retarded. &amp;quot;I&amp;#x27;ve left my husband of 50yrs because I&amp;#x27;m in a relationship with Leonardio DeCaprio on Faceberg&amp;quot;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lol.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857304&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856921&lt;br&gt;There has to be some truth to it. Do you really want to bring some slut back to your parents? But obviously just moving out isn&amp;#x27;t enough to get you laid&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858081&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you fall for obvious psyops like generational shit flinging at the boomers you were never going to make it. How a society treats it&amp;#x27;s vulnerable populations like the elderly and children directly impacts its future. They made mistakes and so will every generation after them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858095&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Imagine being so retarded you fall for something that has never provided any real product or service lmao. Could never happen to crypto investors lmao&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858113&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m honestly more annoying that an Indian scammer can get my parents to go and do things like load a gift card and transfer money when they act fucking retarded when I try to walk them through anything.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are boomers alive and employed who can barely use a computer.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m about to call a Jeet Center and pay them to threaten my dad to go to physical therapy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858115&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856070&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;re giving posters here too much credit. Retards here buy scams shilled in threads so Indian you can actually smell them&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858118&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You don&amp;#x27;t need to outrun the bear, you just need to outrun the fat retards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858123&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858081&lt;br&gt;KILL YOURSELF BOOMER&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858190&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858081&lt;br&gt;No sympathy for boomers. Sorry. There&amp;#x27;s a reason they are uniquely hated by all generations that came after them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858223&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856070&lt;br&gt;No your just retarded. But can you still help me out im a Nigerian price and im temporarily locked out of my fortune if you can help me with some money right now I&amp;#x27;ll be able to help you out ten fold when I get it back&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858749&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858223&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Nigerian price&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s spelled Niggerian&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859045&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858081&lt;br&gt;I hope a nigger beats you to death in a nursing home&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859069&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858081&lt;br&gt;Elderly are respected in cultures where they defer to younger generations. Boomers shut down the world for a flu and ruined lives of young people because they had a slightly higher chance of dying at 75 instead of 80.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859075&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I really do wonder what the scammers of the future will approach us with when we get old&lt;br&gt;Any ideas?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859083&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856070&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;microplastic brains will be MORE CAPABLE at advanced ages.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The dementia has already begun&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859086&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859075&lt;br&gt;Cryptocurrency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859094&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859083&lt;br&gt;More capable than lead and tobacco brain? Yes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>[TICKER | EXPLODING 56.0/hr] GERMANY TO END BURGERGELD PROGRAMS — 14 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858970</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858970?lm=1771210100</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 02:48:20 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;GERMANY TO END BURGERGELD PROGRAMS&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858970'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 14 • Updated: 2026-02-16 02:48 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;WILL BE REPLACED WITH A STRICTER PROGRAM IF YOU REFUSE WORK. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEXT STOP, PRIVATIZED HEALTHCARE.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858974&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Uh oh, Europeans actually have to work for a living now? Aw shucks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858980&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858974&lt;br&gt;They will soon legalize 12 hour work days much like Argentina has done. Even contributing 5% of their GDP to NATO has ultimately bankrupted them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859007&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858970&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wait you could get NEETbux in Germany this whole time by simply “refusing to work”? WTF&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859010&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It gets renamed every few years, but fundamentally nothing changes. Because most of the people who receive it (around 50% don’t have a German passport) are simply completely unemployable in the labor market (fat, sick, IQ below 80)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859053&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858974&lt;br&gt;Not really, it just tries to get you into work more&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859007&lt;br&gt;Yeah, it was introduced during the Ampel coaliation when Scholz was at the top&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859010&lt;br&gt;Bürgi was easier to get than HartzIV, now it seems they&amp;#x27;re trying to get back to HartzIV&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859055&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858970&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;African migrants and Somalis will be exempt&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;KEK&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859060&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858980&lt;br&gt;Technically 12 hour work days are legal in some profession in which it&amp;#x27;s assumed that you&amp;#x27;re not actively working all the time. This then gets noted as 10 hour work shift. I&amp;#x27;m unsure if this is something only reserved for a few specific occupations. The CDU currently is trying to tell us we should just work more. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859055&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t think we even get a noticeable amount of Somalis here, we do have lots of Ethiopians though&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859074&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859053&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crazy shit. I’d take that in a heartbeat. Can white ppl get it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859082&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858970&lt;br&gt;Does this apply to &amp;quot;refugees&amp;quot;?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859089&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859074&lt;br&gt;Yeah but I haven&amp;#x27;t checked the requirements. It&amp;#x27;s not a lot anyway.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859099&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858980&lt;br&gt;Bullshit. During the cold war the defense spending totalled to more than 10% of gdp.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859104&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859099&lt;br&gt;Did the cold war include importing millions of browns that refuse to gain successful employment? No?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859105&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858970&lt;br&gt;This is extremely fascist and racist&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859111&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859082&lt;br&gt;No. They have human rights&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>[TICKER | EXPLODING 37.8/hr] Can you feel it? — 28 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61854436</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61854436?lm=1771207872</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 02:11:12 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Can you feel it?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61854436'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 28 • Updated: 2026-02-16 02:11 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The greatest alt season of all time happens on Hitlers birthday. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;$ICP&lt;br&gt;$LINK&lt;br&gt;$ETH&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What did you pick?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854440&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If people on biz are still calling for altseason then we still have further to drop.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854443&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854440&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;If people on biz&lt;br&gt;I am not from biz I am from pol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854447&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854443&lt;br&gt;Even worse. Looks like next stop is another 70% drop.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854453&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854447&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Even worse&lt;br&gt;9gag pol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854467&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854436&lt;br&gt;delusional altchud&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854469&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854440&lt;br&gt;Just like groundhog day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854475&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854436&lt;br&gt;ICPP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854498&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854436&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;$ICP&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;$LINK&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;$ETH&lt;br&gt;No wonder /biz/ stays poor&lt;br&gt;lmao&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s not 2020 anymore&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854506&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;ve lost all hope and sold everything so it will prob happen now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854512&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854436&lt;br&gt;Altgoys are finished and 99.99999999 will never recover.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854883&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854512&lt;br&gt;Only those that sell.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855000&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;you shouldve&amp;#x27;have bought pepe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855027&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And another opportunity to buy pepe low missed, easy 5-10x from here just like the last .. three times?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855057&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854436&lt;br&gt;kek baggie&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855077&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854436&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;alt season&lt;br&gt;Read the room retard&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855143&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855027&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;And another opportunity to buy pepe low missed, easy 5-10x from here just like the last .. three times?&lt;br&gt;Sorry but I never invest in memecoins. It&amp;#x27;s a policy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855177&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854440&lt;br&gt;I’m a gay nigger tranny Jew from Reddit and I think we’re going to the moon!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855197&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854436&lt;br&gt;Altchuds rise up&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855255&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854436&lt;br&gt;kaspa, keeta&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855268&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855255&lt;br&gt;Crapspa is from Israel, I&amp;#x27;ll pass.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855733&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cronos is coming&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trump-media-files-launch-truth-212246960.html&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855758&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855733&lt;br&gt;thanks mat damon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856762&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855758&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;mat damon&lt;br&gt;No mat damon holds that cardano.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856967&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854498&lt;br&gt;Iccppppp was always shit but no wonder crypto starts to die if people still shit on its best tech because of muh new ponzi.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857529&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854436&lt;br&gt;and wheres the money that will pump the alt run coming from anon because last i checked crypto retail is dead&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857534&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855733&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857542&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857529&lt;br&gt;Not only is retail dead from lack of interest in getting rugged again, but they’re also broke&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859028&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AVAX is coming back u guys&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>[TICKER | EXPLODING 36.0/hr] Privacy Coins — 31 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61849447</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61849447?lm=1771207436</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 02:03:56 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Privacy Coins&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61849447'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 31 • Updated: 2026-02-16 02:03 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whether you like it or not, BTC is dying. Which way anons?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849481&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gold and silver.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849898&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849447&lt;br&gt;XMR as always. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849481&lt;br&gt;Acceptable but unusable for internet transactions and too easily stolen. Also makes smaller or spontaneous transactions harder unless the governments were to issue gold coins again and that would be bearish.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849958&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849447&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;BTC is a pedo coin&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;most used currency for CP is not however&lt;br&gt;quit the infighting, monegro.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850025&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849447&lt;br&gt;I have 100k USD in XMR and Kaspa, I&amp;#x27;m pretty sure crypto has bottomed or is going to crab all year at worst. &lt;br&gt;Lived through multiple cycles and this is always how the bottom looks and feels&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850046&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849958&lt;br&gt;He&amp;#x27;s against Monero but he&amp;#x27;s not very good at making that clear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850071&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why is nobody talking about Aztec? Smart contracts with private functions. Is an L2 on ethereum. Tons of businesses and applications will want private transactions for regulatory and other purposes. Am I missing something, or is the market cap insanely low for what it is? You&amp;#x27;d think bringing privacy to Ethereum would be a big deal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851550&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849447&lt;br&gt;yes I already use privacy coin: Bitcoin. Learn to use proper tools, noob&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61852712&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849958&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850046&lt;br&gt;The OP pic is interesting no matter how you slice it.. I think it calls into question the legitimacy of monegro. Who knows what else is in the &amp;quot;files.&amp;quot; Im not against monergro per se, but I was browsing the XMR general thread and I am not happy with what I saw over there. They are incredibly hostile to anyone non-monegro.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The lack of engagement here also bothers me, as that means that there are no alternatives other than a few eth based ones like the aztec one&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850071&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851550&lt;br&gt;Esptein aside, BTC has severe scalability issues&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;picrelated stolen from the monegro thread, i dont have any other memes on this pc&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854671&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61852712&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The OP pic is interesting no matter how you slice it.&lt;br&gt;Imagine letting demons and satanists control your life so much that you conspire against the letter M. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;They are incredibly hostile to anyone non-monegro.&lt;br&gt;No, we just despise you nerva shills. You&amp;#x27;re just &amp;#x27;asking questions&amp;#x27; but can&amp;#x27;t name a single one that hasn&amp;#x27;t been refuted multiple times. Then you cry about reddit as if that matters to 4chan. And then you just all seem to bring up, out of nowhere and completely unrelated of course, the solution which is an unmaintained jeetcoin with a ring size less than 1/3 of Monero&amp;#x27;s ring size and none of the development Monero received since 2018. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;as that means that there are no alternatives&lt;br&gt;Correct. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;a few eth based ones like the aztec one&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850071&lt;br&gt;ETH is PoS and a L2 will never be as good as a L1.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854812&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;/thread&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855004&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854671&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;ETH is PoS and a L2 will never be as good as a L1.&lt;br&gt;PoS is better that PoW. Something like what Chia has going on is arguably better for decentralization. Don&amp;#x27;t know what you mean by &amp;quot;never as good as L1&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855021&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855004&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;pos better than pow&lt;br&gt;The rest of your arguments are moot, because you start with a probably wrong premise&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855046&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855004&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Chia&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855184&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855021&lt;br&gt;Proof of asic is retarded.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855046&lt;br&gt;No such thing as a storage asic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855597&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849447&lt;br&gt;BTC is more alive than ever, most especially now with BTCFi narrative spreading like wild fire&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855672&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Proof of asic is retarded&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s at least as retarded as proof of space/memory&lt;br&gt;https://github.com/libbitcoin/libbitcoin-system/wiki/Proof-of-Memory-Fa%C3%A7ade&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855855&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849447&lt;br&gt;is monero the only non-jew coin out there?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855859&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;monero is the only actual privacy coin btw, all other coins are backdoored that&amp;#x27;s why nobody use them&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855868&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854671&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Imagine letting demons and satanists control your life so much that you conspire against the letter M.&lt;br&gt;Imagine ignoring it so hard that people like epstein are allowed to exist and eat your next door neighbors children while they backdoor BTC and then promote it. Fuck off.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;No, we just despise you nerva shills. You&amp;#x27;re just &amp;#x27;asking questions&amp;#x27; but can&amp;#x27;t name a single one that hasn&amp;#x27;t been refuted multiple times. Then you cry about reddit as if that matters to 4chan. And then you just all seem to bring up, out of nowhere and completely unrelated of course, the solution which is an unmaintained jeetcoin with a ring size less than 1/3 of Monero&amp;#x27;s ring size and none of the development Monero received since 2018.&lt;br&gt;What the fuck is nerva? and why am I a shill? What questions did I ask that even have a &amp;quot;refutation?&amp;quot; Reddit? &lt;br&gt;Nigger, what the actual fuck are you even talking about? Did you forget your meds? Im going to report your post as spam because none of what you said makes sense.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;picrelated.jpg&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854812&lt;br&gt;The line breaks being inconsistent is the same as all three 6&amp;#x27;s not being in upright position, for the two nuts for the tubal cain facebook logo not matching &amp;quot;Exactly.&amp;quot; If you&amp;#x27;re going to be a schizo, try to get on schizo levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855898&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Privacy coins&lt;br&gt;Why not Zcash?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855919&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855898&lt;br&gt;Several reasons, actually:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Centralized distribution from early dev-taxes to the founders (these taxes are still baked in but go to a slightly-less centralized committee now.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Privacy can be disabled at the protocol level because miners can reject the shielded pool. There is no fix to this because it would require removing the transparent pool entirely which would make Zcash delisted from all exchanges that it intentionally cripples its privacy for.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Mining hashrate is cornered, Zcash is 60% mined by a singe pool at any given time, and the 20% pool is the one that blocks the shielded pool.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Founder outright said they work with DC and will make Zcash private but not so private it could be used for crime.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855926&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849447&lt;br&gt;US Dollars ticker $&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856365&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855898&lt;br&gt;mossad coin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856605&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The line breaks being inconsistent is the same as all three 6&amp;#x27;s not being in upright position, for the two nuts for the tubal cain facebook logo not matching &amp;quot;Exactly.&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;No, it&amp;#x27;s not similar at all. The arches of the M are completely different.&lt;br&gt;The chrome symbol is the divine king symbol and matches exactly, and you can see far more similarities between the tubal Cain and facebook logos.&lt;br&gt;This meme sucks, the discord you got it from sucks, your ability to evaluate schizo levels suck, and you suck.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856661&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856605&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;unironically puts himself in a position that makes him look like he works for the very societies listed in infograph by explaining symbols further&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;t. mossad devil worshipper who sucks mason dick&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;only furthers the stereotype that monegro may be untrustworthy&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;claims i got my low quality infograph from discord&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Nigger i dont use discord&lt;br&gt;kek, the low quality bait and switch tactic always works on self proclaimed smart people&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856710&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849481&lt;br&gt;basedo!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856781&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;hurr durr i tricked you&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;a REAL schizo wouldn&amp;#x27;t know THAT much&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;i also don&amp;#x27;t know what t. means&lt;br&gt;I think we&amp;#x27;re done here&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857609&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849898&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;ve had thousands in BTC stolen via address poisoning, but my gold and silver are safe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858772&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856781&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;i also don&amp;#x27;t know what t. means&lt;br&gt;you have to be 18 to post here anon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858821&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858772&lt;br&gt;I remember when I turned 18 and my parents took me aside and told me that the abbreviated form of &amp;quot;regards&amp;quot; in finnish was a 4chan meme&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859002&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849447&lt;br&gt;Soon enough (this year) everything on ETH will be privacy enabled by ZAMA&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>[TICKER | EXPLODING 33.0/hr] /LETF/ — 28 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61850299</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61850299?lm=1771207481</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 02:04:41 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;/LETF/&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61850299'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 28 • Updated: 2026-02-16 02:04 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Leveraged ETF General /LETF/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Useful links:&lt;br&gt;https://www.optimizedportfolio.com/leveraged-etfs/&lt;br&gt;https://testfol.io&lt;br&gt;https://www.tradingview.com/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What are LETFs?&lt;br&gt;ETFs that use derivatives/debt to multiply daily returns of an index (1.25x, 1.5x, 2x, 3x). &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Popular tickers&lt;br&gt;TQQQ (3x QQQ), UPRO (3x SPY), SOXL (3x semis), TMF (3x long bonds), SPXL (3x SPY), SSO (2x SPY), QLD (2x QQQ), FNGU (3x FANG+)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recommended strategy discussion&lt;br&gt;HFEA (Hedgefundie&amp;#x27;s Excellent Adventure) - 55% UPRO / 45% TMF&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;9 Signal (9Sig)&lt;br&gt;Quarterly rebalance triggered by 9% growth target. Mechanical, removes emotion entirely.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;All Weather Leveraged&lt;br&gt;Risk parity across economic regimes. Typical: 30% UPRO / 40% TMF / 15% UGL / 15% commodities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;200 SMA Trend Following&lt;br&gt;Hold TQQQ/UPRO above 200 SMA, rotate to cash or bonds below. Simple, effective, hard to actually follow during crashes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Buy and Hold&lt;br&gt;Hold TQQQ or UPRO forever. Historically works over 15+ years but you will see 80%+ drawdowns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850323&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bros is this the top&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850542&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;stupidest shit you can possibly do&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850579&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850542&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s safer than holding 1x if you combine with bonds but you&amp;#x27;re a fucking retarded idiot fuck&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850789&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850579&lt;br&gt;you want less money this is the way&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850797&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850579&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;doesnt know about leveraged ETF decay&lt;br&gt;i think you&amp;#x27;re the fucking retarded idiot fuck&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851110&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850789&lt;br&gt;It has higher returns pussy ass faggot&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851116&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850797&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;leveraged ETF decay&lt;br&gt;That&amp;#x27;s not real stop reading Reddit. If TQQQ is at $50 and goes to $25 and goes back to $50 you have the same money. Nothing has changed. Check the backtests retard&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851225&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851116&lt;br&gt;I held a 2x gold etf over a period of a year and ended up making less gains that just holding a 1x spot gold.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851265&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851110&lt;br&gt;nope not only do you make less but you also risk getting liquidated for less in return&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851622&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850299&lt;br&gt;fyi hedgefundie&amp;#x27;s excellent adventure underperforms the state street S&amp;amp;P etf over the last 10 years&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851716&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TS3S&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851768&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850299&lt;br&gt;leverfags are going to get fucking bitchslapped this year&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851778&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851116&lt;br&gt;ok have fun under performing while taking MORE risk you retarded faggot lmao. btw you need to be 18 to post here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851780&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;just keep doing 10:1 reverse splits, it&amp;#x27;s gonna be ok&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851782&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851116&lt;br&gt;what the fuck are you even talking about? holy shit you are retarded&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851974&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851265&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851778&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;https://testfol.io/?s=fEyPujgL7hR&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Explain this then you fucking retards. Why do you talk about things you don&amp;#x27;t know about? Less risk in every measure. Higher returns and bonds to buy at the bottom which you can&amp;#x27;t do in a 1x so the returns actually triple what what this says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853034&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851974&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t know or care what autistic bs you have come up with&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854867&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;So I should or shouldn&amp;#x27;t dump everything into TQQQ?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854950&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854867&lt;br&gt;do it or no balls&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855048&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;many 2x single stock letfs have ripped hard as fuck. i think mstu had the biggest gain of all etfs last year. why do ppl forget about these when discussing letfs?? way better r/r than the upro&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855084&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850299&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; SMA200 for TQQQ and UPRO&lt;br&gt;in my backtests, SMA155 for QQQ and SMA100 for SPY were optimal&lt;br&gt;still LRS is a robust strat, so much so that 200 could be pretty good&lt;br&gt;Note: Take the signal as a crossing of the SMA on the underlying QQQ, then buy/sell TQQQ as per the lead-lag setup from the LRS paper&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856187&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;My Roth IRA is 100% $RSSB&lt;br&gt;Will it pay off? Who knows! Personally, I don&amp;#x27;t think currency will exist by the time I need a Roth IRA. My regular investment portfolio is 100% $UPRO&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856195&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851974&lt;br&gt;when quantum computers crack the stock market the LETFs will be zero in one 50% candle&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856264&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850579&lt;br&gt;You are an idiot nigger, enjoy your daily decay retard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856685&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since we all can agree leveraged ETFs are retarded for anything than holding shit for a single day, what&amp;#x27;s the alternative in case I want to 2x some index?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858796&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854867&lt;br&gt;I dunno. You want a guaranteed +6% by next Friday?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858983&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851116&lt;br&gt;These&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Im bad at math xD&lt;br&gt;Types here give us the stat of the avg investor failing to beat the market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859005&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850789&lt;br&gt;Let&amp;#x27;s look at MU and MUU&lt;br&gt;Both are moving around the same numbers up and down. MU goes up 20, MUU goes up 20. One is 400 one is 200. I can get twice the shares and go up the same amount. I can play this game for a few months and make shit tons of money. You want to go long and stay in MU, cool, no one gives a fuck.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>[TICKER | EXPLODING 28.0/hr] I can’t lose — 7 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61859036</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61859036?lm=1771210071</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 02:47:51 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;I can’t lose&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61859036'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 7 • Updated: 2026-02-16 02:47 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even if crypto is a zero and the macroeconomic environment becomes favorable to international &amp;amp; value, I would still outperform the stock market over the long term because my exposure to crypto is capped &amp;amp; I’m also heavily allocated to AVDV &amp;amp; AVUV &amp;amp; VXUS.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the other hand, even if the macroeconomic environment remains favorable for high-beta tech &amp;amp; growth stocks, I’ll benefit from the asymmetric upside of BTC/ETH/LINK etc. even if the small cap value premium continues to lag the broader stock market. And it’s not like I have no exposure to S&amp;amp;P 500 companies (VTI).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even in a scenario involving a broad liquidity drain or a severe economic recession where everything declines in the short term and crypto goes to zero, that environment would ultimately be positive for small cap value over the long run.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;And yes I’ve backtested this strategy with portfolio strategy. I’ve decided on a 10% allocation to crypto. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;So basically a compensated risk + uncompensated risk but asymmetric upside (crypto) barbell strategy for the long term.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anyone else doing this?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859042&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859036&lt;br&gt;*portfolio visualizer, not portfolio strategy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859048&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859036&lt;br&gt;You already lost honor by posting this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859050&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I dont think it going to 0 would outperform anything&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859052&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859048&lt;br&gt;Kys&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859090&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859036&lt;br&gt;you&amp;#x27;re going to outperform absolutely nothing&lt;br&gt;why not try living a little, you faggot pussy?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859108&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859090&lt;br&gt;I will, cry harder. Make an actual argument you retard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859110&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859036&lt;br&gt;Based OP. Faggots on this board are degenerate gamblers; they wouldn&amp;#x27;t understand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>[TICKER | EXPLODING 19.6/hr] Thread 61859046 — 6 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61859046</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61859046?lm=1771209438</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 02:37:18 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Thread 61859046&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61859046'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 6 • Updated: 2026-02-16 02:37 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;did any of you fall for the NFT thing back in the day?&lt;br&gt;i remember thinking NFTs were some cool futuristic thing, but never bought one, i thought about maybe making some, now i regret not doing it seeing how much money people were paying for an NFT.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859065&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859046&lt;br&gt;I know a guy who’s crushing the NFT market right now believe it or not. I guess he just follows the right people for mints&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859072&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859065&lt;br&gt;see, i don&amp;#x27;t even know what that means&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859076&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859065&lt;br&gt;he&amp;#x27;s trading them? Flipping them?&lt;br&gt;I made some money with them back in the day, tried my best to make beautiful things. Got so much backlash for it. It turned many artists into complete lunatics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859078&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Back in the day? Like two years ago?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859081&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859078&lt;br&gt;i swear NFTs were a 2016 thing no?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859092&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859076&lt;br&gt;He’s all over the place in different NFT groups trading, buying, selling. Actually talked to him today and he said he bought something for $1 and got an offer for .5 ETH. Meanwhile I’ve done nothing but lose money in crypto&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>[TICKER | EXPLODING 19.0/hr] I think I accidentally built a chain that can’t stall — 31 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61856571</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61856571?lm=1771204661</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 01:17:41 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;I think I accidentally built a chain that can’t stall&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61856571'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 31 • Updated: 2026-02-16 01:17 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Been working on a blockchain design alone for ~1 year. Not a fork. Not based on ETH or Cosmos. Entirely custom protocol.&lt;br&gt;noticed something strange while running validator simulations tonight.&lt;br&gt;Even when all validators go offline, the chain continues producing blocks.&lt;br&gt;Not fake blocks. Protocol-generated blocks. Deterministic. Verifiable. No consensus break.&lt;br&gt;This wasn’t originally the goal. It emerged from how ticket burning and slot timing interact.&lt;br&gt;Current properties:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; 3-second slots&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; leader selection via burned tickets (PoAsh)&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; protocol generates blocks if leader fails or no tickets eligible&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; chain never halts, even under 100% validator failure&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; validators can’t stall the chain intentionally or accidentally&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Still has bugs (pic related), but if this holds under edge cases, it removes one of the oldest failure modes in blockchain design: liveness collapse.&lt;br&gt;Still early. Still finding edge cases I didn’t anticipate.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Next test is validator rejoin after extended protocol-only operation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;posting devlogs elsewhere &amp;#x27;cause I kept losing simulation history when threads expire.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;devlogs: https://t [dot] me/+2SXaDc7CMYc4MTZh&lt;br&gt;posting validator logs, failures, and protocol behavior as they happen. easier than losing everything when threads expire.&lt;br&gt;can answer here too, but threads vanish.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856588&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Well have our boys in the lab run the data and get back to you when we have some results. Son, you might have just saved western civilization.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856601&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856588&lt;br&gt;current simulator shows protocol blocks advancing state root deterministically when no validator is eligible. still testing validator reintegration and fork resistance. bugs in pic related came from vault state transition edge case.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856604&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856571&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Not X, not Y, but Z.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;It&amp;#x27;s not X, it&amp;#x27;s Y&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thanks chatgpt, if I wanted to read ai gen shit, I would just message it myself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856611&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI sloppa&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856613&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856601&lt;br&gt;How do they sync later? This is going to be running simultaneously on many nodes. If it is so predictable it doesn&amp;#x27;t require more than one node then I think the advantages of decentralization are lost&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856633&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856613&lt;br&gt;protocol blocks are deterministic functions of prior chain state and slot number. every node computes the same block independently when no validator proposes one, so no fork emerges.&lt;br&gt;validators resume normal block production on top of that state when they return. protocol blocks preserve continuity but don’t replace validator economic function.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856641&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;youre a fucking nerd&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856647&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856571&lt;br&gt;Just shill me the coin ranjeesh don&amp;#x27;t sell me the moon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856654&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856647&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;17&lt;br&gt;no coin yet. still building and testing protocol behavior. economic layer comes after consensus layer is stable.&lt;br&gt;right now just making sure protocol behaves deterministically under failure conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856669&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It added &amp;quot;&amp;gt;17 &amp;#x27; by itdelf. Don&amp;#x27;t knowwhy. Must have been a glitch. I swear I didn&amp;#x27;t write it myself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856673&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856571&lt;br&gt;Probably bullshit, but if it&amp;#x27;s not just sell the tech and make alot of money&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856681&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856673&lt;br&gt;not really something you can sell. value comes from the network existing and being used, not from owning the design. still focused on getting protocol behavior correct first.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856691&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;validator&lt;br&gt;fiat with extra steps&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856695&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856681&lt;br&gt;What further features of the blockchain do you have in mind? Use cases?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What do you anticipate in terms or use cases and can you compare your end goal vs a current state of x competitor chain that you feel is ripe for disruption?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How far from a release of a beta do you think you are? This year?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856697&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856691&lt;br&gt;protocol advances independently of validators. validators only affect economic state transitions, not continuity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856705&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856571&lt;br&gt;sounds very centralized (so useless).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856712&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856695&lt;br&gt;right now the focus is getting the consensus layer stable and predictable under failure conditions. the main property i&amp;#x27;m targeting is guaranteed continuity — the chain advances regardless of validator availability.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;use case-wise, that makes it more reliable as base infrastructure. most chains assume validators are always present and coordinated. removing that assumption reduces fragility during outages, network partitions, or coordination failures.&lt;br&gt;not trying to outcompete eth or sol on throughput or ecosystem initially. goal is a minimal base layer with strong liveness guarantees and deterministic behavior. economic layer and higher-level features come after consensus is proven stable.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;simulator is partially working now. still testing validator reintegration, fork resistance, and edge cases. if behavior holds, public testnet this year is realistic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856716&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856705&lt;br&gt;protocol blocks don’t introduce authority. they’re deterministic and computed independently by every node from prior state. no single node controls them.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;validators still perform the economically meaningful function — proposing transaction-containing blocks and advancing state beyond empty continuity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856723&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856716&lt;br&gt;centralized and doesnt scale, so in other words useless dogshit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856917&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856654&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856571&lt;br&gt;Can you airdrop us altcoin crash victims each 0.1% of the supply at least?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856928&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856917&lt;br&gt;no distribution yet. still focused on getting protocol behavior stable first. economic layer and supply model come after consensus is proven.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856955&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856571&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Been working on a blockchain design alone for ~1 year.&lt;br&gt;Autism?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856983&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856955&lt;br&gt;probably.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856989&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How do I track this obvious scam so I can buy some early and try to dump it ontop of someone else&amp;#x27;s head before it collapses and steals all of my money?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857011&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856989&lt;br&gt;no coin or market yet. still working on protocol and simulator. devlogs are here: https://t&lt;br&gt; [dot] me/+2SXaDc7CMYc4MTZh&lt;br&gt;github coming once core behavior is stable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857041&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856928&lt;br&gt;AIRDROPS ARE BACK ON THE MENU BOYS&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857393&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856571&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;accidentally&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857448&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856633&lt;br&gt;Absolute AI slop, anyone with any technical reasoning level above 0 IQ would understand u made like 3 logical mistakes there&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;node process same block independantly&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Resume ontop of that state&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;No validator proposal&lt;br&gt;And then ofc this doesnt stall? &lt;br&gt;Lol&lt;br&gt;Lmao even&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857466&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856604&lt;br&gt;Exactly my thoughts, chatgpt slop&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857487&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856604&lt;br&gt;/thread&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858876&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856712&lt;br&gt;Thank you. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Can you explain how this chain retains any sort of decentralization when validators are/were offline?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Can you walk me through the scenario when validators are offline but chain activity still occurs, and then one or more validators are brought back online? Give me the before, middle and end states&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>[TICKER | EXPLODING 18.7/hr] Thread 61858975 — 12 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858975</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858975?lm=1771208232</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 02:17:12 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Thread 61858975&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858975'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 12 • Updated: 2026-02-16 02:17 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Is living anywhere except Los Angeles, San Francisco, Washington DC, or New York the same as admitting that your life is meaningless and that you are NOT the main character and will never make it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858982&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;Dubai, Paris, London, Tokyo, Kyoto&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858987&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You burgers aren&amp;#x27;t ready for what&amp;#x27;s coming&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858990&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;HAHAHA&lt;br&gt;HAHAHAHA&lt;br&gt;IMAGINE LIVING IN A BROWN SHITHOLE&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858993&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;your life is meaningless if you don’t live around deranged niggers and violent homeless people&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859000&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;Everyone i know in LA is leaving or wants to leave.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859001&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858993&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;he fell for retarded /pol/ memes&lt;br&gt;California is the most beautiful place on earth&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859017&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859001&lt;br&gt;Are you living in the 1950s?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859021&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859001&lt;br&gt;Yeah, in the places where people aren&amp;#x27;t allowed to live like National Parks and National Forest. In the brown, populated parts of the state there&amp;#x27;s no water or if there is ocean, you can&amp;#x27;t even swim in the water after it rains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859032&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859000&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;true&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859043&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Los Angeles = Mexicans&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;San Francisco = Gays&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Washington DC = Pedos&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;New York = Niggers&lt;br&gt;Why the fuck would you want to live in any of those absolute shitholes around the worst humans alive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859044&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859043&lt;br&gt;the weather is really nice&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859049&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;Why would I want to live amongst mexicans, gays, niggers or jews?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859043&lt;br&gt;New york is jews.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>[TICKER | 848.6/hr] /GME/ - Settle in for Comfy (Long) Weekend Edition — 318 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61853052</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61853052?lm=1771209191</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 02:33:11 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;/GME/ - Settle in for Comfy (Long) Weekend Edition&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61853052'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 318 • Updated: 2026-02-16 02:33 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;Basic Information&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;gme.cac site redacted due to aids&lt;br&gt;https://finra-markets.morningstar.com/MarketData/EquityOptions/detail.jsp?query=14%3A0P000002CH&lt;br&gt;https://gmetimeline.com (up to 2021)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Daily reminder&lt;br&gt;s[Kek Melvies]bzilp4&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Mandatory study time&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The Everything Short&lt;br&gt;reddit.com/mgucv2&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;^watch-along&lt;br&gt;youtu.be/AaalT8rn9lc&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Naked Short Selling and Systemic Risk&lt;br&gt;youtu.be/FCiL4v7_z9E&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Failure to deliver&lt;br&gt;youtu.be/I0WXg5T3cBE&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;GameStop Investor Site&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;SEC 10-K Annual report FY24 &amp;amp; &amp;#x27;25 Proxy Statement&lt;br&gt;news.gamestop.com/annual-meeting/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;What will happen if Citadel becomes insolvent?&lt;br&gt;DTCC with 60T USD, will pay as the final boss with FDIC as the insurance&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Real-Time Trades&lt;br&gt;https://www.nasdaq.com/market-activity/stocks/GME/latest-real-time-trades&lt;br&gt;https://eresearch.fidelity.com/eresearch/gotoBL/fidelityTopOrders.jhtml&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Current Trade Halts + Short Restrictions&lt;br&gt;nasdaqtrader.com/Trader.aspx?id=TradeHalts&lt;br&gt;nyse.com/markets/nyse-arca/notices&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;All other news/DDs/etc&lt;br&gt;en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Stag_hunt&lt;br&gt;https://prospect.org/power/how-the-gamestop-hustle-worked&lt;br&gt;https://computershared.net/?bot=drsbot&lt;br&gt;DRS Guide:&lt;br&gt;reddit.com/ptvaka&lt;br&gt;Avoid DSPP (more information under legacy links):&lt;br&gt;sec.gov/about/reports-publications/investor-publications/holding-your-securities-get-the-facts&lt;br&gt;HF/broker class action lawsuit evidence:&lt;br&gt;storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.flsd.590042/gov.uscourts.flsd.590042.416.0.pdf&lt;br&gt;SEC GME/meme stocks report:&lt;br&gt;sec.gov/files/staff-report-equity-options-market-struction-conditions-early-2021.pdf&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;DD Compilation:&lt;br&gt;reddit.com/mnss65&lt;br&gt;Quarterly Movements, Equity Total Return Swaps, DOOMPs, ITM CALLs, Short Interest, and Futures Roll Periods:&lt;br&gt;reddit.com/pb22oj&lt;br&gt;Cellar Boxing:&lt;br&gt;reddit.com/pmj9yk&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Temporary alliance with reddit and Jaws to take down other sharks, we can go back to hating each other later&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;reddit DDs don&amp;#x27;t take them for fact use your brain&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Check your broker and clearing house to ensure you&amp;#x27;re not rugpulled&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last time on /GME/: &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61847072&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As always:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;sneed hedgies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853060&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853052&lt;br&gt;Still comfy waitin&amp;#x27; and holdin&amp;#x27;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Summary&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;GameStop Info&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Complete corporate revamp by Ryan Cohen&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Debt free with positive increases and reductions (see ER); $8.8 B cash and cash equivalents on hand + high inventory&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;DRS &amp;amp; Computershare&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;~67.0 million shares of ~448.0: 15% total held by Dec 5, 2025&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;~66.7/~447.7: 15% 9/5, ~68.1/~447.3: 15% 6/5, ~69.5/~447.08: 16% 3/19&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;~71.0/~446.8: 16% Dec 4, 2024&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;~72.8/~426.5: 17% 9/4, ~74.6/~351: 21% 6/5&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;~75.3 of ~305 25% by Mar 20, 2024,&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;~75.4 by Nov 30 2023, ~75.4 8/31, ~76.6 6/1, ~76.0 3/22 Vs Cede &amp;amp; Co&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Previously 71.8 (17.95) M shares DRS&amp;#x27;d by Oct 29, 2022, 71.3 by 7/30,&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;12.7 of ~77 by 4/30, 8.9 by 1/29&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;and 5.2 by Oct 30 2021&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unfuddable&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Shorts never closed and there exists more fakes than real shares&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;#x27;MOASS&amp;#x27; is a matter of time&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Further information can found by reading the OP or DYOR!&lt;br&gt;Reply to this pasta for any confusion.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;WGAMI!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other news/reminders:&lt;br&gt;Wednesday RRP: 1.048B, 6P = 0.175B per (roughly)&lt;br&gt;Thursday RRP: 2.844B, 10P = 0.2844B per&lt;br&gt;Friday RRP: 0.377B, 3P = 0.126B per (roughly)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investor site links to SEC for old filings, FAQ for warrants exp [Oct 30 2026]&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;4-for-1 Stock Split Form of stock dividend (Rec: Jul 18, 2022; Dist. 21st AH)&lt;br&gt;^2022-07-06 8-K&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Q3 25 8-K/10-Q&lt;br&gt;^2025-12-09&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Proxy Statement: Stock given in comp issued as RSUs that vest in quarterly increments over 4 years.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;798 pg SEC doc confessions of FIs/MMs/HFs/DCEs/Swaps Counterparties etc on short selling transparency&lt;br&gt;sec.gov/comments/s7-11-23/s71123-typec.pdf&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;100 page comparison DD&lt;br&gt;https://pdfhost.io/v/05TEEk3U6_MOV_GME_Comparison_Doc&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Legacy links&lt;br&gt;wallet.gamestop.com&lt;br&gt;nft.gamestop.com&lt;br&gt;www.gmedd.com/report-model (Nov 2021)&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Use archives&lt;br&gt;Avoid DSPP:&lt;br&gt;reddit.com/r/DRSyourGME/comments/12pfm9s/&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;GME shorted percentage of float as of Jan 15th, 2021: 226.42%&lt;br&gt;www.rosenlegal.com/media/casestudy/2289_Robinhood%20-%20Initial%20Complaint%20-%20Market%20Manipulation%204835-8623-1514%20v.2.pdf&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please don&amp;#x27;t feed spammers and sliders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853135&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s been five years bro. How long you gonna keep posting this?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853136&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853135&lt;br&gt;Im here until I see more jews cry on tv&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858434&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858281&lt;br&gt;Based. There’s no way shorts can kick the can much longer. Shills want you to believe MOASS is really far away.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858442&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857549&lt;br&gt;Don&amp;#x27;t stop I&amp;#x27;m almost there&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858510&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858395&lt;br&gt;my legal teams reaction when it sees the &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;nfa&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858520&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858442&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;w32AYGeE&lt;br&gt;wait, it that an wagmi id?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;wayyy gayyyyy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858584&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858520&lt;br&gt;Do not interrupt my session bruddah&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858599&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;*fart*&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858640&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gamestop has acquired the US Treasury&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858651&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GameStop has acquired Canada&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858681&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858651&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;has acquired Canada&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s over. I sold.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858688&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gamestop acquired Boston Dynamics and the MLP IP.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858699&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alright, time to get serious now lads.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;GameStop has acquired Sonichu&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858703&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858699&lt;br&gt;ah yes, the integer underflow strategy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858730&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858651&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;muttfagging&lt;br&gt;how about you try acquiring gold in men&amp;#x27;s hockey first KEK&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858731&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858341&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858732&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858281&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858299&lt;br&gt;I sold another put option last week, so I may be picking up another 100 with you boys at expiry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858733&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gamestop has acquired 32 pbtid&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858739&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858730&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;gold in men&amp;#x27;s hockey&lt;br&gt;Literally no one cares about the Winter Olympics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858747&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gamestop has acquired CyberNiggers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858755&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858739&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;literally nobody&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;t. mutts that can&amp;#x27;t win at hockey ever&lt;br&gt;yea&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858760&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858755&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;He lied about filtering me earlier. &lt;br&gt;Figures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858768&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;https://youtu.be/7Y1moFmYKu4&lt;br&gt;uh oh stinkies...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858868&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858281&lt;br&gt;everyone and their mother already knew they were suppressing GME price, but it&amp;#x27;s still hilarious how everything else using this &amp;quot;meme&amp;quot; explode in price and confirm it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858890&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858731&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m a fan of big anime tiddies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858896&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858890&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;disgusting hanging utters&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;preferring this over a tight tummied b cup treadmill bunny &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;fucking disgusting. I know what kind of man you are mentally and spiritually. &lt;br&gt;Kill yourself TONIGHT&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858903&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858896&lt;br&gt;Slender women have an appeal but I prefer cows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858953&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857857&lt;br&gt;i ask this same question everytime people talk about selling GME at the top, who the fuck are going to buy it ? we know the answer but it will shut down any shill&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858961&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When they close the buy button down, who is buying the sell?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859073&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858281&lt;br&gt;I have 5000 GME shares, will I get a wife like that?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859085&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859073&lt;br&gt;Consult the chart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>[TICKER | 31.6/hr] Thread 61857490 — 45 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61857490</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61857490?lm=1771205407</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 01:30:07 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Thread 61857490&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61857490'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 45 • Updated: 2026-02-16 01:30 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US is in recession&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857499&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White collar recession comes before regular recession 100% of the time. We&amp;#x27;ve been in a white collar recession since 2020.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857500&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;Always was, its depression for over a year now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857508&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;GDP is growing, recession is fake.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nothing ever happens. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stop putting your vibes and feelings into your job search, learn to get better skills and be more marketable to employers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;McDonalds is always hiring&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857824&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857805&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;International order&lt;br&gt;Largely everything needed can be gotten in the US&amp;#x27;s backyard, such as Venezuelan oil, and be taken with minimal effort. Sure, it is tough to get everything optimal and a transition, but there was no other way&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857825&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857508&lt;br&gt;lmao kill all boomers&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857805&lt;br&gt;Canada isn&amp;#x27;t relevant and never will be relevant, mexico is totally dependent on the US and a parasite narco state. Being a pussy to appease useless europoors is not useful to a country like the USA that can invest in itself and have everything it needs. The only reason we haven&amp;#x27;t invaded greenland is hoping europeans stop with your constant arrogant bullshit and see the error of your faggoty ways.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857830&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857808&lt;br&gt;No it wasn&amp;#x27;t. And continuing to lie on 4chan won&amp;#x27;t change that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857840&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857830&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;it just wasn&amp;#x27;t&lt;br&gt;inflation was going down, employment was going up, consumer optimism was increasing. by every metric the economy was fragile but recovering. this administration destroyed that&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857846&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857824&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;there was no other way &lt;br&gt;Yeah except the way everything has been done for a century. You think the US had to go full autarky because… why exactly? &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857825&lt;br&gt;Canada is the largest consumer of US goods, followed by Mexico. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I mean what, do you guys think life will improve when international trade suffers? You don’t really believe that flippant and transient tariffs that last a few weeks and are leveraged as bargaining chips are going to bring back manufacturing, right?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857862&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The best part:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Almost all the growth is from Healthcare and Social Assistance&lt;br&gt;We are literally living in an economy built for boomers. Only jobs available are changing boomer diapers. GRIM GRIM GIM. &lt;br&gt;This timeline sucks!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857876&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857846&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;do you guys think life will improve when international trade suffers? You don’t really believe that flippant and transient tariffs that last a few weeks and are leveraged as bargaining chips are going to bring back manufacturing, right?&lt;br&gt;Yes, they really do. Burgerfats are that retarded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857890&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857508&lt;br&gt;the GDP growth is propped up by 10% and AI. &lt;br&gt;aka, the jews want us to believe money is moving when it doesn&amp;#x27;t. also consider all the money printing in the last 6 years, like for example during covid&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857891&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857779&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;What exactly have they done that doomed the country in a way it wasn&amp;#x27;t doomed by decisions made before then?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857949&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857808&lt;br&gt;This, and no other anons will admit it because they&amp;#x27;re all retards&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857996&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857949&lt;br&gt;Well, clearly some anons are admitting it, like us omegabased superchads&lt;br&gt;too many republicanfags dont seem to realize the republican party is no longer very libertarian, the big orangutan keeps sticking his dirty hand into the economy, mainly to benefit the jews&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857998&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857779&lt;br&gt;threatening to invade your long term allies for the absolutely worst of reasons is a good one to become an international pariah&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857808&lt;br&gt;this look at hard data not just number go up in a handful of ai stocks that dragged the entire index up&lt;br&gt;without ai spend 2022-23 and 24 were a recession but the stock numbers were moved up&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858020&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They are going to start helicoptering out money for manufacturing at home to end the trade deficit with china.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is all part of a plan. The chinese have been causing all bubbles since the GFC because they have nothing to spend FIAT money on so trump has to end the trade deficit to stabilize things and that means massively devaluing the US dollar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858023&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857508&lt;br&gt;This. The economy is doing great. The Dow Jones is at 50k. Would be a shame if something bad were to happen that causes a crash to these indexes, like not closing a certain investigation against the people who keep your money safe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858033&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857779&lt;br&gt;Reduced confidence in policy stability and increased perception of political corruption&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;quot;Doomed&amp;quot; is hyperbole, though&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858034&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857812&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;pretending there was a point and that you weren&amp;#x27;t just being called out for being retarded (you are)&lt;br&gt;No wonder you&amp;#x27;re unemployed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858084&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858023&lt;br&gt;She&amp;#x27;s pretty cute for a 60 year old, I can&amp;#x27;t help but fantasize her wearing black lingerie doing unspeakable things whenever I see her at a congressional hearing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858131&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;and have you even said thank you ONCE, anon?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858335&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857779&lt;br&gt;Destroyed trust in america, which is the #1 prerequisite for any economic activity&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858342&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857508&lt;br&gt;by this logic, if 1 person earned 100% of GDP but it was high enough, there would be no recession&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858343&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857840&lt;br&gt;Now if only they could put a leash on their trannies and the war-kikes it wouldn&amp;#x27;t have come to this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858364&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;Who gets to decide when the Second Great Depression is under way?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858366&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857808&lt;br&gt;lol, lmao even.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858379&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857824&lt;br&gt;Not only did you pick a commodity (hint: it&amp;#x27;s derived from the word common), you&amp;#x27;re not even right about it because oil companies agree Vlvenezuelan oil is not profitable&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858383&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Weakest year for job creation since the Great Recession&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Almost as many layoffs as during 2020&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How the fuck is unemployment only at 4.3%?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858397&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857499&lt;br&gt;Except 2022 had a labour shortage&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858404&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858383&lt;br&gt;https://fred.stlouisfed.org/series/CIVPART&lt;br&gt;Also I do not think they count gig workers as unemployed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858449&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858383&lt;br&gt;If you don&amp;#x27;t apply for one job a month, you&amp;#x27;re not unemployed. If you have a masters degree and you work at McDonald&amp;#x27;s, you&amp;#x27;re not unemployed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858696&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;I voted for this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858910&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857805&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Disrupted the international order from which the US greatly benefitted and everyone else benefited from the US even more&lt;br&gt;fuck off retard. did you forget&lt;br&gt;-single handedly carrying NATO&lt;br&gt;-protecting international shipping lanes&lt;br&gt;-being the global leader in innovation and tech&lt;br&gt;-only genuine believer and de facto practitioner of promoting human rights&lt;br&gt;? fuck you euronigger canacuck spic or whatever you are. we&amp;#x27;re allowed to take care of ourselves for once.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>[TICKER | 31.3/hr] Thread 61858027 — 41 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858027</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858027?lm=1771205830</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 01:37:10 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Thread 61858027&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858027'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 41 • Updated: 2026-02-16 01:37 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you had to place your entire life savings into ONE crypto currency or ONE single stock,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What would you bet your life savings on?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858042&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858027&lt;br&gt;I though it was a hot webm and feel deceived&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858046&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858027&lt;br&gt;AGNC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858053&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858027&lt;br&gt;Easy: CHAINLINK&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858108&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858054&lt;br&gt;Why tho&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858130&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858087&lt;br&gt;maybe in the past, but it developed into too much of a Buffett cult; which works against you when the leader of the cult is about to retire&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858027&lt;br&gt;It would be a toss-up between three companies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;American Electric Power (AEP)&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; the company has paid a dividend every single quarter for well over 120 years; and the world would probably have to end before they would willingly break that streak&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Waste Management (WM)&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; in a world with few certainties, garbage is one of them. They also pay a dividend&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lockheed Martin (LMT)&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; sure, it&amp;#x27;s possible that peace will break out all over the world and they will lose their customers; but short of the return of Jesus, LMT will keep earning and keep paying a dividend to their shareholders&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858156&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858027&lt;br&gt;Single stock: GOOG&lt;br&gt;If ETF allowed: 2x Nasdaq&lt;br&gt;Your pic: semi-inducing&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858161&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858027&lt;br&gt;Litecoin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858166&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858156&lt;br&gt;Are you me? I&amp;#x27;m mostly GGLL TQQQ&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858180&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cronos (CRO)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Remember this. You&amp;#x27;ll thank me later.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858193&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858166&lt;br&gt;I also have a metric fuck ton of a coin called DOVU&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858199&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858027&lt;br&gt;berkshire&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858226&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858027&lt;br&gt;For &amp;quot;crypto&amp;quot;, obviously Bitcoin (BTC, not any of the scams that claim to be satoshi&amp;#x27;s vision or &amp;quot;cash&amp;quot; or other dogshit).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For stonks, I&amp;#x27;d pick an S&amp;amp;P500 tracking ETF. If you absolutely insist on a single corporation, I&amp;#x27;d wait for the SpaceX IPO. I currently have a little worry about the Democraps trying to destroy Elon, but right now SpaceX is essential, there is no other company that can do what they do. Remember when Biden left astronauts stranded on the ISS for eight months because he refused to let Elon send up a special mission to bring them back? Remember when Artemis finally launched its test flight seven years late?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite BO posturing, BONG only has the capacity of FH but with a wider fairing, while BONS is a fucking amusement park ride for the super-rich; literally the only reason BONG might ever get chosen by private industry is anti-Musk hatred (the feds will subsidize the fuck out of BO just to keep &amp;quot;second source&amp;quot; capability). ULA is having repeated trouble with Vulcan booster failures and only exists due to direct subsidies; it&amp;#x27;s not even remotely cost-competitive with SpaceX, and will probably be dropped as &amp;quot;second source&amp;quot; if BO ever gets certified.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As for foreign competition, no one trusts China with their satellites because of Chinese espionage, the EU&amp;#x27;s ArianeSpace is just France trying to pretend to be relevant, and LOL Russia ROFL, see vidrelated.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Starship will make SpaceX the most efficient launch operator ever, with costs to orbit dropping by literally over an order of magnitude compared to any competitor. They&amp;#x27;re going to be huge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858240&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858027&lt;br&gt;SPXL&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858245&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858226&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;ULA is having repeated trouble with Vulcan booster failures&lt;br&gt;See picrelated, that third plume flowing between the two main ones is a leak from the right-hand bottle.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858199&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858087&lt;br&gt;Buffett and Munger are both in their 90s and retiring; the magic is gone.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858059&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858156&lt;br&gt;One word: antitrust (or if you&amp;#x27;re European, &amp;quot;competition&amp;quot;). The company is going to get forcibly broken up at some point because they&amp;#x27;re being dicks to their customers (deliberately crippling search so that people have to keep trying keywords and thus view more ads; censoring YouTube and GMail due to the management&amp;#x27;s political biases; helping China build its surveillance tools).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858161&lt;br&gt;LOL baggies, you can&amp;#x27;t even beat out the shitcoin known as BCH.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858248&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858027&lt;br&gt;GME warrants&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858252&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858027&lt;br&gt;zoomer makeup is super cute&lt;br&gt;why do zoomer girls have better fashion than millenials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858280&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858245&lt;br&gt;retard, erkshire will be around until Iam dead. The company will probaby grow along the S&amp;amp;P500. Its probably the most conservative long time investment you could make if you only want to invest in 1 stock. it will probably give you the same return as every world ETF&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858303&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858027&lt;br&gt;LINK&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858358&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;bzz&lt;br&gt;anything funded by the ethereum foundation is a safe bet&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858363&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858027&lt;br&gt;Neither&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m already in 100% physical silver&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858417&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858027&lt;br&gt;Monero&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858445&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858245&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The company is going to get forcibly broken up at some point because they&amp;#x27;re being dicks to their customers&lt;br&gt;Absolutely not. They will not be broken up in the US market. The reason being the US NEEDS a tech megascaler who is not a pure AI play. Google is the only such example. &lt;br&gt;Also, antitrust only really starts being necessary when the established corpos make entering the market difficult for newcomers. But that is NOT the case with tech. The opposite. The sector is healthy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858492&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858616&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858108&lt;br&gt;Needs a turn around. Severly beaten down due to AI software panic meme. 85% off all time high, 58% down YTD, and they&amp;#x27;re porfitable. Huge value here for patient investors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858623&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;That&lt;br&gt;Is&lt;br&gt;A&lt;br&gt;Man&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858805&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858027&lt;br&gt;@grok make her naked&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858806&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858027&lt;br&gt;At current prices? MSFT&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858813&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858027&lt;br&gt;Bitcoin, or if an ETF counts, VT&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858829&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why does she look like goddess happa? Forgot her name, the one that did the porn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858835&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;some stupid biotech gamble&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858899&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858829&lt;br&gt;mayli (i thought the same)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858912&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALL my savings? Bitcoin it is.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858932&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858156&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858166&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;ve been on the google + TQQQ train for many years now and have made bank. Was a very obvious play starting around 2015.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Concerned to see it getting shilled in more places lately, makes me think the dumb money has finally arrived and we are due for a reckoning&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>