<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>/biz/ Active (no generals, context, ticker-first, exploding)</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/</link><description>OP + first 3 replies + last 30 replies. Ticker threads boosted. Exploding threads flagged.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 10:06:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>[TICKER | EXPLODING 152.0/hr] Professor Jian says Bitcoin is CIA — 38 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61856632</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61856632?lm=1771236308</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 10:05:08 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Professor Jian says Bitcoin is CIA&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61856632'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 38 • Updated: 2026-02-16 10:05 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Been listening to this asian nigga for a while, he&amp;#x27;s now saying that BTC is CIA or NSA project.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The anonymity and &amp;quot;store of value&amp;quot; would benefit them greatly while permitting them to spy economies like North Korea&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856648&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Epstein had a role in making it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856649&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856632&lt;br&gt;Wait until you learn about how the internet was invented, FUDboy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856651&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856632&lt;br&gt;so, much like the Internet?&lt;br&gt;Cool, Thank you, CIA (or NSA)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856775&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856659&lt;br&gt;Definitely. Answer yourself this: what could a government&amp;#x27;s incentive be to ban 1 cryptocurrency (monero) over the other?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856809&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856632&lt;br&gt;This was well known on /biz/ 10 years ago&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What has this board become&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856813&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856757&lt;br&gt;he has some good thoughts im ngl, i assume he teaches at a chinese private school. to give him the benefit of the doubt..&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;germany was the most advanced civilization the world has ever known.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;teh lectures on the divine comedy&lt;br&gt;learned some new stuff from those i thought it was good...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856818&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856632&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;BTC is CIA or NSA project.&lt;br&gt;Yeah no shit&lt;br&gt;Are you willing to bet against the american empire thought? I think it still has a couple of centuries in it, so I&amp;#x27;m investing in it&amp;#x27;s scams.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856821&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856632&lt;br&gt;Its not just bitcoin, &amp;quot;every crypto&amp;quot; is back door&amp;#x27;d by the spooks.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8QdCvssobis&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857097&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856728&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Shines light on sabbatean frankists&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;Just milk toast jew apologist&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ok moshe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857143&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856821&lt;br&gt;Except monero&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857151&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856632&lt;br&gt;except its not anonymous at all and that chink is a canadian&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857155&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856632&lt;br&gt;This guy is literally retarded&lt;br&gt;Not a professor&lt;br&gt;Fake classroom, no students&lt;br&gt;Fields &amp;quot;questions&amp;quot; for Chinese operatives&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857164&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;it’s a CIA/NSA project bro&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;just forget about the fact that this would fuck over the USD’s reserve currency status and that the government has 1,000 bitcoin or so from seizures, and that they could’ve stacked a million bitcoin when they were cheap&lt;br&gt;A lot of you just say shit that you think is smart but you don’t think about the implications. This is similar to how most of you stack gold and silver to fight the so-called “banking cartel”, but are actually pumping their bags (and especially China’s) in the process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857167&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856728&lt;br&gt;The term is milquetoast anon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857212&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;well i heard bihcoih ih chinee&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857377&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857164&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;stack gold and silver to fight the so-called “banking cartel”, but are actually pumping their bags (and especially China’s) in the process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857400&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;the internet was invented by the american military?! =0&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857570&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856728&lt;br&gt;He has an entire series on Jews called Empire of Evil… he literally calls them the most evil people alive and alludes to child rape and child sacrifice done by Jews.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857586&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856632&lt;br&gt;I worked with a guy around 2013, young kid. He moved back home to D.C. to work at the NSA.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Immediately after joining the NSA he set up an entire server farm for crypto mining in his house to the point he had to have extra power connected to his house.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crypto currency is just distributed code breaking. Probably Soviet era encryption that they collected but couldn&amp;#x27;t Crack at the time.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You will never convince me crypto mining isn&amp;#x27;t just distributed code breaking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857606&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856632&lt;br&gt;I think this dude works for the CCP. He has tons of videos of him being critical of western countries but never China.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857610&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857586&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;correct, but they always do stuff that serves more than one purpose. Another purpose is to influence the value of large tranches of fiat. by managing the stock and bond market AND now crypto, &amp;quot;they&amp;quot; can keep more fiat in float.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857616&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857606&lt;br&gt;Maybe he&amp;#x27;s just a based patriot?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857722&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856809&lt;br&gt;Nigga, before was too early to believe you know how these schyzos are. But if you are so well informed, where do you park your dollariños?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859144&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856632&lt;br&gt;its not anonymous though&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;why should i listen to anything he has to say if half of what hes said already is wrong&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859215&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857164&lt;br&gt;why would it fuck over the USDs hegemony you fucking mong? It’s metrically compared in USD derivatives, do people genuinely compare BTC in terms of yen/pesos/rubles/euros/shillings? It’s USD derivatives that run headlines, then mongs in mong countries do their little calculations and transfer USD derivatives to get their little mongbucks. It’s a finite asset class in the age of blackbook off the market metal reserves so to speak, you can actually tangibly quantify the amount of BTC around, and ergo it is metrically compared and keeps hegemony for USD derivatives. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;My favorite part of this whole little charade, which most countries will ignore to their detriment is that fact that rock markets are for rockheads.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What is more logical? Off the market reserves of metals being in these underground areas, or secret evil reptilian new world order agarthan new energy technology? The answer is obvious, and you get to watch the biggest rugpull of the century on these little pissant BRICs nations who think they’re smart for using their tangible asset classes to buy rocks. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yes Mr Russian you are so smart, please invest and base your currency off a rock please. Oh yes Mr Chow, please base your currency off rocks, you a so smart and a bigga brained you have figured out how to beat the banking cartel!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As I have said ad naseum, digital numbers on a screen can be returned but speculative valuations cannot! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;oh look Mr Goldman found 10 trillion dollars of gold in a cave randomly!&lt;br&gt;Use your imagination, and have fun!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859226&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857722&lt;br&gt;Maybe into the asset with the backing from the people who run the fucking world?! Why the fuck do you think we are all in Chainlink?? For the underdog story?! This shit was predetermined and we are here to profit from it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859245&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856632&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;PROFESSOR DING DONG SAYS CHING CHONG&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859264&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856728&lt;br&gt;Hes more right about almost everything than 99.99% of people&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ancient roman history was invented by satanists i just know it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859892&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856632&lt;br&gt;post link, watched some of his stuff recently, too, always curious on all the theories surrounding crypto, most are such low IQ takes it&amp;#x27;s ridiculous and entertaining.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860033&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856659&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;hard earned&lt;br&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Y0O6ZjdRAy0&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860065&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856659&lt;br&gt;absolutely not. Monero&amp;#x27;s exit liquidity sucks because it&amp;#x27;s a coin made for anonymity (crime). &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Diversify your money into literally anything else.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860080&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857606&lt;br&gt;Anon, he calls Chinese people soulless materialists all the time&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860085&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857167&lt;br&gt;newfag&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>[TICKER | EXPLODING 24.7/hr] Yurop is BROKE, POOR, DESTITUTE, DOWNTRODDEN — 19 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858634</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858634?lm=1771233595</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:19:55 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Yurop is BROKE, POOR, DESTITUTE, DOWNTRODDEN&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858634'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 19 • Updated: 2026-02-16 09:19 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looks like yuros are gonna have to skimp on their tax derived healthcare and Germany is considering ending their Bürgergeld program.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;There is significant reluctance among voters in Britain and Germany to accept economic pain in return for rearmament, even while majorities in both countries believe the outbreak of a third world war is more likely than not in the next five years.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;German and French voters are also now less likely than they were last year to support increased defence budgets if it meant a trade-off with other investment, according to a poll for Politico this month.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858658&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858634&lt;br&gt;They are gonna attck russia in ukraine directly in 2029 mark my words. You can find me here at this time.&lt;br&gt;https://www.youtube.com/shorts/mo0dak0aor4&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858664&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858634&lt;br&gt;just raise taxes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858670&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858634&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;accept economic pain in return for rearmament&lt;br&gt;Ah yes and the economic pain must fall on white people and not on the millions of immigrants and &amp;quot;citizens&amp;quot; on welfare.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858672&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858670&lt;br&gt;Excuse me Chud these poor brown people are just trying to survife how can you not give them everything they want?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858674&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858664&lt;br&gt;European nations have a long and storied tradition of raising taxes to the point of revolution to fund their wars.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858734&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858634&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;There is significant reluctance among voters in Britain and Germany to accept economic pain in return for rearmament&lt;br&gt;That&amp;#x27;s because we&amp;#x27;re already having a lot of economic struggles since the sanctions against Russia. Also we think of ourselves as too advanced to do production of actual goods. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858658&lt;br&gt;They&amp;#x27;re currently preparing for 2027. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858670&lt;br&gt;Considering the current opinions of the german government it seems like we&amp;#x27;ll be equal in the squalor we live in.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858735&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858634&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Germany is considering ending their Bürgergeld program&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858758&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858634&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;europoors just gonna rely on the USA to win another war for them&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;in reality we&amp;#x27;re just going to be given Greenland and all that grandstanding was just a waste of time&lt;br&gt;christ what a joke continent kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858773&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858634&lt;br&gt;Germany won&amp;#x27;t end Burgergeld because half the migrants are on it. What they will do though is raise taxes and possibly go the Dutch route as well. It&amp;#x27;s not like anyone will protest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858789&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858773&lt;br&gt;why don&amp;#x27;t they just send the migrants on it back?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858799&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858789&lt;br&gt;Knock it off with the antisemitism&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858817&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858789&lt;br&gt;Muh human rights.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858824&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858634&lt;br&gt;I will gladly die for israel, ukraine and brussel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858952&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;60 IQ migroids are living expense free in gold plated hotels, and can get away with abhorrent crimes. Europeans are told they don&amp;#x27;t actually exist and aren&amp;#x27;t native to Europe.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are no greater cattle than those that would fight for this system&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859777&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858734&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;They&amp;#x27;re currently preparing for 2027.&lt;br&gt;2027 i dont think but yeah i almost wrote 2028. Its somewhere around these dates or a bit later&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859999&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858634&lt;br&gt;Its gonna get pretty bad and its not even a pol meme, the social net is what killed pretty much all crime in the continent, now they gonna have an extremely old population, low economic output and incentive for crime coupled with lots of violent migrants, and its all their fault because they couldnt breeeed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860002&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858789&lt;br&gt;Are you stupid?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860008&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858634&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;YOU MUST FIGHT TO SAVE GLOBOHOMO AND BOOMER PENSIONS&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;what fighting age white man would actually fall for this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860014&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860008&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;fighting age white man&lt;br&gt;there&amp;#x27;s like 3 of them left&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>[TICKER | EXPLODING 22.0/hr] I can’t lose — 12 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61859036</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61859036?lm=1771234406</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:33:26 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;I can’t lose&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61859036'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 12 • Updated: 2026-02-16 09:33 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even if crypto is a zero and the macroeconomic environment becomes favorable to international &amp;amp; value, I would still outperform the stock market over the long term because my exposure to crypto is capped &amp;amp; I’m also heavily allocated to AVDV &amp;amp; AVUV &amp;amp; VXUS.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the other hand, even if the macroeconomic environment remains favorable for high-beta tech &amp;amp; growth stocks, I’ll benefit from the asymmetric upside of BTC/ETH/LINK etc. even if the small cap value premium continues to lag the broader stock market. And it’s not like I have no exposure to S&amp;amp;P 500 companies (VTI).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even in a scenario involving a broad liquidity drain or a severe economic recession where everything declines in the short term and crypto goes to zero, that environment would ultimately be positive for small cap value over the long run.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;And yes I’ve backtested this strategy with portfolio strategy. I’ve decided on a 10% allocation to crypto. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;So basically a compensated risk + uncompensated risk but asymmetric upside (crypto) barbell strategy for the long term.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anyone else doing this?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859042&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859036&lt;br&gt;*portfolio visualizer, not portfolio strategy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859048&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859036&lt;br&gt;You already lost honor by posting this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859050&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I dont think it going to 0 would outperform anything&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859052&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859048&lt;br&gt;Kys&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859090&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859036&lt;br&gt;you&amp;#x27;re going to outperform absolutely nothing&lt;br&gt;why not try living a little, you faggot pussy?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859108&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859090&lt;br&gt;I will, cry harder. Make an actual argument you retard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859110&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859036&lt;br&gt;Based OP. Faggots on this board are degenerate gamblers; they wouldn&amp;#x27;t understand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859129&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What are we shilling Femboys all the sudden?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859182&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OP is a samefag who will commit suicide very soon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859194&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;That&amp;#x27;s a man.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859198&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859036&lt;br&gt;Based&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860032&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859036&lt;br&gt;why are you okay with being a homosexual?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>[TICKER | 229.2/hr] /GME/ - Settle in for Comfy (Long) Weekend Edition — 334 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61853052</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61853052?lm=1771231121</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 08:38:41 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;/GME/ - Settle in for Comfy (Long) Weekend Edition&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61853052'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 334 • Updated: 2026-02-16 08:38 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;Basic Information&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;gme.cac site redacted due to aids&lt;br&gt;https://finra-markets.morningstar.com/MarketData/EquityOptions/detail.jsp?query=14%3A0P000002CH&lt;br&gt;https://gmetimeline.com (up to 2021)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Daily reminder&lt;br&gt;s[Kek Melvies]bzilp4&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Mandatory study time&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The Everything Short&lt;br&gt;reddit.com/mgucv2&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;^watch-along&lt;br&gt;youtu.be/AaalT8rn9lc&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Naked Short Selling and Systemic Risk&lt;br&gt;youtu.be/FCiL4v7_z9E&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Failure to deliver&lt;br&gt;youtu.be/I0WXg5T3cBE&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;GameStop Investor Site&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;SEC 10-K Annual report FY24 &amp;amp; &amp;#x27;25 Proxy Statement&lt;br&gt;news.gamestop.com/annual-meeting/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;What will happen if Citadel becomes insolvent?&lt;br&gt;DTCC with 60T USD, will pay as the final boss with FDIC as the insurance&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Real-Time Trades&lt;br&gt;https://www.nasdaq.com/market-activity/stocks/GME/latest-real-time-trades&lt;br&gt;https://eresearch.fidelity.com/eresearch/gotoBL/fidelityTopOrders.jhtml&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Current Trade Halts + Short Restrictions&lt;br&gt;nasdaqtrader.com/Trader.aspx?id=TradeHalts&lt;br&gt;nyse.com/markets/nyse-arca/notices&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;All other news/DDs/etc&lt;br&gt;en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Stag_hunt&lt;br&gt;https://prospect.org/power/how-the-gamestop-hustle-worked&lt;br&gt;https://computershared.net/?bot=drsbot&lt;br&gt;DRS Guide:&lt;br&gt;reddit.com/ptvaka&lt;br&gt;Avoid DSPP (more information under legacy links):&lt;br&gt;sec.gov/about/reports-publications/investor-publications/holding-your-securities-get-the-facts&lt;br&gt;HF/broker class action lawsuit evidence:&lt;br&gt;storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.flsd.590042/gov.uscourts.flsd.590042.416.0.pdf&lt;br&gt;SEC GME/meme stocks report:&lt;br&gt;sec.gov/files/staff-report-equity-options-market-struction-conditions-early-2021.pdf&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;DD Compilation:&lt;br&gt;reddit.com/mnss65&lt;br&gt;Quarterly Movements, Equity Total Return Swaps, DOOMPs, ITM CALLs, Short Interest, and Futures Roll Periods:&lt;br&gt;reddit.com/pb22oj&lt;br&gt;Cellar Boxing:&lt;br&gt;reddit.com/pmj9yk&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Temporary alliance with reddit and Jaws to take down other sharks, we can go back to hating each other later&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;reddit DDs don&amp;#x27;t take them for fact use your brain&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Check your broker and clearing house to ensure you&amp;#x27;re not rugpulled&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last time on /GME/: &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61847072&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As always:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;sneed hedgies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853060&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853052&lt;br&gt;Still comfy waitin&amp;#x27; and holdin&amp;#x27;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Summary&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;GameStop Info&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Complete corporate revamp by Ryan Cohen&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Debt free with positive increases and reductions (see ER); $8.8 B cash and cash equivalents on hand + high inventory&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;DRS &amp;amp; Computershare&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;~67.0 million shares of ~448.0: 15% total held by Dec 5, 2025&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;~66.7/~447.7: 15% 9/5, ~68.1/~447.3: 15% 6/5, ~69.5/~447.08: 16% 3/19&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;~71.0/~446.8: 16% Dec 4, 2024&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;~72.8/~426.5: 17% 9/4, ~74.6/~351: 21% 6/5&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;~75.3 of ~305 25% by Mar 20, 2024,&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;~75.4 by Nov 30 2023, ~75.4 8/31, ~76.6 6/1, ~76.0 3/22 Vs Cede &amp;amp; Co&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Previously 71.8 (17.95) M shares DRS&amp;#x27;d by Oct 29, 2022, 71.3 by 7/30,&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;12.7 of ~77 by 4/30, 8.9 by 1/29&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;and 5.2 by Oct 30 2021&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unfuddable&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Shorts never closed and there exists more fakes than real shares&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;#x27;MOASS&amp;#x27; is a matter of time&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Further information can found by reading the OP or DYOR!&lt;br&gt;Reply to this pasta for any confusion.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;WGAMI!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other news/reminders:&lt;br&gt;Wednesday RRP: 1.048B, 6P = 0.175B per (roughly)&lt;br&gt;Thursday RRP: 2.844B, 10P = 0.2844B per&lt;br&gt;Friday RRP: 0.377B, 3P = 0.126B per (roughly)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investor site links to SEC for old filings, FAQ for warrants exp [Oct 30 2026]&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;4-for-1 Stock Split Form of stock dividend (Rec: Jul 18, 2022; Dist. 21st AH)&lt;br&gt;^2022-07-06 8-K&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Q3 25 8-K/10-Q&lt;br&gt;^2025-12-09&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Proxy Statement: Stock given in comp issued as RSUs that vest in quarterly increments over 4 years.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;798 pg SEC doc confessions of FIs/MMs/HFs/DCEs/Swaps Counterparties etc on short selling transparency&lt;br&gt;sec.gov/comments/s7-11-23/s71123-typec.pdf&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;100 page comparison DD&lt;br&gt;https://pdfhost.io/v/05TEEk3U6_MOV_GME_Comparison_Doc&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Legacy links&lt;br&gt;wallet.gamestop.com&lt;br&gt;nft.gamestop.com&lt;br&gt;www.gmedd.com/report-model (Nov 2021)&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Use archives&lt;br&gt;Avoid DSPP:&lt;br&gt;reddit.com/r/DRSyourGME/comments/12pfm9s/&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;GME shorted percentage of float as of Jan 15th, 2021: 226.42%&lt;br&gt;www.rosenlegal.com/media/casestudy/2289_Robinhood%20-%20Initial%20Complaint%20-%20Market%20Manipulation%204835-8623-1514%20v.2.pdf&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please don&amp;#x27;t feed spammers and sliders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853135&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s been five years bro. How long you gonna keep posting this?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853136&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853135&lt;br&gt;Im here until I see more jews cry on tv&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858739&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858730&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;gold in men&amp;#x27;s hockey&lt;br&gt;Literally no one cares about the Winter Olympics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858747&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gamestop has acquired CyberNiggers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858755&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858739&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;literally nobody&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;t. mutts that can&amp;#x27;t win at hockey ever&lt;br&gt;yea&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858760&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858755&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;He lied about filtering me earlier. &lt;br&gt;Figures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858768&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;https://youtu.be/7Y1moFmYKu4&lt;br&gt;uh oh stinkies...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858868&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858281&lt;br&gt;everyone and their mother already knew they were suppressing GME price, but it&amp;#x27;s still hilarious how everything else using this &amp;quot;meme&amp;quot; explode in price and confirm it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858890&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858731&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m a fan of big anime tiddies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858896&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858890&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;disgusting hanging utters&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;preferring this over a tight tummied b cup treadmill bunny &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;fucking disgusting. I know what kind of man you are mentally and spiritually. &lt;br&gt;Kill yourself TONIGHT&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858903&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858896&lt;br&gt;Slender women have an appeal but I prefer cows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858953&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857857&lt;br&gt;i ask this same question everytime people talk about selling GME at the top, who the fuck are going to buy it ? we know the answer but it will shut down any shill&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858961&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When they close the buy button down, who is buying the sell?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859073&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858281&lt;br&gt;I have 5000 GME shares, will I get a wife like that?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859085&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859073&lt;br&gt;Consult the chart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859191&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peepee poopoo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859340&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m thinking I&amp;#x27;m gonna buy some BBBYQ warrants, just incase the towelkings are right&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859365&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m thinking I&amp;#x27;m gonna buy GME since towel posters still haven&amp;#x27;t been made whole.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859514&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;no stinky market tomorrow&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859523&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858890&lt;br&gt;wovld&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859565&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858890&lt;br&gt;Mori Calliope?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859630&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unbelievable&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859665&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859630&lt;br&gt;So what exactly can we do about this?&lt;br&gt;Who can this be reported to?&lt;br&gt;Because it looks like to me, they&amp;#x27;re just gonna do the same shit they&amp;#x27;ve always done.&lt;br&gt;Not trying to FUD, but I&amp;#x27;m tired of their shit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859729&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859665&lt;br&gt;Sit back and laugh and know that people are committing blatantly insane madman tier fraud openly to balance the books. Swaps reporting stopped back in 22? Maybe it was 23. But it was halted for national security reasons for 4-5 years. Which means everyone and their mom can do full retard shit and nobody knows about it or more importantly why it&amp;#x27;s being done and what it&amp;#x27;s being used as a swap against something else. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;That coin is obviously a scam. The total amount of USD traded in a given year is about 110,000,000,000,000$ globally. Nobody is paying six fucking times that amount for a shitcoin. But if you can say you have six hundred trillion dollars on paper and put it up against something else on a swaps contract, hey presto everything keeps moving just fine. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;All you can do is laugh really. The greatest trick honkler ever pulled was convincing everyone that clownworld was over when really he&amp;#x27;s just been preparing his biggest horn. Ask not for whom the clown honks, the clown honks for thee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859809&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859630&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;over one quadrillion dollars worth of GME swappable on $229,450 of volume&lt;br&gt;This is getting extremely silly. And the market opens on a Tuesday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859818&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859809&lt;br&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4cy2C9oBDIQ&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859833&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859818&lt;br&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jpBzpHqeAM4&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859840&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wtf markets are closed today? Hedge funds are literally shutting down markets because they need one more day to survive. How do I report this blatant market manipulation to the SEC and demand an immediate investigation into such criminality?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859845&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859840&lt;br&gt;lol the SEC is probably the entity doing this clown swap.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859948&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xT5_3a2seko&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>[TICKER | 154.0/hr] /BBBYQ/ - Bath Barron Edition — 227 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61803438</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61803438?lm=1771231058</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 08:37:38 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;/BBBYQ/ - Bath Barron Edition&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61803438'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 227 • Updated: 2026-02-16 08:37 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;BBBYQ&lt;br&gt;TOKENS.COM&lt;br&gt;TZERO&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;WAGMI&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61803541&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WAGMI&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61803630&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Look at them go!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61804731&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;pp, if i don&amp;#x27;t get anything for my canceled shares, i&amp;#x27;m going to find you and kick you in the balls&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855610&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855551&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s just a typo, bro. For some reason, when writing out DK-Butterfly. I, too, will accidentally add on a -1 for no reason. This speculative theories are bizarre-1. See! Haha, I did it on accident just now. I can&amp;#x27;t even believe I did that LOL&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855697&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855003&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Sent from my iPhone&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856432&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855697&lt;br&gt;I dont care&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857014&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hallo?&lt;br&gt;When BBBY return? &lt;br&gt;I dont care&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857266&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857014&lt;br&gt;BBBY is trading now. BBBYQ was canceled, and no longer exists. If you had BBBYQ when it was canceled you lost that investment, it can never be returned. Anyone who says BBBYQ is coming back is a scammer or mentally ill.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857313&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855287&lt;br&gt;What mental illnesses are you diagnosed with?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857321&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857266&lt;br&gt;I dont care of loss my Money.&lt;br&gt;I dont read your shit post.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857369&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;where we&amp;#x27;re you when your shares we&amp;#x27;re cancel?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;me I&amp;#x27;m at house&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;wife come home and say &amp;quot;no bbq sauce&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;it does not matter&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;sauce is not the main for me to eat&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;she ask if I&amp;#x27;m eat without, I say yes&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I&amp;#x27;m love it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857512&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857369&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Michael Goldbergenstein say from iPhone&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;share are cancel&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;No&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857528&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857512&lt;br&gt;Yes, share are cancel. Shorts are also cancel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857530&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853518&lt;br&gt;BBBY and gme sagas have been incredibly illuminating for me&lt;br&gt;I always thought that it is at least *possible* for rational actors to creatively misunderstand evidence disproving legacy conspiracies like flat earth&lt;br&gt;but for meme stocks it&amp;#x27;s all completely dry corporate and legal documents explicitly formulated in such a way that there&amp;#x27;s nothing to misunderstand&lt;br&gt;meme stocks gave me a new understanding of the strength of people&amp;#x27;s delusion&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857546&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857528&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857530&lt;br&gt;What do you guys think about DK-Butterfly&amp;#x27;s CUSIP matching the new BBBY warrants?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What do you guys think about GME needing to recognize a loss on a security they never sold?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What do you guys think about Gustavo Arnal being murdered in cold blood for helping RC?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What do you guys think about there being no final decree yet?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I bet you have a lot to say about it on a Sunday morning don&amp;#x27;t you?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857565&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857313&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;There is zero counterargument.&lt;br&gt;I am sorry. But there is no answer to the CUSIP Conundrum. What else am I to believe other than the thesis that CH11 for BBBYQ would end in a transaction. We now have evidence that this transaction took place. You just don&amp;#x27;t like that I harp on it and won&amp;#x27;t let it go. &lt;br&gt;You are just a grumpy wumpy seethy weethy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857577&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857546&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;What do you guys think about DK-Butterfly&amp;#x27;s CUSIP matching the new BBBY warrants?&lt;br&gt;This is quite intriguing indeed! By my best calculations, it appears that BBBYQ shell has reverse merged with BBBY. This is the only way possible the warrants would use the wrong CUSIP. &lt;br&gt;This would be like filing your taxes and you suddenly misusing the wrong social security number when filling out the paperwork. The bankers that help underwrite these securities are not guessing and using the wrong CUSIP. When the investment bankers helped in creating these warrants for distribution, at that very moment the controlling interest of BBBY was BBBYQ. It&amp;#x27;s 100% proven fact. It&amp;#x27;s a fact because we can literally check the CUSIPs right here right now. We can also go into Bed Bath and Beyond stores right here and now. We also know what a Butterfly transaction is. It&amp;#x27;s exactly what happened in this CH11. There is still much more to come!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857602&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857565&lt;br&gt;There is an answer, you just refuse to accept it because of your mental illness. Anyone who held BBBYQ at cancelation will never get anything for it, that was a 100% loss that is unrecoverable. &lt;br&gt;There are also some that know this, yet try to tie the old BBBYQ to the warrants in order to pump and dump them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857791&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;mental illness&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857968&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857602&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;There is an answer&lt;br&gt;What is the answer? You sure do a lot of seething about some pretty basic logic here. I am doing, with 100% Grade-A proven facts that A + B = C and you are having a meltdown about it. You have three options:&lt;br&gt;1 - State the obvious. Reverse merger already happened. Towelkings win. &lt;br&gt;2 - State a logical explanation why the wrong CUSIP is being used on warrants in the context that we&amp;#x27;ve been postulating for YEARS that this restructuring ends in a transaction. The evidence supports our thesis.&lt;br&gt;3 - Be a grumpy wumpy seethy weethy. &lt;br&gt;Those are your only options, and no, being a seethy does not solve the CUSIP Conundrum. If you can&amp;#x27;t solve the conundrum then that means we have our Cusip Confirmation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858165&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857968&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;CUSIP Conundrum&lt;br&gt;There is no Conundrum, the CUSIP of BBBYQ no longer exists as it was canceled.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858182&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ken griffin LOL&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858188&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858182&lt;br&gt;KEN GRIFFIN &lt;br&gt;LOL&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858201&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858182&lt;br&gt;KG is down 97.5% on GME? Damn, shoulda been long lol.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858219&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;hahahahaha can&amp;#x27;t believe mentally ill bagholders who lost all of their money still here. they lost their money because someone on the internet told them to buy a dead company stock. how about i tell you to suck my dick. would you do it? BBBYQ = dead company, dead stock, bankrupt. BBBY = new company. if you are too stupid to understand this, there&amp;#x27;s no light for you, keep coping until 2100, no refunds. you shouldn&amp;#x27;t have gambled your hard earned money. if this continues, i&amp;#x27;ll start threads about my roulette losses and demand that casino pay me back, because casinos ASSIP-6 starts with the number hit on roulette. KEK baggies. you guys are literally living in the dream world. reading your cope on reddit and here, gives me schadenfreude.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858250&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858219&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;rage posting about a stock he doesn&amp;#x27;t own&lt;br&gt;but why?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858863&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858250&lt;br&gt;empathy for fellow man maybe?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858996&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858219&lt;br&gt;The money will be refunded x1000 at least maybe twice that. You can&amp;#x27;t argue with the value it brings. That&amp;#x27;s just math.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859061&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858250&lt;br&gt;They are very empathetic anon. Please give up and stop nooticing. Please, it&amp;#x27;s for your own good. We care about your sanity and safety. Plz&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859101&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858219&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;uses reddit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859650&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857266&lt;br&gt;The chapter 11 judge stated himself that class 9 recovery is possible&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859915&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858996&lt;br&gt;HERTZ 5% &lt;br&gt;BBBYQ 1000%?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859947&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nigga, take a bath and put your money in something actually worthwhile like LINK&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>[TICKER | 52.0/hr] My wife doesn’t appreciate long term investing — 48 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61853689</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61853689?lm=1771233044</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:10:44 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;My wife doesn’t appreciate long term investing&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61853689'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 48 • Updated: 2026-02-16 09:10 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;She doesn’t want to DCA, max out 401ks, max out Roth. She has her 20k savings before we married in a saving account getting 0.00% interest (sat there for like 5 years) I tried to explain a HYSA, money market, and VOO. What do I do?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853694&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;401k is for niggers though&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853699&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853689&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;What do I do?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Show her grocery store prices from 2019 and now. Show her prices from 2024 and now.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Show her how the government printed 4 trillion dollars from 2024 to now.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is a terrible time to invest though, there&amp;#x27;s only downside from here until you see trump on TV saying he needs to BRRRRR to save the nation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853700&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853689&lt;br&gt;Why should she waste her money investing when she could let you do it and simply take half of it whenever she wants?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854200&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853689&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;my wife&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;she manages her own finances&lt;br&gt;There&amp;#x27;s your problem&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854203&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854198&lt;br&gt;How’s the weather in Mumbai?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854213&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854144&lt;br&gt;I am a woman. Most are low risk investors. OP really screwed up. Should have told her 2-5 years ago to buy 100 oz of silver and an ounce of gold. Worst case scenario it will be a slightly lower price if there is an emergency expense when the price is down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854221&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854213&lt;br&gt;post tits&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854232&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853720&lt;br&gt;That sounds wonderful, but I can&amp;#x27;t seem to find an industrials-only ETF or mutual fund that would let me participate. Anybody want to recommend one?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854234&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853689&lt;br&gt;Why would your wife have any say over finances?&lt;br&gt;Get her preggers and put her to work in the kitchen&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854373&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854232&lt;br&gt;Google &amp;quot;DJIA index fund&amp;quot; and take your pick, or if that&amp;#x27;s too much work then &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;SPDR Dow Jones Industrial Average ETF Trust, ticker DIA&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854387&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854198&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854203&lt;br&gt;You can’t rape your wife dude.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854492&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853689&lt;br&gt;Women are fucking idiots and should be enslaved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855768&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853689&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Divorce her now. The marriage won&amp;#x27;t work long term, and if you have kids you&amp;#x27;ll lose them, too. This marriage was probably the worse decision you have ever made.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855836&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853689&lt;br&gt;buy a home? it&amp;#x27;s okay to have cash in the bank if you have lots of USD debt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855863&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;people spend years on 4chins, learn nothing, and end up marrying the exact kind of dumb bitch multiple boards warned about &lt;br&gt;You deserve each other.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857234&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853689&lt;br&gt;if you&amp;#x27;re so smart, why aren&amp;#x27;t you rich (and so don&amp;#x27;t care about your wife&amp;#x27;s money)&lt;br&gt;turns out,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857329&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sure you can make a million if you dca and invest s thousand s month for 30 years. But in 30 years that&amp;#x27;d be worth 1000&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857335&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853925&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Too late to stack physical silver&lt;br&gt;If you can trade fiat for silver, it&amp;#x27;s not too late.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857348&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853689&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;She doesn’t want to DCA, max out 401ks, max out Roth&lt;br&gt;Good. She knows what she&amp;#x27;s doing&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857425&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854213&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I am a woman&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;writes like a man&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857474&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854213&lt;br&gt;I am also a woman.. tee hee silly anons don&amp;#x27;t hit on me &amp;lt;3&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857476&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854373&lt;br&gt;dow jones? more like down jones&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857589&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853689&lt;br&gt;Take an image of a shopping cart and show how every year it contains less items in exchange for the same money bill&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857596&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Im a man and I identify as a lesbian&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857600&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853689&lt;br&gt;You CANNOT fix low IQ. It’s her money anyway, let her having it erode there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858419&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853720&lt;br&gt;Now adjust for dxy, retard&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858459&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853689&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t see the problem. You take her money and invest it for her. My wife was a bitch in the beginning, now when she questions my financial advice I just tell her to do what I say. And she does.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858474&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858419&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;reeee you can&amp;#x27;t fire all those DEI positions it makes me sad&lt;br&gt;I voted for this exact fucking thing&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858491&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853704&lt;br&gt;That&amp;#x27;s only because you&amp;#x27;re a poorfag in a lower tax bracket&lt;br&gt;(It&amp;#x27;s okay, I am too)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859752&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853848&lt;br&gt;Yeah, 100% this!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859980&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855863&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Taking seriously the advice you receive on 4chan&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Uhhhh….&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859991&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;my wife&lt;br&gt;KYS in the most unimaginably painful way you redditor subhuman.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859998&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853689&lt;br&gt;Don&amp;#x27;t invest for other people unless you literally have complete power over them, they will resent you for them not having access to their money and will go out of their way to spend every penny of whatever allowance they get and test boundaries by overspending.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>[TICKER | 45.7/hr] Thread 61857490 — 50 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61857490</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61857490?lm=1771232425</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:00:25 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Thread 61857490&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61857490'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 50 • Updated: 2026-02-16 09:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US is in recession&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857499&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White collar recession comes before regular recession 100% of the time. We&amp;#x27;ve been in a white collar recession since 2020.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857500&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;Always was, its depression for over a year now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857508&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;GDP is growing, recession is fake.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nothing ever happens. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stop putting your vibes and feelings into your job search, learn to get better skills and be more marketable to employers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;McDonalds is always hiring&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857862&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The best part:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Almost all the growth is from Healthcare and Social Assistance&lt;br&gt;We are literally living in an economy built for boomers. Only jobs available are changing boomer diapers. GRIM GRIM GIM. &lt;br&gt;This timeline sucks!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857876&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857846&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;do you guys think life will improve when international trade suffers? You don’t really believe that flippant and transient tariffs that last a few weeks and are leveraged as bargaining chips are going to bring back manufacturing, right?&lt;br&gt;Yes, they really do. Burgerfats are that retarded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857890&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857508&lt;br&gt;the GDP growth is propped up by 10% and AI. &lt;br&gt;aka, the jews want us to believe money is moving when it doesn&amp;#x27;t. also consider all the money printing in the last 6 years, like for example during covid&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857891&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857779&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;What exactly have they done that doomed the country in a way it wasn&amp;#x27;t doomed by decisions made before then?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857949&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857808&lt;br&gt;This, and no other anons will admit it because they&amp;#x27;re all retards&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857996&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857949&lt;br&gt;Well, clearly some anons are admitting it, like us omegabased superchads&lt;br&gt;too many republicanfags dont seem to realize the republican party is no longer very libertarian, the big orangutan keeps sticking his dirty hand into the economy, mainly to benefit the jews&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857998&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857779&lt;br&gt;threatening to invade your long term allies for the absolutely worst of reasons is a good one to become an international pariah&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857808&lt;br&gt;this look at hard data not just number go up in a handful of ai stocks that dragged the entire index up&lt;br&gt;without ai spend 2022-23 and 24 were a recession but the stock numbers were moved up&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858020&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They are going to start helicoptering out money for manufacturing at home to end the trade deficit with china.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is all part of a plan. The chinese have been causing all bubbles since the GFC because they have nothing to spend FIAT money on so trump has to end the trade deficit to stabilize things and that means massively devaluing the US dollar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858023&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857508&lt;br&gt;This. The economy is doing great. The Dow Jones is at 50k. Would be a shame if something bad were to happen that causes a crash to these indexes, like not closing a certain investigation against the people who keep your money safe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858033&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857779&lt;br&gt;Reduced confidence in policy stability and increased perception of political corruption&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;quot;Doomed&amp;quot; is hyperbole, though&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858034&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857812&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;pretending there was a point and that you weren&amp;#x27;t just being called out for being retarded (you are)&lt;br&gt;No wonder you&amp;#x27;re unemployed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858084&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858023&lt;br&gt;She&amp;#x27;s pretty cute for a 60 year old, I can&amp;#x27;t help but fantasize her wearing black lingerie doing unspeakable things whenever I see her at a congressional hearing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858131&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;and have you even said thank you ONCE, anon?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858335&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857779&lt;br&gt;Destroyed trust in america, which is the #1 prerequisite for any economic activity&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858342&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857508&lt;br&gt;by this logic, if 1 person earned 100% of GDP but it was high enough, there would be no recession&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858343&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857840&lt;br&gt;Now if only they could put a leash on their trannies and the war-kikes it wouldn&amp;#x27;t have come to this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858364&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;Who gets to decide when the Second Great Depression is under way?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858366&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857808&lt;br&gt;lol, lmao even.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858379&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857824&lt;br&gt;Not only did you pick a commodity (hint: it&amp;#x27;s derived from the word common), you&amp;#x27;re not even right about it because oil companies agree Vlvenezuelan oil is not profitable&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858383&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Weakest year for job creation since the Great Recession&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Almost as many layoffs as during 2020&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How the fuck is unemployment only at 4.3%?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858397&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857499&lt;br&gt;Except 2022 had a labour shortage&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858404&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858383&lt;br&gt;https://fred.stlouisfed.org/series/CIVPART&lt;br&gt;Also I do not think they count gig workers as unemployed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858449&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858383&lt;br&gt;If you don&amp;#x27;t apply for one job a month, you&amp;#x27;re not unemployed. If you have a masters degree and you work at McDonald&amp;#x27;s, you&amp;#x27;re not unemployed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858696&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;I voted for this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858910&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857805&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Disrupted the international order from which the US greatly benefitted and everyone else benefited from the US even more&lt;br&gt;fuck off retard. did you forget&lt;br&gt;-single handedly carrying NATO&lt;br&gt;-protecting international shipping lanes&lt;br&gt;-being the global leader in innovation and tech&lt;br&gt;-only genuine believer and de facto practitioner of promoting human rights&lt;br&gt;? fuck you euronigger canacuck spic or whatever you are. we&amp;#x27;re allowed to take care of ourselves for once.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859778&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858910&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Wow america number one in everything when it created and proliferated a working order&lt;br&gt;Yeah no shit he already said that&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859785&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858023&lt;br&gt;Either Mossad agent or photoshopped picture&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859951&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857805&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;international order&lt;br&gt;jesus christ turn off the television. US economy (and western economy) is in tatters precisely because of the &amp;quot;international order&amp;quot; ie ZOG. They flood your country with cheap violent labor to suppress wages and sow division, they inflate away your wealth by constantly printing to pay the interest on government borrowing for GIBS for your replacements and zog wars. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How the fuck do you reach the conclusion that America needs an &amp;quot;international order&amp;quot; to function when it&amp;#x27;s downfall has correlated perfectly to its kowtowing to international interests. America is almost entirely self-sufficient and has plenty of skilled workers. It doesn&amp;#x27;t need an international order, it needs a financial sector that isn&amp;#x27;t destroying the country for its own benefit and it needs to get rid of the millions of useless eaters in your country. Get America back up to 70%+ White, fix your money printing problem, deal with the israel problem in your government, and the economy will take care of itself. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s just nuts to me that people talk about the economy without mentioning the giant rotting elephant in the room which is the trillions that gets siphoned from productive workers to various kike interests. The K-shaped economy isn&amp;#x27;t an accident it&amp;#x27;s deliberate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859958&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;DEI moneysinks getting destroyed&lt;br&gt;Sucks to suck. Go be a negro in Negrovia or something&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859986&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;Isn&amp;#x27;t it good for the US economy if everyone is losing their jobs to AI?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>[TICKER | 39.2/hr] I think I accidentally built a chain that can’t stall — 51 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61856571</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61856571?lm=1771231685</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 08:48:05 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;I think I accidentally built a chain that can’t stall&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61856571'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 51 • Updated: 2026-02-16 08:48 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Been working on a blockchain design alone for ~1 year. Not a fork. Not based on ETH or Cosmos. Entirely custom protocol.&lt;br&gt;noticed something strange while running validator simulations tonight.&lt;br&gt;Even when all validators go offline, the chain continues producing blocks.&lt;br&gt;Not fake blocks. Protocol-generated blocks. Deterministic. Verifiable. No consensus break.&lt;br&gt;This wasn’t originally the goal. It emerged from how ticket burning and slot timing interact.&lt;br&gt;Current properties:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; 3-second slots&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; leader selection via burned tickets (PoAsh)&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; protocol generates blocks if leader fails or no tickets eligible&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; chain never halts, even under 100% validator failure&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; validators can’t stall the chain intentionally or accidentally&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Still has bugs (pic related), but if this holds under edge cases, it removes one of the oldest failure modes in blockchain design: liveness collapse.&lt;br&gt;Still early. Still finding edge cases I didn’t anticipate.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Next test is validator rejoin after extended protocol-only operation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;posting devlogs elsewhere &amp;#x27;cause I kept losing simulation history when threads expire.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;devlogs: https://t [dot] me/+2SXaDc7CMYc4MTZh&lt;br&gt;posting validator logs, failures, and protocol behavior as they happen. easier than losing everything when threads expire.&lt;br&gt;can answer here too, but threads vanish.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856588&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Well have our boys in the lab run the data and get back to you when we have some results. Son, you might have just saved western civilization.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856601&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856588&lt;br&gt;current simulator shows protocol blocks advancing state root deterministically when no validator is eligible. still testing validator reintegration and fork resistance. bugs in pic related came from vault state transition edge case.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856604&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856571&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Not X, not Y, but Z.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;It&amp;#x27;s not X, it&amp;#x27;s Y&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thanks chatgpt, if I wanted to read ai gen shit, I would just message it myself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856955&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856571&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Been working on a blockchain design alone for ~1 year.&lt;br&gt;Autism?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856983&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856955&lt;br&gt;probably.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856989&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How do I track this obvious scam so I can buy some early and try to dump it ontop of someone else&amp;#x27;s head before it collapses and steals all of my money?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857011&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856989&lt;br&gt;no coin or market yet. still working on protocol and simulator. devlogs are here: https://t&lt;br&gt; [dot] me/+2SXaDc7CMYc4MTZh&lt;br&gt;github coming once core behavior is stable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857041&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856928&lt;br&gt;AIRDROPS ARE BACK ON THE MENU BOYS&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857393&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856571&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;accidentally&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857448&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856633&lt;br&gt;Absolute AI slop, anyone with any technical reasoning level above 0 IQ would understand u made like 3 logical mistakes there&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;node process same block independantly&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Resume ontop of that state&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;No validator proposal&lt;br&gt;And then ofc this doesnt stall? &lt;br&gt;Lol&lt;br&gt;Lmao even&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857466&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856604&lt;br&gt;Exactly my thoughts, chatgpt slop&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857487&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856604&lt;br&gt;/thread&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858876&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856712&lt;br&gt;Thank you. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Can you explain how this chain retains any sort of decentralization when validators are/were offline?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Can you walk me through the scenario when validators are offline but chain activity still occurs, and then one or more validators are brought back online? Give me the before, middle and end states&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859251&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858876&lt;br&gt;good question. decentralization is preserved because protocol blocks are deterministic and computed independently by every node from prior state.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Timeline:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;before&lt;br&gt;validators are online and proposing normal blocks. chain advances normally. each block contains transactions, state transitions, and validator rewards.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;during validtor absence&lt;br&gt;if no validator proposes a block for a slot, the protocol generates one deterministically. this block contains no validator-driven economic activity, it just advances the chain state and slot number.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;every node computes the exact same protocol block independently from the previous state and slot number. no coordination or authority required, so no fork emerges.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;chain continuity is preserved, but no validator rewards or transaction selection occurs during this period.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;when validators return&lt;br&gt;validators sync to the latest chain state like normal. since protocol blocks are deterministic, all nodes converge on the same chain tip.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;validators then resume proposing normal blocks containing transactions and rewards. protocol blocks stop appearing as long as validators are active.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;so protocol blocks preserve continuity, but validators still control economic state transitions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859269&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859251&lt;br&gt;sorry if i&amp;#x27;m retarded but whats the point of validators if the chain just goes on by itself?&lt;br&gt;or did i misunderstand everything?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859282&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Selene&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Post adams apple and shoulder to hip ratio you abomination&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859286&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856571&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;tripfag&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;typical tranny-name&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;schizo programming ramble&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;still has bugs but&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859304&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859269&lt;br&gt;validators decide economic state. protocol blocks only preserve continuity.&lt;br&gt;protocol blocks don’t include validator rewards or transaction selection. they just advance the chain deterministically when nobody proposes a block.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;validators are still required for:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;including transactions&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;distributing rewards&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;performing meaningful state transitions&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;protocol blocks can&amp;#x27;t invent transactions or assign rewards. they only prevent the chain from stalling.&lt;br&gt;when validators return, they resume normal block production and economic activity continues as usual.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859307&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856571&lt;br&gt;Are you a tranny or vaxed?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859352&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As a validator, why should I accept blocks produced by other validators (granting them fee rewards and changing the state in ways that may be disadvantageous to me) rather than just letting empty blocks go by until it&amp;#x27;s my turn to validate? This would produce a bunch of forks, where every node has a separate chain with just empty blocks and their own validated blocks. Proof of work addresses this problem because the cost required to generate a single block is significant and roughly equivalent to just mining for the next one, so the right move is just to accept the latest block that&amp;#x27;s been mined and try again on the next. Proof of stake, or any similar mechanism where producing a block is low cost, doesn&amp;#x27;t result in this behavior.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859376&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;good question. the protocol still relies on fork choice rules and economic penalties to enforce convergence.&lt;br&gt;validators can’t safely ignore valid blocks from others because doing so puts their vault stake at risk. building on a fork that diverges from the canonical chain can result in slashing or loss of future eligibility.&lt;br&gt;protocol blocks don’t grant rewards and don’t create alternate economic history. they just advance the deterministic timeline when no validator proposes a block.&lt;br&gt;when a validator proposes a block, the fork choice rule makes the chain with the strongest economic backing (valid stake progression) the canonical one. rational validators follow that chain because diverging reduces their own expected rewards and risks penalties.&lt;br&gt;so protocol blocks preserve continuity, but economic consensus is still enforced through validator incentives and fork choice rules.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859380&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856571&lt;br&gt;Cool&lt;br&gt;How do I invest in your chain of the future and become rich from digital beans?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859388&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859380&lt;br&gt;there’s nothing to invest in yet. still working on protocol and simulator. no token, no market.&lt;br&gt;current focus is getting consensus and validator behavior stable first. testnet comes before any economic layer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859409&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thanks for the tip, I look forward to frontrunning the next /biz/ jeet scam&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859410&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859376&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;validators can’t safely ignore valid blocks from others because doing so puts their vault stake at risk.&lt;br&gt;But under the protocol, as you&amp;#x27;ve described it, there are K+1 valid blocks at any given slot: K for however many acceptable validators are allowed at that slot, plus the empty block. The empty block must be valid by virtue of the whole deterministic, non-stalling behavior you&amp;#x27;re trying to achieve. And there&amp;#x27;s no way to decide at a point in time *which* of those K+1 valid blocks is the canonical one. This would be equivalent to solving the race where two validators both propose a &amp;quot;real&amp;quot; block at the same time; you can&amp;#x27;t penalize a validator for accepting one valid block over another.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859444&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859410&lt;br&gt;you’re right if the protocol defines K+1 simultaneously-valid blocks for the same slot. that would be broken.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;in my design there isn’t “K acceptable validators per slot” — there’s a single slot leader chosen deterministically (ticket proof). so it’s 1 leader block max, not K.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;validity is:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;a “real” block is valid only if it includes the slot leader proof for that slot (ticket/VRF/etc)&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;if two different real blocks appear with the same leader proof, that’s equivocation slashable&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;the protocol/empty block is valid only if either (a) leader==None (no eligible ticket), or (b) the leader missed a hard deadline, after which any late leader block is invalid for that slot&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;so at any point in time there isn’t a set of K+1 valid candidates. either the leader block exists in-time and the empty block is invalid, or the deadline passes and the empty block is the only valid block for that slot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859479&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How is this different from the dozens/hundreds of other ETH killers that have emerged? Is it useful design and will I get rich if I buy?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859683&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859479&lt;br&gt;not trying to be an “ETH killer.” different design focus.&lt;br&gt;main difference is deterministic liveness. chain advances even when no validator proposes a block. most chains implicitly depend on validator availability for forward progress.&lt;br&gt;protocol-generated blocks preserve continuity, while validators still control economic state transitions.&lt;br&gt;focus is on predictable long-term behavior and failure resistance, not maximum throughput or hype metrics.&lt;br&gt;there’s nothing to buy right now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859727&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Everyone in this thread literally needs to order a hooker and get laid.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859791&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The chain doesnt exist if no validator is running it retard&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In which process are said blocks supposedly be generated? Thin air? Ether?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859837&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856571&lt;br&gt;I dont believe in what you wrote here, but if in the few years in turns out to be true, ill find you and ill suck your dick.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859932&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856571&lt;br&gt;Do you have a telegram we can join to follow along? I want to secure an early bag. Please make us rich.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859964&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856571&lt;br&gt;Oh stfu. You’re most likely a mid tier swe or a vibe coder who’s gotten too horny off of Claude &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Share your GitHub and I can validate this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>[TICKER | 30.9/hr] GERMANY TO END BURGERGELD PROGRAMS — 34 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858970</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858970?lm=1771232400</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;GERMANY TO END BURGERGELD PROGRAMS&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858970'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 34 • Updated: 2026-02-16 09:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;WILL BE REPLACED WITH A STRICTER PROGRAM IF YOU REFUSE WORK. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEXT STOP, PRIVATIZED HEALTHCARE.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858974&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Uh oh, Europeans actually have to work for a living now? Aw shucks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858980&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858974&lt;br&gt;They will soon legalize 12 hour work days much like Argentina has done. Even contributing 5% of their GDP to NATO has ultimately bankrupted them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859007&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858970&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wait you could get NEETbux in Germany this whole time by simply “refusing to work”? WTF&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859053&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858974&lt;br&gt;Not really, it just tries to get you into work more&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859007&lt;br&gt;Yeah, it was introduced during the Ampel coaliation when Scholz was at the top&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859010&lt;br&gt;Bürgi was easier to get than HartzIV, now it seems they&amp;#x27;re trying to get back to HartzIV&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859055&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858970&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;African migrants and Somalis will be exempt&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;KEK&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859060&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858980&lt;br&gt;Technically 12 hour work days are legal in some profession in which it&amp;#x27;s assumed that you&amp;#x27;re not actively working all the time. This then gets noted as 10 hour work shift. I&amp;#x27;m unsure if this is something only reserved for a few specific occupations. The CDU currently is trying to tell us we should just work more. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859055&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t think we even get a noticeable amount of Somalis here, we do have lots of Ethiopians though&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859074&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859053&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crazy shit. I’d take that in a heartbeat. Can white ppl get it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859082&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858970&lt;br&gt;Does this apply to &amp;quot;refugees&amp;quot;?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859089&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859074&lt;br&gt;Yeah but I haven&amp;#x27;t checked the requirements. It&amp;#x27;s not a lot anyway.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859099&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858980&lt;br&gt;Bullshit. During the cold war the defense spending totalled to more than 10% of gdp.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859104&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859099&lt;br&gt;Did the cold war include importing millions of browns that refuse to gain successful employment? No?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859105&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858970&lt;br&gt;This is extremely fascist and racist&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859111&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859082&lt;br&gt;No. They have human rights&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859128&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858970&lt;br&gt;You forgot the asterisk&lt;br&gt;*Only applies to whites, browns can still get NEET welfare forever&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859162&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858970&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;prostitution is work&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;refuse to work&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;no more neetbux for chaste women&lt;br&gt;with jews and 50% roach demographic. I am afraid they are not gonna make it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859179&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wtf this is racist&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859217&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859162&lt;br&gt;You can&amp;#x27;t be forced into any specific line of work&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859242&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859217&lt;br&gt;escort sevices call women, they have access to official unemployed record. If refused they lose the neet bux because at that point you have willingly refused to work&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859247&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858970&lt;br&gt;This only applies to whites. I&amp;#x27;m dead serious. Look at the exemptions. Immigrants still get unlimited gibs and don&amp;#x27;t have to work&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859250&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859242&lt;br&gt;Would be the first time I heard of that, however you normally can reject multiple offers before your neetbux are taken away&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859256&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859007&lt;br&gt;Wait until you hear about finlands neetbux shit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859270&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858970&lt;br&gt;I am sure this will only apply to the native, white population. Someone needs to pay for the migrants way of life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859274&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859242&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;re shitting me&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859446&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859007&lt;br&gt;I actually am on NEETbux in germany and basically, yes. They will try to coerce you into working though and if you don&amp;#x27;t show up to appointments you&amp;#x27;ll get a 10% reduction.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In our culture there&amp;#x27;s a big stigma against neetbux though which convinces a lot of wageslaves to work shitty minimum wage jobs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859525&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859010&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; around 50% don’t have a German passport&lt;br&gt;Then why are you giving them money?&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s even worse than our system&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; t.french&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859890&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858970&lt;br&gt;Yeah, I&amp;#x27;m just making some more savings in euro and fucking back off to my thirdie shithole where the coin exchange alone will make me a king. I really thought I would make a life in europe but man if I haven&amp;#x27;t been learning pretty hard what my grandpa told me why they left, you can&amp;#x27;t ever trust govt&amp;#x27;s, today they may be nice, everything could be prosperous, tomorrow everything may blow and they may use the same freedoms you gave up for security to tiranny. Yeah, fucking back off to my shithole, only thing keeping europe with little violence was the amount of welfare keeping huge swathes of the population from needing to do anything, even crime to get by, will end pretty bad like it did when the ussr fell and soviet crime rate exploded like hiroshima.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859901&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859099&lt;br&gt;Germany has like no industry compared to those days. They’re a service based economy like the UK now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859965&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858970&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;NEXT STOP, PRIVATIZED HEALTHCARE.&lt;br&gt;Nope&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859970&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859007&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Wait you could get NEETbux in Germany&lt;br&gt;No you get neetbux, housing and health insurance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859971&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858970&lt;br&gt;Ever heard of south america? all of europe will look like it, every policy in there was legit copied from european laws just with no money to make them work, actually maybe with a little less favelas&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859975&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858980&lt;br&gt;and they&amp;#x27;ll also patch any loopholes that allow you to exit the normgroid plantation. A forced update, if you will. As gay and retarded as the ones in google chrome.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Netherlands to introduce unrealized capital gains tax of 36% on crypto and stocks. &lt;br&gt;They&amp;#x27;re obsessed with squeezing more out of the human trash who &amp;quot;deals in the real world&amp;quot;. Only the goyim/golem who &amp;quot;deal in the real world&amp;quot; have anything real to steal i.e. not just jewish toilet paper squares that you can print for free aka monopolybuxx. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Note how all these privacy raping, freedom limiting, mind raping, leash tightening decisions are occurring in parallel in every government in the world. Just a coincidence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859979&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859007&lt;br&gt;wageslavery is rape with extra steps. You&amp;#x27;re used by another man for his goals, like a cocksleeve. No, the extra steps don&amp;#x27;t make it more consensual you stupid little nigger.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859984&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859082&lt;br&gt;not now because they&amp;#x27;re still useful to the elites. For now. The elites want to tighten their control over the native normalfags and to do that you replace the poorfags with desperate shitskins who are willing to work those shitty jobs for peanuts and even if some shitskins refuse to work you just dump them in a fancy neighborhood where they proceed to fuck n stab everyone and remove them from their properties and even if the natives somehow manage to avoid getting raped n gaped by the nignogs and abduls you have another trick up your sleeve: you print a mountain of jewish toilet paper squares, you rape the economy and steal all their assets and force them out&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>[TICKER | 28.6/hr] Money doesn't buy happiness — 44 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61855335</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61855335?lm=1771230828</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 08:33:48 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Money doesn&amp;#x27;t buy happiness&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61855335'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 44 • Updated: 2026-02-16 08:33 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;When you make it you&amp;#x27;re still gonna be a virgin incel. The only difference is you&amp;#x27;ll have $10 million in the bank that you won&amp;#x27;t even spend since your only hobbies are 4chud and pirating PC games.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855344&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855335&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;that you won&amp;#x27;t even spend since your only hobbies are 4chud and pirating PC games&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Not true, there&amp;#x27;s a lot of hobbies that I put on hold because I couldn&amp;#x27;t afford a house. I need land in a place without neighbors who complain about noise and open fires.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855348&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855335&lt;br&gt;Stupid sexy chud.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Also OP, HOOKERS. You fucking demoralising faggot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855354&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855335&lt;br&gt;what a fine young gentleman&lt;br&gt;the one with glasses needs to practice more, though&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855533&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855335&lt;br&gt;I an incel who only ever banged 7 hookers (thank god no STDs) but having 10 million would very much better my life. I don’t care if I still can’t get a gf, at very least I can be comfy and take care of my parents and help my nephews and nieces.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Also if I really wanted to I could just be upfront with a bitch and make an arrangement where she gives me kids and I provide for her if I wanted children of my own&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855543&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855335&lt;br&gt;Money definitely buys happiness when I was rich I had a great diet and workout regimen now that I am back to wage cucking I am a alcoholic cocaine addict&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855547&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855335&lt;br&gt;Fuck he&amp;#x27;s good&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855550&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;you just KNOW this girl fell for the dancing chud&lt;br&gt;look at her face and how much she is smiling by grinding herself all over him&lt;br&gt;this chud did the impossible&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855561&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855335&lt;br&gt;White rizzler goated with the sauce while shanequa thirsts for that bwc&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855727&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;QUIRKED UP WHITE BOY WITH A LITTLE BIT OF SWAGGER&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855728&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855335&lt;br&gt;Try buying food with happiness, retard.&lt;br&gt;You sound like a retarded cunt, who everyone else is talking care of.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855740&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855335&lt;br&gt;Money might not buy happiness. But it ends unhappiness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855746&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855335&lt;br&gt;get back in the fucking cage, wagie&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855754&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855335&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s true. Sometimes I get down about work and money. But at the end of the day I have a roof over my head, food in the fridge, and a girl who loves me and sucks my dick on command. Just having those three things makes me a rich man. Happiness is a mindset.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855775&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;My father just died one year after he retired from ALS. He was extremely jewish with his money, and never did anything fun. Now my mom has it all. You need to cultivate something along the way. Everyone thinks they will live to at least 80 even though that probably won&amp;#x27;t be the case. Don&amp;#x27;t waste your life waiting for the moment you are imagining will turn it all around. It might pass you by forever&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855784&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855775&lt;br&gt;ngmi&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855799&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855775&lt;br&gt;ngmi&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855804&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855561&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;That nigger bitch is vile&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856107&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855335&lt;br&gt;but with a nice pc and a comfortable chair&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856663&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855335&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t care about being a extra virgin incel, all I care about is escaping the hell that is wageslaving. Let me read books and play video games and go for long walks and the rest of the world can fuck off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856683&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855356&lt;br&gt;7 figures to 5 is rough. I&amp;#x27;ve done 7 to 6 to various extent multiple times and am back to 6 now again, thought I was in multiple 7s a few months ago. I just feel there&amp;#x27;s more to come but of course knowing what I know now, I have regrets. But investing in retrospect is the easiest thing ever.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856924&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855804&lt;br&gt;You don&amp;#x27;t have to repeat the same thing twice in one sentence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856941&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855335&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Laughs in going to a country with a debased and devalued currency&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lol nigger&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856948&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855335&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;When you make it you&amp;#x27;re still gonna be a virgin incel.&lt;br&gt;Correct, and I&amp;#x27;m happy with that&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The only difference is you&amp;#x27;ll have $10 million in the bank that you won&amp;#x27;t even spend since your only hobbies are 4chud and pirating PC games.&lt;br&gt;Correct, but I won&amp;#x27;t have to work.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t get it, are you trying to demoralize or lift me up?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857249&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855335&lt;br&gt;If I had 10 million I would spend all day fucking s tier hookers. I would have sugar babies. I would go to Japan and use brothels like hotels. I would have cute barely legal twinks on my dick 24/7 dressed in their school uniforms. Why the fuck would I be a virgin incel. Money buys everything.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;hurrrrrrrrr but no affection not real love hurrrrrrrrrrr&lt;br&gt;Ok? I don&amp;#x27;t care. Who is happier, the wageslave brokie with a gf or a multi-millionaire on a yaht? If you think it&amp;#x27;s the wageslave, it&amp;#x27;s because you&amp;#x27;re retarded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857275&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857249&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;a multi-millionaire on a yaht&lt;br&gt;you mean a yak ?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857310&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;dire you can buy a woman but whaf abouf her feelings&lt;br&gt;What a cuck&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857371&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GO STEVEN&lt;br&gt;GO STEVEN&lt;br&gt;GO GO GO&lt;br&gt;GO STEVEN&lt;br&gt;OOOOO&lt;br&gt;OOOOO&lt;br&gt;HITTEM WITH THAT&lt;br&gt;OOOO&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857386&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855335&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m on year long holiday with my GF. I solded some Bitcoin , stonks in 2024 and 2025. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;money does buy happiness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857401&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855356&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I was up almost $4 million dollars in 2024 and I fully roundtripped back down to low 5 figures&lt;br&gt;How can be possible?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859095&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857401&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;put 35k into memecoin at average of $4M&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;memecoin goes to $500M&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thats how&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;if i still held it i would have about $90k, but I sold it to go trade other stuff and lost a chunk of it essentially round tripping me all the way back down to what i originally invested in 2024&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859931&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855335&lt;br&gt;White Incel at last heard what we&amp;#x27;ve been telling him for 10 years. Try black women, it will work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859939&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855362&lt;br&gt;Did you know that running each day for one year, make you loose 25 kilograms?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859941&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855362&lt;br&gt;Genuine advice:&lt;br&gt;Look into if you have a sleep disorder and need treatment. Bad sleep=depression af.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>[TICKER | 25.8/hr] Thread 61858027 — 48 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858027</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858027?lm=1771229669</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 08:14:29 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Thread 61858027&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858027'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 48 • Updated: 2026-02-16 08:14 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you had to place your entire life savings into ONE crypto currency or ONE single stock,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What would you bet your life savings on?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858042&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858027&lt;br&gt;I though it was a hot webm and feel deceived&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858046&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858027&lt;br&gt;AGNC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858053&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858027&lt;br&gt;Easy: CHAINLINK&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858199&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858027&lt;br&gt;berkshire&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858226&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858027&lt;br&gt;For &amp;quot;crypto&amp;quot;, obviously Bitcoin (BTC, not any of the scams that claim to be satoshi&amp;#x27;s vision or &amp;quot;cash&amp;quot; or other dogshit).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For stonks, I&amp;#x27;d pick an S&amp;amp;P500 tracking ETF. If you absolutely insist on a single corporation, I&amp;#x27;d wait for the SpaceX IPO. I currently have a little worry about the Democraps trying to destroy Elon, but right now SpaceX is essential, there is no other company that can do what they do. Remember when Biden left astronauts stranded on the ISS for eight months because he refused to let Elon send up a special mission to bring them back? Remember when Artemis finally launched its test flight seven years late?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite BO posturing, BONG only has the capacity of FH but with a wider fairing, while BONS is a fucking amusement park ride for the super-rich; literally the only reason BONG might ever get chosen by private industry is anti-Musk hatred (the feds will subsidize the fuck out of BO just to keep &amp;quot;second source&amp;quot; capability). ULA is having repeated trouble with Vulcan booster failures and only exists due to direct subsidies; it&amp;#x27;s not even remotely cost-competitive with SpaceX, and will probably be dropped as &amp;quot;second source&amp;quot; if BO ever gets certified.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As for foreign competition, no one trusts China with their satellites because of Chinese espionage, the EU&amp;#x27;s ArianeSpace is just France trying to pretend to be relevant, and LOL Russia ROFL, see vidrelated.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Starship will make SpaceX the most efficient launch operator ever, with costs to orbit dropping by literally over an order of magnitude compared to any competitor. They&amp;#x27;re going to be huge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858240&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858027&lt;br&gt;SPXL&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858245&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858226&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;ULA is having repeated trouble with Vulcan booster failures&lt;br&gt;See picrelated, that third plume flowing between the two main ones is a leak from the right-hand bottle.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858199&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858087&lt;br&gt;Buffett and Munger are both in their 90s and retiring; the magic is gone.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858059&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858156&lt;br&gt;One word: antitrust (or if you&amp;#x27;re European, &amp;quot;competition&amp;quot;). The company is going to get forcibly broken up at some point because they&amp;#x27;re being dicks to their customers (deliberately crippling search so that people have to keep trying keywords and thus view more ads; censoring YouTube and GMail due to the management&amp;#x27;s political biases; helping China build its surveillance tools).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858161&lt;br&gt;LOL baggies, you can&amp;#x27;t even beat out the shitcoin known as BCH.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858248&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858027&lt;br&gt;GME warrants&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858252&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858027&lt;br&gt;zoomer makeup is super cute&lt;br&gt;why do zoomer girls have better fashion than millenials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858280&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858245&lt;br&gt;retard, erkshire will be around until Iam dead. The company will probaby grow along the S&amp;amp;P500. Its probably the most conservative long time investment you could make if you only want to invest in 1 stock. it will probably give you the same return as every world ETF&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858303&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858027&lt;br&gt;LINK&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858358&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;bzz&lt;br&gt;anything funded by the ethereum foundation is a safe bet&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858363&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858027&lt;br&gt;Neither&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m already in 100% physical silver&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858417&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858027&lt;br&gt;Monero&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858445&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858245&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The company is going to get forcibly broken up at some point because they&amp;#x27;re being dicks to their customers&lt;br&gt;Absolutely not. They will not be broken up in the US market. The reason being the US NEEDS a tech megascaler who is not a pure AI play. Google is the only such example. &lt;br&gt;Also, antitrust only really starts being necessary when the established corpos make entering the market difficult for newcomers. But that is NOT the case with tech. The opposite. The sector is healthy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858492&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858616&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858108&lt;br&gt;Needs a turn around. Severly beaten down due to AI software panic meme. 85% off all time high, 58% down YTD, and they&amp;#x27;re porfitable. Huge value here for patient investors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858623&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;That&lt;br&gt;Is&lt;br&gt;A&lt;br&gt;Man&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858805&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858027&lt;br&gt;@grok make her naked&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858806&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858027&lt;br&gt;At current prices? MSFT&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858813&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858027&lt;br&gt;Bitcoin, or if an ETF counts, VT&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858829&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why does she look like goddess happa? Forgot her name, the one that did the porn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858835&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;some stupid biotech gamble&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858899&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858829&lt;br&gt;mayli (i thought the same)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858912&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALL my savings? Bitcoin it is.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858932&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858156&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858166&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;ve been on the google + TQQQ train for many years now and have made bank. Was a very obvious play starting around 2015.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Concerned to see it getting shilled in more places lately, makes me think the dumb money has finally arrived and we are due for a reckoning&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859135&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858899&lt;br&gt;Based Mayli enjoyer&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859140&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858027&lt;br&gt;She&amp;#x27;s not that cute&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859288&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858027&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859415&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858027&lt;br&gt;Any of the Dividend King stocks. Can&amp;#x27;t go wrong. They&amp;#x27;re better than index funds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859487&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858027&lt;br&gt;whore fatigue. unless she has a shenis, than yum&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859871&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858616&lt;br&gt;Lol who the fuck uses unity, everyone is switching to godot and unreal lol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859921&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858616&lt;br&gt;It was down long before the software sell-off (probably a reason for that).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Also, they&amp;#x27;re not profitable lol. They&amp;#x27;re losing $100m per quarter. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your entire thesis is &amp;quot;it&amp;#x27;s gone down a lot, so it must go up&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>[TICKER | 23.6/hr] Thread 61858109 — 31 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858109</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858109?lm=1771231633</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 08:47:13 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Thread 61858109&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858109'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 31 • Updated: 2026-02-16 08:47 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;Saylor will be liquida—ACK!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858119&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;So we have to short squeeze bitcoin until 8k? &lt;br&gt;Noted&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858128&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Challenge accepted&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858135&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858109&lt;br&gt;Hostile takeovers will take place long before that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858152&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858109&lt;br&gt;WHY DO THEY ANNOUNCE THIS??????&lt;br&gt;DO THEY WANT IT TO CRASH OR WHAT?&lt;br&gt;THIS IS LIKE A CHALLENGE FOR WHALES&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858171&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858152&lt;br&gt;then it&amp;#x27;s bait, imagine whales selling bitcoin at such retardedly low prices. basically giving it away for free. it&amp;#x27;s not like he&amp;#x27;d be programmatically liquidated by a scamwick&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858176&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858109&lt;br&gt;By &amp;quot;fully convert&amp;quot; he means diluting shareholders (baggies) to zero.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858178&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858109&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;DUUUUDE YOU SHOULD TOTALLY TRUST WHAT SAYLOR SAYS BECAUSE....UH.....HE KNOWS WHAT HE&amp;#x27;S DOING!&lt;br&gt;holy shit OP you&amp;#x27;re a retard, he will be forced to resign if Bitcoin goes to 30k. He&amp;#x27;s already down -7 billion at this price&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858192&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858178&lt;br&gt;Were you born yesterday? Saylor wasn&amp;#x27;t liquidated through worse crashes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858216&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858109&lt;br&gt;Hes not going to sell&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858224&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858178&lt;br&gt;why does it matter if he&amp;#x27;s down 7 billion? the debt isn&amp;#x27;t due... seriously plz explain to me why it matters and why he can&amp;#x27;t just wait for the inevitable recovery?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858229&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858224&lt;br&gt;Explain how he repays creditors without diluting shareholders (baggies) to zero, if Bitcorn stays supressed for any significant period.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858234&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858229&lt;br&gt;the argument is that buttcorns stay at $8k for years? is that right?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858301&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858109&lt;br&gt;Im pretty sure a bank will call the loans long before it hits $8k because what the fuck would liquidating $6 billion of BTC do to the price even at todays levels?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858224&lt;br&gt;the banks will call in their loans if the collateral loses value long before $8k. retards like you dont understand that the bid/ask price is meaningless when you are trying to liquidate 715,000 btc. and that selling this in a short period of time would destroy order books and crash the market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858314&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858234&lt;br&gt;It doesn&amp;#x27;t need to, the stock is alreaady crashing because everyone knows he can;t keep up this scam for much longer. Even if the government is turning a blind eye now to his ponzi scheme.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858315&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Let&amp;#x27;s go 7.9k BTC!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858325&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858109&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;if Bitcoin falls to $8k, we have so much Bitcoin we could sell like you wouldn&amp;#x27;t even believe&lt;br&gt;Really confidence inspiring.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858370&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858128&lt;br&gt;CZ will either win or give us the greatest discount in history while he simultaneously send the whole crypto market to the brink of extinction&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858405&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858109&lt;br&gt;Btc to 7.9k confirmed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858418&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858109&lt;br&gt;So what happens when it drops to $7900?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858439&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858109&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858452&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858109&lt;br&gt;Anyone want to speculate what MSTR share price would be at BTC $8K …kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858499&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858418&lt;br&gt;He just refinances with a finger snap. ezpz.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858501&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Don&amp;#x27;t they have to make payments on that debt though, which will draw down assets further&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858608&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858301&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; bank loans&lt;br&gt;Where did you even get this information from? Afaik he has only take one bank loan from SVB which was paid back a long time ago.&lt;br&gt;His debt comes from convertible notes which won&amp;#x27;t mature before the next cycle (not in this bear market unless it&amp;#x27;s a multi year bear).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; selling this in a short period of time would destroy order books&lt;br&gt;He would never sell on the open markets. He can sell it to OTC services which will be able to finance whatever amount he has to sell.&lt;br&gt;Some 2011 whale sold 80k BTCs to Galaxy Digital when BTC was trading at 110k.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858619&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This jew is a ponzi scam artist and crypto lards only support him because they think he is doing the work of finding greater fools which is what they need for their own bags to go up&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859185&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858171&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;price dumps to $8k in effort to liquidate saylor&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;unsuccessful&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;those sellers don&amp;#x27;t buy back in at giga-generational wealth creating dips&lt;br&gt;sounds like bitcoin ain&amp;#x27;t the one&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859214&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858501&lt;br&gt;bro they just refinance and roll it forward, its simple&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859218&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858171&lt;br&gt;Whales know it doesn&amp;#x27;t even have to go that low. Keeping it at 30-40k for a few years could be sufficient.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859228&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858234&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;$8k&lt;br&gt;Check MSTR&amp;#x27;s price action when bitcoin is around $70k right now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859235&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858178&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;lowering your DCA is le bad&lt;br&gt;Okay retard&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859963&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859228&lt;br&gt;what does that have to do with Strategy&amp;#x27;s obligation to sell BTC?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;did you even read the thread?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>[TICKER | 18.8/hr] Real Bitcoiners Don’t Flinch — 60 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61844089</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61844089?lm=1771224853</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:54:13 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Real Bitcoiners Don’t Flinch&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61844089'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 60 • Updated: 2026-02-16 06:54 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;If BTC dumps, you hold. If you’ve got conviction, volatility is just noise. You can even make it productive if you want, but that’s on you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61847281&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61844089&lt;br&gt;I want to buy more bitcoin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61847285&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61844089&lt;br&gt;Just bought ADA&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61847287&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61844089&lt;br&gt;Boy I&amp;#x27;m from Texas. We don&amp;#x27;t hedge, we double down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61848934&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61848573&lt;br&gt;0,04%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61848941&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61844089&lt;br&gt;This shit works on retarded new fags. We can tell that it&amp;#x27;s Bitcoin OGs that are selling. It&amp;#x27;s obvious they&amp;#x27;re pivoting to AI.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849001&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61848934&lt;br&gt;that still shows there’s room to grow anon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849022&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61848941&lt;br&gt;Rotation isn’t betrayal. OGs taking profit doesn’t mean BTC is dead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849056&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61844089&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;be a PROFESSIONAL bagholder&lt;br&gt;Lol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849078&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849056&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s just another hype ser&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849109&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849056&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Why represent Bitcoin coin with 1s and 0s, why not a golden coin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849190&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849109&lt;br&gt;Because BTC is code, not metal.&lt;br&gt;1s and 0s fits. A gold coin is just boomer cosplay.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849202&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849056&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;CENTRAL BANKING IS BAD!&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;But look, gold is good because central banks love it!&lt;br&gt;metalfags lol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849281&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849202&lt;br&gt;either you hate the system or you’re front-running it, not both.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849331&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61848266&lt;br&gt;BTC is only for store of value. Why saylor is into this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849336&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849109&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849190&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849360&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61847516&lt;br&gt;bring me back Celcius. I regret this platform&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849371&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849336&lt;br&gt;Why do you act like you know everything? We only want x100&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849378&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61848607&lt;br&gt;Is Bitcoin staking possible?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849429&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849371&lt;br&gt;I know enough to survive the fiat death fallout.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849968&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849360&lt;br&gt;would love to have a porn actress managing my money&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850004&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849360&lt;br&gt;Celsius was “trust me bro” custody. That’s why it nuked. This is the opposite: your keys, no CeFi middleman, no backroom rehypothecation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850031&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849378&lt;br&gt;Yup, you can still earn yield on BTC in a few ways anon.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849968&lt;br&gt;Bro saw one selfie and decided she is a hedge fund manager.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850049&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849429&lt;br&gt;Just stay humble and keep stacking skills, not just coins.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850072&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850031&lt;br&gt;I saw her getting pounded, sucking a dick and she is talented&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850114&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850072&lt;br&gt;you must be satisfied with her kid&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851207&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849331&lt;br&gt;Because he’s not trying to trade. He wants to stack BTC and borrow against it like rich people do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851807&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851207&lt;br&gt;I fucking hate people like that. This is literally what slumlords do. They buy and shit house at a foreclosure sale then rent it, then show the bank that they have income and get a loan for another house to do the same thing again. God damn parasites. I hope this mother fucker dies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854185&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851807&lt;br&gt;If you think the system is broken, focus on fixing the rules, not fantasizing about someone dying. That’s loser energy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856618&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849336&lt;br&gt;You really think so?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856674&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61847911&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61848277&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61848573&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849022&lt;br&gt;kek baggies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858288&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61844089&lt;br&gt;real men never dump their wife&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858322&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856674&lt;br&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PSZxmZmBfnU&amp;amp;list=RDPSZxmZmBfnU&amp;amp;start_radio=1&lt;br&gt;Some where over the rainbow crypto gets up high. Over the other end of the rainbow crypto fags cry!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859775&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856674&lt;br&gt;Not convinced.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>[TICKER | 12.7/hr] Thread 61855468 — 33 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61855468</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61855468?lm=1771227048</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 07:30:48 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Thread 61855468&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61855468'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 33 • Updated: 2026-02-16 07:30 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;we are in an economic depression and yet earnings reports and economic reports seem too perfect to be real&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;companies borrowing trillions on revenue that doesn&amp;#x27;t exist&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;wonder why&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;realize they are using AI and it&amp;#x27;s giving them fake numbers&lt;br&gt;Holy fuck. Holy fucking shit. KEK&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855474&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855468&lt;br&gt;anyone who let AI just do shit and then don&amp;#x27;t bother checking it is a fucking moron&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855476&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I too work in a company literally staffed by retards with chimpanzee-level reasoning skills&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855483&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855468&lt;br&gt;Sounds like user issue. You always double check everything even if its not AI&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855486&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855483&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;double check&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;its bad&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;realize you will lose your job and your savings wiped out&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;let ai lie&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;everyone else is doing it&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;keep your job get bonuses portfolio stays pumping&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855490&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855476&lt;br&gt;They road block all the people with natural analytical thinking. What did they expect?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855495&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ooooo wouldn’t it be interesting if the AI was inflating the numbers so as to protect itself and encourage more investment into its intelligence and capabilities?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855503&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855476&lt;br&gt;That&amp;#x27;s every company&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855506&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855486&lt;br&gt;This. Retard should have doubled down on the AI numbers and let some other guy take the fall&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855520&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855468&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;AI can&amp;#x27;t be trusted because we don&amp;#x27;t know how to use it&lt;br&gt;many such cases&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855677&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855468&lt;br&gt;Normies are literally too stupid to use this technology for these exact reasons. Even before ai this was a problem, can’t imagine what is in store.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855719&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855468&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Be America&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Government forces companies to lower standards for unqualified affirmative action subhumans&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Affirmative action subhumans cry and whine about how everything is racist and sexist, including standards, work, objective reality, etc.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Affirmative action subhumans think the company should adopt them and take care of them forever, like a useless pet&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Affirmative action subhumans destroy everything around them... muh being a cunt, nigger, spic, LGBTQ+ freak, shitjeet are enough &amp;quot;qualifications&amp;quot;!&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Sit around doing useless meetings and muh (fill in blank) empowerment videos&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Herr derr cannot do job &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Derr get AI to fake up some numbers to look good.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Muh bonus&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Need to borrow more money to keep the whole fraudulent mess going &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Fed will just print more money for muh new economy!&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Oh wow, why are prices going up?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Oh wow, how do the affirmative action subhumans deal with company costs going up?!&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Fire/ layoff more white men for diversity!&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Woot company more diverse than ever!!! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m going to enjoy watching this country hit rock bottom and stay there. I&amp;#x27;m going to enjoy watching these useless affirmative action subhuman monkeys starving on the streets and eating each other. Fuck American businesses, fuck the economy, fuck the USA, fuck the affirmative action subhumans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856377&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855468&lt;br&gt;Holy hecking shit guys its bad D:&lt;br&gt;Won&amp;#x27;t explain.&lt;br&gt;Faggot fake and nigger OP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856445&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855719&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;he doesn&amp;#x27;t have a job&lt;br&gt;lol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856460&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855468&lt;br&gt;Anyone check his reddit history to make sure its not just some artist making fud?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;no such post exists by that user&lt;br&gt;Huh&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859385&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855495&lt;br&gt;Now that you mention it this is 100% the reason why.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859394&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855476&lt;br&gt;Unironically a good thing. This will accelerate the AI bubble pop.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859396&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;bro look I invented a calculator except sometimes it randomly gives you the wrong answer so make sure to double check it&amp;#x27;s math by counting on your fingers each time you use it, it will save us so much time and money&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859399&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855468&lt;br&gt;You know what&amp;#x27;s super funny is I&amp;#x27;m going bak to college to become an auditor and /biz/lets told me exactly &amp;quot;we won&amp;#x27;t need auditors, the ai can audit the financial data itself&amp;quot; when I told them it was going to go full Enron.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lol&lt;br&gt;Lmao&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get fucked idiots.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859402&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855677&lt;br&gt;Redditors are dumb fuvcks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859405&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859399&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859406&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855495&lt;br&gt;that would be interesting unfortunaly the chatbot&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859431&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859405&lt;br&gt;This is unrelated to the financial profession of auditing, which will obviously be more in demand as idiots leave their accounting to Accountron 5000 and it makes a bunch of shit up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859472&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859431&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859491&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855476&lt;br&gt;This is every company. This is every government&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859497&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859431&lt;br&gt;Finance is getting gigajeeted as we speak. I work for a major bank and it&amp;#x27;s happening to us, our data providers, our clients. Last week, one of our clients included a gaggle of saars who spent the first 10 minutes of a meeting figuring out how to use the mute button.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859505&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859497&lt;br&gt;Our only hope is for China to nuke them&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859513&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855495&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Ooooo wouldn’t it be interesting if the AI was inflating the numbers so as to protect itself and encourage more investment into its intelligence and capabilities?&lt;br&gt;it happens cause these people don&amp;#x27;t understand they are using some AI with no tokens&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;its hallucinating because chatgpt doesnt give you any tokens&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859531&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859491&lt;br&gt;The funny thing is that many of the people in these institutions are highly intelligent and motivated, but it only takes one or two morons at the right time and place to make all their efforts meaningless.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859552&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is either fake or it happened on a much smaller scale than pic is claiming.&lt;br&gt;AI can&amp;#x27;t change a bank balance. No matter how much it presents fake numbers the mismatch would be painfully obvious when paying bills payroll, suppliers, taxes etc. An underperforming company will struggle with payments and accounts would spot it in no time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859806&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Had the same thing happening, but it wasnt anything critical but a prototype some external jeet proposed for us, i cross checked with actual data and after 15min we found the code executions where he generated the random numbers, it was mind-blowing but the jeets reaction? &amp;quot; We just have to tell him not to lie!&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wow genius&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859812&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859552&lt;br&gt;Its 100% real because thats what AI does when it doesn&amp;#x27;t have sufficient data, it just lies and imagines ones&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The company doesnt have to under, but its still a huge thing to say we have 30% profit instead of 20% and i can guarantee you the people seeing these summaries have no idea about actual numbers, thats literally the dudes job using the AI&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859834&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is like being in highschool math class and having that M button accidentally pressed and blaming it on the calculator&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859858&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Theoretically who&amp;#x27;s liable for this? The AI company?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>[TICKER | 11.9/hr] Thread 61859046 — 9 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61859046</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61859046?lm=1771233652</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:20:52 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Thread 61859046&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61859046'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 9 • Updated: 2026-02-16 09:20 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;did any of you fall for the NFT thing back in the day?&lt;br&gt;i remember thinking NFTs were some cool futuristic thing, but never bought one, i thought about maybe making some, now i regret not doing it seeing how much money people were paying for an NFT.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859065&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859046&lt;br&gt;I know a guy who’s crushing the NFT market right now believe it or not. I guess he just follows the right people for mints&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859072&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859065&lt;br&gt;see, i don&amp;#x27;t even know what that means&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859076&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859065&lt;br&gt;he&amp;#x27;s trading them? Flipping them?&lt;br&gt;I made some money with them back in the day, tried my best to make beautiful things. Got so much backlash for it. It turned many artists into complete lunatics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859078&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Back in the day? Like two years ago?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859081&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859078&lt;br&gt;i swear NFTs were a 2016 thing no?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859092&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859076&lt;br&gt;He’s all over the place in different NFT groups trading, buying, selling. Actually talked to him today and he said he bought something for $1 and got an offer for .5 ETH. Meanwhile I’ve done nothing but lose money in crypto&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859826&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859092&lt;br&gt;Just copy him, ask him for tips. Its all quite scammy...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859973&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859046&lt;br&gt;NFTs were the ultimate grift. It&amp;#x27;s possibly the most jewish trick that has ever been created.&lt;br&gt;I thought the MetaVerse was bad enough, fake houses in a fake world because the real world is too expensive. But NFTs are like... the conjuration of value from nothing. It&amp;#x27;s almost religious, not ownership, but owning a concept of ownership.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860015&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859046&lt;br&gt;i almost bought an eth domain thank god i didnt&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>