<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>/biz/ Active Threads</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/</link><description>Active threads with replies</description><item><title>/pmg/ - Precious Metals General — 289 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61855017</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61855017</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 21:37:29 +0000</pubDate><description>Open article for full content</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;/pmg/ - Precious Metals General&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61855017'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 289&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;Why precious metals?&lt;br&gt;https://youtu.be/i3S4rl6ehiI &lt;br&gt;https://youtu.be/gksenA5Al_A &lt;br&gt;https://youtu.be/FI7NnOg2rxo &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Huge deficits in minerals such as silver by 2050 inevitable&lt;br&gt;https://youtu.be/iibsrDXdEos [Embed]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Bullion dealers&lt;br&gt;https://libertycoin.com/ (US)&lt;br&gt;https://www.chards.co.uk/ (EU/UK)&lt;br&gt;https://www.silburycoins.co.uk/ (Ancient)&lt;br&gt;https://www.luciteria.com/ (Other rare metals)&lt;br&gt;https://www.ma-shops.com/ (Numismatics)&lt;br&gt;https://www.goldeneaglecoin.com/ (US)&lt;br&gt;https://stoutgold.co/ (US)&lt;br&gt;https://www.aydincoins.com/ (US)&lt;br&gt;https://prospectorsgoldandgems.com/ (US)&lt;br&gt;more at:https://pastebin.com/gZfZHtNE&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Numismatic search&lt;br&gt;https://en.numista.com/catalogue&lt;br&gt;https://www.ngccoin.com/price-guide/world&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;News and graphs&lt;br&gt;https://numismag.com/en/home-en&lt;br&gt;https://silverseek.com&lt;br&gt;https://www.silverdoctors.com&lt;br&gt;https://www.mining.com&lt;br&gt;https://silverbacksnakes.io/finance/silver&lt;br&gt;https://www.gold.org/goldhub/data/gold-reserves-by-country&lt;br&gt;https://wtfhappenedin1971.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Compare&lt;br&gt;https://findbullionprices.com (US)&lt;br&gt;https://eu.compare.pm (EU)&lt;br&gt;https://www.gold.de/aufgeldtabelle (DE/EU)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Resources&lt;br&gt;https://www.jmbullion.com/ultimate-guide-to-90-silver-coins&lt;br&gt;https://kevinsworkbench.com/junksilverguide&lt;br&gt;https://www.coinflation.com&lt;br&gt;http://coinapps.com&lt;br&gt;https://erikasgrig.com/calculators/rpi-calculator-inflation&lt;br&gt;https://learn.apmex.com/buying-guide/buying-in-the-usa&lt;br&gt;https://pastebin.com/5aLmWUUK&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Prospecting&lt;br&gt;https://youtu.be/ZCL6FKQZyoM &lt;br&gt;https://www.usgs.gov/programs/mineral-resources-program/science&lt;br&gt;https://www.mndm.gov.on.ca/en/news/mines-and-minerals&lt;br&gt;https://www.amazon.ca/Gold-Creeks-Ghostowns-British-Columbia/dp/088839988X&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Nitric acid, magnets, and ping test&lt;br&gt;https://youtu.be/3mg9YcAShTo &lt;br&gt;https://youtu.be/NgSXg-WOEVY &lt;br&gt;https://youtu.be/2ymGAyKAg-k &lt;br&gt;https://www.fakebullion.com/index.php/resources/fake-bullion-database&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Silver Hallmarks Encyclopedia&lt;br&gt;https://www.925-1000.com/&lt;br&gt;https://www.silvercollection.it/hallmarks.html&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Previous thread: &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61852374&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856973&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;lmao&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856954&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856936&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856949&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856918&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Frito lays just cut the price of potato chips so yes silver will drop 90%&lt;br&gt;They cut the price of snack foods because RFK jr stopped allowing EBT (welfare) money to be spent on junk food. These multinational nigger&amp;#x27;s goyslop was being subsidized by US taxpayers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856944&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856271&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s exactly why they thought the dollar was collapsing, massive oil price spikes causing inflation. The USSR was at its peak in 1980, chernobyl wouldn&amp;#x27;t happen for 6 more years and the USSR didn&amp;#x27;t collapse until 91. From their perspective the soviets were the future, the setup is the exact same.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The only thing that I think is different this time is the introduction of AI which stands to make millions of jobs irrelevant, although in 1980 computers were doing the same to traditional office jobs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856942&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856626&lt;br&gt;Good video. Thanks for posting it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856937&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856922&lt;br&gt;The worse maximum out come i see happening is we crash for maybe 23 year max, with a 1-2month low of 5-6, and it goes parabolic back to $80 in 2074, assuming the feds bailout the comex or the comex somehow magically gets more silver for delivery for March/April&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856936&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856901&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856737&lt;br&gt;Thanks for the suggestions. &lt;br&gt;I think we got it a little further down.&lt;br&gt;It helps if you compare wrinkles, eye lids, and mouth area. Also consider it was made in 2023&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I didn&amp;#x27;t keep up much with new Epstein stuff.&lt;br&gt;I figured it wasnt worth my time because I already believed the jews were doing all this stuff.&lt;br&gt;But I will say I learned about a lot of different people while researching for that coin.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most interesting to me, Jamie Dimon, CEO of JPMorgan Chase.&lt;br&gt;The very same JPMorgan Chase who in 2020 agreed to pay a $920 Million dollar fine for manipulating the silver market.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;And now we know that in 2011 Epstein was advised by Andersen Bernard that a silver squeeze was possible...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I have always thought that the silver play would have to wait until 2030 to really pay off.&lt;br&gt;These people know how to be patient and play the long game, and to me it looks lie it is all lining up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856922&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856890&lt;br&gt;The worse maximum out come i see happening is we crab for maybe 1 year max, with a 1-2month low of 50-60, and it goes parabolic, assuming the feds bailout the comex or the comex somehow magically gets more silver for delivery for March/April&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856918&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Frito lays just cut the price of potato chips so yes silver will drop 90% &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/cm2y38v4prvo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856912&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856886&lt;br&gt;The Hebrew Hammer points out inflation is 2% that&amp;#x27;s nothing, chicken littles never prosper ,,,die poor crybaby&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856911&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856890&lt;br&gt;Potatoe chips double in price... but silver is going down.&lt;br&gt;Niger please.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856901&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855974&lt;br&gt;It sure looks like Roberts...Oh, and the guy above Clinton sure looks like Alan Dershowitz, another well known visitor to pedo island.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856890&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856856&lt;br&gt;Silver is going down until 2053&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856886&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856874&lt;br&gt;I think this is one of the things they pointed out in that recent Maenco64 interview.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Fed can only do one of two things, &lt;br&gt;-Print or die&lt;br&gt;-inflate or collapse&lt;br&gt;-devalue or die&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;its all the same and it&amp;#x27;s all they&amp;#x27;ve ever done. it&amp;#x27;s built into the system they&amp;#x27;ve designed and wont &amp;quot;work&amp;quot; any other way.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;it&amp;#x27;s like time and tides.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856879&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;61856877&lt;br&gt;Seething shill.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856877&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856859&lt;br&gt;1:10 here, wanna keep the natural balance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856876&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855352&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856874&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856820&lt;br&gt;When did the US government/banking system NOT devalue the dollar? You can look at US monetary history as a sequence of changes all designed to allow endless devaluation of the dollar. The current administration is not going to hit upon devaluing the dollar as some kind of new strategy. It has been THE deliberate operational strategy for fleecing the public for more than a hundred years. Gold and silver were merely obstacles that needed to be pushed out of the way. They don&amp;#x27;t need to revalue gold or silver to continue doing what they have been doing for a century. In fact, as you indicate, they have no choice now. All roads lead to hyperinflation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856859&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856852&lt;br&gt;i do 1oz gold : 100oz silver for my stack&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856856&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856852&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;all in on silver&lt;br&gt;i don&amp;#x27;t think we can go wrong with this strategy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856852&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;thought about buying gold. but still going all in on silver&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856848&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856820&lt;br&gt;Andy Schechtman talked about some of this in a recent interview with Maneco64.&lt;br&gt;Apparently, the GENIUS act is part f the US Govt and the Fed Reserve plan to save the US form absolute collapse.&lt;br&gt;Somehow it a way to eventually be able to bring back manufacturing in the long term.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alot of it is still beyond my understanding much if it is unfamiliar to me but its starting to make sense, Andy describes it as &amp;quot;diabolically&amp;quot; clever, maybe evil. but its an option that prevents outright default of US debt.&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t know but it seems like it boils down to devaluing the dollar so much that by the time they have to payout on things like treasury bills, the USD/gold value is such that it is &amp;quot;cheap&amp;quot; to pay off those t-bill debnts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856842&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856819&lt;br&gt;fine, I&amp;#x27;ll grab one or a handful. It&amp;#x27;ll average £85-86 / Britannia. I hope this does moon because I want my father in law to appreciate that I&amp;#x27;m trying more and more to save for his daughter and our kids in future&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856836&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856552&lt;br&gt;Good rant and based.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856820&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856778&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;How the US government or Federal Reserve &amp;quot;values&amp;quot; gold on its books obviously has no effect on the market price of gold at the moment. Disagree?&lt;br&gt;Correct, simply &amp;quot;revaluing&amp;quot; gold on their books is just an accounting trick and does nothing.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m suggesting that the government will effectively devalue the dollar. They&amp;#x27;ve already devalued it from $2000 to $5000. What&amp;#x27;s two more doublings?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It reduces the cost of servicing their debt by 80% and will happen one way or another as Trump wants yield curve control (lowered interest rates) because they can&amp;#x27;t allow the US Treasury long rates to go above 5% of it starts a cascade of a debt spiral.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is NO money in the social security &amp;quot;trust fund&amp;quot; so all the new boomer entitlements need to be covered by money printing.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Much of the government revenue comes from taxes collected from rising equity prices, hence the &amp;quot;Dow 50000&amp;quot; comment. A recession that market corrects, and results in job losses, cuts government revenues while increasing expenditures for supports and stimulus.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We are sailing into a perfect storm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856819&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856816&lt;br&gt;Just pay the tax, silver is going to $500 in 2 weeks according to the coin merchants&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856816&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m going to buy my first coin this week, hopefully today. I just can&amp;#x27;t shake the VAT addition on the coin(s) I want. Would you recommend I go for gold sovereigns instead or should I start on ebay and vinted for some deals on silver here in Britlandistan&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856810&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Good to be here in /pmg/ where we have some chance of sharing and learning important lessons on the history and current state of the system.&lt;br&gt;it gives us a chance to do what we can, in as much as it is in our power to do so, to protect ourselves from the infernal machinations of the robber-baron abomination that continues to rape and pillage in their constant vampire ball.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856787&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856660&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856717&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856721&lt;br&gt;thanks frens&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856786&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856773&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;StoneX Bullion&lt;br&gt;This website is broken right now, still showing silver at 80$ for many days and wrong prices.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded><enclosure url="https://i.4cdn.org/biz/1771105049951580s.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0" /></item><item><title>/XMR/ Monero General — 247 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61810651</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61810651</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:36:07 +0000</pubDate><description>Open article for full content</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;/XMR/ Monero General&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61810651'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 247&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Welcome to /XMR/ Monero General, dedicated to the discussion of the world&amp;#x27;s most widely adopted privacy coin.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;XMR payments are anonymous, low-fee, and fully fungible. Users can send and receive XMR globally without having to worry about tainted coins. Battle-tested privacy tech (Ring Signatures, Stealth Addresses and RingCT) ensures that critical TX data cannot be gleaned from the Monero blockchain; the TX history of all XMR users is kept hidden, with TXs being optionally transparent via the aid of a view key.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;XMR ensures low TX fees by employing a dynamic block size that can &amp;quot;stretch&amp;quot; to easily accommodate sudden TX spikes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;XMR&amp;#x27;s mining algorithm, RandomX, is optimized for devices using general-purpose CPUs e.g. desktops, laptops, smartphones, tablets, keeping the barrier to entry low and ASICs out of the equation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;XMR&amp;#x27;s tail emission - 0.6 XMR per block forever - incentivizes for-profit miners to keep mining, helping boost long-term network security. This constant linear inflation trends to zero and is offset by coin loss.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;XMR has proven to be the only altcoin capable of overcoming BTC&amp;#x27;s network effect by driving it out of the darknet economy BTC dominated for over 10 years. XMR is also starting to overtake BTC in clearnet commerce as well.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you still have questions, feel free to ask. A MoneroChad will be with you shortly.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;XMR Redpill: https://youtube.com/watch?v=wq6w03E2DS4&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;BUY XMR: https://monero.eco/exchanges/&lt;br&gt;Crypto ATMs: https://coinatmradar.com/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;XMR Resources: https://monero.observer/resources/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;XMR Stats: https://moneroj.net&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;USE XMR: https://cryptwerk.com/pay-with/xmr/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;OFFICIAL WEBSITE: https://getmonero.org&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;MINING: &lt;br&gt;https://www.getmonero.org/get-started/mining/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;WALLETS:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Desktop&lt;br&gt;Official GUI/CLI wallet&lt;br&gt;Featherwallet&lt;br&gt;Stack Wallet&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Mobile&lt;br&gt;Cake Wallet&lt;br&gt;Monero.com&lt;br&gt;Stack Wallet&lt;br&gt;Unstoppable &lt;br&gt;Monerujo (Android)&lt;br&gt;Monfluo (Android)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Infodumps&lt;br&gt;https://rentry.org/monero-explained&lt;br&gt;https://moneroinfodump.neocities.org &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Previous: &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61761870&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856957&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851879&lt;br&gt;Buy from trocador&lt;br&gt;Go to daunt.link for DW link list&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856863&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856711&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;Monero General&amp;quot; thread&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;CTRL + F &amp;quot;nerva&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;140 results&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your unmaintained shitcoin will NEVER be relevant you poojeet retards. Everyone with more than 2 braincells can tell that you&amp;#x27;ve been shitting up the board trying to advertise. Please do the needful and make your own general. Except you can&amp;#x27;t do that right? Because NO ONE cares about it and it dies immediately unless you coordinate to keep it alive in your gay little discord server.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856711&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854237&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854655&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Jewish media bashing monero&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Just like they did with Trump&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Sub Artic IQs dont notice theyre promoting it on purpose&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Paid promoters ITT walk around the fact that concern was brought up by actual users and went unanswered or were outright removed posts/threads, then claim the view key fud was started by the very mossad theyre unironically supporting&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Glowner, promoted by Glews.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855579&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855558&lt;br&gt;I never bought crypto with PayPal but if you can buy LTC, do it. Once you swap to Monero and have it in your personal wallet you become invisible and cannot be deanonymized.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855567&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855558&lt;br&gt;Once it gets to your wallet it disappears.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855558&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855365&lt;br&gt;Ok, installed the cake wallet program, made the wallet, both monero and litecoin. Now I need to actually buy the crypto so I can transfer it to the wallet I just made. I think I still have an old paypal account which apparently allows you to buy crypto now. Is that ok for me to buy litecoin, transfer it to the cake wallet and exchange it for monero or will I be de-anonymized for using paypal just this once?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855365&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855123&lt;br&gt;Yeah, follow the chat here: &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61817263&lt;br&gt;If you have any issue or problem at a specific step ask here and we&amp;#x27;ll help.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Enjoy the &amp;quot;beer&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855123&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I need to send someone 5$ for a beer while anonymous. Thing is I have no fucking clue how any of this cryptocurrency works. Can someone explain to me same way you would to a retard?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855033&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61696670&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;suggest wallet that can store XRP,XMR,USDT and Zcash is there any&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Turns out this actually does exist. Hope this anon is still lurking &lt;br&gt;https://edge.app&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854655&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854237&lt;br&gt;They really seemed to think the view key fud would be more effective if they now need to publish paid articles&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854237&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61810651&lt;br&gt;Bloomberg published an article on Monero this morning. It’s behind a paywall but here is the article thanks to some Twitter anon.&lt;br&gt;https://pastebin.com/6aqniwe1&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;As digital assets go mainstream and law enforcement agencies get more adept at seizing illicit crypto, “privacy coins” like Monero hark back to the industry’s foundational idea: the creation of a decentralized electronic cash system running outside the purview of governments and central banks. That’s given them a cult following among libertarian-leaning crypto users — while providing a handy tool for criminals.&lt;br&gt;The rest of the article is just (((Bloomberg))) seething about how it can’t be tracked and a mention of the upcoming hard fork.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853405&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851879&lt;br&gt;Get any other coin and swap for Monero on Trocador.&lt;br&gt;Have the monero sent to your cake wallet.&lt;br&gt;Go on Dread to find what&amp;#x27;s the current best darknet market.&lt;br&gt;Go on the DNM and buy your product with Monero.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;All the steps take a bit of time but it&amp;#x27;s not complicated. Once you know how everything works it&amp;#x27;s no more complex than an Amazon order.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61852911&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851879&lt;br&gt;What this guy said&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61852742&lt;br&gt;Then visit Dread dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad onion&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61852742&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851879&lt;br&gt;Send any major crypto to Trocador. Swap to XMR.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851879&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I’ve been out of it for a while, how do I buy some and use it to acquire ketamine? Last time I was doing this, we used bitcoin and it was $220.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851533&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851129&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Youll never answer the questions regarding the upcoming fork and always link their github page because YOU dont understand it.&lt;br&gt;I link the github because I like having a source to back up my claims, and I actually want you to stop being a faggot and refute them&lt;br&gt;No, accusations of being a fedfreemasonbot out to get you are not refutations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;For some reason, Monero thinks its better to implement something that is unnecessary rather than something that should be implemented.&lt;br&gt;Who exactly are you to decide whether or not a feature is unnecessary and shouldn&amp;#x27;t be implemented?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Maybe its because you all brought up the &amp;quot;doomer fantasy&amp;quot;? He never mentioned it.&lt;br&gt;Given how he was asking about them&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61838139&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;so when someone says kyc will ask for this and then the feds will use it for surveillance, theyre correct? then it&amp;#x27;s not FUD&lt;br&gt;I hit the fast forward button on his line of thought since he clearly believes that view keys present some sort of threat, and I didn&amp;#x27;t feel like waiting 10 posts for him to go &amp;quot;WELL IF THEY GET ENOUGH TO VIEW KEYS IT&amp;#x27;LL BE THE END OF PRIVACY!&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;If this was wrong of me, then my bad.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Your wins are not the wins you think they are.&lt;br&gt;Who said I was trying to win anything? Why are you perpetuating this weird fantasy? You&amp;#x27;re weird bro. Not a good look at all, man.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851379&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851332&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Ive posted twice&lt;br&gt;Correct, I was speaking about rVCB8pdb, I assume you were doing that too or do you speak about yourself in the third person? &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;and none of it was about nerva.&lt;br&gt;Good job not having and reading comprehension and forgetting you posted: &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;they cant even BTFO nerva jeets lmfao (&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849231)&lt;br&gt;and: &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I was banned recently for criticizing it. Look at the nerva faggots. (&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851129)&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851332&lt;br&gt;You combined any criticism against XMR with nerva. So by your own logic most of the criticism here comes from the nervajeets.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Never did,&lt;br&gt;If you don&amp;#x27;t have any questions, then why do you keep pestering me about needing to answer them? &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Never mentioned it.&lt;br&gt;All three of your posts mentioned nerva in a positive light.&lt;br&gt;Feel free to answer any of my questions (see &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851255 for the easiest ones) or give me any of the question which you apparently don&amp;#x27;t have but are lamenting as being unanswered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851332&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851235&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;No, you retards get banned for shilling for nerva. Also it&amp;#x27;s weird to assume he got banned after his 14th post over 3 days meanwhile you&amp;#x27;ve also posted fud over the days and still are present. &lt;br&gt;Ive posted twice you jeetbot, (3 times now) and none of it was about nerva. Ill disregard the rest of this botpost.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851245&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Your questions? You don&amp;#x27;t seem to have any.&lt;br&gt;Never did, go back and reread my posts.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851255&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;xmrbotpost about nerva. &lt;br&gt;Never mentioned it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Glownero&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851255&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851129&lt;br&gt;In return I&amp;#x27;d like to ask you a few questions: &lt;br&gt;1. How do you ensure unmaintained software keeps up with the security demands it has?&lt;br&gt;2. How do you ensure that no one attacks nerva by locally clustering CPUs? &lt;br&gt;3. Why do your devs believe Discord to be a development platform despite being on github? &lt;br&gt;4. How do you ensure the safety of your devs in case of an attack by glowies if they all use the ID-requiring discord and 40% of them (50% of your lead devs) having doxxed themselves publicly?&lt;br&gt;5. What other questions do you have for me?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851245&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851129&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;always link their github page because&lt;br&gt;Me? No I didn&amp;#x27;t. I know github is something that challenges the nerva jeet heavily so instead I break it down in very simple terms. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;because YOU dont understand it.&lt;br&gt;Your questions? You don&amp;#x27;t seem to have any.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;the reason the reddit comments dont get answered is because NO ONE understands it.&lt;br&gt;I already answered all of the questions I saw. If you have more let me know. The assumption that no one understand cryptography or psychology is absurd considering the existence of that field. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The reason the even more damning questions get deleted is because theyre asking the right questions.&lt;br&gt;Like what? So far each question I saw I answered on here. I don&amp;#x27;t use reddit but feel free to keep me updated on orange site. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;For some reason, Monero thinks its better to implement something that is unnecessary&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;ve already been told that view keys will have some benefits. I recall hardware wallet and merchant software support being named in this thread. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;rather than something that should be implemented.&lt;br&gt;Devs, due to being part of a community and mostly unpaid, decide what they wish to implement. If it&amp;#x27;s fcmp++ they&amp;#x27;ll work on fcmp++, if it&amp;#x27;s carrot, they&amp;#x27;ll work on carrot. You can&amp;#x27;t force strangers that donate their time to do only what you want them to do especially if it&amp;#x27;s a feature you can easily avoid. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Take a good hard look at that statement youre defending&lt;br&gt;That literally nothing will worsen with carrot? Seems like a fine statement to me. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Since youll never post an answer to the questions,&lt;br&gt;I can&amp;#x27;t speak for anon but I already answered every question you have. If you have any other questions let me know.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851235&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851129&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;For some reason, criticizing your shitcoin (Monero) is against jannie law.&lt;br&gt;No, you retards get banned for shilling for nerva. Also it&amp;#x27;s weird to assume he got banned after his 14th post over 3 days meanwhile you&amp;#x27;ve also posted fud over the days and still are present. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;They keep being banned as well.&lt;br&gt;Who knows, maybe it&amp;#x27;s the constant shilling and the spam they don&amp;#x27;t just post here but on the board itself through a variety of threads. Btw when you don&amp;#x27;t get banned your generals just hit page 10 and die. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;What doesnt puzzle anyone is how your general stays up for days without deletion,&lt;br&gt;That&amp;#x27;s because the XMR general is fairly active and removing established generals would just lead to more shitposting. I hope you don&amp;#x27;t want the 10 millionth LINK thread this year.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;yet the only organic traction your threads have are from posters who get banned criticizing you.&lt;br&gt;Did you forget the moonfags that tried to take over this general, the qubic fud, the view key fud and the zioncash shills? All of those happened less than 6 months ago. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;and have this site backdoored.&lt;br&gt;No need for a backdoor when the mods are jews and feds. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;If competition shows up, the thread gets shadow banned and falls off the catalog.&lt;br&gt;Really? What happened to &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61841738 &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61827591 &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61822264 and &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61809799? Those are just some of the ones you had and that died because your community consists entirely of a few jeets and baggies. Graciously I sometimes enter your threads and ask you simple questions which you can&amp;#x27;t answer despite their simplicity. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Youll never answer the questions regarding the upcoming fork&lt;br&gt;I did a few hours ago and now I&amp;#x27;m waiting for more questions. Let me know if you have some.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851129&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849859&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850085&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850591&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I&amp;#x27;ve been waiting for a few hours now. Due to your lack of questions I assume you are agreeing with me that carrot does not pose a privacy threat&lt;br&gt;There is a good chance he&amp;#x27;s banned. For some reason, criticizing your shitcoin (Monero) is against jannie law. I was banned recently for criticizing it. Look at the nerva faggots. They keep being banned as well. What doesnt puzzle anyone is how your general stays up for days without deletion, yet the only organic traction your threads have are from posters who get banned criticizing you. Its because youre a bunch of glowniggers who work for (((the island bunch))) and have this site backdoored. If competition shows up, the thread gets shadow banned and falls off the catalog.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Youll never answer the questions regarding the upcoming fork and always link their github page because YOU dont understand it. Face the truth, the reason the reddit comments dont get answered is because NO ONE understands it. The reason the even more damning questions get deleted is because theyre asking the right questions. For some reason, Monero thinks its better to implement something that is unnecessary rather than something that should be implemented.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;In short: All proposed &amp;#x27;new&amp;#x27; attack vectors already exist&lt;br&gt;Take a good hard look at that statement youre defending&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Which sent anon into a tizzy that didn&amp;#x27;t actually refute anything I posted&lt;br&gt;Maybe its because you all brought up the &amp;quot;doomer fantasy&amp;quot;? He never mentioned it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your wins are not the wins you think they are.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;At what point will you accept this answer? Seriously, what don&amp;#x27;t you faggots get?&lt;br&gt;Since youll never post an answer to the questions, Why should they repeat themselves? Its an XMR thread, not the audience&amp;#x27;s thread. You have to provide an adequate answer and are up for scrutiny, not them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850591&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849231&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61848021&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;ve been waiting for a few hours now. Due to your lack of questions I assume you are agreeing with me that carrot does not pose a privacy threat. I&amp;#x27;m glad we could finally come to an agreement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850085&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849231&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;re clearly retarded and can&amp;#x27;t follow a conversation, so I&amp;#x27;ll highlight the points for you.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I gave the answer to the view key FUD here&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61838278&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Which sent anon into a tizzy that didn&amp;#x27;t actually refute anything I posted, here &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61838817&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;whos doomer porn fantasy? XMRfags cant even keep an eye on whos talking to who in here. I dont care about nerva.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Which I then edited to ease his butthurt here&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61839127&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The TLDR is that this particular doomer porn fantasy can&amp;#x27;t compromise anyone&amp;#x27;s privacy.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;But he wanted an official statement from the devs to ease his butthurt &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61847581&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;So I gave him that too &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61847618&lt;br&gt;Which sent anon into another tizzy, because he seems to agree with some redditor that &amp;quot;it&amp;#x27;s just toooooo hard to read the documentation! Why can&amp;#x27;t they spoonfeed me!?&amp;quot; Here &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61847794&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;why should i trust monero at all&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;picrelated from reddit thread. why cant they just tell reddit why its safe?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To which I then pounted out that he was already given the spoonfed answer that doesn&amp;#x27;t require him to read anything on github or librera &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61848809&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;And then asked the same question I&amp;#x27;ll ask you now:&lt;br&gt;At what point will you accept this answer? Seriously, what don&amp;#x27;t you faggots get?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849859&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61848827&lt;br&gt;I feel like most of the older stuff is still applicable since it&amp;#x27;s just about the basics. See picrel as an example. However I agree that the more specific guides (for example how and where to get XMR) rarely has good pictures. Do you have other bad examples so we can make a list? &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849231&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;cant even tell 4channers in a simple format&lt;br&gt;Five sentences isn&amp;#x27;t hard if you ask me. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;the taxman who says &amp;quot;gib?&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;1. You already need to be deanonymized for that. The ways you can get deanonymized will stay the same. This would also be combated by using an exchange wallet. I&amp;#x27;d probably even use an on-ramp wallet, an off-ramp wallet and a holding wallet. This way even if you were deanonymized and the IRS asks for more than what they&amp;#x27;re allowed to ask (just the income as a number, not the sources or which bank account it went to) you&amp;#x27;d still retain your privacy. &lt;br&gt;2. This is already possible by being coerced through various means. A view key won&amp;#x27;t change that. This is proven by your next sentence. &amp;gt;Normies fold faster than a wet noodle.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In short: All proposed &amp;#x27;new&amp;#x27; attack vectors already exist, require additional information that isn&amp;#x27;t easily obtained (they tried for years and still couldn&amp;#x27;t get it) and are easily mitigated. &lt;br&gt;Additionally, if someone for whatever reason was willing to inform the IRS of the relevant taxes by directly allowing access to view the wallet (which still is absurd and not how it works) it&amp;#x27;d be much easier and also less risky. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you have any other scenarios in which view keys could be exploited which are not covered already please let me know.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849231&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61847794&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61847814&lt;br&gt;They will never provide you an answer anon. Monerocucks are glowniggers, pretending to not be. Its funny watching them recoil in fear though. Just look at the past few generals, they cant even BTFO nerva jeets lmfao... look here&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61831334&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61847825&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;why cant they just tell reddit why its safe?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;doesnt and cant&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;cant even tell 4channers in a simple format&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Well *I* asked *you* that one for a reason.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Please tell me what explicit attack scenario exists in which the five dollar wrench and current KYC measurements are infeasible but having to give out your view keys is.&lt;br&gt;the taxman who says &amp;quot;gib?&amp;quot; Normies fold faster than a wet noodle.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61848809&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;You were already given the a TLDR&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;At what point will you accept this answer?&lt;br&gt;cant even get a copy and paste job on here&lt;br&gt;oh...&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;1pbtid&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You all sound like pathetic freemasons who suck jew dick.&lt;br&gt;&amp;quot;wErE nOt BaD pPl!? oH bUt YoU hAvE tO jOiN uS tO fInD OuT wHaT wE BeLiEvE iN!!!&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;kills you when you defect or tell a secret after finding out they worship the satan&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;lmao moneroniggers and their copium at their finest. Go glow on some other basket weaving forum. Is it any wonder XMR generals never get banned for advertisement? Its because 4chan is backdoored with JDIF, and JDIF &amp;amp; Monero suck each others dicks. One big blowjob circlejerk for their father satan.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;inb4 some cuck even tries to reply to me, you cant even keep up with my precision and speed. anyone who reads this knows im right. i use your shill threads to spread truth, and there is nothing you can do about it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849019&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61848053&lt;br&gt;Thanks anon. No cap fr fr Tbh I had no idea it was there before it was pointed out&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61848827&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We should look for ways to improve Monero&amp;#x27;s (official) material and appearance, not to induce any kind of pump, but to effectively convey the principles and message of why Monero, specifically out of other privacy coins, is extremely unique in the freedom it provides in contrast to all other money systems&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Right now it seems like very old material, links and screencaps keeps getting recycled. There&amp;#x27;s so many recent world events happening that tie in to Monero&amp;#x27;s use and we&amp;#x27;re missing a translation&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Monerochan (mostly AI slop) also doesn&amp;#x27;t communicate anything about Monero&lt;br&gt;There doesn&amp;#x27;t seem to be any good image macros to share from these threads&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Interested in how other people view this issue and what kind of material would get the communication standard up to the same level as its founding principles and tech&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61848809&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61847794&lt;br&gt;You were already given the a TLDR so you don&amp;#x27;t have to read through the chat logs like I and many other anons have&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61839127&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The TLDR is that this particular doomer porn fantasy can&amp;#x27;t compromise anyone&amp;#x27;s privacy.&lt;br&gt;At what point will you accept this answer?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61848342&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61848323&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;1488&lt;br&gt;based&lt;br&gt;monero is the final solution to the taxman question&lt;br&gt;and is what people think btc stands for&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m alive if that&amp;#x27;s what you&amp;#x27;re asking&lt;br&gt;and could unironically use any help if anyone could afford to&lt;br&gt;shamefully posting&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;XMR:&lt;br&gt;893qvnGketXV72jLmcDNhSWQgMQvzP4ab71HdaWMPrBrittG5PPfVrZcFKNYHv9UfXRDBkzvzNSc5bn7m7nJA6taKJ37gQW&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded><enclosure url="https://i.4cdn.org/biz/1770384967790775s.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0" /></item><item><title>/smg/ - stock market general — 203 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61853891</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61853891</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 15:28:14 +0000</pubDate><description>Open article for full content</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;/smg/ - stock market general&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61853891'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 203&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;waifu edition&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Some helpful links to numb the pain&lt;br&gt;https://findahelpline.com/&lt;br&gt;https://www.nvidia.com/refunds/&lt;br&gt;https://www.whitehouse.gov/refunds&lt;br&gt;https://jlingz.com/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Educational sites:&lt;br&gt;https://www.investopedia.com&lt;br&gt;https://www.khanacademy.org/economics-finance-domain&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Financial TV Streams:&lt;br&gt;https://www.newslive.com/american/cnbc.html&lt;br&gt;https://www.livestreamy.net/bloomberg/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Charts:&lt;br&gt;https://www.tradingview.com&lt;br&gt;https://www.finscreener.com&lt;br&gt;https://www.portfoliovisualizer.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Screeners: so you feel like in the movies&lt;br&gt;https://finviz.com/&lt;br&gt;https://etfdb.com/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Gambling:&lt;br&gt;https://www.optionsplaybook.com/options-introduction/&lt;br&gt;https://www.optionsprofitcalculator.com&lt;br&gt;https://optionstrat.com/&lt;br&gt;https://www.optionistics.com/quotes/option-prices&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Pre-Market and Live data:&lt;br&gt;https://www.investing.com/indices/indices-futures&lt;br&gt;https://finance.yahoo.com/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Calendars&lt;br&gt;https://www.marketwatch.com/economy-politics/calendar&lt;br&gt;https://www.earningswhispers.com/calendar&lt;br&gt;https://www.cmegroup.com/trading/interest-rates/countdown-to-fomc.html&lt;br&gt;https://www.mortgagenewsdaily.com/data/building-permits&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Boomer Investing 101: so zoomers with meme stocks can outperform you&lt;br&gt;https://www.bogleheads.org/wiki/Getting_started&lt;br&gt;https://www.sec.gov/search-filings&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Misc smg:&lt;br&gt;https://www.financialjuice.com/home&lt;br&gt;https://finance.yahoo.com/trending-tickers&lt;br&gt;https://market24hclock.com/&lt;br&gt;https://www.dividendchannel.com/drip-returns-calculator&lt;br&gt;https://brokerchooser.com/&lt;br&gt;https://www.chathamfinancial.com/technology/us-market-rates&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Previously on /smg/: &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850998&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856968&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856914&lt;br&gt;if it&amp;#x27;s sold out, doesn&amp;#x27;t that mean it&amp;#x27;s already priced in?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856929&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856525&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856914&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Western digimon we eating good&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856907&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856897&lt;br&gt;I actually already have a contract with a towing company that gives me 10% of the tow fee once the owner pay.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856897&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856868&lt;br&gt;Based&lt;br&gt;Now what you should do is invest in a tow truck&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856868&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I just finished installing metered parking at my rental units. looking forward to some additional passive income to invest this month!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856867&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Didn&amp;#x27;t even beat 3% daily inflation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856849&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856099&lt;br&gt;DeFi stands for definanced because you lose all your money&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856812&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856782&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m Getting New Income!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856801&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856796&lt;br&gt;Nothing ever happens&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856796&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856564&lt;br&gt;trump is in the files, dumbass.&lt;br&gt;QUICK, SEND OVER ANOTHER NEGOTIATING AIRCRAFT CARRIER!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856783&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;god that is some jewish shit. guaranteed glickman or one of the other usual suspects has some backdoor kike shit going on. this is still incredible theft. easily worth well north of $50. i&amp;#x27;m still getting paid but i almost have half a mind to roll a portion of profit out into december $35 strike calls on the chance institutional ownership swats this shit down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856782&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You Didn&amp;#x27;t Think Neetbux Trader Would Fail Right!??&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856763&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856525&lt;br&gt;THAT&amp;#x27;S IT??!?!?!&lt;br&gt;VOTE IT DOWN&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856703&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856629&lt;br&gt;I am the GAMB &amp;amp; GRRR anon lol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856636&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856630&lt;br&gt;*sniffs you* markit closed silly!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856630&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Let&amp;#x27;s Go Guys Trade Stocks!!!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856629&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856514&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856620&lt;br&gt;what is depressing you guys so much maybe I can help?&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m a nice internet UNC who likes the smell of newfrens&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856625&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856594&lt;br&gt;and they closed their gay loophole for people who have extreme returns&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856623&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856594&lt;br&gt;also when I look closer at this it seems its the same in the nl you can just move it into a company and then pay 25% without the unrealizted gains thing. So I think nl is actually just competing with germany because of the weed legal thing boss&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856620&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sometimes I feel sad about my portfolio, all the while a great bullrun carries me - Ancient Bizraeli saying.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856610&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856594&lt;br&gt;because eternally nothing ever happens&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856609&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856594&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;If this happens to your country, what&amp;#x27;s your out?&lt;br&gt;in my country there would probably be some way arround it kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856594&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s fucked.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Netherlands scenario (B) of 36% tax on unrealized gains is actually equivalent to -50% on annualized returns over a lifetime due to volatility resulting in -75% wealth confiscation over a 40 year period.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If this happens to your country, what&amp;#x27;s your out?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856589&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856573&lt;br&gt;reminder to buy when there is blood in the streets&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;https://youtu.be/Jn-Yrp1PVdw?si=Fxcz_J95VD9wXQXh&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856573&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US stock market is very dead for the next couple weeks (plus).&lt;br&gt;Come Monday I will eject almost the last vestiges after already getting rid of MU, meaning my stupid Take Two, SOFI and MSFT plays (bought the dip -- now realize while they will eventually pay off, it&amp;#x27;s dead capital).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Getting really gooky and nippy in my &amp;#x27;folio.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856564&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856525&lt;br&gt;Israel wins again&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;HE CAN&amp;#x27;T KEEP GETTING AWAY WITH IT&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Also lads, Iran deal is on and Bitcoin computer is mooning I think we&amp;#x27;re all gonna be ok on Taco Tuesday!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856563&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856556&lt;br&gt;they&amp;#x27;re waiting for monday to tank the market&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856556&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;long weekend&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;no big geopolitical event has happened yet&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What the fuck is going on???&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856525&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Congrats ZIM bros, buyout at $29-30 now confirmed apparently.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I bought last summer at $16 waiting for this buyout. I did not hold because I got impatient.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I know some of you have been holding.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded><enclosure url="https://i.4cdn.org/biz/1771082894968487s.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0" /></item><item><title>/GME/ - Settle in for Comfy (Long) Weekend Edition — 192 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61853052</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61853052</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 07:58:33 +0000</pubDate><description>Open article for full content</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;/GME/ - Settle in for Comfy (Long) Weekend Edition&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61853052'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 192&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;Basic Information&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;gme.cac site redacted due to aids&lt;br&gt;https://finra-markets.morningstar.com/MarketData/EquityOptions/detail.jsp?query=14%3A0P000002CH&lt;br&gt;https://gmetimeline.com (up to 2021)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Daily reminder&lt;br&gt;s[Kek Melvies]bzilp4&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Mandatory study time&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The Everything Short&lt;br&gt;reddit.com/mgucv2&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;^watch-along&lt;br&gt;youtu.be/AaalT8rn9lc&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Naked Short Selling and Systemic Risk&lt;br&gt;youtu.be/FCiL4v7_z9E&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Failure to deliver&lt;br&gt;youtu.be/I0WXg5T3cBE&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;GameStop Investor Site&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;SEC 10-K Annual report FY24 &amp;amp; &amp;#x27;25 Proxy Statement&lt;br&gt;news.gamestop.com/annual-meeting/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;What will happen if Citadel becomes insolvent?&lt;br&gt;DTCC with 60T USD, will pay as the final boss with FDIC as the insurance&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Real-Time Trades&lt;br&gt;https://www.nasdaq.com/market-activity/stocks/GME/latest-real-time-trades&lt;br&gt;https://eresearch.fidelity.com/eresearch/gotoBL/fidelityTopOrders.jhtml&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Current Trade Halts + Short Restrictions&lt;br&gt;nasdaqtrader.com/Trader.aspx?id=TradeHalts&lt;br&gt;nyse.com/markets/nyse-arca/notices&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;All other news/DDs/etc&lt;br&gt;en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Stag_hunt&lt;br&gt;https://prospect.org/power/how-the-gamestop-hustle-worked&lt;br&gt;https://computershared.net/?bot=drsbot&lt;br&gt;DRS Guide:&lt;br&gt;reddit.com/ptvaka&lt;br&gt;Avoid DSPP (more information under legacy links):&lt;br&gt;sec.gov/about/reports-publications/investor-publications/holding-your-securities-get-the-facts&lt;br&gt;HF/broker class action lawsuit evidence:&lt;br&gt;storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.flsd.590042/gov.uscourts.flsd.590042.416.0.pdf&lt;br&gt;SEC GME/meme stocks report:&lt;br&gt;sec.gov/files/staff-report-equity-options-market-struction-conditions-early-2021.pdf&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;DD Compilation:&lt;br&gt;reddit.com/mnss65&lt;br&gt;Quarterly Movements, Equity Total Return Swaps, DOOMPs, ITM CALLs, Short Interest, and Futures Roll Periods:&lt;br&gt;reddit.com/pb22oj&lt;br&gt;Cellar Boxing:&lt;br&gt;reddit.com/pmj9yk&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Temporary alliance with reddit and Jaws to take down other sharks, we can go back to hating each other later&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;reddit DDs don&amp;#x27;t take them for fact use your brain&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Check your broker and clearing house to ensure you&amp;#x27;re not rugpulled&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last time on /GME/: &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61847072&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As always:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;sneed hedgies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856939&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856934&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856331&lt;br&gt;pressure release valves&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856934&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Very organic&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856910&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856893&lt;br&gt;Fuck you. The real holders know that bbby dk- butterfly tendie off will come through and make us God&amp;#x27;s among men. Maxipads will never have wealth. You will remain poor. We are not feds or spammers! I trust in Ryan Cohen completely and he is a creditor for bbby and the cusip in interesting!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856893&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bbbqy spammers are just feds, that&amp;#x27;s all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856873&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855350&lt;br&gt;So by your logic, everyone on that bbbyq docket (showing DRS holders) are fucked? Given their full government names are listed and clearly have more unwaivering conviction than your typical GME holder?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856861&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855015&lt;br&gt;That&amp;#x27;s why shill get upset when they are mocked and called jeets that eat cow poop. They have to read it. They try to use shaming tactics when they are insulted. The reality is that using slurs against them does make you blend in, because they can&amp;#x27;t reply in kind. Calling them jeets and Jews in the fastest way to make them I&amp;#x27;d jump.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856693&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hi like Ichimoku, I think it is neat. too bad it is useless&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856434&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856331&lt;br&gt;Isn&amp;#x27;t it crazy the implication of systemic stock suppression, is that you&amp;#x27;re gambling all non-suppressed stocks against the suppressed ones? Pretty wacky scenario.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856346&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855460&lt;br&gt;Hope some got laughs at my expense yesterday, not native english. Spent past summer in Amsterdam and having girls that directly available was .. new (and wah the weed). 5 red light visits and 3 of them 10/10 experience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856331&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;55 trillion market cap&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856300&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856282&lt;br&gt;Right at that point I&amp;#x27;d be cutting just-below-threshold deals for securities backed loans and then just not paying them back. Tax free windfall, plowed straight into assets of my choice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856282&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855670&lt;br&gt;I feel like they&amp;#x27;d make an emergency exception of some kind. The worst thing they could possibly do is forcibly diamond hand everyone for a month straight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856112&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Burry is reposting his sneeze summary.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;https://x.com/michaeljburry/status/2022915353601290650&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856100&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855670&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Is it really in our prophecy that moass happens because anons can&amp;#x27;t fucking sell?&lt;br&gt;Technically volatility halts could keep the markets in this autonomous glacier where it becomes very hard to clear/confirm trades: https://www.luldplan.com/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here&amp;#x27;s the NYSE halts that get updated during regular hours: https://www.nyse.com/trade/trading-information&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856072&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jannies are retroactively deleting comments inside threads that are already archived on 4chan.org&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;this comment exists on warosu:&lt;br&gt;https://warosu.org/biz/thread/61791741#p61792435&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;but that same comment was removed from the thread AFTER it was already archived.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61791741&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855930&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I wonder why DFV bought all those chewy shares?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855879&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Any Dutch bros here? Is the bill pretty much guaranteed to pass senate?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855852&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854610&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;just deep value investing in a company experiencing a historic turnaround&lt;br&gt;this sentence is to shills what the garlic is to vampires.&lt;br&gt;it&amp;#x27;s 100% obvious that gamestop is NOT a &amp;quot;memestock&amp;quot; (made up fake label anyways) but a normal stock traded on the stock market and all indicators and fundamentals point towards a bullish outlook. that&amp;#x27;s factual.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855824&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;QED&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855792&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855783&lt;br&gt;Not to mention that in a situation where GME&amp;#x27;s share count is fully reconciled, the options chain will not be a safe haven. Force majeure cash settlement inbound for the optionfags while DRS chads rest easy as gazillionaires.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Sorry goy, an Act of God happened! Here&amp;#x27;s some cash! Sorry about your GME options contract!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855783&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855769&lt;br&gt;I would sooner buy long dated puts on spy than options on gme. Just buying shares and warrants seems smarter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855774&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855769&lt;br&gt;AvailableWarewolf/ftwbiz will be killed post moass&lt;br&gt;lol&lt;br&gt;lmao&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855769&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855529&lt;br&gt;It would explain why everyone who mentions buying LEAPS gets dogpiled by screeching retards even though DFV&amp;#x27;s whole strategy was LEAPS+shares.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855745&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854860&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854674&lt;br&gt;kek we&amp;#x27;re close&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855670&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854868&lt;br&gt;At that price even selling half my shares I qualify for that 30 day &amp;quot;please let me sell&amp;quot; bullshit that anon was talking about. Is it really in our prophecy that moass happens because anons can&amp;#x27;t fucking sell?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855653&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;*all shares in broker = $250k.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855647&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855615&lt;br&gt;I would also argue&lt;br&gt;1 warrant = 1 wagmi - $32&lt;br&gt;1 share in broker = $250k&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855615&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855141&lt;br&gt;1 share in CS:GO = 1 wagmi&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;x+1 share in CS:GO = 1 wagmi &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The bigger x is, the faster 1 wagmi happens&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855166&lt;br&gt;I would like to test being rich now. That would help.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855545&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ken Griffin is having a bad week. Let us take a moment of silence for ken Griffin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855534&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854591&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Is there really a doubt that a “meme stock” has been deemed a new type of security with different rules and exceptions?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;post a link to this new regulatory framework. They can delay as long as the derivatives market allows hiding short interest (bill hwang did this) and hiding positions inside swaps and other bespoke instruments. BBBY owns tzero, nothing happens without M&amp;amp;A activity, guess which companies will be involved?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded><enclosure url="https://i.4cdn.org/biz/1771055913680926s.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0" /></item><item><title>/XSG/ XRP Schizo General #2529 — 240 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61833878</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61833878</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 19:12:23 +0000</pubDate><description>Open article for full content</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;/XSG/ XRP Schizo General #2529&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61833878'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 240&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Previous: &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61810716&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Buy XRP on:&lt;br&gt;Coinbase, Binance, Bitrue, Uphold, Robinhood, Kraken, Kucoin, etc&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Why hold XRP?&lt;br&gt;https://youtu.be/5urrOWO0KDI [Embed]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Newfag Tutorial:&lt;br&gt;https://youtu.be/23Yn5GdYpJc [Embed]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;XRPL Guide:&lt;br&gt;https://xrpl.guide&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;XRPL Explorer:&lt;br&gt;https://bithomp.com&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;XRPL Richlist:&lt;br&gt;https://rich-list.info&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;XRP ETF Tracker:&lt;br&gt;https://xrp-insights.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Latest News:&lt;br&gt;https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XRPUSD/news/?exchange=CRYPTO&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;X:&lt;br&gt;https://x.com/JoelKatz&lt;br&gt;https://x.com/bgarlinghouse&lt;br&gt;https://x.com/Ripple&lt;br&gt;https://x.com/RippleXDev&lt;br&gt;https://x.com/WietseWind&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The Myth of Market Cap:&lt;br&gt;http://galgitron.net/Post/The-Myth-of-Market-Cap---Version-2&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;XRP FUD BINGO:&lt;br&gt;https://fudbingo.com&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;ANTI-FUD:&lt;br&gt;https://pastebin.com/ZESsmqB8&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Lore:&lt;br&gt;https://pastebin.com/Z39w20qf&lt;br&gt;https://X.com/bearableguy123&lt;br&gt;https://x.com/FoJAk3 [Mr. Pool archives]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Schizo Ramblings:&lt;br&gt;https://pastebin.com/YHwQrGDW&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Past /XSG/ Threads:&lt;br&gt;https://pastebin.com/pZdQbREq&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;What wallet do I use?&lt;br&gt;Hot storage - Xaman, Gem Wallet, Crossmark or Bifrost&lt;br&gt;Cold storage - Paper/Metal or Ledger/D’CENT&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856913&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Where&amp;#x27;s Spammy, did he died?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856760&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I would rape spammy until his anus can&amp;#x27;t stop bleeding. Then when he begs me to stop I slice his stupid throat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856680&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Today&amp;#x27;s theme:&lt;br&gt;https://youtu.be/S30XdiTDINc&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856580&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I have the perfect theme for the next bake and I will not let Spammy or that other retard snipe it away from me in 63 posts time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856506&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856444&lt;br&gt;my goodness, would you look at those digits&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856444&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856309&lt;br&gt;Swing high or swing low, eventually you&amp;#x27;ll swing from the neck.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856419&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is this is a fever dream or have we gained back thread engagement without Spammy? What if Spammy changed tactics and all the 1pbtid posts is just Spammy?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856309&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856283&lt;br&gt;what do we say about swingies, anon?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856283&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I sold 1/3 of my bag on $1.3 &lt;br&gt;am I cooked ?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856262&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856205&lt;br&gt;mmm splendid&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856260&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I should have bought way harder but honestly 500 bucks isn&amp;#x27;t bad&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856253&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856246&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;redpill me on crossmark wallet&lt;br&gt;i hate phones, can crossmark be what xaman is just as a desktop browser extension rather than a phone app? can it connect to the xrp toolkit?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856205&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856077&lt;br&gt;Indubitably my good sir, I do say indeed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856186&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why are we going up right now against the rest of the market? I&amp;#x27;m not used to good things happening for us&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856088&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856004&lt;br&gt;i mean, you are right there, get a second job for a year&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856077&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;fascinating climb this coin is doing eh chaps&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856067&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856060&lt;br&gt;That&amp;#x27;s why I am using leverage ... so i can get out ... I want out so I can move to japan and start my life and I have to use leverage since they won&amp;#x27;t just pump this shit to $10&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856064&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856055&lt;br&gt;No but I do some betting on kalshi from time to time for random shit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856060&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEVER USE LEVERAGE&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;IT&amp;#x27;S A TRAP&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;THEY WANT YOU OUT&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856055&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856045&lt;br&gt;Do you also bet on prowrestling?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856045&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856039&lt;br&gt;I mean you don&amp;#x27;t have to be a degenerate like me but you could go 2x or 3x easy and pretty much never get liquidated. I plan on just leveraging a 100k stack here soon at like 4x and just DCA and bring my leverage down over time with degenerate plays&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856039&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856011&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m sorry fren. I should&amp;#x27;ve considered the pain of others when I spoke.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856016&lt;br&gt;Idk. I&amp;#x27;ve seen so many people in these threads swing and fail. I&amp;#x27;ve just been DCAing and once FXRP opened up on the Flare network I bridged and have been loaning it out on Kinetic making ~4% apy paid in FLR.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856016&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856004&lt;br&gt;Just gamble bro it makes inflating your stack ezpz all you have to do is win and not lose&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856011&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856004&lt;br&gt;I only hold 200 xrp because im a poorfag&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856004&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855877&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Tfw only a 1.063% holder according to the richlist&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;tfw a 43.5k stacklet&lt;br&gt;Idk if I can catch up guys. Every purchase after $0.50 has been harder to climb the ranks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856003&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We just hit 10% up on the daily chart.&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m cautiously optimistic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855997&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855700&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I&amp;#x27;ve bagheld XRP too long, with an all or nothing approach.&lt;br&gt;I did similar, but, didn&amp;#x27;t anticipate it falling so hard. We still should see some good gains post Clarity Act, but I should have also cashed some out, at least to have more cash for a fall like we just had down to $1.15.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855885&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61848187&lt;br&gt;congrats bro, hope to see you in the pleasure dome&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855882&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855304&lt;br&gt;i mean, if you are poor it wouldnt be so bad to have 300k&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded><enclosure url="https://i.4cdn.org/biz/1770750743134576s.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0" /></item><item><title>Imagine that they pass unrealized tax gains in your country. — 103 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61851566</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61851566</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 23:01:33 +0000</pubDate><description>Open article for full content</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Imagine that they pass unrealized tax gains in your country.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61851566'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 103&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;What do you do?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856951&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856933&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; No western country has a 4% inflation rate&lt;br&gt;Nigga look at the numbers, is way worse than that 4%. Look at what has happened in the last 6 years. Is only going to accelerate from here.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; World etf or S&amp;amp;P500&lt;br&gt;Cant you read? An etf is not the same as bonds and anon there was talking about putting 2M in bonds at 27 years old. Asuming you are going to live another 60 years is not that clear that putting all on those indexes is going to work for that long. Probably is better to diversify and buy a bit of everything.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856947&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Invest in fertilizer&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856933&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856745&lt;br&gt;No western country has a 4% inflation rate and a simple world ETF or the S&amp;amp;P500 massively outperforms inflation. 2 million invested in the S&amp;amp;P500 means you will have 4 million in 10 years, 8 million in 20 years, 16 million in 30 years by the time you reach normal retirement age, if you leave it all invested to let it compound. If you seriously struggle with 2 million you must be genuinely retarded and judging by your obviously very low IQ I highly doubt you have anywhere close to that much money invested.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856888&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851566&lt;br&gt;I own an illegal tobacco manufactory and sell cheap cigs to gypsies on the job site. Its that easy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856854&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61852029&lt;br&gt;I think youre fucked. Your populations genetics is a mixture of European prison gaurds and prisoners, and highly conformist Asiatics. I don’t mean this rudely, but Corona showed us how distance your population was to being led by the nose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856844&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853104&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Most people aren&amp;#x27;t money minded like we are&lt;br&gt;Yep. This is mostly a genetic problem. Intelligence is capped by genes. Voting rights should not be equal at least.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856837&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851566&lt;br&gt;Realise the gains, take the hit, leave the country and continue investing in a socially stable country with less freedom to criticise the state but societally stable with a ruling class which understands you don’t tax you money makers.&lt;br&gt;Allow the original socialist state I’ve left to collapse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856784&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;rules only apply to those who follow them on an individual level. The law does not apply to large enough groups who actively or passively break it enmasse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856770&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856752&lt;br&gt;Holy shit i didnt know that&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856752&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851566&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;what if&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t have to imagine, i live in France, the most taxed nation in the history of mankind, so ofc we pionnered the concept already back last year.&lt;br&gt;But it didn&amp;#x27;t make much of a fuss since ppl are used to frogs being cucked to death by their (((government))).&lt;br&gt;Also here it&amp;#x27;s only 1% (so far) so it&amp;#x27;s not as &amp;quot;impressive&amp;quot; as the NL, but it&amp;#x27;s for all &amp;quot;unproductive assets&amp;quot;, which is vague enough to eventually put everything in the basket. They already are talking about adding gold, RE, etc.. to the unrealized gains tax.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856745&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856731&lt;br&gt;After 30 years at a 4% inflation rate your 2M will be 1/3 of the initial purchasing power. And your 60k will buy 20k worth, and you will be 57 years old.&lt;br&gt;And that is asuming inflation doesnt go higher (which it will go because there is no other way of getting out of the debt), and rates stay high enough where you get that 3% after taxes (which they wont for 30 years)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856731&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856690&lt;br&gt;even with just 2mil you could make 60k a year AFTER tax with boring ass bonds. That´s 5k a month after tax. I understand we all have different life styles but how much money do you spend a month that requires 4mil (which would be 10k a month).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856690&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856666&lt;br&gt;Checked. Because you are 27. If you were 50 it would be ok.&lt;br&gt;You probably need at least 4M at 27 to retire.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856666&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856643&lt;br&gt;500k?&lt;br&gt;Why is it I have 2m EUR at 27 and it doesn&amp;#x27;t feel like enough at all?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856650&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I live in an offshore tax haven, its all we have going for us that there is no capital gains tax. Everyone would leave it would be so suicidal lol.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856645&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851566&lt;br&gt;I have never paid tax before, so I will do nothing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856644&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856531&lt;br&gt;Catchy slogan&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856643&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856638&lt;br&gt;I personally only require 500k since I still live with my parents and my monthly expenses despite working full time were something like 600-700€ for the past 8 or so years. Will inherit the house anyway. 500k doesnt seem like a lot for most people but I doubt I start spending more than that once I dont work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856639&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856538&lt;br&gt;Realized in the sense of closing a transaction not in the sense of having knowledge of.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856638&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856621&lt;br&gt;How much net worth do you need to retire in your 40&amp;#x27;s?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856621&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851566&lt;br&gt;as things currently go I could retire in 10 years in my 40`s for the rest of my life. if they would introduce the same thing the dutch just did I would have to work for the rest of my life up until 67. this would unironically drive me into suicide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856538&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851566&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;unrealized&lt;br&gt;How can I be taxed for something people don’t realize that I have?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856531&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851566&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m all in on Monero, I don&amp;#x27;t care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856104&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851566&lt;br&gt;Sell everything and put it in monero and leave the country.&lt;br&gt;Anything I can&amp;#x27;t sell I burn to the ground.&lt;br&gt;Do as much sabotage as possible on my way out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856095&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61852029&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;If they pass it in UK (which could be a possibility, since they&amp;#x27;re broke and ruined) they might attempt it here.&lt;br&gt;No, it&amp;#x27;s the other way around, faggot. Your shithole country already taxes pension contributions at 15% and taxed again at 15% if it&amp;#x27;s a TTR, two things that are absolutely unthinkable in the UK. Your financial sector is so underdeveloped you don&amp;#x27;t even have anything similar to an ISA and the only way to avoid CGT is to buy bonds and hold on to them for 10 years lmao. &lt;br&gt;The UK has a million flaws but taxing wealth and investment isn&amp;#x27;t one of them. We get taxed on consumption but not even the most leftist government would think of taxing anything investment-related. &lt;br&gt;Seriously, you can stop pretending you&amp;#x27;re ahead of us when it comes to personal liberties in any way. That mask slipped years ago during COVID when the world saw what a North Korea-tier shithole your country is. And it appears it&amp;#x27;s also a shithole in terms of economic liberties.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856084&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854007&lt;br&gt;Kek delusional flikker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856065&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855818&lt;br&gt;nope, real estate is exempt from the unrealized gains tax, so you don&amp;#x27;t even get affordable housing kek.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855988&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851566&lt;br&gt;Probably form a coalition to remove the Minecraft server admin and the moderators, permanently. I think enough players would be absolutely fucking sick of these shit fuck game mods that action would be required&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855929&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855910&lt;br&gt;what???&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855910&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851578&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;bet $10k on red&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;50/50 odds, so expected value is $10k&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;get taxed on unrealized $10k gains &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;it&amp;#x27;s down to $7k&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;win&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;it&amp;#x27;s now $14k&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;capital gains tax, -$4k&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;back to $10k&lt;br&gt;you VILL own nothing&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded><enclosure url="https://i.4cdn.org/biz/1771023693544742s.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0" /></item><item><title>Thread 61849825 — 149 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61849825</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61849825</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 17:12:20 +0000</pubDate><description>Open article for full content</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Thread 61849825&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61849825'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 149&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most wagies are about to get financially SMOKED&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856905&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856871&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;AI will replace jeets - and that&amp;#x27;s a good thing.&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;d rather have Nipah replace jeets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856898&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856882&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;let the cashier bag your groceries for you&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I see you&amp;#x27;ve never been to ALDI / LIDL&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856882&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849825&lt;br&gt;The self-checkout was invented 40 years ago and yet there are still millions of cashiers employed. Reason being they&amp;#x27;re annoying as fuck to use and you might as well let the cashier bag your groceries for you. Amazon Fresh stores, which had no cashiers, all closed down recently and they depended on Indians watching with cameras to validate some purchases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856881&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854368&lt;br&gt;Nuking America&amp;#x27;s big bities resets demographics to the early 1900s. Predominantly White (heretic) Christian.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856871&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849825&lt;br&gt;AI will replace jeets - and that&amp;#x27;s a good thing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856853&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849825&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;ve been hearing &amp;quot;most white-collar jobs will be be wiped out in the next 1-2 years&amp;quot; for the past three years now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856504&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849825&lt;br&gt;Even if AI can replace all jobs that doesn&amp;#x27;t guarantee that AI itself will be profitable. If AI can make AI there is no reason to use any particular AI, so why would anyone pay for AI?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Servers, electricity, water, real estate, etc these things will be needed to be rented to make AIs run of course, so the money will be in these things, not the producers of AI&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856486&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61852835&lt;br&gt;This makes sense though, financial advice is the type of thing which can be standardized to result in a decent enough result. Diversification, staying with reliabl dividend payers who regular post increasing earnings. The question of how to be an &amp;quot;okay&amp;quot; investor has been solved and the AI is smart enough to scour the internet to regurgitate it to you. If a question hasn&amp;#x27;t been solved there is nothing for the AI to give you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856277&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61852519&lt;br&gt;What a dramatic faggot. Nigga bitch ass NIGGA just pour water on the ai jfc cringy ass nigga&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855870&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849825&lt;br&gt;two more weeks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855862&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849825&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Some of those that are AI shills&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Are the same that force RTO&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850673&lt;br&gt;Here is an extreme scenario: AI+robotics achieve human level thinking and movement, and it is cheaper to manufacture and maintain one compared to owning a literal human slave. If such robots are privately owned, the corporations could develop an independent self sustaining economy. The corporation won&amp;#x27;t even need to think about money at this point. They won&amp;#x27;t have to think about 99% of people who don&amp;#x27;t participate in this robot economy.&lt;br&gt;More &amp;quot;realistic&amp;quot; (not really) scenario: office jobs are eliminated. Everyone is pushed into blue collar jobs, and white collar jobs that need human presence legally. Corporations save tons of money on salaries and real estate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854687&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61852343&lt;br&gt;The problem is that there&amp;#x27;s no plan in place to protect you from AI job loss and government is slow and inefficient at implementing anything, if they ever do at all. We aren&amp;#x27;t going to see UBI until well after people are destitute, and that&amp;#x27;s if UBI is even something they implement.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I wouldn&amp;#x27;t be surprised if people don&amp;#x27;t even care, or darker, say they deserved to lose their jobs and take glee and delight at seeing it happen. I already see it on social media all the time. It&amp;#x27;s even in this thread. &amp;quot;They had do-nothing jobs where they just sat in a chair all day staring at a screen, fuck &amp;#x27;em!&amp;quot; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;No one is saving you. Prepare to take a low-skill physical labor job if you aren&amp;#x27;t proficient in a skilled trade, which you likely aren&amp;#x27;t. Same as most white-collar workers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854569&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854528&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;zogbot&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;metalnigger&lt;br&gt;ngmi&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854561&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849894&lt;br&gt;we cant have flying cars until we do something about niggers and women with drivers licenses and thats just the inconvenient truth. We have the technology for it but it wouldnt be worth it because niggers would fly into nice neighborhoods and shoot up random houses&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854560&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854389&lt;br&gt;no it isn&amp;#x27;t&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854528&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Don’t care, I’m a zogbot. I’ll be fed and housed for as long as I’m useful to our overlords. If you’re not a nepo baby or extremely lucky, enlist/commission. You won’t be rich but you’ll be comfy. (USAF specifically unless you’re actually so retarded that you can’t do well on the asvab)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854522&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If this were true, the first companies to fire the majority of their workers would be the tech companies who are experts at using the AI.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854456&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854368&lt;br&gt;Our least productive and most subversive members are all in major population centers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;https://youtube.com/watch?v=A_PTvdxF_XY&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854389&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850522&lt;br&gt;denial is the most predictable of all human responses&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854384&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850884&lt;br&gt;Anon, this is a solved problem. AI are essentially overly confident humans with limited memory. So you give them tools (i.e. the ability to call a price API or search on the internet) so they don&amp;#x27;t go based on their model training and merely just reason their way with new information.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854377&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850763&lt;br&gt;Anon, the main concern everyone has is what will they do to put food on the table when they get displaced. Everyone is struggling and the dream of owning a home has dissipated.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;But yeah, I am indeed looking forward to not having to hire someone to do something AI can do for me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854368&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850575&lt;br&gt;i dont get that pic&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854316&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;NOOO BASTERD! YOU CANNOT MAKE LIVING WITHOUT COMPANY SAAR LISTEN TU MEEE I AM CEO! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get the hell out of my country.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854312&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854303&lt;br&gt;Once a company goes public it basically can&amp;#x27;t do anything that doesn&amp;#x27;t deliver immediate profits for the shareholders. And once it gets to the size of microsoft it can&amp;#x27;t innovate anymore because every single decision has to go through teams upon teams of people. It&amp;#x27;s the same reason why all democracies are imploding right now, the system cannot come to a consensus on anything.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854303&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849825&lt;br&gt;What never makes sense to me is why these companies just bag the profits made from using ai instead paying workers? Why not expand (which would create new jobs to replace the old) and make your company even bigger and better? &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are numerous examples of how they could grow the company with the money. Microsoft here could now go into robotics and work on the first fully functional sexbot. Or they could go into that Internet cafe shit that&amp;#x27;s popular in Japan and open them here in the US. The possibilities are endless when you now have tens of millions in disposable income as a company.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854296&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It fails the logic test. If AI was so good this would have already happened.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854287&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854047&lt;br&gt;Yes, wanna fight about it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854219&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Papa John’s CEO says “most, if not all meals” will be replaced with pizza in the next 12-18 months&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854202&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ai is making it so I can ex nihilo why are people worried do they have no talents and no way to profit from this situation?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854194&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854063&lt;br&gt;like 80% of people who have a job?&lt;br&gt;outlook&lt;br&gt;excel&lt;br&gt;word&lt;br&gt;windows&lt;br&gt;xbox&lt;br&gt;azure&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded><enclosure url="https://i.4cdn.org/biz/1771002740425739s.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0" /></item><item><title>Thread 61854715 — 74 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61854715</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61854715</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 20:15:34 +0000</pubDate><description>Open article for full content</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Thread 61854715&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61854715'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 74&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;toothpastebros...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856971&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854715&lt;br&gt;I hate this dogshit country so fucking much. I wish America or Russia nuked us already.&lt;br&gt;Completely fucking braindead&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856962&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856790&lt;br&gt;You will see how the backtrack&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856790&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854726&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;relax, the politicians will backtrack their authoritarian push for more power&lt;br&gt;holy cope&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856772&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854715&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;shitskinned failed country getting turned into a more goycattle farm&lt;br&gt;why the fuck should i care&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856702&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854715&lt;br&gt;when will the senate decide about this catastrophy?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856508&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854817&lt;br&gt;Yes but your gooning sessions aren’t degenerate at all :)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856505&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854715&lt;br&gt;Lel&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856343&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856310&lt;br&gt;Yeah the USA posters don&amp;#x27;t know how good they have it. And I&amp;#x27;ve seen some threads encouraging people to take their money out of USA assets.. JUST FUCKING LOL. Trust me STAY OUT OF EUROPE&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856326&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854817&lt;br&gt;They&amp;#x27;re dopamine fiends with actual ass parasites burrowing into their spinal cord causing them to act this way.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856322&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854715&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;getting taxed on money that doesn&amp;#x27;t exist yet&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856321&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856301&lt;br&gt;Kek. Would this work?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856310&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856293&lt;br&gt;used to live there, arabs are the worth, the destruction was planned long ago, slowly for surely invading the more civilized world&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856306&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854833&lt;br&gt;Are you implying the markets are somehow manipulated?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856303&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Monero solves this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856301&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From the last thread:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;make a shitcoin with an absurdly high number of coins, all minted at the start&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;before the first record date sell one to an anonymous alt account for 1 EUR&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Belastingdienst now thinks you ar ethe richest man on earth&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;between the first and second record date sell another coin for 0,01 EUR&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;your quadrillions of paper losses now count against the gains in your portfolio&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;0% tax for a year and get the hell out to the Antilles&lt;br&gt;(or sell another coin after the second record date for 1 EUR and watch the government try to press more taxes out of you that exist in the entire world economy for the lolz)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856293&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855207&lt;br&gt;They do care bro, people in the USA got their 401k, there&amp;#x27;s non of that here, here people rely 100% on the gob for their retirement. If you don&amp;#x27;t live in europe you have no idea how retarded the niggercattle locals are here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856292&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855199&lt;br&gt;40% of population in netherlands are niggers and arabs. In few decades they will be 80%. Economy route they are taking is completely irrelevant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856280&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peasants and serfs don&amp;#x27;t need to own/profit off investments, just put it in your ecb backed bank account and pay your taxes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856275&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856226&lt;br&gt;Why would they? They need to forcibly transfer all the speculative money into real estate. Boomers won&amp;#x27;t say no to that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856259&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;long weed, pharmaceutical and funeral stuff&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856233&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856226&lt;br&gt;someone has to be first anon. governments around the world are licking their lips with glee&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856232&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854767&lt;br&gt;Amsterdam Exchange.&lt;br&gt;They have some big companies like Shell where boomers probably have a lot cash of parked since they dividends.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856226&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854715&lt;br&gt;guys do you think there will be economic sanctions on the Netherlands?&lt;br&gt;i can&amp;#x27;t believe the rest of the world will just sit by when one country completely nukes their stock market. since the whole economy is connected, i could imagine the USA or other countries having a thing or two to say about this bs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855702&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Goes into effect in 2028, other first world nations will push to do the same around then. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The clock is officially ticking now. Only a few years left to make it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855272&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We got jewed in the &amp;#x27;golden age&amp;#x27; because of cheap labor and since then the coffers have been bleeding dry. the king is a traitor. some people love to grandstand about piet hein and muh VOC...... enjoy the past while you suffer at present&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855270&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854715&lt;br&gt;how does a society fall so fast?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855264&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855253&lt;br&gt;the germanic weakness to state propaganda combines with fascination with and fetishization of tribal cultures to create an abominable race&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855253&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855216&lt;br&gt;Aren&amp;#x27;t the dutch the most cucked people? Seems like half the dutch girls are with nafris or blacks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855240&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;anyway we can mail eerstekamer faggots, politely and nicely, they probably never get contacted unlike 2eK turbofags&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855235&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855216&lt;br&gt;indeed but 80% went along with covid, and you know what being in the &amp;lt;20% is like. only 15% buy equity here. that&amp;#x27;s why the only possible protest can come from a bunch of 0.01%&amp;#x27;ers. but they dont care because they can afford to buy ways out of the system. thats a flat rate, not a %. ie. spending 20k eur for an offshore setup is a nobrainer for them but not feasible for normal people&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded><enclosure url="https://i.4cdn.org/biz/1771100134377209s.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0" /></item><item><title>The EU is going full degen — 74 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61856214</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61856214</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 07:38:08 +0000</pubDate><description>Open article for full content</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;The EU is going full degen&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61856214'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 74&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856969&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856923&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;“Swedes have good reason to be thankful for the ISK account,” said Mohammed Salih, a 32-year-old communications manager who lives in Listerby in southern Sweden. He has invested with the system for more than 10 years. “I have always saved money and tried to build an economically stable future, but I didn’t know how to make the money grow.”&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Mohammed Salih&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;lives in southern Sweden&lt;br&gt;Stop giving niggers free shit? No let&amp;#x27;s force people to invest in our eu funded companies. I hope Trump disintegrate the EU soon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856966&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856223&lt;br&gt;How do I profit from this?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856961&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856668&lt;br&gt;The good part is that if and when whitey is reduced to nothing there will be absolutely no unity left. As if these fags will somehow have a society of cohesion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856960&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856896&lt;br&gt;Every single market crash since modern times is because of US overinflated companies. US tech companies are bubbles and their value is not rooted in any kind of reality - US stock performance is heavily dependent on a few mega-cap tech firms overinflated by degenerate jewish gamblers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856915&lt;br&gt;Stocks say almost nothing about economy in the first place.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seethe all you want but EU stock market is more attractive right now, which is the only point that I was making.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856953&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856463&lt;br&gt;You say it like a Nazi, but unfortunately Hitler would have NEVER let this much bullshit happen with Muslims. He&amp;#x27;d Holocaust 2: etc etc them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856946&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856885&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;$10 junk company goes to $20&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;check out this performance amerilard&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856943&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856363&lt;br&gt;thanks chatgpt&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856935&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856923&lt;br&gt;its very difficult to change your opinion on things once you are past a certain age especially when it comes to finance and your life savings. creating an incentive is good but its mostly for a new and younger generation which, in this financial environment, lacks the financial means to participate in the stock market to begin with. it will take decades before the eu sees noticiable changes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856923&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856774&lt;br&gt;https://www.businesstimes.com.sg/international/eu-sees-sweden-model-it-looks-encourage-investors&lt;br&gt;they were talking about this this past summer, so i assume this is what von der leyen is talking about. isk makes it easy for normies to buy stocks and with very low taxes. i don&amp;#x27;t know what the doomers itt are talking about, but making it easier for people to join the casino is a good thing for all of us, more money means higher prices on our bags. and a better euro economy overall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856915&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856885&lt;br&gt;And massively underperformed US stocks the past 20 years. Also you&amp;#x27;re ignoring the fact that the US Dollar lost 13% of its value compared to the Euro since last year. It&amp;#x27;s pretty easy to &amp;quot;outperform&amp;quot; the S&amp;amp;p500 when you&amp;#x27;re starting off with +13% gains over US assets right from the start. That says nothing about the quality of EU stocks or the EU economy though.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856900&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856214&lt;br&gt;Interesting. Because they&amp;#x27;re also moving towards taxation of unrealised gain on investments. So&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A. Forced to invest in turbo woke employers&lt;br&gt;B. Then taxed without even selling said investment &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m sure I remember people like the kkk mentioning some poppycock about&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;grandscale robbery&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;and other such nonsense at some point.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856896&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856885&lt;br&gt;thats great and all but 2-3 big7 companies alone are as big as the whole european market combined.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856885&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856699&lt;br&gt;yet outperformed US stocks in 2025 and 2026 so far too&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856862&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856542&lt;br&gt;Yeah no shit, dimwit. Thats why we kvetch about the EU all day that we cannot afford to heat our commieblock because of Uschi Vanderleyen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856857&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856214&lt;br&gt;guillotines&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856845&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856214&lt;br&gt;How? Infighting kills every venture the EU goes on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856826&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856363&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;If you want, I can also explain what the Savings and Investments Union would mean in practice and what concrete measures are being discussed.&lt;br&gt;go on then&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856814&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856792&lt;br&gt;thats dumb. I have even less faith in these shitty as places and like I said no one wants to move every few years, thats just straight up larp. yes you can hide your wealth but how do you explain the money once you want to convert it back into fiat. by hiding I assume mean cold wallets or pm. one of those things you cant move between countries so there is that. you cant run from the system, its global.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856800&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856418&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856774&lt;br&gt;Latvia has something called a &amp;quot;tier 3 pension pillar&amp;quot; but once your money goes in you cannot get it back no matter what until retirement and any capital gains are taxed at 25.5% when you start withdrawals.&lt;br&gt;If your employer matches your contributions from your AFTER tax wages the matching is taxed at 25.5% up front.&lt;br&gt;And you can only invest in managed funds that invest mostly in Latvian and E.U. bonds - so if the S&amp;amp;P is up 20% this year you will be up like 6%.&lt;br&gt;Americans have it good, especially with the Roth IRA.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856792&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856769&lt;br&gt;sea, south america for starters. cheap places where you can bribe your way. if not then simply become a neet, declare bankruptcy and hide your wealth, not only don&amp;#x27;t pay any taxes but ontop become a drain on the system funding you by their tax money lmao.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Or suffer, your choice. realize you play their game on their terms. personally i no longer participate they can go fuck themselve.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856776&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investment, aka giving the money to your pals&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856223&lt;br&gt;kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856774&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856418&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I really hope we get the euro equivalent of a 401k soon.&lt;br&gt;swedes have trading accounts (ISK) that are somewhat similar but their account is not necessarily for retirement and are very popular there. recently a swede was in my country (iceland) talking about this account. its something that would be nice to have. doing foreign investment here is rather bothersome. a foreign account like ibkr is needed and local banks have no online trades and 1% fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856769&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856758&lt;br&gt;move where? no country offers you 100% certainty. you almost always have to rely on the government to make rational decisions lol. no on wants to move like a bum every few years just to no get tax-raped to death because the government ran out of money.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856758&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;quite easy to understand, no? either move or become another burden&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856749&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856418&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Germany also has so many good companies you can&amp;#x27;t invest in because they are private.&lt;br&gt;Those companies are good because they&amp;#x27;re private&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856740&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856214&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;private savings&lt;br&gt;fuck fuck fuck they&amp;#x27;re going to take my money&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856725&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856214&lt;br&gt;Buddy, that is literally what US is doing tho.&lt;br&gt;When you put your savings into S&amp;amp;P500 you are investing in US economy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856714&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856418&lt;br&gt;Bankers can rob your 401k. Some companies force their employees into have them and make withdrawing any money from it a pain in the ass. If they start looting 401k&amp;#x27;s it could take days to recover yours. By then it might be too late.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856699&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856363&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;connect citizens’ savings with investments within the EU&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;looks inside EU stocks&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;shit that plummets to 0 in a couple of years&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;subsidized green energy bullshit&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;dying vehicle companies&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;penny stocks&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;banks&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;ASML is the only thing that is doing actually ok&lt;br&gt;hell no&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856692&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856393&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I want to see a modern bank run and for everyone to pull out at once&lt;br&gt;Computer says &amp;quot;no&amp;quot; and limits withdrawals&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded><enclosure url="https://i.4cdn.org/biz/1771141088339567s.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0" /></item><item><title>Big Boss Sergay — 55 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61845525</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61845525</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:49:45 +0000</pubDate><description>Open article for full content</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Big Boss Sergay&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61845525'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 55&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;https://x.com/chainlink/status/2022063428874252607&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856956&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850186&lt;br&gt;Skitzo bs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856952&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854760&lt;br&gt;kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854760&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61845539&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;David Schwimmer, CEO, LSEG&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61852968&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61852895&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61852901&lt;br&gt;the best part is that Chainlink themselves are acting like this is a much bigger deal than it is&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61852901&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61845588&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61845628&lt;br&gt;BREAKING: CEOS OF FAN DUEL AND DRAFTKINGS (not kidding) ANNOUNCED TO SAME!!!!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61852895&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61845525&lt;br&gt;OP acting like 30 other CEOs from crypto companies and others aren&amp;#x27;t also included.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61852227&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850186&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;God I&amp;#x27;m so happy for you.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shut the fuck up goddamit. Everytime this is posted Chainlink shits itself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61852225&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61846366&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61852216&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61848885&lt;br&gt;XRP Chads can&amp;#x27;t stop winning&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851137&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850888&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850911&lt;br&gt;checked&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850979&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850888&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;not worshipping king sergey&lt;br&gt;cringe, bro&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850911&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850186&lt;br&gt;Im starting to think something will happen on 2/16&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850888&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850186&lt;br&gt;whats this fucking king shit?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850422&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61845539&lt;br&gt;New Epstein client list just dropped&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850405&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850358&lt;br&gt;i broke you tho&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850358&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61846366&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849053&lt;br&gt;yikes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850186&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;21. Sergey Nazarov&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sergey&lt;br&gt;Six&lt;br&gt;21. S&lt;br&gt;216&lt;br&gt;Saturn&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;21&lt;br&gt;7+7+7&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;That list is not in alphabetical order. That was intentional. Kingmade. They had to throw in those other names to make it less obvious. God I&amp;#x27;m so happy for you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850124&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;how many of you are holding from $48?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849067&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61845539&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;you shouldn&amp;#x27;t have posted this list, it cheapens your &amp;quot;big&amp;quot; announcement by showing it&amp;#x27;s an empty gesture and already every grifter in the space is named&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;it&amp;#x27;s the equivalent of your job giving out &amp;quot;awards&amp;quot; to people instead of actual cash raises &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;congratulations jonny, you&amp;#x27;re our new process champion&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849053&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849003&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;see the last part &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;love how this advocate is so devoid of material he couldn&amp;#x27;t&amp;#x27; even read a few sentences of exchange &lt;br&gt;that&amp;#x27;s how hard i bodied him over the years&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE Cuckolds of crypto&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849003&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61848998&lt;br&gt;t. jeet from mumbai&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61848998&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;duuuuuuuuuuude the company i cheer for just made a COMMITTEE&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;umm ok what does that mean&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;duuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuude its LE SECRET&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;ok why are you telling me then&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;because duuuuuuuuuude you just understand how much money i&amp;#x27;ll make on link&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;holy shit are you holding that funding coin&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;duuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuude you&amp;#x27;re brown!!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;but you&amp;#x27;re literally standing next to me and can see i&amp;#x27;m white&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;duuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuude i&amp;#x27;m not falling for that, i&amp;#x27;m an elite autist!!!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61848943&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61848903&lt;br&gt;if you refused the corona hoax injection, youll refuse to be a slave. that is the type they fear; fear more than they love money&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61848903&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61848761&lt;br&gt;Nice meme, made me kek&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61848801&lt;br&gt;Do you think so? Im just an insignificant 2022 stacklet, but most anons would probably just buy a nice house, while others would overdose on cocaine and thai ladyboys...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61848885&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61845539&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Brad Garlinghouse, CEO, Ripple&lt;br&gt;Bullish for xrp&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61848834&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61848061&lt;br&gt;Fondness for the community&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61848801&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61848397&lt;br&gt;the only explanation for the link price is that theyre afraid of me and you, white men of /biz, and what we may do with money and power, not joking. without the years and years of suppression the token would be *at least* $200 by now&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61848776&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61845539&lt;br&gt;I just love how linkies conviently ignore Brad being up there with the rest of them&lt;br&gt;it really kills you retards, doesn&amp;#x27;t it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61848555&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61845525&lt;br&gt;kek&lt;br&gt;They are DESPERATE to save the old system with &amp;quot;le crypto solution layer&amp;quot;.&lt;br&gt;lmao&lt;br&gt;CL is shit and literally not needed at all for anything, but old, tech illiterate retards in the EU and SWIFT are at the end of their rope.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded><enclosure url="https://i.4cdn.org/biz/1770932985954628s.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0" /></item><item><title>Thread 61850016 — 48 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61850016</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61850016</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 17:50:43 +0000</pubDate><description>Open article for full content</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Thread 61850016&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61850016'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 48&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;know people with multiple six figures but never had a gf&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How is that even possible?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856970&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854408&lt;br&gt;This, kinda. &amp;quot;Size&amp;quot; here actually means proportion, or size relative to the rest of the body, not absolute. Reduce the fat everywhere, that will help with the perception of main body parts and overall. Become more athletic for endurance, that will help with expected sex endurance&lt;br&gt;Small woman with great proportions, or a woman with larger ass and larger tits yet she is way larger too?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855735&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850237&lt;br&gt;Why though? You can&amp;#x27;t beat toys when it comes to size / girth. 6.4 x 6.25 here, not coping just wanted to share&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855563&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61852036&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;falling in love with a woman&lt;br&gt;You need to stop that shit, immediately. Pairing because of love is the stupidest thing a man can do, just be glad she is taken so she doesn&amp;#x27;t have full control over you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855542&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850016&lt;br&gt;That&amp;#x27;s literally me&lt;br&gt;Also khhv&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855537&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850016&lt;br&gt;Just become a tutor for high schoolers, if you are in shape and not too old some horny chick will want to live out a fucking her teacher fantasy&lt;br&gt;source: me&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855221&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850105&lt;br&gt;6.5 x 5.5 here.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;i don&amp;#x27;t know because i don&amp;#x27;t have a small dick, i also haven&amp;#x27;t had sex in like 10 years lol. im 33 btw. only had sex with 2 girls, one was my ex the other was fuck meat. my ex told me i should be proud of my dick, fuck meat said my dick was thick, both said i stretched them out. I never really spent money on these girls, I attribute that to my dick.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854926&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850110&lt;br&gt;small&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854728&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854568&lt;br&gt;eternal honey pot&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854720&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854608&lt;br&gt;Holy based&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854713&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850093&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;cut your losses on fantasy like gf and marriage&lt;br&gt;been there, done that, regret will hit you hard in your 50s, but if you dont kys your fine afterwards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854704&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850016&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;d rather spend my money on an AI girlfriend, considering how women are these days. I even trust my cummingtonite more than an animal that bleeds for a whole week and doesn&amp;#x27;t die&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m still waiting for the day when robot wives are created&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854703&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850077&lt;br&gt;theres is nothing like rawdogging a woman, jerking off is just sad.&lt;br&gt;glad it works for you tho, and nice pepe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854663&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850016&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;How is that even possible?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;When women become a second job where you pay to work and potentially have your life destroyed on a whim, it becomes very possible.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;No it&amp;#x27;s not just in my head, two women could be having a full on conversation at a store and when they walk by where I&amp;#x27;m standing looking at some shit on the shelf they immediately shut up and you can feel them tense up like I&amp;#x27;m some kind of predator. It doesn&amp;#x27;t matter what age either except for old grannies. It&amp;#x27;s not just me, it&amp;#x27;s their reaction to any man they don&amp;#x27;t know in general.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854645&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854408&lt;br&gt;truth nuke&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854608&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850016&lt;br&gt;Betabuxxing is an outdated strategy. &lt;br&gt;The assumption was always that women naturally wanted to be mothers.&lt;br&gt;What we have learned is that when given the freedom, women will chose to do anything other than be mothers. &lt;br&gt;The assumption tied into myths about female purity and feminine &amp;quot;caring&amp;quot; natures. &lt;br&gt;We are learning that such a thing was strictly socially enforced and doesn&amp;#x27;t actually exist as an emergent property of women.&lt;br&gt;In other words real women have not been invented yet. Foids (men with tits) are an outdated technology that we are rapidly replacing with genetic sciences and robotics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854568&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;women are mossad agents&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854408&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850105&lt;br&gt;I am pretty inexperienced with women, but my theory is that a her perception of the size is what matters more than the actual size. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The female mind doesn’t really relate to reality directly, there is a buffer, in between themselves and reality and that is their emotional state. This state can massively shift their experience of the same objective thing. Like, if a woman is in love with you, then your dick becomes massive in her eyes, but when the feelings fade, it becomes small. Men have this too but to a much lesser extent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854346&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850310&lt;br&gt;Height &amp;gt; frame &amp;gt; face &amp;gt; charisma &amp;gt; status &amp;gt; money&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61852199&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850016&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s about genetics, not money&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61852198&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850077&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;jacking off in the morning&lt;br&gt;suboptimal, you&amp;#x27;ll feel tired for work&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61852193&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850105&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yes lol. I’ve listened to women absolutely THRASH the dick size of their exes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61852056&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Women are fucking expensive&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61852036&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I don’t show off my wealth, most people would assume I have $1000 to my name. In my day-to-day life I engage with 3 women my age who are all in long term relationships. I’m deeply in love with one of them. I’m also socially awkward and probably low test, and broken minded from long term 4chan browsing. &lt;br&gt;Average height, average weight, average dick. Despise fat chicks (phisically and morally).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851627&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850052&lt;br&gt;i didn&amp;#x27;t realize until much later but i likely have borderline autism and borderline schizoid PD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851626&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850081&lt;br&gt;I bet your parents are wishing that you had.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850479&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since 2023 I have been mostly living off credit (while paying obligatory monthly bills) and putting free cash into investments that I thought would push me from 15k to 1 million. Turns out unless you&amp;#x27;re going hard on high risk stuff, this is very hard. I recently realized my credit to assets ratio is now unfavorable and thus have to grind for the next bullrun so I can make it. Keep gambling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850429&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850110&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;small tits&lt;br&gt;small&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850105&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850030&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;thick big dicks&lt;br&gt;this take fucking sucks because i have a huge dick and hookers hate it not to mention that i literally cant get sex without paying for it&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;big dick is a fucking meme and i would give up my huge cock for a more attractive face&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850310&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850293&lt;br&gt;This. They can&amp;#x27;t see your balance sheet. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I was one of those dudes basically invisible at $0 and the same at $1.2 and $1.5 million. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Face is huge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850293&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Money doesn&amp;#x27;t mean shit in terms of girls being interested in you unless you literally drive around in a neon green lambo.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s not like girls magically jump on your dick the moment your networth hits a million or whatever&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850274&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850016&lt;br&gt;That is precisely why they have six figs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded><enclosure url="https://i.4cdn.org/biz/1771005043719921s.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0" /></item><item><title>Money doesn't buy happiness — 34 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61855335</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61855335</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 23:35:01 +0000</pubDate><description>Open article for full content</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Money doesn&amp;#x27;t buy happiness&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61855335'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 34&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;When you make it you&amp;#x27;re still gonna be a virgin incel. The only difference is you&amp;#x27;ll have $10 million in the bank that you won&amp;#x27;t even spend since your only hobbies are 4chud and pirating PC games.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856948&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855335&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;When you make it you&amp;#x27;re still gonna be a virgin incel.&lt;br&gt;Correct, and I&amp;#x27;m happy with that&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The only difference is you&amp;#x27;ll have $10 million in the bank that you won&amp;#x27;t even spend since your only hobbies are 4chud and pirating PC games.&lt;br&gt;Correct, but I won&amp;#x27;t have to work.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t get it, are you trying to demoralize or lift me up?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856941&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855335&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Laughs in going to a country with a debased and devalued currency&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lol nigger&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856924&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855804&lt;br&gt;You don&amp;#x27;t have to repeat the same thing twice in one sentence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856683&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855356&lt;br&gt;7 figures to 5 is rough. I&amp;#x27;ve done 7 to 6 to various extent multiple times and am back to 6 now again, thought I was in multiple 7s a few months ago. I just feel there&amp;#x27;s more to come but of course knowing what I know now, I have regrets. But investing in retrospect is the easiest thing ever.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856663&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855335&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t care about being a extra virgin incel, all I care about is escaping the hell that is wageslaving. Let me read books and play video games and go for long walks and the rest of the world can fuck off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856107&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855335&lt;br&gt;but with a nice pc and a comfortable chair&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855804&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855561&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;That nigger bitch is vile&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855799&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855775&lt;br&gt;ngmi&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855784&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855775&lt;br&gt;ngmi&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855775&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;My father just died one year after he retired from ALS. He was extremely jewish with his money, and never did anything fun. Now my mom has it all. You need to cultivate something along the way. Everyone thinks they will live to at least 80 even though that probably won&amp;#x27;t be the case. Don&amp;#x27;t waste your life waiting for the moment you are imagining will turn it all around. It might pass you by forever&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855754&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855335&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s true. Sometimes I get down about work and money. But at the end of the day I have a roof over my head, food in the fridge, and a girl who loves me and sucks my dick on command. Just having those three things makes me a rich man. Happiness is a mindset.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855746&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855335&lt;br&gt;get back in the fucking cage, wagie&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855740&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855335&lt;br&gt;Money might not buy happiness. But it ends unhappiness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855728&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855335&lt;br&gt;Try buying food with happiness, retard.&lt;br&gt;You sound like a retarded cunt, who everyone else is talking care of.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855727&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;QUIRKED UP WHITE BOY WITH A LITTLE BIT OF SWAGGER&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855561&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855335&lt;br&gt;White rizzler goated with the sauce while shanequa thirsts for that bwc&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855550&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;you just KNOW this girl fell for the dancing chud&lt;br&gt;look at her face and how much she is smiling by grinding herself all over him&lt;br&gt;this chud did the impossible&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855547&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855335&lt;br&gt;Fuck he&amp;#x27;s good&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855543&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855335&lt;br&gt;Money definitely buys happiness when I was rich I had a great diet and workout regimen now that I am back to wage cucking I am a alcoholic cocaine addict&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855533&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855335&lt;br&gt;I an incel who only ever banged 7 hookers (thank god no STDs) but having 10 million would very much better my life. I don’t care if I still can’t get a gf, at very least I can be comfy and take care of my parents and help my nephews and nieces.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Also if I really wanted to I could just be upfront with a bitch and make an arrangement where she gives me kids and I provide for her if I wanted children of my own&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855484&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855335&lt;br&gt;it&amp;#x27;s interesting how some people look like they just aren&amp;#x27;t meant to be dancers&lt;br&gt;bless that dude for trying though&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855473&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855461&lt;br&gt;you know nothing about me faggot. he&amp;#x27;ll never see 4 million again in his life I guarantee it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855465&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yeah well 10k sure would make me a lot more happy than I am now, my friend died this morning, plus I&amp;#x27;m broke and it&amp;#x27;s raining.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855461&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855377&lt;br&gt;There is a reason he made all that money snd you didn&amp;#x27;t. It&amp;#x27;s the same reason he will again while you do not.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855456&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855362&lt;br&gt;Just do push ups snd sit ups daily fatty. All you need to do is more than you do now. So I guess 2 sets is plenty. The hardest part is starting and you&amp;#x27;ve created s gigacope excuse that you cannot get your fat ass on the floor doing push ups until you own a ranch. Unless you weight 17 tonnes and need a barn to lay down, I think you&amp;#x27;re being a faggot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855377&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855372&lt;br&gt;no you can&amp;#x27;t lmao&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855372&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855358&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855363&lt;br&gt;I have done it once I can do it again&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855363&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855358&lt;br&gt;This. &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855356 if that it isn&amp;#x27;t a LARP you fucked up big time. You&amp;#x27;ll likely never see the kind of money again in your life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855362&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855348&lt;br&gt;Forgive me but I&amp;#x27;m a depressed fatass that can&amp;#x27;t lose weight while living with mom. The only thing I&amp;#x27;ll do when I make it is buy a ranch and do keto omad until my titties are gone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855358&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855356&lt;br&gt;It could have made you autistic and retired.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;But now you&amp;#x27;ll wage away for the rest of your life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded><enclosure url="https://i.4cdn.org/biz/1771112101370155s.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0" /></item></channel></rss>