<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>/biz/ Active (filtered, with replies)</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/</link><description>Filtered out: general, gme, bbbyq. OP + first 3 replies + last 30 replies.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:32:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>When did you realize that you were NOT going to make it? — 51 replies — 204.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61862922</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61862922?lm=1771342300</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:31:40 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;When did you realize that you were NOT going to make it?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61862922'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 51 • Updated: 2026-02-17 15:31 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862935&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;is he ok&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862944&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862935&lt;br&gt;just some minor scratches (on his brain)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862956&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;the funniest part is that you think &amp;quot;maybe he survived the crash, just barely&amp;quot; but then it erupts in flames and he&amp;#x27;s cooked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863924&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863681&lt;br&gt;I hate to admit it but ever since the documents were released, I&amp;#x27;ve been feeling absolutely despondent. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I would just like to know if all that crap about satan, moloch worship, demons, etc., it&amp;#x27;s just like a game because they simply like to eat and torture babies or do those entities really exist. I guess if demons really exist, God might exist too. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the end, I am a goy and I will have to deal with shit in the real world. I would probably end up roping. I&amp;#x27;m poor and my parents are already starting to forget shit. The next years are gonna be hell.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863947&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863681&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863899&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863924&lt;br&gt;I can&amp;#x27;t imagine letting agitprop like that affect your life in any meaningful way. Get a grip on reality for fuck&amp;#x27;s sake. Fucking pathetic losers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Imagine being a &amp;quot;conspiracy theorist&amp;quot; and trusting everything fed to you by people that hate you and want to fuck with your well-being. You idiot cattle deserve to be mindraped like the slaves you are.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863976&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863529&lt;br&gt;its a retarded zoomer on a bike, it happens everywhere&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864092&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863183&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s for emergency vehicles, and also emergency stops in case of engine trouble for the cars on the road. It&amp;#x27;s not bad design, it&amp;#x27;s an essential safety feature.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864128&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863240&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;virgin&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;bent over&lt;br&gt;ain&amp;#x27;t no virgins doing nothing but missionary the first time&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864155&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;In the DMV handbook, they advise matching the flow of the traffic. Going to fast or too slow relative to traffic will result in accidents like this. If you match the flow of traffic, you can more easily take evasive maneuvers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864158&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why didn&amp;#x27;t the white car give way to him? You can&amp;#x27;t just turn in front of someone like that, it&amp;#x27;s dangerous.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864207&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;the fire looks so fake and gay it&amp;#x27;s not even funny anymore&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864461&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864092&lt;br&gt;Then it&amp;#x27;s 100% the motorcyclist’s fault.&lt;br&gt;The picture only confused me because where I live, roads like that always have a center barrier separating the lanes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864540&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864461&lt;br&gt;How are you supposed to pass on two way highways?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864595&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863976&lt;br&gt;This, America just couldn&amp;#x27;t afford mass surveillance before. Soon, total Amerimutt death will flood teh interwebz&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864624&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864540&lt;br&gt;This is how it should be done safely. There’s a median barrier, a shoulder, an acceleration lane at entries, and a deceleration lane at exits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864646&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864595&lt;br&gt;America had plenty of money for this sorta shit, it was just rejected by Joe Citizen as unnecessary Big Brother. They even put up cameras at all the traffic points in my shithole Missouri town to issue tickets, until people got fed up. Now they just sit there deactivated.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Of course now that MIGA is running the country for Big Corp, everyone is embracing Big Brother to &amp;quot;own teh libz&amp;quot; and trannies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864685&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;Watching link refuse to pump over the last 2 years made me certain, but I had an inkling in late 2021.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864687&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864699&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863924&lt;br&gt;Reap or not you have to understand 2 things:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;the pedo elite (redundant, there are no non-pedo elite) believe in this shit HARD. If you know your enemies motivations, you can outmaneuver them&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;we currently inhabit this material plane, largely outside the strong harmonic influences of what we would call gods. Just don&amp;#x27;t be such a conniving piece of shit when you can help it&lt;br&gt;Don&amp;#x27;t over think it, anon.&lt;br&gt;Yes, I know I misused greentext; leave it alone, well poisoners&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864709&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Driving in hard shoulder&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Driving way too fast&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Slamming on the brakes causing you to front flip&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Not trying to switch lane&lt;br&gt;Darwin award.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864714&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863183&lt;br&gt;you&amp;#x27;re not supposed to drive there&lt;br&gt;play stupid games, win stupid prices&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864734&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863411&lt;br&gt;When I got my permit in the EU the first evasion maneuver you learn is the quick jerking of the handle to swerve and avoid this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864738&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863681&lt;br&gt;Should we just back china then?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is this the only way to topple the status quo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864767&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;Why do you care what other people are thinking? Does it hurt your feelings when Jesus leaves you on read? You still don&amp;#x27;t have to be atheist.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864769&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864709&lt;br&gt;not starting with &amp;gt;riding a motorcycle&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864775&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;I BOUGHT SHINY ROCK @ $120 &lt;br&gt;BIZ TOLD ME IT WAS GOING TO $5000 EOY&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864842&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864092&lt;br&gt;No it&amp;#x27;s not dumbass. Nearly all roads in Asia are like this and they all have motorbikes that drive on it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864852&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864842&lt;br&gt;Well then it&amp;#x27;s a retarded design if you have to give way to vehicles turning every 2 seconds - and it has no markings to indicate as such.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864870&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;That finishing final destination touch&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865341&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864842&lt;br&gt;Just because people abuse the emergency lane it illegal doesn&amp;#x27;t mean that&amp;#x27;s what it is designed for.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865399&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862935&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;he&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865412&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864842&lt;br&gt;they have roads where motorcycles try to front brake doing 70mph? lol, this chink deserved what he got, like it or not.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865437&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s not tragic to die doing what you love&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>$ICP just partnered with the government of Pakistan — 45 replies — 100.2/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61850558</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61850558?lm=1771340736</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:05:36 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;$ICP just partnered with the government of Pakistan&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61850558'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 45 • Updated: 2026-02-17 15:05 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=r-RmZyeuxzo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850566&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;ICY PEE PARTNERS WITH POO &lt;br&gt;so the prophecy was right icy pee poo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850573&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850566&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;WITH POO&lt;br&gt;You mean one of the most populated countries on planet Earth? Seethe more linky retard and kill yourself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850584&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850558&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I can tell this is hogwash because it&amp;#x27;s news anouncement via Youtube.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851240&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851054&lt;br&gt;Upset because of what? Because the icp devs bribes some pakistani to announce some bullshit on twitter?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851416&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851240&lt;br&gt;Why open your mouth when you don&amp;#x27;t know what you&amp;#x27;re saying?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851738&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850558&lt;br&gt;i&amp;#x27;ve been to the world computer summit in june last year and i&amp;#x27;ve talked to anyone in the team that i came across. let me tell you one thing; they&amp;#x27;re comfortable. they all get hundreds of thousands in salaries each year and could not care less about the price. at the event there were two very clear very seperate pockets. the VC&amp;#x27;s and the (((COMMUNITY))) and you could see the disgust in the eyes of the VC&amp;#x27;s for the community. any questions regarding tech or details to the team were answered dismissively, there is not an ounce of passion present in the entire team. i think all they care about is doing research on cryptography.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; i&amp;#x27;ve met the guy from openchat and he looked like he hadn&amp;#x27;t slept a full 8h in several weeks, he looked anxious and stressed.&lt;br&gt;when talking to the community members i&amp;#x27;ve probed for interesting projects, and literally the best project present was windoge98.&lt;br&gt;after that dominic played with an llm on stage for an hour straight everyone pretended it&amp;#x27;s the second coming of steve jobs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;they gave away bags of coffee because of caffeine.ai and it was unironically the best thing at the event. so good i even thought about licensing the coffee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851740&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851040&lt;br&gt;So Pakistanis are now jeets too?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851814&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850926&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;ppl&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851833&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851416&lt;br&gt;Im just guessing&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851740&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;So Pakistanis are now jeets too?&lt;br&gt;???? Always were. Bangladesh and Sri lanka too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61852144&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850558&lt;br&gt;The Saarnet&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61852793&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850584&lt;br&gt;Don&amp;#x27;t know about this one but poos did sign many crypto deals with trump. Ironically crypto has been dumping since&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853251&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851833&lt;br&gt;Pakistanis are white&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853281&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;61853251&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853296&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850611&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;AI licenses&lt;br&gt;So this is a thirdie government jumping the gun and getting in the way of something that people aren&amp;#x27;t doing yet to make sure that they don&amp;#x27;t start, just so they can take a cut if anyone dares to try. Classic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853824&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853296&lt;br&gt;Man shut the fuck up, you sound like a bitch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853832&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853281&lt;br&gt;racist&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853871&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850642&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850740&lt;br&gt;pakistans hate indians tho, its actually p based&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853919&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853871&lt;br&gt;Only Indians can be jeets, end of&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854123&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851738&lt;br&gt;This checks out with my impression of DFINITY. They are extremely arrogant and have borderline disdain for their own users. And honestly the Pakistan news is demoralizing. Yes the tech is great but God damn I am down by about $50K. And mission 70 is not the solution -- gaining adoption is.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854128&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850558&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853824&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853832&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853919&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;SARR PAKISTANIS ARE WHITE SARR&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854229&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For some reason I misread that as plundered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854266&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854128&lt;br&gt;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/India%E2%80%93Pakistan_relations&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854891&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854128&lt;br&gt;Pakistanis are more white than an average American lol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854914&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850566&lt;br&gt;holy kek..&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857209&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850566&lt;br&gt;witnessed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860272&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854914&lt;br&gt;you kek at racism?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860593&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850558&lt;br&gt;ICPoo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860624&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850558&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;internet &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;computer&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;holy kek - only for Pookistani this might sound exotic and alluring&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861733&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850558&lt;br&gt;icp parterned with pakistan? well fuckin whoop whoop my brothers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862328&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854123&lt;br&gt;clanker hands typed this post&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863387&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851738&lt;br&gt;I was there too and have a slightly different view. Dfinity devs care about their work, upper management is the problem. Literally biggest official event ever and Dom was nowhere to be seen other than when he larped as tech visionary on stage. Btw applauses were scripted, they were all started by Dom&amp;#x27;s yes men, if you watch back the presentation it&amp;#x27;s obvious.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many good people were let go due to price action and poor leadership&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865248&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862328&lt;br&gt;despite my use of the em dash i am 100% a real person that is down $50K usd on icp&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>stock market: allocation and frequency — 14 replies — 43.1/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61862099</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61862099?lm=1771341184</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:13:04 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;stock market: allocation and frequency&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61862099'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 14 • Updated: 2026-02-17 15:13 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Am I insane foe wanting to invest in 50 different comapnies and 3 ETFs? Am I overdoing it? Or should i just choose sector ETFs instead of companies to reduce my list.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Also how often should I invest per year to reduce overall commission costs? Quarterly? Is there a way on IBKR to place a basket order so I only pay for one trade across multiple stocks?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862142&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;50 is too much, portfolio theory says around 20-30 before it&amp;#x27;s not worth it and I would lean towards the smaller number&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862144&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862099&lt;br&gt;In general it&amp;#x27;s better to bet on something broader than something more specific. As long as the sector grows you&amp;#x27;ll grow but a company can easily fail even if the product or the sector is wanted. When I was younger I invested in Nikola because I thought I would be hedging against Tesla. Turns out the company was a mess and people don&amp;#x27;t care that they&amp;#x27;re sucked dry by Elon. I still believe EVs will be more important for long haul and business use.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862220&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862144&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I invested in Nikola because I thought I would be hedging against Tesla. Turns out the company was a mess and people don&amp;#x27;t care that they&amp;#x27;re sucked dry by Elon&lt;br&gt;you thought the ceo who would go on to lead tsla to a 20x was sucking they company dry so instead you put your money into an obvious scam whose CEO would go on to be arrested for securities and wire fraud? Where do you do your research, the daily show???&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862273&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Translation: &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;PLEASE GOD STOP DUMPING MICROSOFT AHHHHHHHH&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862287&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862142&lt;br&gt;Why?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862313&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862099&lt;br&gt;https://investcalc.github.io/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862329&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862220&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;you thought the ceo who would go on to lead tsla to a 20x was sucking they company dry&lt;br&gt;No stop trying to twist the words on my screen. Elon is milking his customer base and its obvious and apparent to everyone. I thought people would notice that and move to a better car manufacturer. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;whose CEO would go on to be arrested for securities and wire fraud?&lt;br&gt;Hindsight is 20/20&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Where do you do your research, the daily show???&lt;br&gt;I invested long before any of the scandals came to be and the focus on long haul makes sense for as long as we don&amp;#x27;t have a sufficient hydrogen infrastructure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862353&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862099&lt;br&gt;Can he take one picture where he doesn&amp;#x27;t look like a slimeball piece of shit? Just one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862425&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862287&lt;br&gt;MPT claims you can only diversify away idiosyncratic (company specific) risk, and at some point you have so many different companies and exposure to so many different sectors that adding another company doesn&amp;#x27;t reduce risk by much if at all. I think markowitz or sharpe has a mathematical proof on it out there somewhere. Apparently they say that number is around 20-30&lt;br&gt;I say lean towards less because you have to take into consideration transaction costs and time and energy spent reorganizing your portfolio and tracking your positions as well. If you&amp;#x27;re just an average person and not a portfolio manager getting paid you&amp;#x27;re probably just fine with 12-15&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862458&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862099&lt;br&gt;the idea of diversifying is reducing the volatility of your portfolio value, if you want to do it properly you should study the correlations between your picks, this has a cost of reducing the potential gains but they become more steady. For example if you pick 50 tech companies and etfs and the ai bubble bursts, the stocks are so highly correlated between them that all of them would go down at the same time and diversifying would be useless, even if between your picks you picked the one tech company that survives&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864023&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;My strategy was to invest in a new company every month&lt;br&gt;Guess I&amp;#x27;m retarded...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864325&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864023&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The average diversified portfolio holds between 20 and 30 stocks, but could have even more. The Motley Fool&amp;#x27;s position is that investors should own 25 or more different stocks. Diversifying your portfolio in the stock market is a good idea for investors because it decreases risk by ensuring that no single company has too much influence over the value of your holdings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864389&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862099&lt;br&gt;You will have the slowest and most ass returns.&lt;br&gt;Only do this if you are interested in your retirement situation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865302&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862099&lt;br&gt;I have over 200 stocks and about a dozen etfs. I have the stocks because I enjoy looking at all the little dividend payments. I am also beating the market so there is that. Sometimes one of my picks does a 10x and that makes up for the ones that -50%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Are there ANY good job boards left besides fucking LinkedIn by Microslop?? — 7 replies — 20.5/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61864195</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61864195?lm=1771341123</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:12:03 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Are there ANY good job boards left besides fucking LinkedIn by Microslop??&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61864195'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 7 • Updated: 2026-02-17 15:12 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Are there ANY good job boards left besides fucking LinkedIn by Microslop??&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864202&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LinkedIn is complete dogshit so I guess not.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864249&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864195&lt;br&gt;I got my job off a posting on Handshake&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864299&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864195&lt;br&gt;I honestly don&amp;#x27;t believe anyone is getting jobs on linkedin anymore. Nobody.&lt;br&gt;I tried almost 2 years and sent hundreds upon hundreds of applications.&lt;br&gt;Fake jobs.&lt;br&gt;AI fake recruiters.&lt;br&gt;All bullshit man.&lt;br&gt;I got my job off a local job board finally.&lt;br&gt;LinkedIn has only one use to find you a job: post to your hundreds of connections asking if anyone can refer you to a job. It&amp;#x27;s a networking site.&lt;br&gt;I add the maximum number of connections every week in my industry targeted at companies I might want to work for in the future.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864306&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864195&lt;br&gt;LinkedIn is full of indians&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865108&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864249&lt;br&gt;handshake.firm&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865182&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Believe it or not, careerbuilder. it’s jam packed with indians but once a week I got a good lead from a mag7 recruiter and one of them hired me&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865294&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864195&lt;br&gt;80% of job openings are fake and just HRM wasting everyone&amp;#x27;s time.&lt;br&gt;19.999999% of jobs go to nepo hire scum, so you never had a chance anyways.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Its so OVER for crypto! — 4 replies — 15.2/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61864565</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61864565?lm=1771341404</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:16:44 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Its so OVER for crypto!&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61864565'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 4 • Updated: 2026-02-17 15:16 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865291&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Im going to KILL MYSELF RIGHT NOW!!!!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865324&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;so long gay bowser&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865329&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864565&lt;br&gt;holy shit guys this meme arrow also just popped up in my chart. what&amp;#x27;s going on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865334&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865324&lt;br&gt;Kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>PLEASE MAKE IT FUCKING STOP — 5 replies — 11.1/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61865162</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61865162?lm=1771340727</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:05:27 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;PLEASE MAKE IT FUCKING STOP&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61865162'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 5 • Updated: 2026-02-17 15:05 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;PLEASE MAKE IT FUCKING STOP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865166&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ACCEPT THE DEAL YOU BALD HEADED PRICK&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865174&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;sell now nigga its just going lower&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865177&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You should have apologized to dan pena now you lose everything&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865188&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865162&lt;br&gt;you&amp;#x27;re profiting in BTC anon, just buy more!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865247&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865162&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;buy the dip&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;bro there is literally no more flesh on my skeleton&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>NIGGER LIFE — 7 replies — 10.4/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61863888</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61863888?lm=1771339922</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 14:52:02 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;NIGGER LIFE&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61863888'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 7 • Updated: 2026-02-17 14:52 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;PUMP... AND DUMP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863890&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;it&amp;#x27;s over for buttcoin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863896&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863888&lt;br&gt;SUPER NIGGER GALAXY&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863903&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Looks fine to me&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864134&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863888&lt;br&gt;NIGGER CZ!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864323&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NIGGER NIGGER&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865150&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IT&amp;#x27;S JUST ONE THOSE DAYS WHEN YOU DON&amp;#x27;T WANNA WAKE UP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>/smg/ - Stock Market Gambling — 380 replies — 1184.4/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861684</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861684?lm=1771341198</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:13:18 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;/smg/ - Stock Market Gambling&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861684'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 380 • Updated: 2026-02-17 15:13 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Casino Economy Edition&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Some helpful links to numb the pain&lt;br&gt;https://findahelpline.com/&lt;br&gt;https://www.nvidia.com/refunds/&lt;br&gt;https://www.whitehouse.gov/refunds&lt;br&gt;https://jlingz.com/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Educational sites:&lt;br&gt;https://www.investopedia.com&lt;br&gt;https://www.khanacademy.org/economics-finance-domain&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Financial TV Streams:&lt;br&gt;https://www.newslive.com/american/cnbc.html&lt;br&gt;https://www.livestreamy.net/bloomberg/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Charts:&lt;br&gt;https://www.tradingview.com&lt;br&gt;https://www.finscreener.com&lt;br&gt;https://www.portfoliovisualizer.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Screeners: so you feel like in the movies&lt;br&gt;https://finviz.com/&lt;br&gt;https://etfdb.com/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Gambling:&lt;br&gt;https://www.optionsplaybook.com/options-introduction/&lt;br&gt;https://www.optionsprofitcalculator.com&lt;br&gt;https://optionstrat.com/&lt;br&gt;https://www.optionistics.com/quotes/option-prices&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Pre-Market and Live data:&lt;br&gt;https://www.investing.com/indices/indices-futures&lt;br&gt;https://finance.yahoo.com/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Calendars&lt;br&gt;https://www.marketwatch.com/economy-politics/calendar&lt;br&gt;https://www.earningswhispers.com/calendar&lt;br&gt;https://www.cmegroup.com/trading/interest-rates/countdown-to-fomc.html&lt;br&gt;https://www.mortgagenewsdaily.com/data/building-permits&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Boomer Investing 101: so zoomers with meme stocks can outperform you&lt;br&gt;https://www.bogleheads.org/wiki/Getting_started&lt;br&gt;https://www.sec.gov/search-filings&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Misc smg:&lt;br&gt;https://www.financialjuice.com/home&lt;br&gt;https://finance.yahoo.com/trending-tickers&lt;br&gt;https://market24hclock.com/&lt;br&gt;https://www.dividendchannel.com/drip-returns-calculator&lt;br&gt;https://brokerchooser.com/&lt;br&gt;https://www.chathamfinancial.com/technology/us-market-rates&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Previously on /smg/: &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858740&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861716&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m an American, I have extreme anxiety that i can&amp;#x27;t sell or buy right now&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;so me, and my fellow americans formally decided were panic selling everything Tuesday&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;sorry euros&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861738&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861716&lt;br&gt;i just watch the spot silver chart and get either mad or relieved when it doesnt move very far from 75&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864779&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This europoor just bought 70k USD worth of a global index fund and an ex-USA fund. Feel sick desu but I can’t sit on this cash forever&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864791&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864756&lt;br&gt;I dunno... what portion of nearly 50% of John Q Investor&amp;#x27;s assets are going to go into gold after he capitulates between now and August?&lt;br&gt;What is it they were saying 6 months ago? 60/20/20?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864794&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864791&lt;br&gt;forgot pic&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864805&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864588&lt;br&gt;enjoy your anal lysis&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864818&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;it&amp;#x27;s over.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864862&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;anyone know how to get fidelity to display my port value in premarket it doesn&amp;#x27;t update until market open and i need to aaaaaaaaaaahhhhhh more accurately right now&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864869&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864862&lt;br&gt;Have you tried to do math, you nigger gorilla?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864875&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864869&lt;br&gt;shiet wypipo be making computers hard to learn and shit to keep the black man down&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864876&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861707&lt;br&gt;ETOR&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864877&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864750&lt;br&gt;LEMEOW&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864887&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862034&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862207&lt;br&gt;DOSH&lt;br&gt;LOADS O MONE&lt;br&gt;SMG BTFO AGAIN&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864895&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864887&lt;br&gt;ok but how does that affect you personally?&lt;br&gt;post your profits big boy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864940&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864877&lt;br&gt;That&amp;#x27;s your 47% tariff doing it&amp;#x27;s job&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864953&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864895&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;GME baggie coping&lt;br&gt;go back to your containment thread&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864962&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ready for the bloodbath?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864974&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;soxl down 10%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864975&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;everyone&amp;#x27;s expecting it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864982&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The nurse at the psychs office called after out appointment today saying she was worried about me and asked if I wanted to get institutionalized.&lt;br&gt;While on one hand it feels good that someone cares about me, fuck no give me pills to survive [society] or stfu.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;what are the market implicaitons of this?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864986&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864777&lt;br&gt;I hope you guys bought hopium when I said. up another 20%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865002&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864982&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;asked if I wanted to get institutionalized&lt;br&gt;newby here. is this common in finance?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865011&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864411&lt;br&gt;hi bob&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865015&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865002&lt;br&gt;if you aren&amp;#x27;t getting wellness checks from the county health system or your female broker you probably aren&amp;#x27;t taking enough risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865028&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALL HANDS ON DECK&lt;br&gt;GET READY TO DEPLOY THOSE V&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865049&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865002&lt;br&gt;Yes. Saying &amp;quot;getting balls deep in leverage to see green or red numbers is the only thing that makes me feel anything&amp;quot; was the wrong answer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865127&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Well my mining portfolio has just been raped&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865178&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;jesus christ&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865184&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;bought google at 300 &lt;br&gt;how bad of an idea was that?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865241&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864986&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864777&lt;br&gt;Hopium currently up 324%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865274&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is today the day to slurp google&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865308&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865274&lt;br&gt;For me it&amp;#x27;s XOM&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Privacy Coins — 66 replies — 161.1/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61849447</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61849447?lm=1771340878</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:07:58 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Privacy Coins&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61849447'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 66 • Updated: 2026-02-17 15:07 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whether you like it or not, BTC is dying. Which way anons?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849481&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gold and silver.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849898&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849447&lt;br&gt;XMR as always. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849481&lt;br&gt;Acceptable but unusable for internet transactions and too easily stolen. Also makes smaller or spontaneous transactions harder unless the governments were to issue gold coins again and that would be bearish.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849958&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849447&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;BTC is a pedo coin&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;most used currency for CP is not however&lt;br&gt;quit the infighting, monegro.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862129&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849481&lt;br&gt;aggressively low IQ take on the left&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862460&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861669&lt;br&gt;l knew if i waited Iong enough, the bot wouId show. You cant foIIow any post and its repIies worth a damn. ldk why you keep bring up the same shit spamming it everywhere. l wish jannies wouId range ban your ass.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;No, we just despise you nerva shills. ... And then you just all seem to bring up, out of nowhere and completely unrelated of course, the solution which is an unmaintained jeetcoin with a ring size less than 1/3 of Monero&amp;#x27;s ring size and none of the development Monero received since 2018&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Wrong, nervajeet&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Preferable to jeets on discord&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Because we don&amp;#x27;t tolerate jeetcoins? lol&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Are you seriously claiming that nerva wasn&amp;#x27;t mentioned at all in the last three generals?&lt;br&gt;Cant fucking follow a conversation worth shit, you dumb bot code gets so mixed up between threads you think everyone is a nervjeet or whatever the fucking you keep going on about.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Says someone defending the literal jeetcoin, how ironic.&lt;br&gt;Niggerbot who brings up nerva in every thread he spams to(&amp;lt;- thats you, no one mentions nerva BUT you)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862129&lt;br&gt;super genius is blind to anything regarding esptein emails, even tho this shit has been identified for years.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861976&lt;br&gt;actually kind of funny, didnt even notice my id&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862475&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849447&lt;br&gt;How do I buy Monero without leaving a KYC trace?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I can&amp;#x27;t buy XMR directly on exchanges (UK). If I buy BTC -&amp;gt; the tax man can see I have BTC and will expect to see a &amp;quot;sell&amp;quot; at some point.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tried Bisq, but hardly any sellers and also a risk of your bank account getting flagged / closed if the person is dodgy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862494&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862460&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;the bot wouId show.&lt;br&gt;How come you didn&amp;#x27;t know this when I posted &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849898? Maybe you need to refine your instincts or could it be that all of your anti-Monero arguments are moot so you try to attack me? &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862460&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Cant fucking follow a conversation worth shit,&lt;br&gt;I directly replied to all of your points. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Niggerbot who brings up nerva in every thread he spams to(&amp;lt;- thats you, no one mentions nerva BUT you)&lt;br&gt;How come you always use this excuse when you got the pic from a nervajeet in the XMR general?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862530&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849447&lt;br&gt;Monero is the only privacy coin.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Any other digital asset is traceable.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You have 1 (one) more opportunity for an early Bitcoin moment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Monero will be the world currency of the 2030s and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862538&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;steals pic that is interesting from nervjeet&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;stolen image literally has the fucking fileneame from the post it came from&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;this bot thinks im the same guy&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;his nonsensical bot reply gives him away within a few posts because it always handles the same&lt;br&gt;Report this fucker, if he doesnt get banned, all the more reason to NOT trust monero or anyone pushing monero, because the bot is being run from 4chan itself.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;on the XMR thread, this is the same bot&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860201 DXIC7i+b&lt;br&gt;it just goes on and on. hope real anons find this post and start to question wtf is going on around here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862542&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862475&lt;br&gt;Do you have Revolut?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Use it on Hodlhodl (trade escrow service)&lt;br&gt;Send it to some BTC wallet (Sparrow)&lt;br&gt;Use Trocador to convert it to XMR&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862551&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859002&lt;br&gt;Privacy is basically impossible to do for smart contracts outside of creating a specific app such as Tornado. When you create specific apps such as Tornado, you make it extremely vulnerable to censorship from the government, like happened to Tornado. Even though the lawsuit was &amp;quot;dropped&amp;quot;, activity on Tornado is basically nonexistent because nobody trusts it anymore. They shouldn&amp;#x27;t. Likewise, nobody should ever trust a &amp;quot;privacy app&amp;quot; on top of a public L1.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;And don&amp;#x27;t get me started on how ridiculous a &amp;quot;privacy L2&amp;quot; would be on top of a public L1.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you want privacy, you start at the L1 layer.&lt;br&gt;If you want privacy, you choose Monero.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862566&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862538&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;this bot thinks im the same guy&lt;br&gt;No, I think you&amp;#x27;re a nerva shill that tries to play stupid and make this about BTC (it never was) and me being bad because I expose your stupidity. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;his nonsensical bot reply gives him away within a few posts because it always handles the same&lt;br&gt;If it took you 7 posts to undercover my identity as the jeet enemy #1 then either I&amp;#x27;m not as predictable as you say or you&amp;#x27;re retarded. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;it just goes on and on.&lt;br&gt;Because I always refute every point nervajeets make. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;hope real anons find this post and start to question wtf is going on around here.&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m real, that&amp;#x27;s why I continuously offer you to ask me anything regarding XMR. All of the questions you (in English this can be used both for singular and plural, raj) posted have been answered. I&amp;#x27;m glad you visited the general again and saw that they actually have been answered three years ago already on your favorite platform - reddit. &lt;br&gt;If you have any flaws in XMR&amp;#x27;s you wish to point out let me know, otherwise admit defeat or continue embarrassing yourself publicly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862582&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849447&lt;br&gt;framing bitcoin as an epstein jewish globalist pedo creation to sabotage it right as it was on the cusp of actually elbowing its way into the world financial system was a masterstroke psyop&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862608&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862566&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Because I always refute every point nervajeets make. &lt;br&gt;NO ONE MADE ANY POINTS ITT you fucking poo stain bot. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I&amp;#x27;m real, that&amp;#x27;s why I continuously offer you to ask me anything regarding XMR. All of the questions you (in English this can be used both for singular and plural, raj) posted have been answered. I&amp;#x27;m glad you visited the general again and saw that they actually have been answered three years ago already on your favorite platform - reddit.&lt;br&gt;If you have any flaws in XMR&amp;#x27;s you wish to point out let me know, otherwise admit defeat or continue embarrassing yourself publicly.&lt;br&gt;No thanks Alexa, get the fuck of this thread&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862631&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862608&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;NO ONE MADE ANY POINTS ITT you fucking poo stain bot.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The OP pic is interesting no matter how you slice it..&lt;br&gt;Did &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61852712 not make any points then? &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;If you have any flaws in XMR&amp;#x27;s you wish to point out let me know, otherwise admit defeat or continue embarrassing yourself publicly.&lt;br&gt;Hey, I remember someone saying that!&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;No thanks Alexa, get the fuck of this thread&lt;br&gt;I appreciate your concern but I&amp;#x27;ll continue staying here if you are continuing to smear the only properly functioning crypto currency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862698&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861669&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;CTRL+F &amp;quot;Nerva&amp;quot;, first person to mention anything about Nerva is the retarded nigger from the Monero threads&lt;br&gt;&amp;quot;Nervajeets&amp;quot; living rent free lmao&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Nerva network hashrate just hit another ATH today.&lt;br&gt;No signs of slowing down&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862796&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862631&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;monerobot has woke the nervatrolls&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;im the troll&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;i like monero&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;this guy single handedly made me say fuck monegros tho&lt;br&gt;Nerva is actually a privacy coin, eat my ballsack and suck my memedick&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863379&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849447&lt;br&gt;Buy Decred.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863975&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863379&lt;br&gt;Irrelevant shitcoin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864393&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862698&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;Nervajeets&amp;quot; living rent free lmao&lt;br&gt;No, but I notice patterns, like the smell of cow shit, overuse of the word sir (misspoken as sar) and the incessant need to shill some unmaintained jeet coin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864510&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862698&lt;br&gt;Irrelevant shitcoin #2&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864651&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864393&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Nerva sucks as a privacy coin&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Nerva was forked from moneros code&lt;br&gt;You only get to pick one, bot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864667&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864651&lt;br&gt;Nice try but having less than 1/3 of our ring size and no mitigations against multiple attacks that worked on our code base (the devs don&amp;#x27;t even know whether their code has the same flaws or not) means it is not sufficient as a privacy coin. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;picrel&lt;br&gt;Next time try something somebody actually said&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864677&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849898&lt;br&gt;why would that be bearish&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864683&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864677&lt;br&gt;The governments as they are currently don&amp;#x27;t want to embrace our freedom or even anything to our benefit. If they go back to gold coins there will be some catch. If the jew embraces something, try to move as far away from that as possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864708&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855597&lt;br&gt;BTCFi is giving it more use cases with Babylon leading the charge. And I think when we have more projects offering native BTC staking, then we will see the narrative go viral&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864866&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864667&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Try something somebody actually said&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;literally you on every general&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;almost you entirely&lt;br&gt;Cry me some diodes, clanker.&lt;br&gt;Nerva is here to stay.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864897&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864866&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Nerva is here to stay.&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t care if it stays as long as you stop smearing XMR and spamming our threads&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864948&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864897&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I don&amp;#x27;t care if it stays as long as you stop smearing XMR and spamming our threads&lt;br&gt;The only spammer is you, in both this thread and the xmr general. You came here to start shit and have done so in every privacy thread that has popped up. You also accuse everyone of being a poojeet and promoting nerva. Again, the only person promoting (xmr in your case) and causing a stink has been YOU. So fuck off back to your little monero hole, jeetbot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865014&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864948&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The only spammer is you,&lt;br&gt;I wish that were true but sadly the nervajeets constantly try to shit up our thread and this board. There&amp;#x27;s a reason all of these anti-Monero threads pop up when they lose the discussion in the general. Notice how quiet they&amp;#x27;ve become after &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860646 was posted. All of their anti-Monero arguments (which was the entire value proposition for nerva) are gone. Their questions they claim never were answered poofed up into air. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;You came here to start shit&lt;br&gt;OP literally accuses XMR of being some freemason bullshit. You&amp;#x27;re the perfect representation of the jew asking what harm he has done to us. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;You also accuse everyone of being a poojeet and promoting nerva.&lt;br&gt;No, I say that the ones that copy all of the points the nervajeets make to be a nervajeets. That&amp;#x27;s because the only people interested in nerva are jeets.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Please don&amp;#x27;t challenge me when I smear the only functional crypto currency please just go away I can&amp;#x27;t handle it please please please&lt;br&gt;No sar, you wish to talk about XMR? I&amp;#x27;ll be there and refute each on of your pathetic claims.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865124&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864651&lt;br&gt;Holy shit, XMR to a fucking T anon...&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865014&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;bot programmed to hate random shitcoin&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;even if not true, makes it look like hes funded by masons/jews because he literally cannot stop promoting monero&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;becomes a meme in and of himself here&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864651&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;he seriously cant stop&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;he will bring nerva up in random threads every chance he gets even when no one is talking about it&lt;br&gt;Just fucking stop and go away monegro. Maybe they didnt stop after that was posted, because they were never spamming up your threads in the first place you pathetic fucking loser. Only you were, they were just asking questions, something anyone can do. I scoured your xmr generals, and your clearly the psychopath across every fucking one. Non stop blogposts of text that do nothing but go in circles, and now youre doing it here. Save yourself some time and go shit up someone elses thread. Oh right, you cant, because youre a monegro botnet that works for monero glowies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I started this thread to discuss privacy coins and all youve done is shit up my thread you piece of shit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865161&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865014&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;bot&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865268&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862698&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862796&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864651&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864866&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865161&lt;br&gt;good morning nervasaaars&lt;br&gt;truly xnv is the most aryan bharatoken superior peer-to-poop privacy coin xnvsaars redeem asap&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>What the fuck is the deal with PTO — 23 replies — 92.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860903</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860903?lm=1771342157</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:29:17 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;What the fuck is the deal with PTO&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860903'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 23 • Updated: 2026-02-17 15:29 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;So I&amp;#x27;ve only worked one white collar job my whole life, and we would always just book our vacations in advance, we were given 5 weeks of vacation every year and we would just tell them what days we want off.&lt;br&gt;Now I&amp;#x27;m going into this new corporate job and they&amp;#x27;re saying I have to earn my vacations? And earn my holidays? Wtf is this shit. How giving fast do I earn these good boy vacation days. THIS IS FUCKING RETARDED&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860924&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860903&lt;br&gt;they expect you to work like a jeet, congratulations thanks for playing&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860942&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860903&lt;br&gt;5 weeks of vacation is 200 hours. you earn 16.67 hours a month. some places let you take vacation as you want and only make a big deal if you quit or run deep into the negatives. other, shittier places make no exceptions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860971&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860903&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;be me&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;want to take vacation&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;no accrual (though technically I could probably owe them money if I took 4 weeks in January and then quit)&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;put it on my calendar&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;don&amp;#x27;t check with nobody&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;not even logged with the timesheet accounting&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;day comes&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;set email responder &lt;br&gt;This is why I&amp;#x27;m hesitant to look for a new job.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860987&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860924&lt;br&gt;Basically this&lt;br&gt;Corporate got filled with low trust taskmasters in the wake of flooding every major urban area with low trust resource sinks&lt;br&gt;The only solution at this point is a parallel economy that turns into a (non official because oy vey) parallel state apparatus. &lt;br&gt;We have the resources to do this now, but no coherent culture to nucleate around&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860994&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;wah my boss won&amp;#x27;t pay for me to not work&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861001&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860987&lt;br&gt;So you&amp;#x27;re saying that the quality of the employee went down, that&amp;#x27;s the quality of their supervisors went down, thus trust was lost in the old fashioned system like I had in my first job is the way the dinosaur now and it&amp;#x27;s probably is very rare to have a job where you can just get a set amount of vacation per year without earning it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861025&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860903&lt;br&gt;I worked at a tech company with unlimited PTO, and barely anyone actually took time off. I always felt weird taking sick days or whatever because all of my coworkers were workaholics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861031&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861025&lt;br&gt;&amp;quot;unlimited PTO&amp;quot; means you just get fired without warning if you take time off&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861033&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861001&lt;br&gt;Yes, that&amp;#x27;s basically it&lt;br&gt;Blame every single policymaker and adherent to &amp;quot;multiculturalism.&amp;quot; Many cultures on the planet are in no way bad, even sampled within one area, but there are ZERO instances of long term multiculturalism without major strife, war, and civilizational/societal degradation. Homogeneous cultures, planted at the root of the psyche, are the one guaranteed pathway to the success of the human macroorganism&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861082&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860903&lt;br&gt;The thing that pisses me off about PTO is that I&amp;#x27;m unable to take UPTO. Sure, give me a certain amount of paid days off but if I want to take unpaid days off I should be able to have as many as I want. Fuck you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861089&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861082&lt;br&gt;That too. I might not have made a profit while self employed, but these white collar mind games suck&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861115&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861082&lt;br&gt;That would mean your job is so expendable that they can allow you to just leave and come back as you please without having any significant impact on business operations. In which case they might as well just replace you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861197&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thinly veiled data-mining thread&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thinly vailed ragebait thread&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;OP is/will always be a cuck&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861198&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860903&lt;br&gt;If you signed, it&amp;#x27;s your fault anon. Next time be ready to do a 360 on the spot if you don&amp;#x27;t like the contract&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861502&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861115&lt;br&gt;Kind of, but also not really...I work in admin in the life insurance &amp;amp; personal finance industry, if I&amp;#x27;ve shown myself to be dependable come crunch time, am able to develop processes to make sure cases are compliant, basically keep shit in order, it&amp;#x27;s way more expensive to attempt to hire new and retrain (not to mention re-certify new hires if they come in unlicensed) and re-vet potential new hires. Just because I do all this doesn&amp;#x27;t mean I shouldn&amp;#x27;t be able to take as much time off as I want when it&amp;#x27;s a slow period, or I&amp;#x27;m able to find someone else to cover while I&amp;#x27;m away, you know?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861533&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860903&lt;br&gt;Yeah I had to work for 2 years with no days off to earn enough PTO to take two weeks off at one job. If you called in they took a PTO day away and gave you a point. 7 points and it was automatic termination.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861543&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;earn means time in this case&lt;br&gt;this is so you can&amp;#x27;t take you 5 weeks on day one and then quit after that&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863592&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861502&lt;br&gt;No, exactly really. If you&amp;#x27;re completely optional, then you&amp;#x27;re completely unneeded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864938&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860903&lt;br&gt;youd be surprised at how badly niggers abuserd the system in large corpos so they cracked down. &lt;br&gt;Just another perk of life ruined by fucking niggers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864971&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I get 28 days off guaranteed every year and nobody &amp;quot;abuses&amp;quot; the system, lmao mutts will suck cock and say its le efficient or fair I hope your cancer country gets nuked cya&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865006&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860903&lt;br&gt;Just say you have covid and complications with COVID. Buy an old positive test, go to the doctor and get a note. Boom your off for a few days&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865036&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860903&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Now I&amp;#x27;m going into this new corporate job and they&amp;#x27;re saying I have to earn my vacations? And earn my holidays? Wtf is this shit. How giving fast do I earn these good boy vacation days. THIS IS FUCKING RETARDED&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Loads of jobs have people show up and quit or suck ass and need to be fired. Handing people five weeks they can take day 1 on the job is silly.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;So instead they&amp;#x27;ll make you work X months and then only award 1 day per 2 weeks or whatever. You still earn 5 weeks off a year but then you just haven&amp;#x27;t gotten it all to blow&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865426&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I started taking an hour of leave every day because i couldnt do 9 hours a day in the office and wanted to go to the gym before it was pitch dark outside and i got called in by my 3 supervisors and HR and counselling asking if i was suicidal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>The US is in recession — 82 replies — 83.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61857490</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61857490?lm=1771338795</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 14:33:15 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;The US is in recession&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61857490'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 82 • Updated: 2026-02-17 14:33 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US is in recession&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857499&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White collar recession comes before regular recession 100% of the time. We&amp;#x27;ve been in a white collar recession since 2020.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857500&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;Always was, its depression for over a year now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857508&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;GDP is growing, recession is fake.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nothing ever happens. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stop putting your vibes and feelings into your job search, learn to get better skills and be more marketable to employers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;McDonalds is always hiring&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860619&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859951&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Get America back up to 70%+ White, fix your money printing problem, deal with the israel problem in your government, and the economy will take care of itself.&lt;br&gt;anything else while we have the magic wand out sir?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860705&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859951&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;How the fuck do you reach the conclusion that America needs an &amp;quot;international order&amp;quot; to function when it&amp;#x27;s downfall has correlated perfectly to its kowtowing to international interests&lt;br&gt;What international interests? The US has been profiting off the international order since Breton Woods. Its rise as a superpower correlates to the dollar’s international dominance. It’s the opposite of what you’re describing.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;America is almost entirely self-sufficient&lt;br&gt;It is completely dependent on foreign pharmaceuticals and various input goods for manufacturing. It has virtually no domestic source of lithium, cobalt, graphite or REMs. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;the problem is international Jewry and this will be rectified when the us becomes an autarky &lt;br&gt;Why? &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rotting elephant in the room is a declining dollar, obscene debt, and an overinflated market + made up statistics. None of this gets better by fucking up international trade.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860719&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857750&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;US being in a recession isn&amp;#x27;t about Trump.&lt;br&gt;Yes he&amp;#x27;s a fucking retarded boomer brained moron, but US has been doomed to hit this point sooner or later ever since they decided to crank the money printers on permanently after 2008 and doomed the entire West to be stuck in a slow death limbo.&lt;br&gt;Everyone has basically just been waiting for the big one for years now and we&amp;#x27;re getting closer and closer to it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860738&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859951&lt;br&gt;You have no idea how the dollar system works and it shows. What&amp;#x27;s happening to the United States right now is irreversible&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860813&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860719&lt;br&gt;Printing after 2008 happened because 2008 happened, which happened because republicans deregulated finance. You&amp;#x27;re right, it&amp;#x27;s not about Trump, it&amp;#x27;s about half the country being fucking retarded hicks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860867&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860813&lt;br&gt;Republicans like Raegan deregulated finance, that’s true (though some of that was put into motion by Jimmy Carter). That said, it’s impossible to talk about 2008 without recognizing that Clinton is the one who repealed the Glass-Steagall act and let insurance banking merge with commercial banking. Pretty much every president for the 30 years leading up to 2008 did something to enable it or make it worse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860880&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860867&lt;br&gt;I forgot that Clinton was also the one that made derivatives immune to regulation. He really fucked up finance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860916&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857825&lt;br&gt;Holy shit this is the most retarded post I have ever read on /biz/, why are you on a finance board??&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860980&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860880&lt;br&gt;Clinton also forced banks to give mortgages to people with bad credit scores and low income&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861063&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857508&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;GDP was never meant to measure the health of the economy. Simon Kuznets advised against using it for that purpose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861445&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860705&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;It has virtually no domestic source of lithium, cobalt, graphite or REMs. &lt;br&gt;There are actually fucking tons of sources, but none of them are developed because US companies exported the environmental cost of mining them to &amp;quot;dEvElOpInG&amp;quot; nations for cheaper labor/materials and most of the mines shut down because they couldn&amp;#x27;t compete. There are ludicrous amounts of these materials just sitting there in the US.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US could be self-sufficient (example: fracking boom was because oil price had gotten to the point where domestic supply was economically viable again - in less than a decade the US had more oil than it could even use, because the oil was already in the ground, just not being extracted), but the profit motive won&amp;#x27;t allow self-sufficiency to persist if it&amp;#x27;s cheaper to import.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861531&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861445&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;”we are almost entirely self-sufficient”&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;”ok we currently have no infrastructure to mine these resources”&lt;br&gt;Yes, exactly. We are totally dependent on foreign suppliers and as of right now we do not have a domestic source for these things. My point stands and yours is wrong. Coping about how we COULD have these things eventually doesn’t matter. Like it or not, the US is not self-sufficient, and it isn’t close. We import tremendous amounts of goods. Don’t even bother looking into pharmaceuticals because it will just depress you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861694&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857750&lt;br&gt;We&amp;#x27;ve been in a recession since 2023. This isn&amp;#x27;t glorphf&amp;#x27;s fault or joepedo. Our economy is fake and gay made up of jewish daycare bullshit jobs. Soon it will all unravel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861711&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861531&lt;br&gt;Don&amp;#x27;t get your panties in a bunch, all I took issue with was saying &amp;quot;virtually no domestic source.&amp;quot; Some people in these discussions act like SEA is the only place in the world that has minerals.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A water source is still there even if nobody builds a well. Since you seem to get that, you were probably looking for the phrase &amp;quot;domestic SUPPLY.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861724&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857805&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oh no, its over, the Europeans and Anglos are mad we voted a republican again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861729&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858084&lt;br&gt;The fantasy is better than the reality&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861769&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857805&lt;br&gt;We should be bombing Mexico.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861811&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861711&lt;br&gt;No I wasn’t. I don’t feel like explaining it to you so I’ll just let AI do it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863135&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858023&lt;br&gt;Pam Bondi was such a hot piece of ass when she was young. She&amp;#x27;s still sorta cute give that she&amp;#x27;s sixty years old. It&amp;#x27;s too bad she&amp;#x27;s protecting Jewish pedophiles and cannibals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863175&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;BUMP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863206&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And the burger gov is again burning absolutely everything in the market, including themselves to make a smoke screen to cover the crashing dollar.&lt;br&gt;Nobody wants that shit yet it is going up with not only no buyers but countries constantly throwing it into the market. Absolute shitshow from a drowning in shit man.&lt;br&gt;Funny isn&amp;#x27;t it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863218&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860719&lt;br&gt;The boat that is jewsa has been sinking for a while. The orange nigger is actively making more holes in it and setting it on fire&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863252&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What&amp;#x27;s the polymarket for that??&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863679&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857500&lt;br&gt;Try since 08. Things have never actually genuinely recovered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864332&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;End of the Juglar cycle. Overproduction crisis. Fed interest rates plunging toward zero. Soon an other Capital idling necessary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864333&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863679&lt;br&gt;Capital final crisis since 2008.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864989&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863206&lt;br&gt;2006 was giving out loans like candy to people who had absolutely no way of ever servicing them&lt;br&gt;this then resulted in a lot of forced selling into a no bid market as all of this inventory was cleared when the bubble popped&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;right now we dont have excessive loans, quite the opposite retards arent given insane loans this is legit existing money bidding up hard assets because so much money got printed and it has to go somewhere&lt;br&gt;you dont get a crash in housing without forced selling and who is going to force sell his real estate at low prices without the bank margin calling them&lt;br&gt;unlike stocks which are completely fungible and its price is set at the margin, housing isnt and the owner can just sit on the asset forever and not be forced to take any offer being made at market price&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;to disrupt this &amp;#x27;bubble&amp;#x27; you need the government unprinting the money supply (lol, lmao even) or you need a large section of boomers dying off and leaving their heirs with no way to pay the taxes/upkeep and force dump it&lt;br&gt;the second one is the only realistic option, tho there is also the risk that the heirs can pay for the inheritance and real estate is now permanently locked up in magnate hands and the nation reduced to permarenting slave&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865001&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It really isn&amp;#x27;t mentioned enough that our &amp;quot;recovery&amp;quot; after 2008 was just setting interest rates to 0 for 10 years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865048&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864989&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;...a large section of boomers dying off and leaving their heirs with no way to pay the taxes/upkeep...real estate is now permanently locked up in magnate hands....&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;ve laid out exactly what&amp;#x27;s been going on since 2008&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865068&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865048&lt;br&gt;yes thats the point, the implication here is that real estate is now permanently priced out of the middle class income range&lt;br&gt;not that a crash is imminent like the anon i was replying to seemed to suggest&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Is living anywhere except Los Angeles, San Francisco, Washington DC, or New York the same as admitting that your life is… — 77 replies — 35.4/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858975</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858975?lm=1771334529</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 13:22:09 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Is living anywhere except Los Angeles, San Francisco, Washington DC, or New York the same as admitting that your life is…&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858975'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 77 • Updated: 2026-02-17 13:22 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Is living anywhere except Los Angeles, San Francisco, Washington DC, or New York the same as admitting that your life is meaningless and that you are NOT the main character and will never make it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858982&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;Dubai, Paris, London, Tokyo, Kyoto&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858987&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You burgers aren&amp;#x27;t ready for what&amp;#x27;s coming&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858990&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;HAHAHA&lt;br&gt;HAHAHAHA&lt;br&gt;IMAGINE LIVING IN A BROWN SHITHOLE&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859468&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859319&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;45 minutes away in LA&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oh so it&amp;#x27;s 5 miles away?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;LA is filled with tards. I guess the weather is nice. I bet that guy you&amp;#x27;re replying to lives in Boise, Idaho though. The nicest city in America by far.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859470&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859400&lt;br&gt;All of the runoff concentrates into drainages that dump directly into the ocean. It doesn&amp;#x27;t rain often so months of garbage, human shit, needles collect in the street and dump directly into the ocean.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;https://www.pacificsurf.com/surfing-after-it-rains/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;A few of the things you could get are ear infections, sinus infections, pink eye, the flu,gastroenteritis, MRSA, Hepatitis, and Staph.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860590&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;d consider living there after you threw all the non-Whites out. Otherwise, I&amp;#x27;d visit it but not stay there permanently.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860659&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Assuming you’ve made it, what are the benefits of living in these cities when job opportunities are no longer a factor&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860666&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;No. You can also live in a remote cabin in Alaska. At least until your old crew calls you out of retirement for one last job.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860681&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;My life is given meaning through devotion and love for the LORD Jesus Christ&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860712&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859314&lt;br&gt;Guarantee me a couple of slam piglets and a square meal and I&amp;#x27;ll see what I can do about sabotaging the caravans wheels to steer it on coarse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860728&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;imagine living in new york, not being the richest guy in new york, and imagining that living in new york means your life isn&amp;#x27;t meaningless&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860769&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858982&lt;br&gt;t. lolicerdo criminal&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860793&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;Living anywhere except Los Angeles, San Francisco, Washington DC, or New York is the same as admitting that your life is meaningless and that you are NOT the main character and will never make it.&lt;br&gt;This is true. Imagine living anywhere near these mega slave cities.&lt;br&gt;You will just be worker number 10000000. Almost anywhere else is better.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860802&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859145&lt;br&gt;Holy shit imagine thinking thats a good place to live in. The nederlands are already way overpopulated. Our natural habitat which means the place we are most happy at is the forest with a small group of tribespeople.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860804&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860793&lt;br&gt;*in&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860828&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Is living anywhere except Chongqing, Shanghai, Beijing, Guangzhou and Shenzhen the same as admitting that your life is meaningless and that you are NOT the main character and will never make it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861578&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859032&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;thirdie hivan complains but won&amp;#x27;t move back(will move to oc instead)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861585&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;I live in Chinook montana. I would ask for nothing else&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861591&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;I am from D.C.&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s full of drones. Some are deluded enough to think being the GS-15 in charge of whatever the fuck department for whatever government agency actually makes them important.&lt;br&gt;It doesn&amp;#x27;t.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861595&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858990&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;IMAGINE LIVING IN A BROWN SHITHOLE&lt;br&gt;D.C. suburbs in 2012 be like...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862146&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;Los Angeles is a shithole. San Francisco lost all sovl because no one who lives there is actually from San Francisco anymore. D.C. is literally a dilapidated nigger den. New York is cool and iconic but is also a lonely hive where everyone is disconnected despite living 10,000 to a city block.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t think you&amp;#x27;ve been to any of them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862164&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859319&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;worst street&lt;br&gt;So you admit that the left-wing billionaires delegate certain streets for the homeless while they live on the nice streets in their high rises, with private security?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862191&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862164&lt;br&gt;They delegate entire states for the washed out retards to live in, while even the homeless here in LA have more upward mobility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862210&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858982&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Non-Americans&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Main Character&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Even Once&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anon...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862380&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861591&lt;br&gt;This. I&amp;#x27;m from DC too, but I left that shithole years ago. Everyone is a bureaucratic suit who aspires to work for the government or some adjacent entity. Sure there might be ethnic diversity, but there is no cultural diversity at all. Quite literally everyone is a libtard. Not to mention the women there are not only busted but also extremely deluded in thinking that they deserve Chads. A DC 10 is a Miami or NYC 6.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862537&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859324&lt;br&gt;Can confirm, LA is great. Every month I have to remember to not self-dox because retards are talking about what a shithole it is here, and I want to take a photo of my window view showing that it looks exactly the same as the white southern suburb they all fantasize about. Just don&amp;#x27;t live in the poor part of town. That rule applies to every city on earth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862543&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We have *real* mexican food for cheap, no bad weather, and as many asian women and big booty latinas as you could ever want.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864183&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862380&lt;br&gt;D.C. has long been &amp;quot;Hollywood for ugly people.&amp;quot; It&amp;#x27;s where ugly people go to make it - with their 6 figure bullshit government job.&lt;br&gt;I lived in Fairfax and worked in Arlington - at least I wasn&amp;#x27;t on the nigger side of the Potomac.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864233&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858982&lt;br&gt;These places are all horrible unless you’re rich or are on a clear path to wealth. I’m convinced the only places left on earth where it’s still possible to safely and comfortably raise a family on a middling firstie income are Southeast Asia and Eastern Europe (the Catholic ones in the EU not the orthodox shitholes)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864442&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864233&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Eastern Europe&lt;br&gt;Can confirm it&amp;#x27;s comfy as fuck here with just a few hundred grand of wealth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864757&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862146&lt;br&gt;Erm but all my favorite movies take place in those cities so they must be the best and most important in America!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864780&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;most of those cities suck ass and are basically open air prisons for white collar wageslaves. people with money &amp;quot;in LA&amp;quot; live on or near the beach. people with money &amp;quot;in DC&amp;quot; live in surrounding areas like bethesda or chevy chase.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864816&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;I enjoy Manhattan and visiting SOCAL but living there would be too much. I lived on in Santa Monica for a year and anytime you&amp;#x27;d want to do something you had to plan around traffic. Not a way to live you entire life. There&amp;#x27;s a ton of great nature in southern California so even if you&amp;#x27;re not into le hustle and bustle you&amp;#x27;re still able to have a good time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Crypto has ruined my life honestly I’m 69, going 70. — 32 replies — 34.4/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61862685</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61862685?lm=1771339000</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 14:36:40 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Crypto has ruined my life honestly I’m 69, going 70.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61862685'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 32 • Updated: 2026-02-17 14:36 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Crypto has ruined my life honestly&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I’m 69, going 70. Down to my last 17 BSV with no job willing to hire me. In debt of over $33k borrowing from friends and family in a span of 9 months&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now i’m not sure where to even start with my life, feeling depressed almost every single day&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862713&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862685&lt;br&gt;if you got time on your hands and live in USA get into the pokemon hustle, learn all your local Target/Walmart/Best buy location pokemon drops and wait in like for 2-6 hours(if needed) to get the stuff and then flip it through various online sources or FB marketplace, etc. Also do not tell your friends about it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862738&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862685&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;start with my life&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;70&lt;br&gt;I think your life is over, Boomboom. If you didn&amp;#x27;t have kids, or you fucked over your kids and grandkids like all the other boomers, don&amp;#x27;t expect an easy death. Take your due. Get right with Jesus and prepare for the end. And if you kill yourself, you can give up on going to heaven.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862799&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;this is going to be most millennials in just 10 years kek.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862801&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862738&lt;br&gt;This, don&amp;#x27;t kill yourself or you won&amp;#x27;t get into Valhalla. Die in glorious battle, killing judeo-christian golem and their masters. It&amp;#x27;s the redemption you seek.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862860&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862801&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862861&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;as evidenced by the above comments, maybe don&amp;#x27;t spend so much time online, esp degenerate 4chan. As long as you can keep living in good health there is a lot of enjoyment you can get out of life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862862&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;nigga you are 70 you are done for&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862884&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862801&lt;br&gt;Synagogue of Satan &amp;quot;jew&amp;quot; who say he is a jew but isn&amp;#x27;t spotted. Revelations 3:4 KJV&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862897&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;chainlink general thread of the near future&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863327&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862685&lt;br&gt;I hear you fren. 52 here and only had a single gf ever. I&amp;#x27;m in Rio since born and only today I realized that literally &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;every single person &lt;br&gt;finds my present self ugly, creepy and downright crazed looking &lt;br&gt;I honestly had&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;no idea&lt;br&gt;A fat woman literally said&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;jesus christ &lt;br&gt;and it was about my looks. I used to look alright and even on the handsome side as a young man (my gf was a model when she left me).&lt;br&gt;I&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;never&lt;br&gt;even had a woman approach me during carnival and I see niggers with all kinds of beautiful women.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;one impregnated the blonde i was once in love with (she barely noticed me)&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;it&amp;#x27;s all so tiresome &lt;br&gt;Keep up the faith anon. You&amp;#x27;re not alone in failure and bottomless desperation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863331&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862685&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863373&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862799&lt;br&gt;Millennials invested in rocks. We&amp;#x27;re looking at 400% or higher all-time returns to date.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862861&lt;br&gt;I didn&amp;#x27;t say he&amp;#x27;s dead, but I mean, what does he have to look forward to? He&amp;#x27;s got maybe 10-15 years of non-disabled life left and he&amp;#x27;s in massive debt to his own family. I mean, at least it&amp;#x27;s not a bank? Family is going to want him to die by the time he becomes disabled. If boomers weren&amp;#x27;t such greedy fucks they&amp;#x27;re kids wouldn&amp;#x27;t hate them so much. Imagine if the guy just invested in his children/grandchildren&amp;#x27;s inheritance instead of a fucking shitcoin? Then they would have no qualms about nursing him till his last breath.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863603&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862685&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;BSV&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;lol...faggot. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;kys&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864551&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862860&lt;br&gt;Kike subversion tactic. I won&amp;#x27;t be brown and you won&amp;#x27;t be white no matter how hard you kvetch&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864556&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862685&lt;br&gt;bro you are 70&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;just kill yourself&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864559&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862685&lt;br&gt;My dad died aged 63 of a brain tumor. Be grateful for the time you had - but your time has ended boomer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864572&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862713&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;get into flipping Pokémon cards&lt;br&gt;Jesus Christ is it that bad in America for real?&lt;br&gt;Just get into stealing stuff. That&amp;#x27;s what I would do. Get to know people at the local nerd shops and figure out which ones live alone and when they&amp;#x27;re not home break in and steal their card collections.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864577&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862685&lt;br&gt;Oh brother, life is over. Pick a place on a slum near a public hospital and that&amp;#x27;s that&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864764&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Imagine stressing about anything when youre almost dead&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864774&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862685&lt;br&gt;Sorry you fell for the scam that is Bitcoin and crapto.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;BSV&lt;br&gt;Jesus&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864787&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864572&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Is it that bad in America?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Steal&lt;br&gt;The third world will never change.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864798&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862685&lt;br&gt;Come to canada, walk into any hospital and tell them you&amp;#x27;re broke, they&amp;#x27;ll give you MAID for free.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864807&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jesuschrist, am I interacting with people that are in their 70s? Man... how low 4chan has fallen. I spent some time checking other boards, and man... boards with flags make you wanna leave this place. It&amp;#x27;s all indians and brazilians. Even mexicans. tv is just alcoholic and depressed millennials. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I can&amp;#x27;t wait for twitter to allow banning countries on X. Once they do that, goodbye&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Countries I&amp;#x27;m planning to block&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Israel&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;All Latin American countries&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;AFRICA&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Germany&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Turkey&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The Netherlands&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;All Asian countries except Iran and the orientals&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864845&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864807&lt;br&gt;Why Netherlands?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864858&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862685&lt;br&gt;Have you tried selling that sloppy roid infested ass of yours yet? You might get a few bucks from that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864867&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862685&lt;br&gt;DONT LOSE HOPE&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864927&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is now a Babylon 5 thread.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864955&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862685&lt;br&gt;Hey look, it&amp;#x27;s Satoshi&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864956&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862685&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;owing exactly 33&lt;br&gt;we know freemason.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865022&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862685&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862685&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Now i’m not sure where to even start with my life&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Don&amp;#x27;t worry about it. Let me help you. Statistically you have about 3 years left to live. So basically you haven&amp;#x27;t found the malignant tumor yet providing from a vital organ but that day is coming&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865070&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I feel less bad about my stock picks when everything is getting fucked. Like it&amp;#x27;s not my fault.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;But please god just bring back the green. I can&amp;#x27;t take it much longer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865081&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862685&lt;br&gt;Focus on your health, exercise, eat well, take senolytics, if you can survive long enough you&amp;#x27;ll be able to extend your lifespan and health longer and make up for any mistakes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>&gt;mom yells at me for not having a job 5 months after I got laid off from my last one &gt;Complains how we need more money t… — 38 replies — 21.4/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61863594</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61863594?lm=1771335968</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 13:46:08 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;&amp;gt;mom yells at me for not having a job 5 months after I got laid off from my last one &amp;gt;Complains how we need more money t…&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61863594'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 38 • Updated: 2026-02-17 13:46 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;mom yells at me for not having a job 5 months after I got laid off from my last one&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Complains how we need more money to pay the bills and how she can&amp;#x27;t keep working 10 hour shifts to pay our bills&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Look through her purse when she&amp;#x27;s not looking &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;See a $600 receipt for perfume and makeup, and a bank note evidencing a $1800 transfer to her neet sister who also has 2 neet sons and a neet daughter. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Dad gambled away another $10K in stocks. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;He keeps sending me job openings in other states/cities that require 10+ years of experience and he tells me &amp;quot;just walk up to them and ask them to train you, that&amp;#x27;s how we did it back in the old days&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;My own savings are slowly dwindling and I&amp;#x27;ve got no more than a few months left before I&amp;#x27;m officially broke &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;800+ job apps and nothing yet&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m not sure how much more of this I can take bros...&lt;br&gt;Why won&amp;#x27;t the economy get better? &lt;br&gt;Who do I blame for this miserable situation?&lt;br&gt;What are some easy painless ways to check out of this economy earlier don&amp;#x27;t speak?&lt;br&gt;Why are old people all so stupid and contemptible?&lt;br&gt;NGMI?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863604&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863594&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Who do I blame for this miserable situation?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863605&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;See a $600 receipt for perfume and makeup&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;a bank note evidencing a $1800 transfer to&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Dad gambled away another $10K in stocks&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Complains how we need more money to pay the bills &lt;br&gt;what came first?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863607&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863594&lt;br&gt;Meant to say, So to speak, not don&amp;#x27;t speak &lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s been almost a few decades of smartphone development and auto correct still doesn&amp;#x27;t work properly yet AI fags are still like &amp;quot;we&amp;#x27;re totally gonna get agi and self driving cars this year bro!!!&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863651&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Navy or Air Force is better than army.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863758&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863594&lt;br&gt;Your mother seems ro be a stupid as mine. When mine dies her ashes are going directly into the toilet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863782&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863651&lt;br&gt;NTA but I was medically disqualified after an injury helping a relative&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863786&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863594&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Join ICE.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863791&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863651&lt;br&gt;Most active duty army tried to join a different branch first (bar combat arms), but couldn&amp;#x27;t due to various reasons. Be real this is /biz/.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863810&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Do you live with your parents? That sounds like a lot of the problem&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863822&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863810&lt;br&gt;COL being what it is means even living with asshole parents is better in every circumstance other than them literally being physically abusive or outright robbing you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863846&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;mom seething that she might have to come out of early retirement because her 401k is only up 5% since the start of the year and she spends too much on vacations&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;complains &amp;quot;it&amp;#x27;s not fair, I should get to have a life&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;mfw she used to say this all the time whne I was in highschool when she grounded me -for existing- so she could go out with her friends on fridays, preventing me from ever having a life&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;realize she&amp;#x27;s a narcissist and deserves to suffer and am glad ot be an albatross around her neck&lt;br&gt;Shouldn&amp;#x27;t have stolen 20,000 dollars from me when I was 23, bitch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863852&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863651&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863648&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863782&lt;br&gt;Army is good because it runs weeaboo psyops.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863786&lt;br&gt;I applied for ICE in 2024 before Trump got elected, they&amp;#x27;re hiring beaners instead. Turns out no one will just &amp;#x27;let&amp;#x27; you be useful to society while making 150k a year working 80 hours a week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863856&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863822&lt;br&gt;He&amp;#x27;s just gonna tell you you&amp;#x27;re a loser and to get an apartment with a crackhead roommate or something. Your parents are the problem for not hooking you up with a year of rent and a job if they don&amp;#x27;t want you around. American parents deserve everything coming to them for stealing from their own kids. Who the fuck thinks they can just peace out and retire when society is collapsing lmao. Anyone who says &amp;quot;not my problem, I&amp;#x27;ll be dead by the time it gets REAL bad&amp;quot; is a person I conside rit my duty to cause as much suffering as posible for.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863912&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sounds like your whole family is dead weight except your mom. The perfume and makeup is probably a desperate move to hopefully find a man.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863922&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863856&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Anyone who says &amp;quot;not my problem, I&amp;#x27;ll be dead by the time it gets REAL bad&amp;quot; is a person I conside rit my duty to cause as much suffering as posible for.&lt;br&gt;They&amp;#x27;ll all be abused by Indians in the retirement home while their actual children are estranged. Poetic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864141&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863594&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863622&lt;br&gt;How old are you, OP? Sounds like your family is financially abusive to you. Can you move out on your own (as soon as you find a job, I mean) and cut contact?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864148&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863822&lt;br&gt;It really isn&amp;#x27;t. You can live VERY cheaply in a lot of Asian countries (Thailand, Laos, Indonesia) and do ridiculously low-paying remote work and still come out with net savings every month.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I worked in Taiwan (DON&amp;#x27;T GO THERE) for a while and was able to save over 50% of my pay even though I made half as much as an American would make doing the same job (not ESLosering).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wish I hadn&amp;#x27;t because it completely destroyed my health permanently (they&amp;#x27;re just as bad, maybe worse, about dumping toxic industrial chemicals in food as the mainland chinsects), but it was the only thing available to me after the 2008-12 crash during the Obamaconomy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864222&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863594&lt;br&gt;corner your dad and mom about that 600+1.8k+10k$. That&amp;#x27;ll make them shut for another 1 month.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864358&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863594&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;neet sister who also has 2 neet sons and a neet daughter.&lt;br&gt;nigga how old are you? &lt;br&gt;or are you calling infants neets kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864379&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863594&lt;br&gt;What the fuck does your retarded family have to do with the economy?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864420&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864358&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;her neet sister&lt;br&gt;His aunt is the neet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864425&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863648&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863651&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863643&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;just go get killed for ZOG!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The only military worth joining is the russian one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864429&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864222&lt;br&gt;These are classic case narcissists or sociopaths. They’ll become affronted, say something along the lines of ‘none of your business’ and if they are reticent then it would most certainly be for lip service.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864434&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864425&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;just go get killed for ZOG (east)!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864449&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863643&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863648&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863651&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863852&lt;br&gt;Wow the sõyjack party leaks were true this place is infested with glowies&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864425&lt;br&gt;come on dude&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864740&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864358&lt;br&gt;My neet aunts children are in there fucking 40s and never worked jobs yet live like kings. One of them is 400 pounds and my mom complains about how she needs to keep buying him bigger and bigger gift shirts every year...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864743&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;beat your mother&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864751&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864141&lt;br&gt;I can&amp;#x27;t unfortunately.&lt;br&gt;I tried really hard but it didn&amp;#x27;t work out&lt;br&gt;Got my mom&amp;#x27;s adhd+schizophrenic OCD and my dad&amp;#x27;s autism adhd. I can barely function and the few years I worked a job I was tempted to drive my car into oncoming traffic every single day to and back from work &lt;br&gt;Col is just too high plus I can&amp;#x27;t get a good paying job&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864222&lt;br&gt;Have you read a certain painters description of a certain group of people being like jelly when you argue with them? It&amp;#x27;s impossible to discuss anything with these animals I have for parents. They forget everything the next day and gaslight you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864763&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864743&lt;br&gt;My dad already does and she fucking loves it.&lt;br&gt;Meanwhile I slightly raise my voice to make sure she can hear me and she goes berserk calling me an asshole who&amp;#x27;ll never get women cuz I have no job meanwhile my dad gambled 200k on stock margins in the 90s and lost his job for a decade and she still dutifully stuck with him. It&amp;#x27;s comical how everyday my dad cusses her out and yells at her calling her a dumb bitch at the top of his lungs and she&amp;#x27;ll dutifully have dinner ready for him in an hour while washing all his clothes for him yet she&amp;#x27;ll scold me for not cooking my own food even though I never asked her to cook for me&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864768&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863594&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;He keeps sending me job openings in other states/cities that require 10+ years of experience and he tells me &amp;quot;just walk up to them and ask them to train you, that&amp;#x27;s how we did it back in the old days&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;my dad used to do this&lt;br&gt;holy shit it pissed the fuck out of me&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864788&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864763&lt;br&gt;She loves getting beat?&lt;br&gt;Huh&lt;br&gt;Wonder if she’d love getting her pussy beat into smithereens. Tell your dad to try that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864795&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863604&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863594&lt;br&gt;Ironically the same people who make these demoralisation threads&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864888&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863856&lt;br&gt;Average zoomer blaming everyone but themselves&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>AAVE is gonna do what all the Chainlink shills tell you LINK will do — 16 replies — 16.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861383</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861383?lm=1771338764</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 14:32:44 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;AAVE is gonna do what all the Chainlink shills tell you LINK will do&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861383'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 16 • Updated: 2026-02-17 14:32 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;AAVE is gonna do what all the Chainlink shills tell you LINK will do&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861393&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861383&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;tokenized abundance assets&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861407&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;for me it&amp;#x27;s tokenized scarcity assets&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861409&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;That guy is nearly as abundant as Sergey, if you catch my drift&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861478&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861393&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;yeah Aave is somehow more globohomo than Link.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861492&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861383&lt;br&gt;my aave tokens got liquidated by the gay little fight between aave labs and their faggot contributors, so they can all get fucked in my humble opinion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861532&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861393&lt;br&gt;cool buzz word kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861571&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861383&lt;br&gt;aave and chainlink are so deep up each other&amp;#x27;s ass that when you cheer for one you cheer for the other&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861574&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861383&lt;br&gt;Powered by Chainlink&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861647&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861492&lt;br&gt;What kind of retarded fud is this? How did your Aave tokens &amp;quot;get liquidated&amp;quot;?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861649&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861647&lt;br&gt;how do you think, moron?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861665&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861649&lt;br&gt;Longing with leverage? Should&amp;#x27;ve be a stakechad&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861668&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861665&lt;br&gt;aave&amp;#x27;s entire business model is based on leverage&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861675&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861668&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The casino&amp;#x27;s entire business model is gambling&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;And?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861980&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861383&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;could&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;by 2050&lt;br&gt;kek baggies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861984&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861383&lt;br&gt;Which is?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865066&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;why are these guys all fat as fuck?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>