<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>/biz/ Active (filtered, with replies)</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/</link><description>Filtered out: general, gme, bbbyq. OP + first 3 replies + last 30 replies.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 20:42:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>I just found out my ex got married AND pregnant one year after we broke up What are the financial consequences for simps… — 42 replies — 168.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861117</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861117?lm=1771274347</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 20:39:07 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;I just found out my ex got married AND pregnant one year after we broke up What are the financial consequences for simps…&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861117'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 42 • Updated: 2026-02-16 20:39 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;I just found out my ex got married AND pregnant one year after we broke up&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What are the financial consequences for simps to marry and impregnate women they don&amp;#x27;t even know?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861127&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861117&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;OPs ex dodged a bullet by prolonging her fertile years with a loser and instead got married and did her god-given duty&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861151&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861127&lt;br&gt;well, in this situation i dodged a bullet because she was just a do-nothing ukrainian whore vaping and drinking coca-cola 24/7 who was on tv in her early 20&amp;#x27;s (so a prostitute) and even admitted she had sex with a nigger in moscow&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I saw the picture of the wedding and the guy who married her look like he is in his 40&amp;#x27;s and is quite ugly but he must have money, not even sure the bedroom of the kid look like shit...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;i was just asking why do men MARRY women at any point? Even more after 6/12 months of relationship?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861301&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861117&lt;br&gt;listen up, i will make this so clear for you.&lt;br&gt; a woman&amp;#x27;s asset is her youth and consequently beauty. Once a girl hits 30s, her options become incredibly limited, given she is not in the top 10% in looks. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;your ex probably panicked about her future, and found an easily manipulatable guy to provide her the sense of security she was looking for. If the guy she married is in his 40s, this guy is also experiencing a mid life crisis and is trying to make up for lost time. And yeah, if he is 40 single and childless, granted he has a 9-5 job, he likely has money saved up. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Only an idiot would risk half his belongings like that on less than a year of relationship. someone not thinking in their right mind, because even a year isn&amp;#x27;t enough to know someone. In fact, 3-4 years is ideal time to propose because the initial feelings of love would have worn off and then the real question if you want to be with this person for the rest of your life becomes easier to answer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861605&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861151&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;dating an Eastern European&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;execting class&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;bitciing about her finding someone older and probably more financially stable than a 4chan neet &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861616&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861117&lt;br&gt;I knocked up my wife about 8 months after we met.&lt;br&gt;Consequences? It&amp;#x27;s 9 years later and we have 4 kids and are married.&lt;br&gt;Financial consequences? She&amp;#x27;s a medical doctor (resident) so in a few years she&amp;#x27;ll be making $300k a year with upside from there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861630&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861592&lt;br&gt;just don&amp;#x27;t be poor lol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861632&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861592&lt;br&gt;God-Jesus the ever living IS risen kike.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861660&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861616&lt;br&gt;at what age did she start school to be a doctor?&lt;br&gt;anyway, congrats brother&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861677&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861117&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;My ex left me and found someone better. Please help me to cope.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861680&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I read the subject of this thread and felt like shit...&lt;br&gt;If someone told me this about my ex, I&amp;#x27;d have a panic attack, I think.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861699&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861117&lt;br&gt;women are whores such is life&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861720&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861632&lt;br&gt;You worship a kike you dumb bitch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861727&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861630&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m not like most posters here who claim to be &amp;quot;blessed by YHWH&amp;quot; because they&amp;#x27;re rich and they believe in the just world fallacy. You aren&amp;#x27;t cursed if you are poor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861744&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861548&lt;br&gt;Massive cope probably has daughters&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861592&lt;br&gt;Jesus Christ is God The Son and your Lord like it or not.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861775&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861744&lt;br&gt;Your lord is a kike?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861795&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861744&lt;br&gt;back to /pol/ boomer&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861804&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861117&lt;br&gt;if the woman closes her eyes during sex shes thinking about someone else&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861807&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861660&lt;br&gt;19, I got her after she graduated then she took years off having babies before starting residency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861821&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861541&lt;br&gt;she can&amp;#x27;t cook even a fucking egg&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861826&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861677&lt;br&gt;i didn&amp;#x27;t check her instagram for two years, i don&amp;#x27;t care about her&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861903&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861151&lt;br&gt;Technically you touched wieners with a nigger&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861915&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861826&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;for two years!&lt;br&gt;then you did&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862004&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861915&lt;br&gt;yes i don&amp;#x27;t know why my brain told me &amp;quot;check it&amp;quot; and i even reinstalled instagram for that after 8 months being idle on there&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;i&amp;#x27;m not jealous of their situation, i&amp;#x27;m actually in the same somehow with my actual gf of two years, we are now talking about having a baby together but she already gave birth like 6 months ago&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;so even in the best timeline, they knew each other 8 months before planning to have a kid, that&amp;#x27;s insanely fast but i also understand women don&amp;#x27;t go for the best, they just have baby pulsions and just find a beta cuck &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;again, i really dodged a bullet with this woman one day she told me &amp;quot;if you want me to give you a baby you need to buy me a car&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;and i also see in her instagram so she is in a fancy leather car so i can imagine he bought her a 200K kilometers used up audi because the baby&amp;#x27;s bedroom really look like shit so i dont think the guy is loaded&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;anyway that was my 2 cents, you can now gtfo of my thread i just didn&amp;#x27;t expect to have this feeling as early in my life&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862014&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862004&lt;br&gt;you are fucking clearly missing her in some weird way probably because you don&amp;#x27;t feel you&amp;#x27;ll have someone as attractive/whatever as her. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; that was my 2 cents, you can now gtfo of my thread&lt;br&gt;lmao suck my cock retard you&amp;#x27;re the one making whiney cry threads about your ex on the fucking finance board. fuck off and go think of her being fucked on your own time retard&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862017&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861117&lt;br&gt;idk if anyone else itt has told you this yet but she was fuckin him before you broke up broski&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862029&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862014&lt;br&gt;are you dumb or what?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;i got her during her prime and i still dumped her because she was obviously not a good mother&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;she can&amp;#x27;t cook&lt;br&gt;she earns 800 euros per month&lt;br&gt;she got a credit to buy a bmw when we were together and when i asked her who is going to pay for the reparations if she crashes it (because there was nothing in her bank account) she answered that it should be my role&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;you don&amp;#x27;t even understand how much i would hate myself to have a kid with her&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;i just feel sorry for this cuck who is the last in the queue with a suit and flowers after all the town stretched her for peanuts&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862040&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862017&lt;br&gt;impossible, we were living together and she does nothing all day except watch netflix, vape and drink cola&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;i dumped her when i bought my flat and left her in the rental we were living and told her to keep the deposit and the tv &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;i abandoned her like a furniture because i was so fed up&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862041&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862029&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;are you dumb or what?&lt;br&gt;are you lonely or something? what the fuck are you talking about?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;i got her during her prime and i still dumped her because she was obviously not a good mother&lt;br&gt;yeah that must be why you&amp;#x27;re making cope threads about this cheating whore on the FINANCE BOARD of 4chan years later!&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;you don&amp;#x27;t even understand how much i would hate myself to have a kid with her&lt;br&gt;no, i dont GIVE A FUCK retard, this is the finance board no the &amp;quot;whine about my ex who i&amp;#x27;m not over and was fucking other guys while we were together&amp;quot; board&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;i just feel sorry for this cuck&lt;br&gt;at least we can agree on that, you retarded fucking cuck&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862047&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862040&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;impossible, we were living together and she does nothing all day except watch netflix, vape and drink cola&lt;br&gt;you&amp;#x27;re delusional and if even you read back your post you&amp;#x27;d understand how hard you&amp;#x27;re coping lmfao&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;i abandoned her like a furniture because i was so fed up&lt;br&gt;so fed up you have to make cope posts here and not fuck off to /soc/ to whine about your woman problems&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862056&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862047&lt;br&gt;you are writing a lot, thank you for bumping my thread&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862066&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862056&lt;br&gt;i see you have no further response and want to just sling shit at the wall. i hope you know you&amp;#x27;re pathetic and everyone here can see how transparent you are in regards to being hung up over your ex. your ex, by the way, has no doubt fucked countless men, likely while you were together and you were whining about her &amp;quot;vaping&amp;quot; or whatever the fuck. maybe go take your emotional trauma to /soc/ instead of the finance board of 4chan?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862077&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862066&lt;br&gt;incel much, you smell like jealousy&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;quot;no its not possible that she was trash, they are all queens and you need to simp for them and for sure she dumped you&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862080&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862077&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;incel much, you smell like jealousy&lt;br&gt;nobody here is jealous of someone so hung up on their ex they make /biz/ threads about them&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;no its not possible that she was trash&lt;br&gt;of course she&amp;#x27;s trash, she dated you, my point is you being hung up on her and making crying threads about it makes YOU look even worse. she was definitely cheating on you btw.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;heres another bump! :)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>there are people buying BTC at $67k expecting it to miraculously recover and moon to $300k+. — 28 replies — 112.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860893</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860893?lm=1771274174</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 20:36:14 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;there are people buying BTC at $67k expecting it to miraculously recover and moon to $300k+.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860893'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 28 • Updated: 2026-02-16 20:36 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;there are people buying BTC at $67k expecting it to miraculously recover and moon to $300k+. what is society doing to help these mentally ill people&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860896&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860893&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;what is society doing&lt;br&gt;collapsing expeditiously&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860897&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;idk why they do this but i will gladly buy their bags at 20-30K when they lose hope&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860925&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860893&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;there are people buying BTC at $5k expecting it to miraculously recover and moon to $100k+. what is society doing to help these mentally ill people&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;how you sound right now &lt;br&gt;Buy the Dip, Always Bank on the Bigger Fool&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860927&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860925&lt;br&gt;at 67K we are not at the dip, sorry&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860933&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m buying at $30k later this year and selling at $150k in 2029.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860934&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860893&lt;br&gt;people have given up on traditional means of success because basic things like owning the shelter over your head are out of reach for them. so they resort to risky financial behavior because they think that&amp;#x27;s the only way for them to really get ahead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860938&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860893&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;ll buy back at $8k once Saylor has capitulated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860972&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860933&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I&amp;#x27;m buying at a level that will never happen to sell at a price at only half the next ATH&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860981&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860893&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;expecting it to miraculously recover and moon to $300k+&lt;br&gt;uuuuh yes? retardo froggo. Not anytime soon, but yes in many years&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860988&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;bitcoin is an easy 3x from here, dude&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860990&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860893&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;we could be at the bottom now&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861000&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860927&lt;br&gt;Nigger we are -50% this is the bottom. The pumps are weaker but the dumps are too. Your brain is like a retarded child’s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861002&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860925&lt;br&gt;Except 100k had been tagged. The hype is done, the meme target was reached now what&amp;#x27;s left to keep this thing up long term is fundamentals&lt;br&gt;Oh wait&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861013&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860893&lt;br&gt;His name&amp;#x27;s Michael.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861023&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861000&lt;br&gt;this&lt;br&gt;bobotards are really expecting a -80% capitulation just like mumutards were expecting a 6x ATH from the last one&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861052&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861002&lt;br&gt;the meme target has always been bitcoin to $1,000,000&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861054&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860893&lt;br&gt;I expect it to fall a little further but I buy every week&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861058&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860893&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;There are people buying Bitcoin over $1 expect it to go to $100&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;What is wrong with these people&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Idk man&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861067&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;not buying until saylor capitulates&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861094&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861013&lt;br&gt;kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861100&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Moot spoke with Epstein via email&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Epstein got /pol/ created&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;flooding of BTC threads on /pol/ and /g/&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;/biz/ later created as crypto containment board&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;emails implicate Epstein on creating and /or getting BTC funded to extract wealth from lower class individuals.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bonus - Epstein asked by rich Elite friends if BTC worth is &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;anything via email.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;lol no” -Epstein&lt;br&gt;l&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861191&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861100&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;everything was made by Epstein because he emailed someone vaguely related to X &lt;br&gt;shalom&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861195&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861052&lt;br&gt;No, that was the fundamental long term target if BTC would be widely adopted. As a payment method it&amp;#x27;s even less adopted now than 10 years ago, the fundamental case is dead and buried. 100k it is sorry buddy, and it will never go to 100k again&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861199&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860938&lt;br&gt;It has to stay at $8k for 3 years for Strategy to be forced to sell some.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861243&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861199&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862007&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860934&lt;br&gt;people with that attitude are not going to be rewarded with gains. btc is basically guaranteed to crash imo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862021&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860893&lt;br&gt;because after over a decade people just can&amp;#x27;t seem to understand it takes a year for btc to fully crash after an ATH.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862065&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860893&lt;br&gt;No they don&amp;#x27;t. People bought at obvious support levels like 60k and sold at 72k for a free 20%. Meanwhile you&amp;#x27;re stuck holding USD which is constantly losing purchase power.&lt;br&gt;You are insecure and mad because buyers stop it from crashing further.&lt;br&gt;You are not a real bobo, you are a bull troon who wants to time the bottom which is why you deserve to get sidelined.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>/smg/ - Stock Market Gambling — 15 replies — 60.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861684</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861684?lm=1771274453</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 20:40:53 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;/smg/ - Stock Market Gambling&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861684'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 15 • Updated: 2026-02-16 20:40 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Casino Economy Edition&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Some helpful links to numb the pain&lt;br&gt;https://findahelpline.com/&lt;br&gt;https://www.nvidia.com/refunds/&lt;br&gt;https://www.whitehouse.gov/refunds&lt;br&gt;https://jlingz.com/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Educational sites:&lt;br&gt;https://www.investopedia.com&lt;br&gt;https://www.khanacademy.org/economics-finance-domain&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Financial TV Streams:&lt;br&gt;https://www.newslive.com/american/cnbc.html&lt;br&gt;https://www.livestreamy.net/bloomberg/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Charts:&lt;br&gt;https://www.tradingview.com&lt;br&gt;https://www.finscreener.com&lt;br&gt;https://www.portfoliovisualizer.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Screeners: so you feel like in the movies&lt;br&gt;https://finviz.com/&lt;br&gt;https://etfdb.com/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Gambling:&lt;br&gt;https://www.optionsplaybook.com/options-introduction/&lt;br&gt;https://www.optionsprofitcalculator.com&lt;br&gt;https://optionstrat.com/&lt;br&gt;https://www.optionistics.com/quotes/option-prices&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Pre-Market and Live data:&lt;br&gt;https://www.investing.com/indices/indices-futures&lt;br&gt;https://finance.yahoo.com/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Calendars&lt;br&gt;https://www.marketwatch.com/economy-politics/calendar&lt;br&gt;https://www.earningswhispers.com/calendar&lt;br&gt;https://www.cmegroup.com/trading/interest-rates/countdown-to-fomc.html&lt;br&gt;https://www.mortgagenewsdaily.com/data/building-permits&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Boomer Investing 101: so zoomers with meme stocks can outperform you&lt;br&gt;https://www.bogleheads.org/wiki/Getting_started&lt;br&gt;https://www.sec.gov/search-filings&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Misc smg:&lt;br&gt;https://www.financialjuice.com/home&lt;br&gt;https://finance.yahoo.com/trending-tickers&lt;br&gt;https://market24hclock.com/&lt;br&gt;https://www.dividendchannel.com/drip-returns-calculator&lt;br&gt;https://brokerchooser.com/&lt;br&gt;https://www.chathamfinancial.com/technology/us-market-rates&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Previously on /smg/: &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858740&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861716&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m an American, I have extreme anxiety that i can&amp;#x27;t sell or buy right now&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;so me, and my fellow americans formally decided were panic selling everything Tuesday&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;sorry euros&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861738&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861716&lt;br&gt;i just watch the spot silver chart and get either mad or relieved when it doesnt move very far from 75&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861835&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We Europoors fomo into shit that pumped during the american market hours then it pumps during premarket hours and then amerimutts wake up and cash in and leave europe holding the bag then we do the same shit next week regardless .&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861957&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What fictional holiday will the Jews come up with for next week as an excuse to keep the stock market closed?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861968&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861716&lt;br&gt;Don&amp;#x27;t care, I&amp;#x27;ve been avoiding everything American (both stocks and goods) for a while now. Fuck mutts and their hellhole of a country.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861974&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;inb4 /smg/schizo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861998&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; NFLX&lt;br&gt;where&amp;#x27;s the bottom bros&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862005&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;He bought&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862013&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861974&lt;br&gt;Ha kek! This place is worse than pmg now!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862034&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;smg crying about crypto chads&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;gets btfo&lt;br&gt;stay broke retards&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862035&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861707&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;carvana &lt;br&gt;God I wish I had the balls to short this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862038&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hope you all had a good Presidents’ Day&lt;br&gt;I hope you’re all ready to get back to work and provide some value to the shareholders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862039&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HMAX ANON, IN A PREVIOUS THREAD YOU TOLD ME TO INVEST IN HMAX WITH MY TFSA. I SIMPLY ASK WHY?&lt;br&gt;DO THIS, AND MY LIFE IS YOURS&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862088&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861957&lt;br&gt;Ash Wednesday&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Are people really shifting to the EU? I keep seeing more and more threads focussed on EU biz? Did Trump really fuck the… — 11 replies — 44.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861131</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861131?lm=1771274373</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 20:39:33 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Are people really shifting to the EU? I keep seeing more and more threads focussed on EU biz? Did Trump really fuck the…&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861131'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 11 • Updated: 2026-02-16 20:39 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Are people really shifting to the EU? I keep seeing more and more threads focussed on EU biz? Did Trump really fuck the US economy that much? Should i start investing in Europe too?&lt;br&gt;t.asian biz bro&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861139&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861131&lt;br&gt;no...that was the move over a year ago. those are the exit liquidity farming shills youre seeing&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861253&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861139&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;over a year ago&lt;br&gt;What about all the investment firms that started pulling out of the US over Trump&amp;#x27;s Greenland threats? This happened recently. Are you sure that the move has stopped or is it still ongoing?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861308&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861131&lt;br&gt;yes they have always been the main character. america is strong but there is nothing holy in this stolen country. it will always remain a european colony in spirit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861368&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861131&lt;br&gt;how many european companies do you know?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861374&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;he isn&amp;#x27;t already&lt;br&gt;I shiggy doo, better hurry up!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861920&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861131&lt;br&gt;America has been in a crab market since Oct and possibly a bear market since a few weeks. Meanwhile Europe is in a bull market. You need to pick the right ETFs and stocks though. Best ask Gemini. I&amp;#x27;m big on Siemens Energy and country index ETFs like UK, Poland, Italy, Greece, etc&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861932&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861131&lt;br&gt;There&amp;#x27;s literally nothing good about the EU for finance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861959&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I’m european and the shift from my childhood is just immense. Back then most of the music would be american, most of film and television, most video games ect. Nowdays there aren’t any big trends coming from USA anymore, nobody cares about american pop culture and it just feels mild and old fashioned.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861986&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861959&lt;br&gt;American pop culture is dogshit now. The US used to be where all the cool movies came from, now it&amp;#x27;s all slop.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862063&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861986&lt;br&gt;Yeah the last time american culture was cool was in like 2011 or so.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862081&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861131&lt;br&gt;Europe is a joke dude. Putting a bunch of dead civilizations into the same economic zone, salting it with Muslims, and picking a fight with both Russia and the US doesn’t look great. They don’t produce much, spend like crazy, don’t reproduce, and are filled with leftists and degenerates. In 50 years it’ll be an Islamic caliphate. You’re better off looking elsewhere&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>WHAT THE FUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUCK SHE JUST TIMED ANOTHER TOP — 7 replies — 23.8/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861785</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861785?lm=1771273419</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 20:23:39 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;WHAT THE FUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUCK SHE JUST TIMED ANOTHER TOP&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861785'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 7 • Updated: 2026-02-16 20:23 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHAT THE FUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUCK SHE JUST TIMED ANOTHER TOP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861796&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861785&lt;br&gt;This is why the price is crashing&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861854&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861785&lt;br&gt;If i saw this i would have felt safe shorting 100x&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861860&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861785&lt;br&gt;i bet they started shorting that very night&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861869&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861785&lt;br&gt;I kneel&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861981&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861785&lt;br&gt;She also did a post about getting all her friends to download phantom wallet at the pico top of the sol blow off top.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861994&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861785&lt;br&gt;imagine le smelle&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862000&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861785&lt;br&gt;Heyyyy boys come follow our new podcast, Big Boob Bitcoin Babes! We discuss everything about Bitcoin, boobs, vaginas and women! Women in crypto girls women females vagina&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>SAY IT /BIZ/ ETHEREUM = PROGRAMMABLE MONEY — 5 replies — 20.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860962</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860962?lm=1771273668</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 20:27:48 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;SAY IT /BIZ/ ETHEREUM = PROGRAMMABLE MONEY&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860962'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 5 • Updated: 2026-02-16 20:27 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;SAY IT /BIZ/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;ETHEREUM = PROGRAMMABLE MONEY&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860982&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860962&lt;br&gt;ultrasound chads can&amp;#x27;t stop winning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861322&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860962&lt;br&gt;lol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861377&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860962&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;PROGRAMMABLE MONEY&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;There is no use case for this in the real world&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;B-B-BUT-&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;No&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861389&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860962&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;$87M&lt;br&gt;Wow it&amp;#x27;s literally nothing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862015&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860962&lt;br&gt;Not going back to that 25 dollar swap fee scam chain. Also the eth team could just fork the entire project whenever they feel like it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>My new theory is the DOW Jones will go sideways for 9-12 months while crypto pumps the whole time. — 2 replies — 8.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61862059</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61862059?lm=1771274226</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 20:37:06 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;My new theory is the DOW Jones will go sideways for 9-12 months while crypto pumps the whole time.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61862059'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 2 • Updated: 2026-02-16 20:37 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;My new theory is the DOW Jones will go sideways for 9-12 months while crypto pumps the whole time. Your thoughts?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862071&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;i think you need to call your mother she&amp;#x27;s been very worried about you. We all have&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862072&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862059&lt;br&gt;I think that video of yours is very anti semetic oyvey goyim&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;No additional replies in the latest window.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>The US is in recession — 70 replies — 71.4/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61857490</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61857490?lm=1771270949</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 19:42:29 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;The US is in recession&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61857490'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 70 • Updated: 2026-02-16 19:42 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US is in recession&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857499&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White collar recession comes before regular recession 100% of the time. We&amp;#x27;ve been in a white collar recession since 2020.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857500&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;Always was, its depression for over a year now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857508&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;GDP is growing, recession is fake.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nothing ever happens. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stop putting your vibes and feelings into your job search, learn to get better skills and be more marketable to employers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;McDonalds is always hiring&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858397&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857499&lt;br&gt;Except 2022 had a labour shortage&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858404&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858383&lt;br&gt;https://fred.stlouisfed.org/series/CIVPART&lt;br&gt;Also I do not think they count gig workers as unemployed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858449&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858383&lt;br&gt;If you don&amp;#x27;t apply for one job a month, you&amp;#x27;re not unemployed. If you have a masters degree and you work at McDonald&amp;#x27;s, you&amp;#x27;re not unemployed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858696&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;I voted for this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858910&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857805&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Disrupted the international order from which the US greatly benefitted and everyone else benefited from the US even more&lt;br&gt;fuck off retard. did you forget&lt;br&gt;-single handedly carrying NATO&lt;br&gt;-protecting international shipping lanes&lt;br&gt;-being the global leader in innovation and tech&lt;br&gt;-only genuine believer and de facto practitioner of promoting human rights&lt;br&gt;? fuck you euronigger canacuck spic or whatever you are. we&amp;#x27;re allowed to take care of ourselves for once.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859778&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858910&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Wow america number one in everything when it created and proliferated a working order&lt;br&gt;Yeah no shit he already said that&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859785&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858023&lt;br&gt;Either Mossad agent or photoshopped picture&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859951&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857805&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;international order&lt;br&gt;jesus christ turn off the television. US economy (and western economy) is in tatters precisely because of the &amp;quot;international order&amp;quot; ie ZOG. They flood your country with cheap violent labor to suppress wages and sow division, they inflate away your wealth by constantly printing to pay the interest on government borrowing for GIBS for your replacements and zog wars. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How the fuck do you reach the conclusion that America needs an &amp;quot;international order&amp;quot; to function when it&amp;#x27;s downfall has correlated perfectly to its kowtowing to international interests. America is almost entirely self-sufficient and has plenty of skilled workers. It doesn&amp;#x27;t need an international order, it needs a financial sector that isn&amp;#x27;t destroying the country for its own benefit and it needs to get rid of the millions of useless eaters in your country. Get America back up to 70%+ White, fix your money printing problem, deal with the israel problem in your government, and the economy will take care of itself. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s just nuts to me that people talk about the economy without mentioning the giant rotting elephant in the room which is the trillions that gets siphoned from productive workers to various kike interests. The K-shaped economy isn&amp;#x27;t an accident it&amp;#x27;s deliberate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859958&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;DEI moneysinks getting destroyed&lt;br&gt;Sucks to suck. Go be a negro in Negrovia or something&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859986&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;Isn&amp;#x27;t it good for the US economy if everyone is losing their jobs to AI?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860143&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858383&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;go to jobcentre &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;get offerd the a streetsweeper&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;I din&amp;#x27;t waste 6 years of my life getting a master&amp;#x27;s to sweep puke and shit of the sidewalk&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;well if you don&amp;#x27;t want to work than you can&amp;#x27;t be unemployed, so no benefits for you&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;Call me Broomy-Mcbroomster guvna&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860535&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860143&lt;br&gt;I wish I got benefits, I&amp;#x27;ve been unemployed in Poland for 7 years now and I&amp;#x27;ve gotten a grand total of $0 in benefits&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860619&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859951&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Get America back up to 70%+ White, fix your money printing problem, deal with the israel problem in your government, and the economy will take care of itself.&lt;br&gt;anything else while we have the magic wand out sir?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860705&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859951&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;How the fuck do you reach the conclusion that America needs an &amp;quot;international order&amp;quot; to function when it&amp;#x27;s downfall has correlated perfectly to its kowtowing to international interests&lt;br&gt;What international interests? The US has been profiting off the international order since Breton Woods. Its rise as a superpower correlates to the dollar’s international dominance. It’s the opposite of what you’re describing.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;America is almost entirely self-sufficient&lt;br&gt;It is completely dependent on foreign pharmaceuticals and various input goods for manufacturing. It has virtually no domestic source of lithium, cobalt, graphite or REMs. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;the problem is international Jewry and this will be rectified when the us becomes an autarky &lt;br&gt;Why? &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rotting elephant in the room is a declining dollar, obscene debt, and an overinflated market + made up statistics. None of this gets better by fucking up international trade.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860719&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857750&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;US being in a recession isn&amp;#x27;t about Trump.&lt;br&gt;Yes he&amp;#x27;s a fucking retarded boomer brained moron, but US has been doomed to hit this point sooner or later ever since they decided to crank the money printers on permanently after 2008 and doomed the entire West to be stuck in a slow death limbo.&lt;br&gt;Everyone has basically just been waiting for the big one for years now and we&amp;#x27;re getting closer and closer to it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860738&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859951&lt;br&gt;You have no idea how the dollar system works and it shows. What&amp;#x27;s happening to the United States right now is irreversible&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860813&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860719&lt;br&gt;Printing after 2008 happened because 2008 happened, which happened because republicans deregulated finance. You&amp;#x27;re right, it&amp;#x27;s not about Trump, it&amp;#x27;s about half the country being fucking retarded hicks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860867&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860813&lt;br&gt;Republicans like Raegan deregulated finance, that’s true (though some of that was put into motion by Jimmy Carter). That said, it’s impossible to talk about 2008 without recognizing that Clinton is the one who repealed the Glass-Steagall act and let insurance banking merge with commercial banking. Pretty much every president for the 30 years leading up to 2008 did something to enable it or make it worse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860880&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860867&lt;br&gt;I forgot that Clinton was also the one that made derivatives immune to regulation. He really fucked up finance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860916&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857825&lt;br&gt;Holy shit this is the most retarded post I have ever read on /biz/, why are you on a finance board??&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860980&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860880&lt;br&gt;Clinton also forced banks to give mortgages to people with bad credit scores and low income&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861063&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857508&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;GDP was never meant to measure the health of the economy. Simon Kuznets advised against using it for that purpose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861445&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860705&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;It has virtually no domestic source of lithium, cobalt, graphite or REMs. &lt;br&gt;There are actually fucking tons of sources, but none of them are developed because US companies exported the environmental cost of mining them to &amp;quot;dEvElOpInG&amp;quot; nations for cheaper labor/materials and most of the mines shut down because they couldn&amp;#x27;t compete. There are ludicrous amounts of these materials just sitting there in the US.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US could be self-sufficient (example: fracking boom was because oil price had gotten to the point where domestic supply was economically viable again - in less than a decade the US had more oil than it could even use, because the oil was already in the ground, just not being extracted), but the profit motive won&amp;#x27;t allow self-sufficiency to persist if it&amp;#x27;s cheaper to import.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861531&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861445&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;”we are almost entirely self-sufficient”&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;”ok we currently have no infrastructure to mine these resources”&lt;br&gt;Yes, exactly. We are totally dependent on foreign suppliers and as of right now we do not have a domestic source for these things. My point stands and yours is wrong. Coping about how we COULD have these things eventually doesn’t matter. Like it or not, the US is not self-sufficient, and it isn’t close. We import tremendous amounts of goods. Don’t even bother looking into pharmaceuticals because it will just depress you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861694&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857750&lt;br&gt;We&amp;#x27;ve been in a recession since 2023. This isn&amp;#x27;t glorphf&amp;#x27;s fault or joepedo. Our economy is fake and gay made up of jewish daycare bullshit jobs. Soon it will all unravel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861711&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861531&lt;br&gt;Don&amp;#x27;t get your panties in a bunch, all I took issue with was saying &amp;quot;virtually no domestic source.&amp;quot; Some people in these discussions act like SEA is the only place in the world that has minerals.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A water source is still there even if nobody builds a well. Since you seem to get that, you were probably looking for the phrase &amp;quot;domestic SUPPLY.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861724&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857805&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oh no, its over, the Europeans and Anglos are mad we voted a republican again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861729&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858084&lt;br&gt;The fantasy is better than the reality&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861769&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857805&lt;br&gt;We should be bombing Mexico.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861811&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861711&lt;br&gt;No I wasn’t. I don’t feel like explaining it to you so I’ll just let AI do it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>GERMANY TO END BURGERGELD PROGRAMS — 65 replies — 68.2/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858970</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858970?lm=1771271045</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 19:44:05 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;GERMANY TO END BURGERGELD PROGRAMS&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858970'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 65 • Updated: 2026-02-16 19:44 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;WILL BE REPLACED WITH A STRICTER PROGRAM IF YOU REFUSE WORK. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEXT STOP, PRIVATIZED HEALTHCARE.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858974&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Uh oh, Europeans actually have to work for a living now? Aw shucks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858980&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858974&lt;br&gt;They will soon legalize 12 hour work days much like Argentina has done. Even contributing 5% of their GDP to NATO has ultimately bankrupted them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859007&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858970&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wait you could get NEETbux in Germany this whole time by simply “refusing to work”? WTF&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860177&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860147&lt;br&gt;all of this applies to america which is below 40% white&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860191&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Germnanys real current issue is that they might run out of Gas and then its lights out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860401&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858970&lt;br&gt;still easy to get around that.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;go to job center appointment smelling like smegma and piss&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;send half assed CV to places that hire&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;nobody will hire you anyway&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;if they invite you to some interview just pretend to be officer doofy tier retarded&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;continue getting NEETbucks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860422&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859979&lt;br&gt;Shouldn&amp;#x27;t you be updating your resume instead of wasting time on 4chan? It&amp;#x27;ll be hard to explain the 10+ year gap in employment to interviewers, but I&amp;#x27;m sure you&amp;#x27;ll come up with something.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860441&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860422&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;It&amp;#x27;ll be hard to explain the 10+ year gap &lt;br&gt;a 10+ year gap is good and makes you unemployable.&lt;br&gt;also talk really slow like a retard and pretend not to know more complicated words. like just play an idiot. you will never have to wagecuck again and can collect neetbux freely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860446&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860441&lt;br&gt;Why are you on this board if you aim to live in poverty?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860499&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860422&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;the super sewious big boy wageslave loses his shit on 4chan&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;the post wasn&amp;#x27;t even directed at him &lt;br&gt;lol lmao even&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860527&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860446&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;hurr durr the only way to make money is by sucking a jews dick&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860538&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860527&lt;br&gt;wageslaves are so traumatized by wageslavery and interviewing that they&amp;#x27;re spreading their defeatism everywhere they go as a shitty coping mechanism. You know that they&amp;#x27;re forcing goyim to humiliate themselves with 5-10 round interviews nowadays? Insane.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860550&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860538&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;wagecuck&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;hypergamble to a few million&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;live in poverty on welfare&lt;br&gt;Not great options. I choose to wagecuck.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860567&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860527&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;You just can&amp;#x27;t have a business, ok????&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860591&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860550&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;it&amp;#x27;s either the whip or picking cotton&lt;br&gt;That false dichotomy is sure proof of wageslave brainrot. I don&amp;#x27;t blame you, though. The whole system is rigged against you from birth and every aspect of your human nature is weaponized against you by the very thing you&amp;#x27;re meant to worship as a social animal, i.e. society.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860601&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858970&lt;br&gt;They just gave away all our money to Ausländers and now that the social systems are running dry they are simply getting rid of them kek.&lt;br&gt;Nothing they do will fix this. Humanity is doomed.&lt;br&gt;Accelerationism is the only way.&lt;br&gt;Let the third world starve and divert fund into AI datacenters.&lt;br&gt;The wolf will chew its own leg off to survive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860612&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860601&lt;br&gt;third world is the biggest net exporter of food to the point frenchoids were crying it would kill their overpriced artistical wine or something, they aint starving bro&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860626&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860591&lt;br&gt;Sorry chief, I find the idea of opening a business to be enticing but I don’t see any sort of moat I could pursue with it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860651&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858970&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858974&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860660&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860612&lt;br&gt;Africa imports a lot of food&lt;br&gt;And France was rightfully complaining that imposing huge restrictions on European agriculture while signing free trade agreements with countries having little restrictions is retarded&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860678&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859446&lt;br&gt;a 10% reduction? kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860682&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860422&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;10 year gap&lt;br&gt;I tell them it is due to the government forcing employers to lower standards to hire the affirmative action subhumans. They never call me back, because they are off giving useless lazy meritless and sometime convict affirmative action subhumans jobs. &lt;br&gt;Enjoy paying to taxes to niggers, spics, and cunts that hate you, just in the vain hopes they one day stop calling you a racist and sexist. Get back to work wagie... the whole economy rests on you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860686&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860191&lt;br&gt;Gas?!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860707&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860422&lt;br&gt;kek, they won&amp;#x27;t work at all, german economy will implode and as merz said they already can&amp;#x27;t afford the welfare + pensions, it will just shrink till it gets too low to live then they will just kys as by now they are legit unable to live at all&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860723&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859099&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;this nigga thinks German economy circa 1988 is anything like today&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lol&lt;br&gt;Lmao even&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860724&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860401&lt;br&gt;a drooly retard eh? yeah that sounds just perfect for our new expanded military, the bundeswehr needs you to pick this uniform, this little sign and just stand there to block the evil russian drones with your face for us&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860758&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;tfw the only time in my life where I might receive neetbux for a few months is the exact time this happens&lt;br&gt;fucking lol my entire life is me getting fucked by the universe. Nothing good ever happens to me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860764&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860626&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;moat&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;he fell for Buffett boomer brain rot &lt;br&gt;The only moats Buffett had were his generous throat and his congressman daddy. And let&amp;#x27;s not forget about being lucky enough to be born in close proximity to swollen jewish nuts in Israel&amp;#x27;s 2nd state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860766&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860758&lt;br&gt;join a gang, sell weed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861462&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858970&lt;br&gt;NooOoOO&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861576&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858970&lt;br&gt;thats gut. not because of the money, it wont help in any significant way but because its a statement. fuck bürgis, fuck ausländer&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861599&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858970&lt;br&gt;They have been rebranding the same system for almost 25 years now. The previous government eased up on some of the welfare restrictions because they were largely pointless. The new(old) sanctions don&amp;#x27;t really change anything because even with them you can be permanently on welfare in Germany as long as you show up to your jobcenter appointments. Nobody in Germany is going to hire someone who hasn&amp;#x27;t worked for years and is clearly just applying because the jobcenter is pressuring them. This is just a huge waste of everyone&amp;#x27;s time and part of Germany&amp;#x27;s soviet-tier obscuring of unemployment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861817&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860422&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;It&amp;#x27;ll be hard to explain the 10+ year gap&lt;br&gt;16 years gapmaxxer here, would you hire me?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>So... is this "le AI will take your jerb!" just a lame FUD to make people (men, really) focus on becoming electricians,… — 21 replies — 64.6/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860974</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860974?lm=1771273305</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 20:21:45 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;So... is this &amp;quot;le AI will take your jerb!&amp;quot; just a lame FUD to make people (men, really) focus on becoming electricians,…&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860974'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 21 • Updated: 2026-02-16 20:21 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;So... is this &amp;quot;le AI will take your jerb!&amp;quot; just a lame FUD to make people (men, really) focus on becoming electricians, plumbers,or construction workers out of fear of being unemployed in the future? Society is running out of people interested on being blue collars, after all&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860984&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No it&amp;#x27;s just overselling shit on levels you&amp;#x27;ve never even dreamed were possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860993&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;every narrative is always fake and gay, just do the opposite of what jews say&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861009&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860974&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;just a lame FUD to make people (men, really) focus on becoming electricians,&lt;br&gt;It is FUD meant to oversell the technology and justify spending.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;It can destroy the world&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;It will take all the jobs&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;It is the most powerful and terrible thing ever&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;And this is because you must give us your money&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861012&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860974&lt;br&gt;That&amp;#x27;s why you have illegal immigrants doing it for half the cost.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;But don&amp;#x27;t worry, in a few years there will be waymo robot fleets that you can hire to do plumbing for 20$&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861030&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860974&lt;br&gt;I don’t know &lt;br&gt;But what I do know is if a Jew is saying it, then it’s a lie.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861182&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861009&lt;br&gt;I was imagining white hetero guys being strategically denied jobs by roasties as well, jews want women in position of power doing bullshit white collar jobs while men have to clean the toilets for a living. Men get no respect from women anymore, stay demoralized and depressed, while these &amp;quot;successful&amp;quot; women that have breakfast and brunchs every hour in the office aim for nepo jewish babies and give them childrenses. But yeah it&amp;#x27;s also about selling smoke, make profits from retards. What a circus the West has become, oh boy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861239&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861012&lt;br&gt;By plumbing, do you mean service my wife?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861575&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861239&lt;br&gt;No, that job will never be taken from the illegals&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861608&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860974&lt;br&gt;Not at all.&lt;br&gt;I am using AI to do basically all my work these days.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;claude spit out a RACI matrix in confluence markdown language for my new program.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;gemeni draw me a pyramid with 3 sections labeled such and such&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;chatgpt how do I even do my job?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;claude draw me a flow chart in mermaid format that is as follows&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is not a meme. AI can replace almost any white collar job right now if it is trained and focused on that role. Give it a couple years and they&amp;#x27;ll be good enough to just replace you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861611&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860974&lt;br&gt;the point is to demoralize people during a time when it&amp;#x27;s easier than ever to build stuff and take control of things&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861623&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;its powerful if you&amp;#x27;re a sigma male. the issue is you still need a network to push things + capital to make the numbers go up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861626&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860974&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;electricians, plumbers, contractors &lt;br&gt;Making a significant portion of their revenues from white-collar clients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861670&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860974&lt;br&gt;For all the &amp;quot;AI taking all the jobs&amp;quot; yap, I still get up every day and go to work, so guess it&amp;#x27;s BS&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861687&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861670&lt;br&gt;this essentially, I don&amp;#x27;t know anyone IRL who has told me &amp;quot;i lost my job because of AI, fugg&amp;quot; that&amp;#x27;s why I tell is just FUD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861691&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860974&lt;br&gt;I hope it takes my job. Cause I hate my job.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861737&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861687&lt;br&gt;most people still don&amp;#x27;t know how to harness it. think about how long it took for companies to even get half decent websites.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861756&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860974&lt;br&gt;It’s literal Indian scammers (tech CEOs) trying to pump their bags before they dump on retail and the gravy train comes to an end. LLMs are a dead end&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861803&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861009&lt;br&gt;How do you explain the mass layoffs then if it&amp;#x27;s all just made up hype? I see people on LinkedIn that have been unemployed for over a year complaining about AI taking their positions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861865&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Humans don&amp;#x27;t have the capacity to evaluate things in order, it&amp;#x27;s either on or off. People fantasize about having to survive in the post-apocalyptic world after most of humanity has been wiped out but can&amp;#x27;t fathom the same end result happening slowly after years and decades. The same thing is true about AI&amp;#x27;s effect on the job market. People can only think about AI either being shit and irrelevant or so advanced it makes their job obsolete. The reality is that AI will slowly but surely get integrated into most jobs, just like all technology is. Think about social media, the internet, computers, phones, calculators, etc. They have all become part of business and they have all changed the job market in unpredictable ways. We thought social media and the internet would connect us and bring countless benefits, the reality is that we are more divided, hateful, and exploited. The only guarantee is wages wont increase to keep pace with productivity and workers will suffer. Technology always has and always will benefit the business owners and harms the workers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;TLDR: you will still have to work, you will get less money, and there is nothing you can do about it because technology is the enemy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861983&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861803&lt;br&gt;either lies or bots, what else my friend? Don&amp;#x27;t tell me you trust (((linkedin))) or the media, lol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861991&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860974&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s demoralisation posting. Anyone who visits alternative media like 4chan must be forcibly blackpilled and distracted&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Oldfags I summon you — 36 replies — 39.9/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61856347</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61856347?lm=1771271228</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 19:47:08 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Oldfags I summon you&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61856347'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 36 • Updated: 2026-02-16 19:47 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oldfags I know you&amp;#x27;re still here. A lot of charts look like they&amp;#x27;ve bottomed. Tell me what to stack I have 3.8 BTC and looking to acquire alts as I think they will start pumping now the money printers returning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856352&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;looking to acquire alts&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856368&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856347&lt;br&gt;Took one of these Topgolf girls to a round of golf once and they were terrible lmao&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856433&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856368&lt;br&gt;What the fuck is a topgolf girl that girls swing is immaculate 99% of people at these ranges cannot hit a ball straight&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856550&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856347&lt;br&gt;ethbtc is sus, I dont think cz is finished dumping on wintermute for now!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856551&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856347&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;looks like it bottomed&lt;br&gt;Holy shit I swear biz is full of handicapped newfags. Just check the previous cycles, the bear market started THREE MONTHS ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856682&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856347&lt;br&gt;how many bitcoin for a golf bunny like that?&lt;br&gt;also moar&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856732&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856347&lt;br&gt;old fags no longer hold crypto&lt;br&gt;t. old fag&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856793&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856732&lt;br&gt;this desu&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856797&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856347&lt;br&gt;we finna linu&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857022&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856488&lt;br&gt;The only weird guy are you assuming you have to hire a girl to go play golf with her&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857025&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856551&lt;br&gt;Nah everything was frontrunned, the alt bear market started more then a year ago&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857031&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;alts will never pump again&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;the only notable alt that pumped last cycle was xrp&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;unless you&amp;#x27;re counting like a 2-3x as pumping then goodluck, they can also fall 90% or more from here&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857237&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Binance coin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857946&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856509&lt;br&gt;You guys are faggots man&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857986&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857025&lt;br&gt;this look to alts the bear market started in jan 2025&lt;br&gt;btc was just lucky some boomers pumped the etf to get a higher high in oct, but this market has been a ghost town for the past year&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858251&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856347&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;looking to acquire alts&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;re doomed. Shitcoins aren&amp;#x27;t going to pump ever again. I sincerely doubt ETH will even survive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858300&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856347&lt;br&gt;Not an originalfag or a 2017 oldfag, but I am a 2019 unc. Get out now and for the love of God stay away from alts, not even memeing. The bear was confirmed the moment we closed under 100k.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I rotated to stocks back in November.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856551&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856732&lt;br&gt;this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858317&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856509&lt;br&gt;how&amp;#x27;d you find her name? also what is it? asking for a fren&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858346&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856732&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858300&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856551&lt;br&gt;jewish posts&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860179&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856433&lt;br&gt;I hit straight balls if you know what I mean :)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860219&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oldest fag possible. Migrated day one from /g/. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The real dumping hasn&amp;#x27;t started yet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860260&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856551&lt;br&gt;Looks ljke the next &amp;#x27;cycle&amp;#x27; is going to go alll the wayy to 155k.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860609&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meaningfully buying across any of these is extremely high confidence, with particular emphasis on the front end:&lt;br&gt;XRP, QNT, CC, XDC, ALGO, DAG, HBAR, XLM, SUI, SEI, APT, FLR, ONDO, NOM, ADA, HYPE, SOL, POL, ATOM, DAG, AAVE, DOT, VET, ZRO, RED.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860614&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ancientfag here (I used to mine btc on my gaming pc back in 2012)&lt;br&gt;why are faggots still falling for the jeetcoin rugpulls in &amp;lt;current year&amp;gt;?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860615&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Topgolf is retarded&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Everytime I went the place was filled with whores, niggers and trailer trash&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860630&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860615&lt;br&gt;this is everywhere except certain higher grocery stores.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860639&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856347&lt;br&gt;XRP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860653&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856347&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;a bitch like that will make more money in a year than 90% of normal men will make in a decade &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;women will still call this society a fucking patriarchy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861628&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860219&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The real dumping hasn&amp;#x27;t started yet.&lt;br&gt;what will dump the least, or what will gain the most as the rest dumps?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861782&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860653&lt;br&gt;They only say that because 99% of billionaires are men.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861800&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856347&lt;br&gt;She probably leaves the cutest little turds in the toilet you ever seen&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861818&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860653&lt;br&gt;shows what kind of man you are really. My friend complained to me once about how unfair it was that girls can make easy money being whores on OF and social media and I told him that he was pretty much complaining about how he can&amp;#x27;t show his cock and balls on the internet for money just because he is a man, and that makes him a faggot&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861828&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860219&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;That fact that you even know buttcoin was on /g/ before the containment board /biz/, proves to me you are a confirmed oldfag. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Based.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>&gt;Saylor will be liquida—ACK! — 38 replies — 38.2/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858109</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858109?lm=1771270893</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 19:41:33 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;&amp;gt;Saylor will be liquida—ACK!&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858109'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 38 • Updated: 2026-02-16 19:41 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;Saylor will be liquida—ACK!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858119&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;So we have to short squeeze bitcoin until 8k? &lt;br&gt;Noted&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858128&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Challenge accepted&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858135&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858109&lt;br&gt;Hostile takeovers will take place long before that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858216&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858109&lt;br&gt;Hes not going to sell&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858224&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858178&lt;br&gt;why does it matter if he&amp;#x27;s down 7 billion? the debt isn&amp;#x27;t due... seriously plz explain to me why it matters and why he can&amp;#x27;t just wait for the inevitable recovery?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858229&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858224&lt;br&gt;Explain how he repays creditors without diluting shareholders (baggies) to zero, if Bitcorn stays supressed for any significant period.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858234&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858229&lt;br&gt;the argument is that buttcorns stay at $8k for years? is that right?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858301&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858109&lt;br&gt;Im pretty sure a bank will call the loans long before it hits $8k because what the fuck would liquidating $6 billion of BTC do to the price even at todays levels?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858224&lt;br&gt;the banks will call in their loans if the collateral loses value long before $8k. retards like you dont understand that the bid/ask price is meaningless when you are trying to liquidate 715,000 btc. and that selling this in a short period of time would destroy order books and crash the market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858314&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858234&lt;br&gt;It doesn&amp;#x27;t need to, the stock is alreaady crashing because everyone knows he can;t keep up this scam for much longer. Even if the government is turning a blind eye now to his ponzi scheme.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858315&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Let&amp;#x27;s go 7.9k BTC!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858325&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858109&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;if Bitcoin falls to $8k, we have so much Bitcoin we could sell like you wouldn&amp;#x27;t even believe&lt;br&gt;Really confidence inspiring.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858370&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858128&lt;br&gt;CZ will either win or give us the greatest discount in history while he simultaneously send the whole crypto market to the brink of extinction&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858405&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858109&lt;br&gt;Btc to 7.9k confirmed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858418&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858109&lt;br&gt;So what happens when it drops to $7900?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858439&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858109&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858452&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858109&lt;br&gt;Anyone want to speculate what MSTR share price would be at BTC $8K …kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858499&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858418&lt;br&gt;He just refinances with a finger snap. ezpz.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858501&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Don&amp;#x27;t they have to make payments on that debt though, which will draw down assets further&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858608&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858301&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; bank loans&lt;br&gt;Where did you even get this information from? Afaik he has only take one bank loan from SVB which was paid back a long time ago.&lt;br&gt;His debt comes from convertible notes which won&amp;#x27;t mature before the next cycle (not in this bear market unless it&amp;#x27;s a multi year bear).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; selling this in a short period of time would destroy order books&lt;br&gt;He would never sell on the open markets. He can sell it to OTC services which will be able to finance whatever amount he has to sell.&lt;br&gt;Some 2011 whale sold 80k BTCs to Galaxy Digital when BTC was trading at 110k.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858619&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This jew is a ponzi scam artist and crypto lards only support him because they think he is doing the work of finding greater fools which is what they need for their own bags to go up&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859185&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858171&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;price dumps to $8k in effort to liquidate saylor&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;unsuccessful&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;those sellers don&amp;#x27;t buy back in at giga-generational wealth creating dips&lt;br&gt;sounds like bitcoin ain&amp;#x27;t the one&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859214&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858501&lt;br&gt;bro they just refinance and roll it forward, its simple&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859218&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858171&lt;br&gt;Whales know it doesn&amp;#x27;t even have to go that low. Keeping it at 30-40k for a few years could be sufficient.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859228&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858234&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;$8k&lt;br&gt;Check MSTR&amp;#x27;s price action when bitcoin is around $70k right now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859235&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858178&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;lowering your DCA is le bad&lt;br&gt;Okay retard&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859963&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859228&lt;br&gt;what does that have to do with Strategy&amp;#x27;s obligation to sell BTC?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;did you even read the thread?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860237&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858501&lt;br&gt;lol no, their convertible notes have a 0% coupon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860245&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The jeet brain can&amp;#x27;t comprehend Strategy&amp;#x27;s business model.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860247&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858109&lt;br&gt;ChatGPT says ther total liabilities are actually 15BN as of q3 2025 filings, but that still gives them a 60BN net asset position. I guess they&amp;#x27;re actually in a pretty safe position in terms of debt/margin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860391&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858152&lt;br&gt;Too many other players with too much skin in the game for them to do this. Pension funds, corpos and governments are tied to bitcoin now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860465&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860237&lt;br&gt;What about the coupé notes?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861801&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858109&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;ll be buying at $7999 then&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861808&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858178&lt;br&gt;Wow big deal. just refinance at a lower rate&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Is living anywhere except Los Angeles, San Francisco, Washington DC, or New York the same as admitting that your life is… — 64 replies — 34.9/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858975</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858975?lm=1771267869</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 18:51:09 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Is living anywhere except Los Angeles, San Francisco, Washington DC, or New York the same as admitting that your life is…&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858975'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 64 • Updated: 2026-02-16 18:51 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Is living anywhere except Los Angeles, San Francisco, Washington DC, or New York the same as admitting that your life is meaningless and that you are NOT the main character and will never make it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858982&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;Dubai, Paris, London, Tokyo, Kyoto&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858987&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You burgers aren&amp;#x27;t ready for what&amp;#x27;s coming&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858990&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;HAHAHA&lt;br&gt;HAHAHAHA&lt;br&gt;IMAGINE LIVING IN A BROWN SHITHOLE&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859311&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;san fran&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;dc&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The only cities worth living in are NYC, Miami, and LA. Saying anything else is pure cope.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859314&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859303&lt;br&gt;Boise, Idaho. I have lived all over the United States, including in several supposedly very &amp;quot;trendy&amp;quot; cities according to faggots like OP, and nothing comes remotely close to Boise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859319&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859279&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Walk through skid row right now&lt;br&gt;Good boy, you memorized the name of the worst street in Los Angeles. Wonder how many people know the name of your city. Skid Row is 45 minutes away from me btw, that&amp;#x27;s how large this city is.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859324&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OP and &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858982 are correct for the most part. Most people ITT seem to be falling for /pol/ memes, are scared, or it’s sour grapes, but if you actually want to have upward economic mobility, living in a major metro area is almost necessary. Certainly makes it so much easier. &lt;br&gt;I know it’s cliche but it’s true that your network is everything. And the best place to build a good network and have the best economic opportunities is in a major city. &lt;br&gt;I grew up poor as fuck in central valley CA (209 represent) but moved to SF after college and I now have a 8 figure networth and an incredible career. That would not have happened if I lived anywhere else.&lt;br&gt;Haters will say it’s false&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859347&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;There are retards that honestly believe this and get stabbed by an AIDS infected needle waiting for a bus that&amp;#x27;s 45 minutes late. Meanwhile I work an easy job here in Tennessee and dump everything into investments and have a higher networth with a better quality of life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859355&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;All of these cities are NPC central dude. The objective in life is to live as far away from bug men as possible, in peace, and with a lot of land. You are insane to want to live in these places&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859373&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859314&lt;br&gt;Sounds comfy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859400&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859021&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;you can&amp;#x27;t even swim in the water after it rains.&lt;br&gt;Why?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859407&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859314&lt;br&gt;Dude shut the fuck up, next thing you know youll be flooded with 869848584 billion brown californians. Ops doing you a favor, dont end up like us (colorado)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859450&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858987&lt;br&gt;what&amp;#x27;s coming?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;hard to imagine how you &amp;quot;make it&amp;quot; blowing all your money on taxes, rent, parking, and getting nickle and dimed 1000x other ways&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859453&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859001&lt;br&gt;i took an uber ride through SF a bit ago to go to a tiki bar. there&amp;#x27;s millionaires bathing in wealth mixed in with fent zombies and literal bottles of piss and shit just scattered along the street. it&amp;#x27;s a very fucked place&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859461&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859314&lt;br&gt;Come visit Creston BC sometime &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1488&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859463&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859043&lt;br&gt;Gays really aren&amp;#x27;t that bad. Just let them pack fudge in peace and enjoy the nice weather and unparalleled upward mobility opportunities that san fran has to offer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859468&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859319&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;45 minutes away in LA&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oh so it&amp;#x27;s 5 miles away?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;LA is filled with tards. I guess the weather is nice. I bet that guy you&amp;#x27;re replying to lives in Boise, Idaho though. The nicest city in America by far.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859470&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859400&lt;br&gt;All of the runoff concentrates into drainages that dump directly into the ocean. It doesn&amp;#x27;t rain often so months of garbage, human shit, needles collect in the street and dump directly into the ocean.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;https://www.pacificsurf.com/surfing-after-it-rains/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;A few of the things you could get are ear infections, sinus infections, pink eye, the flu,gastroenteritis, MRSA, Hepatitis, and Staph.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860590&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;d consider living there after you threw all the non-Whites out. Otherwise, I&amp;#x27;d visit it but not stay there permanently.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860659&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Assuming you’ve made it, what are the benefits of living in these cities when job opportunities are no longer a factor&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860666&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;No. You can also live in a remote cabin in Alaska. At least until your old crew calls you out of retirement for one last job.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860681&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;My life is given meaning through devotion and love for the LORD Jesus Christ&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860712&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859314&lt;br&gt;Guarantee me a couple of slam piglets and a square meal and I&amp;#x27;ll see what I can do about sabotaging the caravans wheels to steer it on coarse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860728&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;imagine living in new york, not being the richest guy in new york, and imagining that living in new york means your life isn&amp;#x27;t meaningless&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860769&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858982&lt;br&gt;t. lolicerdo criminal&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860793&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;Living anywhere except Los Angeles, San Francisco, Washington DC, or New York is the same as admitting that your life is meaningless and that you are NOT the main character and will never make it.&lt;br&gt;This is true. Imagine living anywhere near these mega slave cities.&lt;br&gt;You will just be worker number 10000000. Almost anywhere else is better.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860802&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859145&lt;br&gt;Holy shit imagine thinking thats a good place to live in. The nederlands are already way overpopulated. Our natural habitat which means the place we are most happy at is the forest with a small group of tribespeople.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860804&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860793&lt;br&gt;*in&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860828&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Is living anywhere except Chongqing, Shanghai, Beijing, Guangzhou and Shenzhen the same as admitting that your life is meaningless and that you are NOT the main character and will never make it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861578&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859032&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;thirdie hivan complains but won&amp;#x27;t move back(will move to oc instead)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861585&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;I live in Chinook montana. I would ask for nothing else&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861591&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;I am from D.C.&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s full of drones. Some are deluded enough to think being the GS-15 in charge of whatever the fuck department for whatever government agency actually makes them important.&lt;br&gt;It doesn&amp;#x27;t.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861595&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858990&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;IMAGINE LIVING IN A BROWN SHITHOLE&lt;br&gt;D.C. suburbs in 2012 be like...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>$ICP just partnered with the government of Pakistan — 42 replies — 33.5/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61850558</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61850558?lm=1771269956</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 19:25:56 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;$ICP just partnered with the government of Pakistan&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61850558'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 42 • Updated: 2026-02-16 19:25 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=r-RmZyeuxzo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850566&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;ICY PEE PARTNERS WITH POO &lt;br&gt;so the prophecy was right icy pee poo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850573&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850566&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;WITH POO&lt;br&gt;You mean one of the most populated countries on planet Earth? Seethe more linky retard and kill yourself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850584&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850558&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I can tell this is hogwash because it&amp;#x27;s news anouncement via Youtube.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851054&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850558&lt;br&gt;Won’t the Jews be upset with this?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851101&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850566&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851112&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850558&lt;br&gt;Holy fuck this is so BEARISH&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851240&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851054&lt;br&gt;Upset because of what? Because the icp devs bribes some pakistani to announce some bullshit on twitter?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851416&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851240&lt;br&gt;Why open your mouth when you don&amp;#x27;t know what you&amp;#x27;re saying?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851738&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850558&lt;br&gt;i&amp;#x27;ve been to the world computer summit in june last year and i&amp;#x27;ve talked to anyone in the team that i came across. let me tell you one thing; they&amp;#x27;re comfortable. they all get hundreds of thousands in salaries each year and could not care less about the price. at the event there were two very clear very seperate pockets. the VC&amp;#x27;s and the (((COMMUNITY))) and you could see the disgust in the eyes of the VC&amp;#x27;s for the community. any questions regarding tech or details to the team were answered dismissively, there is not an ounce of passion present in the entire team. i think all they care about is doing research on cryptography.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; i&amp;#x27;ve met the guy from openchat and he looked like he hadn&amp;#x27;t slept a full 8h in several weeks, he looked anxious and stressed.&lt;br&gt;when talking to the community members i&amp;#x27;ve probed for interesting projects, and literally the best project present was windoge98.&lt;br&gt;after that dominic played with an llm on stage for an hour straight everyone pretended it&amp;#x27;s the second coming of steve jobs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;they gave away bags of coffee because of caffeine.ai and it was unironically the best thing at the event. so good i even thought about licensing the coffee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851740&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851040&lt;br&gt;So Pakistanis are now jeets too?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851814&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850926&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;ppl&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851833&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851416&lt;br&gt;Im just guessing&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851740&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;So Pakistanis are now jeets too?&lt;br&gt;???? Always were. Bangladesh and Sri lanka too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61852144&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850558&lt;br&gt;The Saarnet&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61852793&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850584&lt;br&gt;Don&amp;#x27;t know about this one but poos did sign many crypto deals with trump. Ironically crypto has been dumping since&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853251&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851833&lt;br&gt;Pakistanis are white&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853281&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;61853251&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853296&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850611&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;AI licenses&lt;br&gt;So this is a thirdie government jumping the gun and getting in the way of something that people aren&amp;#x27;t doing yet to make sure that they don&amp;#x27;t start, just so they can take a cut if anyone dares to try. Classic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853824&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853296&lt;br&gt;Man shut the fuck up, you sound like a bitch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853832&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853281&lt;br&gt;racist&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853871&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850642&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850740&lt;br&gt;pakistans hate indians tho, its actually p based&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853919&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853871&lt;br&gt;Only Indians can be jeets, end of&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854123&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851738&lt;br&gt;This checks out with my impression of DFINITY. They are extremely arrogant and have borderline disdain for their own users. And honestly the Pakistan news is demoralizing. Yes the tech is great but God damn I am down by about $50K. And mission 70 is not the solution -- gaining adoption is.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854128&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850558&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853824&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853832&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853919&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;SARR PAKISTANIS ARE WHITE SARR&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854229&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For some reason I misread that as plundered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854266&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854128&lt;br&gt;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/India%E2%80%93Pakistan_relations&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854891&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854128&lt;br&gt;Pakistanis are more white than an average American lol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854914&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850566&lt;br&gt;holy kek..&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857209&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850566&lt;br&gt;witnessed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860272&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854914&lt;br&gt;you kek at racism?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860593&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850558&lt;br&gt;ICPoo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860624&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850558&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;internet &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;computer&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;holy kek - only for Pookistani this might sound exotic and alluring&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861733&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850558&lt;br&gt;icp parterned with pakistan? well fuckin whoop whoop my brothers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>My wife doesn’t appreciate long term investing — 55 replies — 17.9/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61853689</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61853689?lm=1771263434</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:37:14 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;My wife doesn’t appreciate long term investing&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61853689'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 55 • Updated: 2026-02-16 17:37 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;She doesn’t want to DCA, max out 401ks, max out Roth. She has her 20k savings before we married in a saving account getting 0.00% interest (sat there for like 5 years) I tried to explain a HYSA, money market, and VOO. What do I do?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853694&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;401k is for niggers though&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853699&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853689&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;What do I do?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Show her grocery store prices from 2019 and now. Show her prices from 2024 and now.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Show her how the government printed 4 trillion dollars from 2024 to now.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is a terrible time to invest though, there&amp;#x27;s only downside from here until you see trump on TV saying he needs to BRRRRR to save the nation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853700&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853689&lt;br&gt;Why should she waste her money investing when she could let you do it and simply take half of it whenever she wants?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854387&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854198&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854203&lt;br&gt;You can’t rape your wife dude.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854492&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853689&lt;br&gt;Women are fucking idiots and should be enslaved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855768&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853689&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Divorce her now. The marriage won&amp;#x27;t work long term, and if you have kids you&amp;#x27;ll lose them, too. This marriage was probably the worse decision you have ever made.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855836&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853689&lt;br&gt;buy a home? it&amp;#x27;s okay to have cash in the bank if you have lots of USD debt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855863&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;people spend years on 4chins, learn nothing, and end up marrying the exact kind of dumb bitch multiple boards warned about &lt;br&gt;You deserve each other.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857234&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853689&lt;br&gt;if you&amp;#x27;re so smart, why aren&amp;#x27;t you rich (and so don&amp;#x27;t care about your wife&amp;#x27;s money)&lt;br&gt;turns out,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857329&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sure you can make a million if you dca and invest s thousand s month for 30 years. But in 30 years that&amp;#x27;d be worth 1000&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857335&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853925&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Too late to stack physical silver&lt;br&gt;If you can trade fiat for silver, it&amp;#x27;s not too late.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857348&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853689&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;She doesn’t want to DCA, max out 401ks, max out Roth&lt;br&gt;Good. She knows what she&amp;#x27;s doing&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857425&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854213&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I am a woman&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;writes like a man&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857474&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854213&lt;br&gt;I am also a woman.. tee hee silly anons don&amp;#x27;t hit on me &amp;lt;3&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857476&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854373&lt;br&gt;dow jones? more like down jones&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857589&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853689&lt;br&gt;Take an image of a shopping cart and show how every year it contains less items in exchange for the same money bill&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857596&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Im a man and I identify as a lesbian&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857600&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853689&lt;br&gt;You CANNOT fix low IQ. It’s her money anyway, let her having it erode there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858419&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853720&lt;br&gt;Now adjust for dxy, retard&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858459&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853689&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t see the problem. You take her money and invest it for her. My wife was a bitch in the beginning, now when she questions my financial advice I just tell her to do what I say. And she does.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858474&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858419&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;reeee you can&amp;#x27;t fire all those DEI positions it makes me sad&lt;br&gt;I voted for this exact fucking thing&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858491&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853704&lt;br&gt;That&amp;#x27;s only because you&amp;#x27;re a poorfag in a lower tax bracket&lt;br&gt;(It&amp;#x27;s okay, I am too)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859752&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853848&lt;br&gt;Yeah, 100% this!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859980&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855863&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Taking seriously the advice you receive on 4chan&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Uhhhh….&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859991&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;my wife&lt;br&gt;KYS in the most unimaginably painful way you redditor subhuman.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859998&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853689&lt;br&gt;Don&amp;#x27;t invest for other people unless you literally have complete power over them, they will resent you for them not having access to their money and will go out of their way to spend every penny of whatever allowance they get and test boundaries by overspending.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860464&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858419&lt;br&gt;Do you get payed for your diligent work?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860469&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;1pbitd&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;49 bot replies&lt;br&gt;This websites dead as fuck.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860480&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853689&lt;br&gt;Women are retards. My wife has brought me nothing but financial ruin. These hoes are out of control. If I didn’t have 3 kids I’d ghost this bitch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860658&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860464&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;payed&lt;br&gt;no and I believe your kind should be adressing me as &amp;quot;sir&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861232&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859991&lt;br&gt;Based&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861244&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854232&lt;br&gt;guys he wants the up only ETF,, who has the list?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861274&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853689&lt;br&gt;Yours? half of 404ks and roth are not yours. $20k is not yours. if your wife move that, there&amp;#x27;s a chance that half of that might become yours.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>