<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>/biz/ FAST Threads</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/</link><description>Rapidly moving threads (oldest→newest within thread)</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 17:18:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>[FAST 507.3/hr] /XMR/ Monero General — 248 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61810651</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61810651?lm=1771174168</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 16:49:28 +0000</pubDate><description>Open article for full thread</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;[FAST 507.3/hr] /XMR/ Monero General&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61810651'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 248 • Updated: 2026-02-15 16:49 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Welcome to /XMR/ Monero General, dedicated to the discussion of the world&amp;#x27;s most widely adopted privacy coin.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;XMR payments are anonymous, low-fee, and fully fungible. Users can send and receive XMR globally without having to worry about tainted coins. Battle-tested privacy tech (Ring Signatures, Stealth Addresses and RingCT) ensures that critical TX data cannot be gleaned from the Monero blockchain; the TX history of all XMR users is kept hidden, with TXs being optionally transparent via the aid of a view key.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;XMR ensures low TX fees by employing a dynamic block size that can &amp;quot;stretch&amp;quot; to easily accommodate sudden TX spikes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;XMR&amp;#x27;s mining algorithm, RandomX, is optimized for devices using general-purpose CPUs e.g. desktops, laptops, smartphones, tablets, keeping the barrier to entry low and ASICs out of the equation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;XMR&amp;#x27;s tail emission - 0.6 XMR per block forever - incentivizes for-profit miners to keep mining, helping boost long-term network security. This constant linear inflation trends to zero and is offset by coin loss.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;XMR has proven to be the only altcoin capable of overcoming BTC&amp;#x27;s network effect by driving it out of the darknet economy BTC dominated for over 10 years. XMR is also starting to overtake BTC in clearnet commerce as well.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you still have questions, feel free to ask. A MoneroChad will be with you shortly.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;XMR Redpill: https://youtube.com/watch?v=wq6w03E2DS4&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;BUY XMR: https://monero.eco/exchanges/&lt;br&gt;Crypto ATMs: https://coinatmradar.com/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;XMR Resources: https://monero.observer/resources/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;XMR Stats: https://moneroj.net&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;USE XMR: https://cryptwerk.com/pay-with/xmr/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;OFFICIAL WEBSITE: https://getmonero.org&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;MINING: &lt;br&gt;https://www.getmonero.org/get-started/mining/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;WALLETS:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Desktop&lt;br&gt;Official GUI/CLI wallet&lt;br&gt;Featherwallet&lt;br&gt;Stack Wallet&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Mobile&lt;br&gt;Cake Wallet&lt;br&gt;Monero.com&lt;br&gt;Stack Wallet&lt;br&gt;Unstoppable &lt;br&gt;Monerujo (Android)&lt;br&gt;Monfluo (Android)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Infodumps&lt;br&gt;https://rentry.org/monero-explained&lt;br&gt;https://moneroinfodump.neocities.org &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Previous: &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61761870&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Replies (oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61848809&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61847794&lt;br&gt;You were already given the a TLDR so you don&amp;#x27;t have to read through the chat logs like I and many other anons have&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61839127&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The TLDR is that this particular doomer porn fantasy can&amp;#x27;t compromise anyone&amp;#x27;s privacy.&lt;br&gt;At what point will you accept this answer?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61848827&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We should look for ways to improve Monero&amp;#x27;s (official) material and appearance, not to induce any kind of pump, but to effectively convey the principles and message of why Monero, specifically out of other privacy coins, is extremely unique in the freedom it provides in contrast to all other money systems&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Right now it seems like very old material, links and screencaps keeps getting recycled. There&amp;#x27;s so many recent world events happening that tie in to Monero&amp;#x27;s use and we&amp;#x27;re missing a translation&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Monerochan (mostly AI slop) also doesn&amp;#x27;t communicate anything about Monero&lt;br&gt;There doesn&amp;#x27;t seem to be any good image macros to share from these threads&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Interested in how other people view this issue and what kind of material would get the communication standard up to the same level as its founding principles and tech&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849019&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61848053&lt;br&gt;Thanks anon. No cap fr fr Tbh I had no idea it was there before it was pointed out&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849231&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61847794&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61847814&lt;br&gt;They will never provide you an answer anon. Monerocucks are glowniggers, pretending to not be. Its funny watching them recoil in fear though. Just look at the past few generals, they cant even BTFO nerva jeets lmfao... look here&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61831334&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61847825&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;why cant they just tell reddit why its safe?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;doesnt and cant&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;cant even tell 4channers in a simple format&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Well *I* asked *you* that one for a reason.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Please tell me what explicit attack scenario exists in which the five dollar wrench and current KYC measurements are infeasible but having to give out your view keys is.&lt;br&gt;the taxman who says &amp;quot;gib?&amp;quot; Normies fold faster than a wet noodle.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61848809&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;You were already given the a TLDR&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;At what point will you accept this answer?&lt;br&gt;cant even get a copy and paste job on here&lt;br&gt;oh...&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;1pbtid&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You all sound like pathetic freemasons who suck jew dick.&lt;br&gt;&amp;quot;wErE nOt BaD pPl!? oH bUt YoU hAvE tO jOiN uS tO fInD OuT wHaT wE BeLiEvE iN!!!&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;kills you when you defect or tell a secret after finding out they worship the satan&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;lmao moneroniggers and their copium at their finest. Go glow on some other basket weaving forum. Is it any wonder XMR generals never get banned for advertisement? Its because 4chan is backdoored with JDIF, and JDIF &amp;amp; Monero suck each others dicks. One big blowjob circlejerk for their father satan.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;inb4 some cuck even tries to reply to me, you cant even keep up with my precision and speed. anyone who reads this knows im right. i use your shill threads to spread truth, and there is nothing you can do about it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849859&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61848827&lt;br&gt;I feel like most of the older stuff is still applicable since it&amp;#x27;s just about the basics. See picrel as an example. However I agree that the more specific guides (for example how and where to get XMR) rarely has good pictures. Do you have other bad examples so we can make a list? &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849231&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;cant even tell 4channers in a simple format&lt;br&gt;Five sentences isn&amp;#x27;t hard if you ask me. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;the taxman who says &amp;quot;gib?&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;1. You already need to be deanonymized for that. The ways you can get deanonymized will stay the same. This would also be combated by using an exchange wallet. I&amp;#x27;d probably even use an on-ramp wallet, an off-ramp wallet and a holding wallet. This way even if you were deanonymized and the IRS asks for more than what they&amp;#x27;re allowed to ask (just the income as a number, not the sources or which bank account it went to) you&amp;#x27;d still retain your privacy. &lt;br&gt;2. This is already possible by being coerced through various means. A view key won&amp;#x27;t change that. This is proven by your next sentence. &amp;gt;Normies fold faster than a wet noodle.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In short: All proposed &amp;#x27;new&amp;#x27; attack vectors already exist, require additional information that isn&amp;#x27;t easily obtained (they tried for years and still couldn&amp;#x27;t get it) and are easily mitigated. &lt;br&gt;Additionally, if someone for whatever reason was willing to inform the IRS of the relevant taxes by directly allowing access to view the wallet (which still is absurd and not how it works) it&amp;#x27;d be much easier and also less risky. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you have any other scenarios in which view keys could be exploited which are not covered already please let me know.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850085&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849231&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;re clearly retarded and can&amp;#x27;t follow a conversation, so I&amp;#x27;ll highlight the points for you.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I gave the answer to the view key FUD here&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61838278&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Which sent anon into a tizzy that didn&amp;#x27;t actually refute anything I posted, here &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61838817&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;whos doomer porn fantasy? XMRfags cant even keep an eye on whos talking to who in here. I dont care about nerva.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Which I then edited to ease his butthurt here&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61839127&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The TLDR is that this particular doomer porn fantasy can&amp;#x27;t compromise anyone&amp;#x27;s privacy.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;But he wanted an official statement from the devs to ease his butthurt &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61847581&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;So I gave him that too &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61847618&lt;br&gt;Which sent anon into another tizzy, because he seems to agree with some redditor that &amp;quot;it&amp;#x27;s just toooooo hard to read the documentation! Why can&amp;#x27;t they spoonfeed me!?&amp;quot; Here &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61847794&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;why should i trust monero at all&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;picrelated from reddit thread. why cant they just tell reddit why its safe?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To which I then pounted out that he was already given the spoonfed answer that doesn&amp;#x27;t require him to read anything on github or librera &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61848809&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;And then asked the same question I&amp;#x27;ll ask you now:&lt;br&gt;At what point will you accept this answer? Seriously, what don&amp;#x27;t you faggots get?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850591&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849231&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61848021&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;ve been waiting for a few hours now. Due to your lack of questions I assume you are agreeing with me that carrot does not pose a privacy threat. I&amp;#x27;m glad we could finally come to an agreement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851129&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849859&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850085&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850591&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I&amp;#x27;ve been waiting for a few hours now. Due to your lack of questions I assume you are agreeing with me that carrot does not pose a privacy threat&lt;br&gt;There is a good chance he&amp;#x27;s banned. For some reason, criticizing your shitcoin (Monero) is against jannie law. I was banned recently for criticizing it. Look at the nerva faggots. They keep being banned as well. What doesnt puzzle anyone is how your general stays up for days without deletion, yet the only organic traction your threads have are from posters who get banned criticizing you. Its because youre a bunch of glowniggers who work for (((the island bunch))) and have this site backdoored. If competition shows up, the thread gets shadow banned and falls off the catalog.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Youll never answer the questions regarding the upcoming fork and always link their github page because YOU dont understand it. Face the truth, the reason the reddit comments dont get answered is because NO ONE understands it. The reason the even more damning questions get deleted is because theyre asking the right questions. For some reason, Monero thinks its better to implement something that is unnecessary rather than something that should be implemented.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;In short: All proposed &amp;#x27;new&amp;#x27; attack vectors already exist&lt;br&gt;Take a good hard look at that statement youre defending&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Which sent anon into a tizzy that didn&amp;#x27;t actually refute anything I posted&lt;br&gt;Maybe its because you all brought up the &amp;quot;doomer fantasy&amp;quot;? He never mentioned it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your wins are not the wins you think they are.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;At what point will you accept this answer? Seriously, what don&amp;#x27;t you faggots get?&lt;br&gt;Since youll never post an answer to the questions, Why should they repeat themselves? Its an XMR thread, not the audience&amp;#x27;s thread. You have to provide an adequate answer and are up for scrutiny, not them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851235&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851129&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;For some reason, criticizing your shitcoin (Monero) is against jannie law.&lt;br&gt;No, you retards get banned for shilling for nerva. Also it&amp;#x27;s weird to assume he got banned after his 14th post over 3 days meanwhile you&amp;#x27;ve also posted fud over the days and still are present. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;They keep being banned as well.&lt;br&gt;Who knows, maybe it&amp;#x27;s the constant shilling and the spam they don&amp;#x27;t just post here but on the board itself through a variety of threads. Btw when you don&amp;#x27;t get banned your generals just hit page 10 and die. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;What doesnt puzzle anyone is how your general stays up for days without deletion,&lt;br&gt;That&amp;#x27;s because the XMR general is fairly active and removing established generals would just lead to more shitposting. I hope you don&amp;#x27;t want the 10 millionth LINK thread this year.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;yet the only organic traction your threads have are from posters who get banned criticizing you.&lt;br&gt;Did you forget the moonfags that tried to take over this general, the qubic fud, the view key fud and the zioncash shills? All of those happened less than 6 months ago. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;and have this site backdoored.&lt;br&gt;No need for a backdoor when the mods are jews and feds. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;If competition shows up, the thread gets shadow banned and falls off the catalog.&lt;br&gt;Really? What happened to &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61841738 &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61827591 &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61822264 and &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61809799? Those are just some of the ones you had and that died because your community consists entirely of a few jeets and baggies. Graciously I sometimes enter your threads and ask you simple questions which you can&amp;#x27;t answer despite their simplicity. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Youll never answer the questions regarding the upcoming fork&lt;br&gt;I did a few hours ago and now I&amp;#x27;m waiting for more questions. Let me know if you have some.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851245&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851129&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;always link their github page because&lt;br&gt;Me? No I didn&amp;#x27;t. I know github is something that challenges the nerva jeet heavily so instead I break it down in very simple terms. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;because YOU dont understand it.&lt;br&gt;Your questions? You don&amp;#x27;t seem to have any.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;the reason the reddit comments dont get answered is because NO ONE understands it.&lt;br&gt;I already answered all of the questions I saw. If you have more let me know. The assumption that no one understand cryptography or psychology is absurd considering the existence of that field. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The reason the even more damning questions get deleted is because theyre asking the right questions.&lt;br&gt;Like what? So far each question I saw I answered on here. I don&amp;#x27;t use reddit but feel free to keep me updated on orange site. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;For some reason, Monero thinks its better to implement something that is unnecessary&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;ve already been told that view keys will have some benefits. I recall hardware wallet and merchant software support being named in this thread. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;rather than something that should be implemented.&lt;br&gt;Devs, due to being part of a community and mostly unpaid, decide what they wish to implement. If it&amp;#x27;s fcmp++ they&amp;#x27;ll work on fcmp++, if it&amp;#x27;s carrot, they&amp;#x27;ll work on carrot. You can&amp;#x27;t force strangers that donate their time to do only what you want them to do especially if it&amp;#x27;s a feature you can easily avoid. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Take a good hard look at that statement youre defending&lt;br&gt;That literally nothing will worsen with carrot? Seems like a fine statement to me. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Since youll never post an answer to the questions,&lt;br&gt;I can&amp;#x27;t speak for anon but I already answered every question you have. If you have any other questions let me know.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851255&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851129&lt;br&gt;In return I&amp;#x27;d like to ask you a few questions: &lt;br&gt;1. How do you ensure unmaintained software keeps up with the security demands it has?&lt;br&gt;2. How do you ensure that no one attacks nerva by locally clustering CPUs? &lt;br&gt;3. Why do your devs believe Discord to be a development platform despite being on github? &lt;br&gt;4. How do you ensure the safety of your devs in case of an attack by glowies if they all use the ID-requiring discord and 40% of them (50% of your lead devs) having doxxed themselves publicly?&lt;br&gt;5. What other questions do you have for me?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851332&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851235&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;No, you retards get banned for shilling for nerva. Also it&amp;#x27;s weird to assume he got banned after his 14th post over 3 days meanwhile you&amp;#x27;ve also posted fud over the days and still are present. &lt;br&gt;Ive posted twice you jeetbot, (3 times now) and none of it was about nerva. Ill disregard the rest of this botpost.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851245&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Your questions? You don&amp;#x27;t seem to have any.&lt;br&gt;Never did, go back and reread my posts.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851255&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;xmrbotpost about nerva. &lt;br&gt;Never mentioned it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Glownero&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851379&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851332&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Ive posted twice&lt;br&gt;Correct, I was speaking about rVCB8pdb, I assume you were doing that too or do you speak about yourself in the third person? &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;and none of it was about nerva.&lt;br&gt;Good job not having and reading comprehension and forgetting you posted: &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;they cant even BTFO nerva jeets lmfao (&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849231)&lt;br&gt;and: &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I was banned recently for criticizing it. Look at the nerva faggots. (&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851129)&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851332&lt;br&gt;You combined any criticism against XMR with nerva. So by your own logic most of the criticism here comes from the nervajeets.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Never did,&lt;br&gt;If you don&amp;#x27;t have any questions, then why do you keep pestering me about needing to answer them? &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Never mentioned it.&lt;br&gt;All three of your posts mentioned nerva in a positive light.&lt;br&gt;Feel free to answer any of my questions (see &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851255 for the easiest ones) or give me any of the question which you apparently don&amp;#x27;t have but are lamenting as being unanswered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851533&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851129&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Youll never answer the questions regarding the upcoming fork and always link their github page because YOU dont understand it.&lt;br&gt;I link the github because I like having a source to back up my claims, and I actually want you to stop being a faggot and refute them&lt;br&gt;No, accusations of being a fedfreemasonbot out to get you are not refutations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;For some reason, Monero thinks its better to implement something that is unnecessary rather than something that should be implemented.&lt;br&gt;Who exactly are you to decide whether or not a feature is unnecessary and shouldn&amp;#x27;t be implemented?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Maybe its because you all brought up the &amp;quot;doomer fantasy&amp;quot;? He never mentioned it.&lt;br&gt;Given how he was asking about them&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61838139&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;so when someone says kyc will ask for this and then the feds will use it for surveillance, theyre correct? then it&amp;#x27;s not FUD&lt;br&gt;I hit the fast forward button on his line of thought since he clearly believes that view keys present some sort of threat, and I didn&amp;#x27;t feel like waiting 10 posts for him to go &amp;quot;WELL IF THEY GET ENOUGH TO VIEW KEYS IT&amp;#x27;LL BE THE END OF PRIVACY!&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;If this was wrong of me, then my bad.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Your wins are not the wins you think they are.&lt;br&gt;Who said I was trying to win anything? Why are you perpetuating this weird fantasy? You&amp;#x27;re weird bro. Not a good look at all, man.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851879&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I’ve been out of it for a while, how do I buy some and use it to acquire ketamine? Last time I was doing this, we used bitcoin and it was $220.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61852742&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851879&lt;br&gt;Send any major crypto to Trocador. Swap to XMR.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61852911&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851879&lt;br&gt;What this guy said&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61852742&lt;br&gt;Then visit Dread dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad onion&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853405&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851879&lt;br&gt;Get any other coin and swap for Monero on Trocador.&lt;br&gt;Have the monero sent to your cake wallet.&lt;br&gt;Go on Dread to find what&amp;#x27;s the current best darknet market.&lt;br&gt;Go on the DNM and buy your product with Monero.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;All the steps take a bit of time but it&amp;#x27;s not complicated. Once you know how everything works it&amp;#x27;s no more complex than an Amazon order.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854237&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61810651&lt;br&gt;Bloomberg published an article on Monero this morning. It’s behind a paywall but here is the article thanks to some Twitter anon.&lt;br&gt;https://pastebin.com/6aqniwe1&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;As digital assets go mainstream and law enforcement agencies get more adept at seizing illicit crypto, “privacy coins” like Monero hark back to the industry’s foundational idea: the creation of a decentralized electronic cash system running outside the purview of governments and central banks. That’s given them a cult following among libertarian-leaning crypto users — while providing a handy tool for criminals.&lt;br&gt;The rest of the article is just (((Bloomberg))) seething about how it can’t be tracked and a mention of the upcoming hard fork.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854655&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854237&lt;br&gt;They really seemed to think the view key fud would be more effective if they now need to publish paid articles&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855033&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61696670&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;suggest wallet that can store XRP,XMR,USDT and Zcash is there any&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Turns out this actually does exist. Hope this anon is still lurking &lt;br&gt;https://edge.app&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855123&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I need to send someone 5$ for a beer while anonymous. Thing is I have no fucking clue how any of this cryptocurrency works. Can someone explain to me same way you would to a retard?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855365&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855123&lt;br&gt;Yeah, follow the chat here: &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61817263&lt;br&gt;If you have any issue or problem at a specific step ask here and we&amp;#x27;ll help.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Enjoy the &amp;quot;beer&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855558&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855365&lt;br&gt;Ok, installed the cake wallet program, made the wallet, both monero and litecoin. Now I need to actually buy the crypto so I can transfer it to the wallet I just made. I think I still have an old paypal account which apparently allows you to buy crypto now. Is that ok for me to buy litecoin, transfer it to the cake wallet and exchange it for monero or will I be de-anonymized for using paypal just this once?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855567&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855558&lt;br&gt;Once it gets to your wallet it disappears.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855579&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855558&lt;br&gt;I never bought crypto with PayPal but if you can buy LTC, do it. Once you swap to Monero and have it in your personal wallet you become invisible and cannot be deanonymized.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856711&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854237&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854655&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Jewish media bashing monero&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Just like they did with Trump&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Sub Artic IQs dont notice theyre promoting it on purpose&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Paid promoters ITT walk around the fact that concern was brought up by actual users and went unanswered or were outright removed posts/threads, then claim the view key fud was started by the very mossad theyre unironically supporting&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Glowner, promoted by Glews.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856863&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856711&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;Monero General&amp;quot; thread&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;CTRL + F &amp;quot;nerva&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;140 results&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your unmaintained shitcoin will NEVER be relevant you poojeet retards. Everyone with more than 2 braincells can tell that you&amp;#x27;ve been shitting up the board trying to advertise. Please do the needful and make your own general. Except you can&amp;#x27;t do that right? Because NO ONE cares about it and it dies immediately unless you coordinate to keep it alive in your gay little discord server.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856957&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851879&lt;br&gt;Buy from trocador&lt;br&gt;Go to daunt.link for DW link list&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857243&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856957&lt;br&gt;wagyu . xyz??&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded><enclosure url="https://i.4cdn.org/biz/1770384967790775s.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0" /></item><item><title>[FAST 372.0/hr] The EU is going full degen — 93 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61856214</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61856214?lm=1771175055</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 17:04:15 +0000</pubDate><description>Open article for full thread</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;[FAST 372.0/hr] The EU is going full degen&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61856214'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 93 • Updated: 2026-02-15 17:04 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Replies (oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856900&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856214&lt;br&gt;Interesting. Because they&amp;#x27;re also moving towards taxation of unrealised gain on investments. So&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A. Forced to invest in turbo woke employers&lt;br&gt;B. Then taxed without even selling said investment &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m sure I remember people like the kkk mentioning some poppycock about&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;grandscale robbery&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;and other such nonsense at some point.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856915&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856885&lt;br&gt;And massively underperformed US stocks the past 20 years. Also you&amp;#x27;re ignoring the fact that the US Dollar lost 13% of its value compared to the Euro since last year. It&amp;#x27;s pretty easy to &amp;quot;outperform&amp;quot; the S&amp;amp;p500 when you&amp;#x27;re starting off with +13% gains over US assets right from the start. That says nothing about the quality of EU stocks or the EU economy though.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856923&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856774&lt;br&gt;https://www.businesstimes.com.sg/international/eu-sees-sweden-model-it-looks-encourage-investors&lt;br&gt;they were talking about this this past summer, so i assume this is what von der leyen is talking about. isk makes it easy for normies to buy stocks and with very low taxes. i don&amp;#x27;t know what the doomers itt are talking about, but making it easier for people to join the casino is a good thing for all of us, more money means higher prices on our bags. and a better euro economy overall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856935&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856923&lt;br&gt;its very difficult to change your opinion on things once you are past a certain age especially when it comes to finance and your life savings. creating an incentive is good but its mostly for a new and younger generation which, in this financial environment, lacks the financial means to participate in the stock market to begin with. it will take decades before the eu sees noticiable changes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856943&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856363&lt;br&gt;thanks chatgpt&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856946&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856885&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;$10 junk company goes to $20&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;check out this performance amerilard&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856953&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856463&lt;br&gt;You say it like a Nazi, but unfortunately Hitler would have NEVER let this much bullshit happen with Muslims. He&amp;#x27;d Holocaust 2: etc etc them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856960&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856896&lt;br&gt;Every single market crash since modern times is because of US overinflated companies. US tech companies are bubbles and their value is not rooted in any kind of reality - US stock performance is heavily dependent on a few mega-cap tech firms overinflated by degenerate jewish gamblers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856915&lt;br&gt;Stocks say almost nothing about economy in the first place.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seethe all you want but EU stock market is more attractive right now, which is the only point that I was making.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856961&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856668&lt;br&gt;The good part is that if and when whitey is reduced to nothing there will be absolutely no unity left. As if these fags will somehow have a society of cohesion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856966&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856223&lt;br&gt;How do I profit from this?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856969&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856923&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;“Swedes have good reason to be thankful for the ISK account,” said Mohammed Salih, a 32-year-old communications manager who lives in Listerby in southern Sweden. He has invested with the system for more than 10 years. “I have always saved money and tried to build an economically stable future, but I didn’t know how to make the money grow.”&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Mohammed Salih&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;lives in southern Sweden&lt;br&gt;Stop giving niggers free shit? No let&amp;#x27;s force people to invest in our eu funded companies. I hope Trump disintegrate the EU soon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856984&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856214&lt;br&gt;the EU has not the power to go after private savings. They can just incentivise to spend. So they have to create some kind of finance product that is worth buying. &lt;br&gt;They want eurobonds but they are very controversial&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856988&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856969&lt;br&gt;what are you talking about?&lt;br&gt;what free shit did this guy recieve? and who will force people to invest in euro companies? you are making shit up to get mad about, typical chud retard behaviour&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857015&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856988&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;tax savings&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;you can only invest tax free in eu companies&lt;br&gt;It will work like this, you are just delusional.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857018&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857015&lt;br&gt;you just made shit up again&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857021&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856896&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s called a bubble for a reson. May god have mercy on America when the AI bubble pops.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857036&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857021&lt;br&gt;the european market is just as much tied to the american market. if america goes down, so will the european. america makes up 70% of the msci world lol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857043&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857018&lt;br&gt;Any bank account with savings over 5k is taxed in my country and eu goverment bonds are taxed 12,5% while stocks 25% to support public finances, this started years ago. You are just ignorant and probably underage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857054&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857043&lt;br&gt;interesting tax facts i guess, but it has nothing to do with the claim you dreamt up&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857073&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856885&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;bagholds for almost 20 years&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;to break even&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;inflation adjusted its still far from break even&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;going from 100% nav to 20% is a -80% loss&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;but going back to 100% nav from 20% is a 500% &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;somehow this is outperforming sp500&lt;br&gt;i know this spanish index is a bit of a cherry pick, but cac40 (france) looks about the same. dax (germany) on the other hand looks like a sp500 but grows at half of its pace&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857079&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856725&lt;br&gt;European domestic investments do not generate remotely the same return as American ones, so the European savings just goes into the S&amp;amp;P as well. So what Ursula here is talking about is capital controls, forcing domestic savings into domestic investment sinks. This is not dissimilar to what China has going on, except Europeans don&amp;#x27;t have the right capital or population structure to justify domestic investment on that scale. They already have infrastructure and though we call them Europoors, they aren&amp;#x27;t nearly as destitute as the median Chinaman. It&amp;#x27;s going to be the malinvestment spectacle of the century if the EU actually manages to implement a regime to this effect, amidst some stiff competition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857085&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856214&lt;br&gt;The Great Taking begins.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857095&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857085&lt;br&gt;Shut the fuck up + you won&amp;#x27;t do shit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857118&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856420&lt;br&gt;Go cry somewhere else faggot&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857134&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857118&lt;br&gt;Ok suck israeli dick, Mr. Trump.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857170&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856214&lt;br&gt;wow literally the same exact faggotry as the cheetos mandatory savings account for children what a cohencidence!!!! still think the MIGA orange kike isnt deepstate?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857184&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856214&lt;br&gt;So the EU either steals from their people or it fails.&lt;br&gt;lol, muh powerful union.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857196&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856542&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s seething libtards who hate Russia because they aren&amp;#x27;t nice to fags&lt;br&gt;I wish I was joking&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857261&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856542&lt;br&gt;I can&amp;#x27;t wait for the US to pull all military support from the EU. Then we see the dominoes of all their socialized programs (which only exist because they outsource all military defense expenses to the US) start falling apart.&lt;br&gt;Imagine how much they start seething when they realize that they were in fact an American vassal state all along and never had any relevance on the global stage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857279&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856214&lt;br&gt;so they want shit like in USA where you put money into something and hope that will be enough when you retire ? hahahaha, at this rate you need to save at minimum 1000 or more monthly if you want to survive in 30-40 years &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856288&lt;br&gt;stfu faggot you don&amp;#x27;t know shit&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;408 billions go yearly for Rente aka pensions, this is without healthcare who&amp;#x27;s 325 billions yearly, but a big portion of healthcare is used by boomers not by young people &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Welfare is 58 billions&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded><enclosure url="https://i.4cdn.org/biz/1771141088339567s.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0" /></item><item><title>[FAST 904.0/hr] /GME/ - Settle in for Comfy (Long) Weekend Edition — 226 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61853052</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61853052?lm=1771175093</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 17:04:53 +0000</pubDate><description>Open article for full thread</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;[FAST 904.0/hr] /GME/ - Settle in for Comfy (Long) Weekend Edition&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61853052'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 226 • Updated: 2026-02-15 17:04 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;Basic Information&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;gme.cac site redacted due to aids&lt;br&gt;https://finra-markets.morningstar.com/MarketData/EquityOptions/detail.jsp?query=14%3A0P000002CH&lt;br&gt;https://gmetimeline.com (up to 2021)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Daily reminder&lt;br&gt;s[Kek Melvies]bzilp4&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Mandatory study time&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The Everything Short&lt;br&gt;reddit.com/mgucv2&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;^watch-along&lt;br&gt;youtu.be/AaalT8rn9lc&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Naked Short Selling and Systemic Risk&lt;br&gt;youtu.be/FCiL4v7_z9E&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Failure to deliver&lt;br&gt;youtu.be/I0WXg5T3cBE&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;GameStop Investor Site&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;SEC 10-K Annual report FY24 &amp;amp; &amp;#x27;25 Proxy Statement&lt;br&gt;news.gamestop.com/annual-meeting/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;What will happen if Citadel becomes insolvent?&lt;br&gt;DTCC with 60T USD, will pay as the final boss with FDIC as the insurance&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Real-Time Trades&lt;br&gt;https://www.nasdaq.com/market-activity/stocks/GME/latest-real-time-trades&lt;br&gt;https://eresearch.fidelity.com/eresearch/gotoBL/fidelityTopOrders.jhtml&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Current Trade Halts + Short Restrictions&lt;br&gt;nasdaqtrader.com/Trader.aspx?id=TradeHalts&lt;br&gt;nyse.com/markets/nyse-arca/notices&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;All other news/DDs/etc&lt;br&gt;en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Stag_hunt&lt;br&gt;https://prospect.org/power/how-the-gamestop-hustle-worked&lt;br&gt;https://computershared.net/?bot=drsbot&lt;br&gt;DRS Guide:&lt;br&gt;reddit.com/ptvaka&lt;br&gt;Avoid DSPP (more information under legacy links):&lt;br&gt;sec.gov/about/reports-publications/investor-publications/holding-your-securities-get-the-facts&lt;br&gt;HF/broker class action lawsuit evidence:&lt;br&gt;storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.flsd.590042/gov.uscourts.flsd.590042.416.0.pdf&lt;br&gt;SEC GME/meme stocks report:&lt;br&gt;sec.gov/files/staff-report-equity-options-market-struction-conditions-early-2021.pdf&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;DD Compilation:&lt;br&gt;reddit.com/mnss65&lt;br&gt;Quarterly Movements, Equity Total Return Swaps, DOOMPs, ITM CALLs, Short Interest, and Futures Roll Periods:&lt;br&gt;reddit.com/pb22oj&lt;br&gt;Cellar Boxing:&lt;br&gt;reddit.com/pmj9yk&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Temporary alliance with reddit and Jaws to take down other sharks, we can go back to hating each other later&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;reddit DDs don&amp;#x27;t take them for fact use your brain&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Check your broker and clearing house to ensure you&amp;#x27;re not rugpulled&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last time on /GME/: &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61847072&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As always:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;sneed hedgies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Replies (oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857050&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gamestop has aquired Valve&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857052&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GameStop has acquired Burger King&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857080&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857050&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857052&lt;br&gt;Cusip???&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857084&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857080&lt;br&gt;*flicks through 1000&amp;#x27;s of documents*&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s a match.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857087&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GameStop has acquired Sneed&amp;#x27;s Feed &amp;amp; Seed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857094&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sneed has acquired Chuck&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857101&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857094&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857087&lt;br&gt;HOLY FUCK THEYRE KEIRESTUING ALL OVER MY BOY HOLES &lt;br&gt;NO MORE MERGERS&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857104&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I fully trust Ryan Cohen, who tried to buy bbbyq.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857108&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The lone GME WS I have in my Vanguard account&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857109&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GameStop has acquired Home Depot&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857114&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857104&lt;br&gt;This makes me inexplicably angrier than anything else.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857117&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GameStop has acquired eBay.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857119&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857114&lt;br&gt;Just ask them what the status of the offer is, usually stun locks them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857121&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857117&lt;br&gt;GameStop has acquired Amazon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857124&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857117&lt;br&gt;Why does eBay look like that?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857125&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857119&lt;br&gt;It looks like the BBBYQ shell has reverse merged with BBBY and most likely some other transaction is yet to be revealed until we have the Final Decree. We know the first part is true because of the CUSIP Confirmation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857130&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;gamestop will acquire a few things&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857131&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GameStop has acquired Detroit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857132&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857109&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m proooompting Grok to depict GameStop as an eldritch horror that merges and acquires various businesses and humanoids to varying success.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857137&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857132&lt;br&gt;Why do you associate the best happening in our lifetimes with such horror?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857138&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gamestop acquired Valve.&lt;br&gt;Gamestop received permission to sell Nintendo games on Valve. (Cohen posted about wanting to speak with Miyamoto)&lt;br&gt;Valve goes public.&lt;br&gt;GME holders get nothing.&lt;br&gt;Valve goes parabolic.&lt;br&gt;Gamestop stays at $23.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857150&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856331&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856934&lt;br&gt;They can slide with up to 1200 posts per minute. Remember what you&amp;#x27;re fighting for.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857166&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857137&lt;br&gt;I am just grateful ((we)) are the horror this time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857171&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857138&lt;br&gt;GameStop acquires SEGA &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ultimate autist franchise is now ours.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857173&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857137&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;with such horror&lt;br&gt;All a matter of perspective&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857177&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857171&lt;br&gt;Umm akshully GameStop acquired Bethesda GW, with Todd Howard maintaining creative control.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857188&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857177&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Skyrim will release 3 more times before we get Fallout 5&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857191&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857188&lt;br&gt;Skyrim Remastered&lt;br&gt;Skyrim Remastered: GameStop Exclusive&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857235&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857188&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Ryan will make a joke about hiring for Skyrimjobs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857281&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bAhOPaue_TY&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded><enclosure url="https://i.4cdn.org/biz/1771055913680926s.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0" /></item><item><title>[FAST 364.0/hr] Thread 61854715 — 91 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61854715</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61854715?lm=1771175146</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 17:05:46 +0000</pubDate><description>Open article for full thread</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;[FAST 364.0/hr] Thread 61854715&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61854715'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 91 • Updated: 2026-02-15 17:05 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;toothpastebros...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Replies (oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856306&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854833&lt;br&gt;Are you implying the markets are somehow manipulated?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856310&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856293&lt;br&gt;used to live there, arabs are the worth, the destruction was planned long ago, slowly for surely invading the more civilized world&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856321&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856301&lt;br&gt;Kek. Would this work?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856322&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854715&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;getting taxed on money that doesn&amp;#x27;t exist yet&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856326&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854817&lt;br&gt;They&amp;#x27;re dopamine fiends with actual ass parasites burrowing into their spinal cord causing them to act this way.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856343&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856310&lt;br&gt;Yeah the USA posters don&amp;#x27;t know how good they have it. And I&amp;#x27;ve seen some threads encouraging people to take their money out of USA assets.. JUST FUCKING LOL. Trust me STAY OUT OF EUROPE&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856505&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854715&lt;br&gt;Lel&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856508&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854817&lt;br&gt;Yes but your gooning sessions aren’t degenerate at all :)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856702&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854715&lt;br&gt;when will the senate decide about this catastrophy?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856772&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854715&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;shitskinned failed country getting turned into a more goycattle farm&lt;br&gt;why the fuck should i care&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856790&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854726&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;relax, the politicians will backtrack their authoritarian push for more power&lt;br&gt;holy cope&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856962&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856790&lt;br&gt;You will see how the backtrack&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856971&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854715&lt;br&gt;I hate this dogshit country so fucking much. I wish America or Russia nuked us already.&lt;br&gt;Completely fucking braindead&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856982&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856971&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854715&lt;br&gt;The first 1800 in profit are excluded. Which practically means the tax free capital profit drops from 56k+ to like 20k.&lt;br&gt;The 36% percentage also happens to be the highest in Europe.&lt;br&gt;It would be funny if it weren&amp;#x27;t so fucking dumb&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856996&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856982&lt;br&gt;Why are dutchniggers so dumb?&lt;br&gt;Why do they tolerate this abuse?&lt;br&gt;What causes this?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857026&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854715&lt;br&gt;Based total cryptonigger death!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857027&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854726&lt;br&gt;when? we all know how slow the european bureaucratic apparatus is. imagine losing 7-8 years in the market. you could double your money in that time span with just boomer index funds. lol I dont think you understand how dire the situation is rn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857028&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What happens when you sell all of it on 31 december, rebuy jan 1st? No unrealized gains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857032&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857028&lt;br&gt;thats what everyone is supposed to do now but it will kill compounding gains in stuff like etf`s which after a awhile is most of your gains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857034&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857028&lt;br&gt;Sorry Goy: https://www.gov.uk/hmrc-internal-manuals/capital-gains-manual/cg13350&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857038&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857028&lt;br&gt;Then you pay realized gains...&lt;br&gt;The jews thought of everything, no escape (except leaving the country).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857062&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857038&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m Belgian but I plan to buy gold and move it out of europe when I have enough to retire in a cheap place. Would that work?&lt;br&gt;I know you&amp;#x27;re &amp;quot;not allowed&amp;quot; to travel with that much but there isn&amp;#x27;t much they can do if I drive to spain and take a ferry out of europe. I assume my luggage won&amp;#x27;t be checked as thouroughly compared to a plane&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857068&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857062&lt;br&gt;As long as they don&amp;#x27;t get your ID when you buy and as long as you don&amp;#x27;t get robbed along the way then that might work, unless I&amp;#x27;m missing something&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857113&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857062&lt;br&gt;Gold in the form of jewelry is draws less attention than coins but then you&amp;#x27;d have to pay VAT on the gold. Honestly crypto is the best way to move currency across borders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857115&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856996&lt;br&gt;dutch are the jews of the germanic world&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857127&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854715&lt;br&gt;That would be the point at which I wouldn&amp;#x27;t condem tax evasion. Hopefully such bullshit is never proposed at where I live.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857253&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857127&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;That would be the point at which I wouldn&amp;#x27;t condem tax evasion&lt;br&gt;tax evasion is the most honorable thing one can do in europe. depriving our greedy degenerate overlords of any cent is one of the greatest actions for humanity in existence&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857260&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857115&lt;br&gt;So why are jews jewing themselves??&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857273&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857113&lt;br&gt;There is going to be solid gold and silver Mr. T. style jewelry being sold as a get around for bullion taxes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857287&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855187&lt;br&gt;LOL&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded><enclosure url="https://i.4cdn.org/biz/1771100134377209s.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0" /></item><item><title>[FAST 1008.0/hr] /XSG/ XRP Schizo General #2529 — 252 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61833878</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61833878?lm=1771175363</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 17:09:23 +0000</pubDate><description>Open article for full thread</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;[FAST 1008.0/hr] /XSG/ XRP Schizo General #2529&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61833878'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 252 • Updated: 2026-02-15 17:09 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Previous: &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61810716&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Buy XRP on:&lt;br&gt;Coinbase, Binance, Bitrue, Uphold, Robinhood, Kraken, Kucoin, etc&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Why hold XRP?&lt;br&gt;https://youtu.be/5urrOWO0KDI [Embed]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Newfag Tutorial:&lt;br&gt;https://youtu.be/23Yn5GdYpJc [Embed]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;XRPL Guide:&lt;br&gt;https://xrpl.guide&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;XRPL Explorer:&lt;br&gt;https://bithomp.com&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;XRPL Richlist:&lt;br&gt;https://rich-list.info&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;XRP ETF Tracker:&lt;br&gt;https://xrp-insights.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Latest News:&lt;br&gt;https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XRPUSD/news/?exchange=CRYPTO&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;X:&lt;br&gt;https://x.com/JoelKatz&lt;br&gt;https://x.com/bgarlinghouse&lt;br&gt;https://x.com/Ripple&lt;br&gt;https://x.com/RippleXDev&lt;br&gt;https://x.com/WietseWind&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The Myth of Market Cap:&lt;br&gt;http://galgitron.net/Post/The-Myth-of-Market-Cap---Version-2&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;XRP FUD BINGO:&lt;br&gt;https://fudbingo.com&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;ANTI-FUD:&lt;br&gt;https://pastebin.com/ZESsmqB8&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Lore:&lt;br&gt;https://pastebin.com/Z39w20qf&lt;br&gt;https://X.com/bearableguy123&lt;br&gt;https://x.com/FoJAk3 [Mr. Pool archives]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Schizo Ramblings:&lt;br&gt;https://pastebin.com/YHwQrGDW&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Past /XSG/ Threads:&lt;br&gt;https://pastebin.com/pZdQbREq&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;What wallet do I use?&lt;br&gt;Hot storage - Xaman, Gem Wallet, Crossmark or Bifrost&lt;br&gt;Cold storage - Paper/Metal or Ledger/D’CENT&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Replies (oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856067&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856060&lt;br&gt;That&amp;#x27;s why I am using leverage ... so i can get out ... I want out so I can move to japan and start my life and I have to use leverage since they won&amp;#x27;t just pump this shit to $10&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856077&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;fascinating climb this coin is doing eh chaps&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856088&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856004&lt;br&gt;i mean, you are right there, get a second job for a year&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856186&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why are we going up right now against the rest of the market? I&amp;#x27;m not used to good things happening for us&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856205&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856077&lt;br&gt;Indubitably my good sir, I do say indeed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856246&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;redpill me on crossmark wallet&lt;br&gt;i hate phones, can crossmark be what xaman is just as a desktop browser extension rather than a phone app? can it connect to the xrp toolkit?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856253&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856260&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I should have bought way harder but honestly 500 bucks isn&amp;#x27;t bad&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856262&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856205&lt;br&gt;mmm splendid&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856283&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I sold 1/3 of my bag on $1.3 &lt;br&gt;am I cooked ?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856309&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856283&lt;br&gt;what do we say about swingies, anon?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856419&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is this is a fever dream or have we gained back thread engagement without Spammy? What if Spammy changed tactics and all the 1pbtid posts is just Spammy?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856444&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856309&lt;br&gt;Swing high or swing low, eventually you&amp;#x27;ll swing from the neck.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856506&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856444&lt;br&gt;my goodness, would you look at those digits&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856580&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I have the perfect theme for the next bake and I will not let Spammy or that other retard snipe it away from me in 63 posts time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856680&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Today&amp;#x27;s theme:&lt;br&gt;https://youtu.be/S30XdiTDINc&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856760&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I would rape spammy until his anus can&amp;#x27;t stop bleeding. Then when he begs me to stop I slice his stupid throat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856913&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Where&amp;#x27;s Spammy, did he died?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857019&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856246&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m not familiar with crossmark wallet.&lt;br&gt;https://www.xrptoolkit.com/connect-wallet&lt;br&gt;XRP Toolkit lists the following compatible wallets on its site:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Bitfrost Wallet&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Ledger Device&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Xaman Wallet&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;D&amp;#x27;Cent Wallet&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Keystone&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Cobo Vault&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beside those, it also gives the option to enter an address, with this note:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;View your account or prepare transactions to be signed by another account, for example an account set as regular key.&lt;br&gt;Based on the wording here, it doesn&amp;#x27;t sound like you&amp;#x27;d be able to actually sign transactions this way.&lt;br&gt;Read only basically; unless I&amp;#x27;m misunderstanding the wording here.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you want to connect and interact with XRP Toolkit, then you&amp;#x27;ll need to limit yourself to the above listed choices.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857030&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spammy and kill spammy are the same person, he posts it for sympathy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857067&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anyone mentioning spammy in any way either positive, neutral or negative is spammy.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;No sane person cares about him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857074&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I will lock Spammy up, playing XRP tubers on loudspeaker 24/7 and when he asks for release from his personal hell I&amp;#x27;ll approach the cell door and gently whisper, &amp;quot;just two more weeks, your release is around the corner&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857078&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m gonna fuck spammy until he bleeds and begs me to stop&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857112&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856580&lt;br&gt;Maybe a preview? Some riddle of a hint.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857169&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Guys, schizo chicken lady here, recovering from a week of waging after my xrp stack never mooned. Honestly I think we&amp;#x27;re deluded thinking xrp is going to moon at all. There are only 1000 active accounts and 50k daily transactions on the xrp ledger. I think any price pumps were due to ripple marketing. Sorry. I sold 25% of my xrp this week for Tron. There&amp;#x27;s zero hype about Tron in news or gematria. In fact i can&amp;#x27;t find any secondary information about it. But it has 850m daily transactions and has outperformed xrp since inception.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857211&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The meme is that xrp will moon when it finds utility. But the ledger has been around for 14 years and no one is using it, mo natter how many riddles, acquisitions, or tweets ripple spits out. The ledger just seems like an clunky ibm project.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857230&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857211&lt;br&gt;Then why is it that every time we break out and start to climb they dump the whole market to suppress us?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857238&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857230&lt;br&gt;The chart the last six months just looks like a steady decline, not a surpresssed breakout&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857247&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857169&lt;br&gt;CHICKEN TRANNY&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857298&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857238&lt;br&gt;Yeah except last night we were chartmogging BTC by pumpmaxing to 1.66 out of nowhere and the Epstein client list got mad and pissed their pants and dumped the market to bring us back into line by dragging us down with them. How many times you been to the island chicken schizo?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded><enclosure url="https://i.4cdn.org/biz/1770750743134576s.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0" /></item><item><title>[FAST 240.0/hr] Thread 61836502 — 60 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61836502</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61836502?lm=1771175445</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 17:10:45 +0000</pubDate><description>Open article for full thread</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;[FAST 240.0/hr] Thread 61836502&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61836502'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 60 • Updated: 2026-02-15 17:10 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;solves the crypto doesn&amp;#x27;t do anything problem in your path&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Replies (oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61843844&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61843808&lt;br&gt;I remember crashing games with scroll wheel weapon changing by doing that lmao&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61844633&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;92 PEOPLE PRESSING THE BUTTON&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATH BUTTON PRESSERS&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;WILL WE SEE 100 SOON????&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61844730&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61841653&lt;br&gt;sure, but the cool thing about crypto is that even extremely small amounts can be traded and used as a currency. Not a nano shill, I&amp;#x27;m a BTC maxi, but its cool to see a faucet in today&amp;#x27;s day and age again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61844761&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61836524&lt;br&gt;Reminds me of the minimum wage machine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61844823&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IT&amp;#x27;S HAPPENIONGGGGGGGGGGG&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE DOLLAR IS DYING IN FRONT OF OUR VERY EYES!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61848018&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;110 people clicking at off hours&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61848848&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;124 clickers, billions must click&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61848919&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;re telling me this is a good investment?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849275&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61848919&lt;br&gt;now look at XRP from 2013 onwards&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850437&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;130 users&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850476&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;is this the 2026 version of the hamster shit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850524&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850476&lt;br&gt;what&amp;#x27;s the hamster shit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851465&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;160 clickers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851881&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;230!!!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61852882&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61842531&lt;br&gt;Most parasites are.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853224&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61852882&lt;br&gt;colonizers be like&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853256&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;wtf happened it was at 100 a couple of hours ago&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853475&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;chat is this real&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853827&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ayo????&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854179&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;the sweet smell of money&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854277&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853827&lt;br&gt;someone playing around with bots, looks like there&amp;#x27;s around 150 real users today&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856192&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UH OH STINKY&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856403&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;which we picking??&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856406&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856403&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856447&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We need to kill every Indian on earth this thread proves this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856456&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856447&lt;br&gt;you can try&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856689&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61837135&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Few understand the significance of this moment.&lt;br&gt;yeah, biz niggas are broke.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856825&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856689&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857159&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853224&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;re ACTUALLY trying to chadify India while shilling a coin. HAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857300&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857159&lt;br&gt;We don&amp;#x27;t need to try.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded><enclosure url="https://i.4cdn.org/biz/1770801864893883s.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0" /></item><item><title>[FAST 444.0/hr] Imagine that they pass unrealized tax gains in your country. — 111 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61851566</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61851566?lm=1771175461</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 17:11:01 +0000</pubDate><description>Open article for full thread</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;[FAST 444.0/hr] Imagine that they pass unrealized tax gains in your country.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61851566'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 111 • Updated: 2026-02-15 17:11 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;What do you do?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Replies (oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856538&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851566&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;unrealized&lt;br&gt;How can I be taxed for something people don’t realize that I have?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856621&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851566&lt;br&gt;as things currently go I could retire in 10 years in my 40`s for the rest of my life. if they would introduce the same thing the dutch just did I would have to work for the rest of my life up until 67. this would unironically drive me into suicide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856638&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856621&lt;br&gt;How much net worth do you need to retire in your 40&amp;#x27;s?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856639&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856538&lt;br&gt;Realized in the sense of closing a transaction not in the sense of having knowledge of.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856643&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856638&lt;br&gt;I personally only require 500k since I still live with my parents and my monthly expenses despite working full time were something like 600-700€ for the past 8 or so years. Will inherit the house anyway. 500k doesnt seem like a lot for most people but I doubt I start spending more than that once I dont work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856644&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856531&lt;br&gt;Catchy slogan&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856645&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851566&lt;br&gt;I have never paid tax before, so I will do nothing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856650&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I live in an offshore tax haven, its all we have going for us that there is no capital gains tax. Everyone would leave it would be so suicidal lol.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856666&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856643&lt;br&gt;500k?&lt;br&gt;Why is it I have 2m EUR at 27 and it doesn&amp;#x27;t feel like enough at all?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856690&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856666&lt;br&gt;Checked. Because you are 27. If you were 50 it would be ok.&lt;br&gt;You probably need at least 4M at 27 to retire.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856731&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856690&lt;br&gt;even with just 2mil you could make 60k a year AFTER tax with boring ass bonds. That´s 5k a month after tax. I understand we all have different life styles but how much money do you spend a month that requires 4mil (which would be 10k a month).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856745&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856731&lt;br&gt;After 30 years at a 4% inflation rate your 2M will be 1/3 of the initial purchasing power. And your 60k will buy 20k worth, and you will be 57 years old.&lt;br&gt;And that is asuming inflation doesnt go higher (which it will go because there is no other way of getting out of the debt), and rates stay high enough where you get that 3% after taxes (which they wont for 30 years)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856752&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851566&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;what if&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t have to imagine, i live in France, the most taxed nation in the history of mankind, so ofc we pionnered the concept already back last year.&lt;br&gt;But it didn&amp;#x27;t make much of a fuss since ppl are used to frogs being cucked to death by their (((government))).&lt;br&gt;Also here it&amp;#x27;s only 1% (so far) so it&amp;#x27;s not as &amp;quot;impressive&amp;quot; as the NL, but it&amp;#x27;s for all &amp;quot;unproductive assets&amp;quot;, which is vague enough to eventually put everything in the basket. They already are talking about adding gold, RE, etc.. to the unrealized gains tax.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856770&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856752&lt;br&gt;Holy shit i didnt know that&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856784&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;rules only apply to those who follow them on an individual level. The law does not apply to large enough groups who actively or passively break it enmasse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856837&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851566&lt;br&gt;Realise the gains, take the hit, leave the country and continue investing in a socially stable country with less freedom to criticise the state but societally stable with a ruling class which understands you don’t tax you money makers.&lt;br&gt;Allow the original socialist state I’ve left to collapse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856844&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853104&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Most people aren&amp;#x27;t money minded like we are&lt;br&gt;Yep. This is mostly a genetic problem. Intelligence is capped by genes. Voting rights should not be equal at least.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856854&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61852029&lt;br&gt;I think youre fucked. Your populations genetics is a mixture of European prison gaurds and prisoners, and highly conformist Asiatics. I don’t mean this rudely, but Corona showed us how distance your population was to being led by the nose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856888&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851566&lt;br&gt;I own an illegal tobacco manufactory and sell cheap cigs to gypsies on the job site. Its that easy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856933&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856745&lt;br&gt;No western country has a 4% inflation rate and a simple world ETF or the S&amp;amp;P500 massively outperforms inflation. 2 million invested in the S&amp;amp;P500 means you will have 4 million in 10 years, 8 million in 20 years, 16 million in 30 years by the time you reach normal retirement age, if you leave it all invested to let it compound. If you seriously struggle with 2 million you must be genuinely retarded and judging by your obviously very low IQ I highly doubt you have anywhere close to that much money invested.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856947&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Invest in fertilizer&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856951&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856933&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; No western country has a 4% inflation rate&lt;br&gt;Nigga look at the numbers, is way worse than that 4%. Look at what has happened in the last 6 years. Is only going to accelerate from here.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; World etf or S&amp;amp;P500&lt;br&gt;Cant you read? An etf is not the same as bonds and anon there was talking about putting 2M in bonds at 27 years old. Asuming you are going to live another 60 years is not that clear that putting all on those indexes is going to work for that long. Probably is better to diversify and buy a bit of everything.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856995&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851566&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;create company&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;company grows too fast&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;forced to sell company &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;buy gold, bury it in garden&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;how would an unrealized gains tax help anyone again. It just seems like a soviet style entrepreneur killer tax forcing you to shelter your wealth and live a lie.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856999&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851566&lt;br&gt;That&amp;#x27;s fine - I don&amp;#x27;t have any gains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857003&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856095&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;We get taxed on consumption but not even the most leftist government would think of taxing anything investment-related.&lt;br&gt;HMRC wants to tax people&amp;#x27;s &amp;quot;excess cash&amp;quot; in S&amp;amp;S ISA&amp;#x27;s, because of the reduction to £12k in the ISA allowance. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Also, they&amp;#x27;ll probably reduce the £20k limit in future, &amp;quot;because only rich people can fill that up anyway&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857139&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Coldcard and start buying bitcoin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857161&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851566&lt;br&gt;ignore it like i ignore all kike laws and defend my property with ar15&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857185&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851566&lt;br&gt;Do I get a check from the govt for all of my unrealized losses?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857265&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857161&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; he thinks we can have ar15s overhere&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857302&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851566&lt;br&gt;Unironically just leg it. No point working at that point. I&amp;#x27;d just give up, take my money, go travelling in Argentina whilst Europe descends into communism and war. Then just take it from there, fuck knows how it&amp;#x27;ll work out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded><enclosure url="https://i.4cdn.org/biz/1771023693544742s.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0" /></item><item><title>[FAST 1364.0/hr] /pmg/ - Precious Metals General — 341 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61855017</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61855017?lm=1771175571</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 17:12:51 +0000</pubDate><description>Open article for full thread</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;[FAST 1364.0/hr] /pmg/ - Precious Metals General&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61855017'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 341 • Updated: 2026-02-15 17:12 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;Why precious metals?&lt;br&gt;https://youtu.be/i3S4rl6ehiI &lt;br&gt;https://youtu.be/gksenA5Al_A &lt;br&gt;https://youtu.be/FI7NnOg2rxo &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Huge deficits in minerals such as silver by 2050 inevitable&lt;br&gt;https://youtu.be/iibsrDXdEos [Embed]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Bullion dealers&lt;br&gt;https://libertycoin.com/ (US)&lt;br&gt;https://www.chards.co.uk/ (EU/UK)&lt;br&gt;https://www.silburycoins.co.uk/ (Ancient)&lt;br&gt;https://www.luciteria.com/ (Other rare metals)&lt;br&gt;https://www.ma-shops.com/ (Numismatics)&lt;br&gt;https://www.goldeneaglecoin.com/ (US)&lt;br&gt;https://stoutgold.co/ (US)&lt;br&gt;https://www.aydincoins.com/ (US)&lt;br&gt;https://prospectorsgoldandgems.com/ (US)&lt;br&gt;more at:https://pastebin.com/gZfZHtNE&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Numismatic search&lt;br&gt;https://en.numista.com/catalogue&lt;br&gt;https://www.ngccoin.com/price-guide/world&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;News and graphs&lt;br&gt;https://numismag.com/en/home-en&lt;br&gt;https://silverseek.com&lt;br&gt;https://www.silverdoctors.com&lt;br&gt;https://www.mining.com&lt;br&gt;https://silverbacksnakes.io/finance/silver&lt;br&gt;https://www.gold.org/goldhub/data/gold-reserves-by-country&lt;br&gt;https://wtfhappenedin1971.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Compare&lt;br&gt;https://findbullionprices.com (US)&lt;br&gt;https://eu.compare.pm (EU)&lt;br&gt;https://www.gold.de/aufgeldtabelle (DE/EU)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Resources&lt;br&gt;https://www.jmbullion.com/ultimate-guide-to-90-silver-coins&lt;br&gt;https://kevinsworkbench.com/junksilverguide&lt;br&gt;https://www.coinflation.com&lt;br&gt;http://coinapps.com&lt;br&gt;https://erikasgrig.com/calculators/rpi-calculator-inflation&lt;br&gt;https://learn.apmex.com/buying-guide/buying-in-the-usa&lt;br&gt;https://pastebin.com/5aLmWUUK&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Prospecting&lt;br&gt;https://youtu.be/ZCL6FKQZyoM &lt;br&gt;https://www.usgs.gov/programs/mineral-resources-program/science&lt;br&gt;https://www.mndm.gov.on.ca/en/news/mines-and-minerals&lt;br&gt;https://www.amazon.ca/Gold-Creeks-Ghostowns-British-Columbia/dp/088839988X&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Nitric acid, magnets, and ping test&lt;br&gt;https://youtu.be/3mg9YcAShTo &lt;br&gt;https://youtu.be/NgSXg-WOEVY &lt;br&gt;https://youtu.be/2ymGAyKAg-k &lt;br&gt;https://www.fakebullion.com/index.php/resources/fake-bullion-database&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Silver Hallmarks Encyclopedia&lt;br&gt;https://www.925-1000.com/&lt;br&gt;https://www.silvercollection.it/hallmarks.html&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Previous thread: &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61852374&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Replies (oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857064&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857020&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;It&amp;#x27;s different this time &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lmao, it took 45 years for silver to break even from 1980&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857083&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;crazy to think that silver broke $100 before gold did $5000, and look at the prices now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857086&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857064&lt;br&gt;anon i genuinely hope youre right&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857088&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anyone bought from StonexBullion? Silver is at 65€ right now and they boldly lie about it saying silver is at 80€ in their prices. &lt;br&gt;Lmao, 65€ per oz and they&amp;#x27;re selling at 113€/oz while claiming they have a 10% premium.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857089&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857088&lt;br&gt;Their gold is often a very good price. Silver mje&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857098&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857029&lt;br&gt;Industrial demand is down supply is up the only thing propping it up are incels buying but now y&amp;#x27;all broke&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857100&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857064&lt;br&gt;Technically this spike was lower than the 1980 one when you adjust it for inflation. Too many people seem to forget about that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857102&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857059&lt;br&gt;lots of options for me, I&amp;#x27;ll hopefully have a good choice soon. I want it ordered before the wage life commences tomorrow&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857103&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857089&lt;br&gt;Back when it was called coininvest and had a separate website for silver and gold I had bought silver from them and the premium was like 1-2€.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857165&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seems like shills are back after Shabbath.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857180&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857059&lt;br&gt;my friend, if you&amp;#x27;re UK based, may I ask where you&amp;#x27;re buying your coins from?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857189&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;the orca tube, it will be 11 orcas and 3 twin maples. does this sound acceptable or would the 3 twin maples bother you to the point of buying 3 more orcas?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857201&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857098&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;supply is up&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857202&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;pringles silver &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ej1NE-0gzGs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857220&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857180&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m in the Netherlands.&lt;br&gt;Often stonexbullion.com, goldsilbershop.de, some dutch places, ma shops.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857224&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Good one&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sent from my iPod&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Sep 1,2011, at 10:16 AM wrote:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;From: Clay Dunnagan&lt;br&gt;Sent: Wednesday, August 31, 2011 10:39 PM&lt;br&gt;Subject: The Silver Screw&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE SILVER SCREW&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Once upon a time, a young lad was born without a belly button. In its place was a silver screw. All the doctors told his mother that there was nothing they could do.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Like it or not, he was stuck with it . . . He was screwed.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;All the years of growing up were real tough on him, as all who saw the screw made fun of him. He avoided leaving his house . . . And thus, never made any friends.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;One day, a mysterious stranger saw his belly and told him of a monk in Tibet who could get rid of the screw for him. He was thrilled. The next day, he took all of his life&amp;#x27;s savings and bought a ticket to Nepal .&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;After several days of climbing up steep cliffs, he came upon a giant monastery. The monk knew exactly why he had come. The screwy guy was told to sleep in the highest tower of the monastery and the following day when he awoke, the screw would have been removed. The man immediately went to the room and fell asleep.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;During the night while he slept, a purple fog floated in an open window. In the mist floated a solid silver screwdriver. In just moments, the screwdriver removed the screw and disappeared out the window.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The next morning when the man awoke, he saw the silver screw laying on the pillow next to him. Reaching down, he felt his navel, and there was no screw there! Jubilant, he leaped out of bed . . . And his ass fell off.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The moral to this is:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#x27;Don&amp;#x27;t screw around with things you don&amp;#x27;t understand -- You could lose your ass.&amp;#x27;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sent from my iPhone&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857228&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857180&lt;br&gt;In the UK Chards looks good imo. You have quite a few very good bullion dealers there;)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857246&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857224&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857264&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856890&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;2053&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;he doesn&amp;#x27;t know&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857267&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857088&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Stonexbullion&lt;br&gt;Yes. That dutch anon is recommending it all the time and it&amp;#x27;s a total scam.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Best options for europe are goldsilber.be, metalmarket and europeanmint&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857271&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857267&lt;br&gt;I would add hollandgold too, but they are very sketchy with delivery times and their shipping costs are 80 euro (lol).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857274&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;and just like that this edition of pmg met it&amp;#x27;s 10-20% quota for kike posters&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857277&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Almost all countries have a tax about capital gain, you could try to avoid paying it if you don&amp;#x27;t want, but what stops me from going into a coin shop/bullion dealer and buying 5 oz of gold at the current price paying with my own 5 oz of gold that I bought back when it was sub 1k€ an ounce? &lt;br&gt;Wouldn&amp;#x27;t that reset my capital gain tax for the future at the current 4.2k€/oz therefore if I wanted to sell it the legit way reduce my tax burden?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857267&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;europeanmint&lt;br&gt;I bought some stuff from there back in 2015 but even back then they barely had any stock.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857280&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855742&lt;br&gt;did she respond?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857286&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857228&lt;br&gt;Is it wise to consider buying from their &amp;quot;used&amp;quot; coin range? The coins I&amp;#x27;m looking at are either out of stock or have quite a high premium, so now I&amp;#x27;m considering buying from the used bin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857288&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857284&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857284&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857284&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857284&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Baked&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857289&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857267&lt;br&gt;Gildsilverbe seem goid I&amp;#x27;m gonna try them next year. My experience is only good so far with StoneX. Mainly they ship when promised and it arrives without stress. So far.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857297&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857286&lt;br&gt;Well depends on how you want your coin. For example 1 ducat I prefer uncirculated.&lt;br&gt;But a Britannia or krugerrand id not mind circulated as long as the gold weight is ok.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857303&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857297&lt;br&gt;Would the gold weight not always match that of an uncirculated coin of the same type? 1oz sovereign used vs 1oz sovereign uncirculated? Unless chips and dents are on the coin eh?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857309&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857289&lt;br&gt;Do you buy silver from there? Because they are charging 110 euro for silver coins. It&amp;#x27;s as if they haven&amp;#x27;t updated the website since the crash. For gold prices are more normal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded><enclosure url="https://i.4cdn.org/biz/1771105049951580s.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0" /></item><item><title>[FAST 192.0/hr] A Kalshi marked experienced a liquidity panic; whale gamblers got bailed out — 48 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61849677</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61849677?lm=1771175589</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 17:13:09 +0000</pubDate><description>Open article for full thread</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;[FAST 192.0/hr] A Kalshi marked experienced a liquidity panic; whale gamblers got bailed out&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61849677'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 48 • Updated: 2026-02-15 17:13 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Holy shit!&lt;br&gt;$3.6 million market decided despite clear rules and video evidence!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was a Mentions market based on the recent Bernie Sanders rally in Greensboro (on 2/12). Trading was ramping up before the event, with all of the typical Bernie triggers at 90% (Trump, socialism, immigration, corruption, billionaire, etc.). Pretty typical, low liquidity mentions market, maybe $400k. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the blink of an eye, it shoots ip to $1.5 million, as Kalshi began advertising it in their front page. I heard they also sent a text alert to users. This market would eventually balloon to $3.6 million.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I’m watching the prices and searching for a live stream. Maybe 10 minutes after the event started the prices begin to plummet. Not just a few positions; all Yes positions drop drastically to the bottom. Things that Sanders says in literally every speech he’s given in the last 20 years drop to below 10%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Replies (oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850282&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849772&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Quite rare &lt;br&gt;The fact that it happens at all is enough of a reason not to use this retarded platform&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850309&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I was always suspicious of these free form text event bets websites. Ultimately they decide what reality is, and will give you money or not according to their views, which can be whatever they want. If the boss misclicked or bet wrong, it will be the reality which is wrong.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850431&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850309&lt;br&gt;Kalshi and Polymarket don’t have money to give anyone. Gamblers are gambling against one another, not against the platform. It’s not like Kalshi kept everyone’s money. They just gave it to the whales.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850439&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even a shitcoin would be safer than this retarded shit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850455&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850431&lt;br&gt;To me it&amp;#x27;s clear that at least in this case, the owners bet against other users. When they fucked up, they just said &amp;quot;didn&amp;#x27;t happen lol&amp;quot;.&lt;br&gt;The same thing as exchanges act as the market maker really. But if you manage to trick their algo and fuck them, they will just block your account for abuse or something.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850461&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850282&lt;br&gt;This is the first case I know of where the documented evidence (a video recording) was downright ignored. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;There have been some shady wordings, like “what will trump say during his meeting with the President of Columbia?” Well, know one can know what was actually said because it was a closed-door meeting. There are media reports and press statements, but no actual record. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;They began voiding markets though, like anything with Charlie Kirk after he was killed. And I think the Niki Minaj market was voided as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850471&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850439&lt;br&gt;You can gamble on the price of Bitcoin and it’s acktchually safer than buying bitcoin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850578&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850282&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849772&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850614&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849677&lt;br&gt;will you faggots stop looking for sympathy when these nebulous prediction markets don&amp;#x27;t work out for you. we don&amp;#x27;t give a fuck&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850649&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849729&lt;br&gt;betting in these gay prediction markets makes you extremely jewish&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850653&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850461&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;This is the first case I know of where the documented evidence (a video recording) was downright ignored.&lt;br&gt;and it won&amp;#x27;t be the last&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850875&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850614&lt;br&gt;It’s an interesting case. It’s not personal; I’m not gonna sweat $6.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850649&lt;br&gt;Please explain the decision fference between gambling in the price of silver going up or the chance of Taylor Swift getting married this year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851319&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Give me some good bets to make i just threw 100 bucks on this fucking app &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Truly incredible how easy it is to set up. No ID or nothing&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851376&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851319&lt;br&gt;its almost like it was built by kike intel agencies to steal and launder money or something. weird!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853737&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;seems like a shitco&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853755&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854842&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851319&lt;br&gt;The are long term, short term, and medium term markets. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Short term would be ones that only last about a hour, such as “Will the price of Bitcoin be 66,500 or greater by 2pm?” Every one of those markets are actually broken down into 1,000 or 500 increments and you can gamble in each one. “Will BC be over 58,000 by 2pm?” That bet will have a very small returnif you buy Yes, and it resolves as Yes, because everyone will be betting Yes as well (because it’s very likely t to hat the price will be over 58k). Will it be over 69,750? Well, the price for those contracts can change drastically over the hour, as Bitcoin rises and falls in real time, hovering around that point, dipping above and below it. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another short term bet are the mentions markets like in the OP. Some don’t open until the day of the event. But some are two or three days before. Sportsball games are often medium term as well, with prices changing in the lead up and during the games.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;There’s a week long “what will trump say this week” market that resets every Monday morning. Those can be lucrative if you can get in early (around 10am eastern time on Monday), buy the right positions, and have a little luck. For instance a No position on a term he hasn’t been using lately might be cheap at the start of the week but much more expensive as the week goes on. But you have to get in early, almost like an IPO. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are long term options that won’t resolve for weeks or months the, but they see very little movement unless the news changes. Who will be the Dem president rial nominee? Well, even if you’re right you won’t see a resolution until the DNC announces who it is in 2028. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You could also stick with small bets on sportsball. It can be pretty safe if you pick 75%+ odds, and pay attention to the game so far if you’re betting on live action.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854894&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849677&lt;br&gt;Tl;dr - in unregulated gambling the goyim thought they were out jewing the jew but the jew jewed them good.&lt;br&gt;Better luck next time goyim hehe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855391&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854842&lt;br&gt;Think of wins and losses as a percentage. “It’s only $3,” sure. But that’s 3% of your portfolio. That’s a huge loss. If you could sell now and make $0.25 on a $2 bet instead of risking a resolution, you made an 12.5% return. “It’s only $0.25,” sure, but it’s a substantial gain relative to the buy in.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855406&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854894&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;unregulated&lt;br&gt;Why do you choose to operate on low information? Is it because you’re brown or just a regular retard?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856379&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;these betting sites are scams&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856388&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How the fuck are predictions markets not regulated like online gambling? Is this some jewish trick or something?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856496&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856388&lt;br&gt;The only one that isn’t regulated is Polymarket. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856379&lt;br&gt;Sounds like a conspiracy theory to me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856595&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850471&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;safer&lt;br&gt;No it’s not faggot&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857072&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854842&lt;br&gt;I want long shots only&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857106&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849678&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;COMEX IS GOING TO BLOW UP BECAUSE THEY&amp;#x27;RE OUT OF SILVER!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You guys really think you can win in some one else&amp;#x27;s casino?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857285&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850471&lt;br&gt;You have to be 18 to post here&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857305&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849677&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849678&lt;br&gt;Well then their credibility tanks to zero and responsible people stop using their platform. I’d never heard of it so idc but I’m sorry for your loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857308&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849729&lt;br&gt;A 6 million dollar bet you say?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857312&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850159&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850649&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851376&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854894&lt;br&gt;only a few gets it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded><enclosure url="https://i.4cdn.org/biz/1771001248899060s.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0" /></item><item><title>[FAST 944.0/hr] /smg/ - stock market general — 236 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61853891</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61853891?lm=1771175804</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 17:16:44 +0000</pubDate><description>Open article for full thread</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;[FAST 944.0/hr] /smg/ - stock market general&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61853891'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 236 • Updated: 2026-02-15 17:16 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;waifu edition&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Some helpful links to numb the pain&lt;br&gt;https://findahelpline.com/&lt;br&gt;https://www.nvidia.com/refunds/&lt;br&gt;https://www.whitehouse.gov/refunds&lt;br&gt;https://jlingz.com/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Educational sites:&lt;br&gt;https://www.investopedia.com&lt;br&gt;https://www.khanacademy.org/economics-finance-domain&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Financial TV Streams:&lt;br&gt;https://www.newslive.com/american/cnbc.html&lt;br&gt;https://www.livestreamy.net/bloomberg/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Charts:&lt;br&gt;https://www.tradingview.com&lt;br&gt;https://www.finscreener.com&lt;br&gt;https://www.portfoliovisualizer.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Screeners: so you feel like in the movies&lt;br&gt;https://finviz.com/&lt;br&gt;https://etfdb.com/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Gambling:&lt;br&gt;https://www.optionsplaybook.com/options-introduction/&lt;br&gt;https://www.optionsprofitcalculator.com&lt;br&gt;https://optionstrat.com/&lt;br&gt;https://www.optionistics.com/quotes/option-prices&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Pre-Market and Live data:&lt;br&gt;https://www.investing.com/indices/indices-futures&lt;br&gt;https://finance.yahoo.com/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Calendars&lt;br&gt;https://www.marketwatch.com/economy-politics/calendar&lt;br&gt;https://www.earningswhispers.com/calendar&lt;br&gt;https://www.cmegroup.com/trading/interest-rates/countdown-to-fomc.html&lt;br&gt;https://www.mortgagenewsdaily.com/data/building-permits&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Boomer Investing 101: so zoomers with meme stocks can outperform you&lt;br&gt;https://www.bogleheads.org/wiki/Getting_started&lt;br&gt;https://www.sec.gov/search-filings&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Misc smg:&lt;br&gt;https://www.financialjuice.com/home&lt;br&gt;https://finance.yahoo.com/trending-tickers&lt;br&gt;https://market24hclock.com/&lt;br&gt;https://www.dividendchannel.com/drip-returns-calculator&lt;br&gt;https://brokerchooser.com/&lt;br&gt;https://www.chathamfinancial.com/technology/us-market-rates&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Previously on /smg/: &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850998&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Replies (oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857057&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856594&lt;br&gt;suicide in fortnite. I sure as hell wont work until death because thats literally and unironically what they expect of you at this point.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857066&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Are markets opened tomorrow? It’s a federal holiday (Trump day) tomorrow&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857069&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857066&lt;br&gt;no which is a good thing because amerisharts are responsible for all the recent dumps.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857075&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857066&lt;br&gt;futes are open 6pm-1pm still I think&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857076&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857066&lt;br&gt;Yes, non-nigger markets are open. UCITS ETFs will even allow some trading with US indices since they replicate them with futures. &lt;br&gt;t. europoor&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857077&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857069&lt;br&gt;they are always responsible for dumps&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857096&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;we are so back eu bros&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857110&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857066&lt;br&gt;Europe is open, amerifart. You are not the center of the world. No longer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857116&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is China invading Taiwan bullish or bearish?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857120&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857096&lt;br&gt;is that in regard to the recent dutch unrealized gains thingy? if so its at least a positive statement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857135&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857120&lt;br&gt;I dont know the context of that statement but it basically means that thte dutch approach is wrong according to Lagardes opinion no?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857141&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856525&lt;br&gt;sweet I hope I can retire on the 5 april calls I&amp;#x27;ve been holding&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857144&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857141&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857145&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857096&lt;br&gt;This garbage law would at least double my tax&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857148&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robinhood Gold!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857154&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853947&lt;br&gt;maybe you could talk me into it. i owned some before and got out when silver was dumping and i see anoter silver dump coming soon in the charts, what is your reason for buyng on monday?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857163&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robinhood Gold Actual User!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857183&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857154&lt;br&gt;earnings report on tuesday&lt;br&gt;you know how well buying shit the day off earnings works&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857190&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857183&lt;br&gt;Robinhood Is Gud1!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857193&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857190&lt;br&gt;thanks you for the free alpha saar&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857195&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857163&lt;br&gt;Is there something bad about Gold? I get a 3 percent match on my Roth for $5 a month. That’s $165 dollars for free after the cost.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857215&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robinhood Is Nice1!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857218&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Tripfags&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Spamfags&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Avatarfags&lt;br&gt;Most of you are alright but holy shit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857223&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857215&lt;br&gt;you are but a filthy dalit compared to the chop loss hidden tigers amc naked calls pajeet of yesteryear you mother benchod saar begone the black death upon you and your mother&amp;#x27;s mother&amp;#x27;s mother&amp;#x27;s mother.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857250&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robinhood Gold Annual Plan!! NOT REALLY!!!!!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857255&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856868&lt;br&gt;charging your tenants y the hour for parking is the most jewish shit ive ever heard&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857259&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857250&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t get it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857263&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857215&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857276&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;can we just make 2 /smg/s at a time, then just post in the one he&amp;#x27;s not in?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857319&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857276&lt;br&gt;the one on /bant/ exists&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded><enclosure url="https://i.4cdn.org/biz/1771082894968487s.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0" /></item><item><title>[FAST 816.0/hr] /BBBYQ/ - Bath Barron Edition — 204 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61803438</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61803438?lm=1771175829</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 17:17:09 +0000</pubDate><description>Open article for full thread</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;[FAST 816.0/hr] /BBBYQ/ - Bath Barron Edition&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61803438'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 204 • Updated: 2026-02-15 17:17 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;BBBYQ&lt;br&gt;TOKENS.COM&lt;br&gt;TZERO&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;WAGMI&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Replies (oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853279&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61852941&lt;br&gt;you lost tranny, stop the cope. you lost your money by investing a random about to bankrupt company. it&amp;#x27;s over. time to rope. you can start 1000000000 threads in /biz/, will not change the FACT that: THEY&amp;#x27;LL NEVER PAY YOU ANYTHING, YOU LOST YOUR MONEY LIKE A RETARD, NOW YOU ARE IN FULL COPE MODE, but it&amp;#x27;s over. you are a retard. You could just buy some good ETF. VCs fooled you, like an idiot savant, they took your money and throw you out to the street. Keep opening this threads for me to get a nice KEK from your cope.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;inb4&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;hurrr durrr ASSIP numbers are same, hurr durr ASSIP-6 same give me back my money&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;hurr durrrr ryan cohen&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;hurr durrr there&amp;#x27;s some shady stuff going on&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;let me ELI5 that for you:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;YOU (RETARD) BOUGHT MEME STOCKS OF &amp;quot;ABOUT TO BANKRUPT&amp;quot; COMPANY&lt;br&gt;COMPANY BANKRUPTS&lt;br&gt;SOMEONE ELSE CAME AND BOUGHT THE NAMES AND STUFF FOR THEIR DEBT&lt;br&gt;THEY STARTED SAME COMPANY WITH SAME NAME AND ASSIP6&lt;br&gt;NOW YOU OWN NOTHING&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;just kek baggie.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853283&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853279&lt;br&gt;they are not gonna pay anything to you and I hope they hold you personally resposible for unpaid depts, since as a stockholder you were partner of the company, you knew they have debts, you bought the stock anyway, so you are responsible, time to pay more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853404&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853279&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853283&lt;br&gt;Hard to tell if this is sarcasm/satire posting because Doug cifu ruined his life and career from seething about an ostensibly dead towel store.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853416&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853283&lt;br&gt;I dont care.&lt;br&gt;I dont read this shit.&lt;br&gt;I loss my Money? I dont care,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853494&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853279&lt;br&gt;Uh oh having a melty?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853500&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853494&lt;br&gt;They&amp;#x27;re spiraling the last few days. Perhaps a tendie offer has rattled them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853518&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853494&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853500&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853416&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853404&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853283&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t care about any of it since I buy real stocks, not meme ones. You gambled and you lost. COPING, SEETHING and DILATING here is not going to change the FACT that: &amp;quot;YOU LOST YOUR MONEY LIKE AN IDIOT SAVANT, YOU&amp;#x27;LL NEVER GET IT BACK&amp;quot;. I&amp;#x27;m talking with facts. You are talking with COPE. Instead of spamming biz with these retardic threads, you should go and get some therapy. Also hey don&amp;#x27;t shoot the messenger, i&amp;#x27;m just relaying you information about REALITY. Yes I&amp;#x27;m the messenger of REALITY. You&amp;#x27;ve been living in a dream world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853536&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nuh uh&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853587&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;You loss all? I REALLY care about it for some reason!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853613&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This better be one of you larping. Kek. If it’s not I haven’t seen seething like this in a while.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853632&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853518&lt;br&gt;i dont care.&lt;br&gt;im love it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853794&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;not your problem, man&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853831&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853279&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853518&lt;br&gt;The shilly doth protest too much&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854168&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853518&lt;br&gt;kek!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854282&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853500&lt;br&gt;Is it still true that Marcus lemonois doesn’t get paid if bbby doesn’t rise a lot this month? &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I remember he had a change of job title recently. Idk if that means a different pay structure&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854525&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854282&lt;br&gt;FY 2026 proposed pay structure pending approval at next shareholder meeting:&lt;br&gt;https://www.ainvest.com/news/bed-bath-shares-surge-5-55-pre-market-ceo-compensation-package-disclosure-2601/&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;$300k salary&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Up to $2.2 million bonus cash based on performance&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Up to 2.1 million shares and RSU&lt;br&gt;This does not spark joy. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;FY 2025 pay structure:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;3/28/2025 DEF 14A&lt;br&gt;https://investors.beyond.com/financials/sec-filings/default.aspx&lt;br&gt;$0 salary&lt;br&gt;$0 cash bonus&lt;br&gt;424,300 shares (this does not spark joy) &lt;br&gt;2.25 million shares in call options at $45, $50, $60 tranches with a 4.98% increase in share price the day following disclosure of MNPI&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t see anything about the vesting period for the call options expiring after 2 years specifically&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854548&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61852611&lt;br&gt;jake2b&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854641&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s amazing how how Clarifying the Cusip Conunudrum is. Concern trolls want to Crypost but their caustic concerns completely crumble by the confirmation of the CUSIP Confirmation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854722&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854641&lt;br&gt;there is also a conundrum concerning a certain creditor to the company :o)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854941&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854722&lt;br&gt;Checked. Who could it be? What does it all mean?!?!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855003&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I dont care.&lt;br&gt;I dont cafè&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855287&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855003&lt;br&gt;This goes to show you just how dumb and disingenuous the silly shillies are. You can ask Goldberg whatever the hell you want but he is not obligated to give you a truthful answer when M&amp;amp;A is involved. He wouldn&amp;#x27;t tell you so this is completely useless. &lt;br&gt;This still does not solve the CUSIP Conundrum. Words only get you so far, but right here right now in 2026 there are open Bed Bath and Beyond stores and the company that operates them is not even using the Overstock/BYON/BBBY CUSIP. They issued new securities in October using BBBYQs CUSIP. &lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s already proven 100% fact that a reverse merger of the BBBYQ shell has already occurred with BBBY. There is zero counterargument. &lt;br&gt;Overstock, BYON and BBBY all kept them same CUSIP. So why now does it suddenly switch? Occams Razor solves the puzzle: BBBYQ shell reverse merger has already occured and the details are not in any known docket.&lt;br&gt;BBBY mystery has been solved by yours truly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855551&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855003&lt;br&gt;Mayhaps DK-Butterfly and DK-Butterfly1 are different entities. As per the Jake DD.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855610&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855551&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s just a typo, bro. For some reason, when writing out DK-Butterfly. I, too, will accidentally add on a -1 for no reason. This speculative theories are bizarre-1. See! Haha, I did it on accident just now. I can&amp;#x27;t even believe I did that LOL&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855697&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855003&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Sent from my iPhone&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856432&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855697&lt;br&gt;I dont care&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857014&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hallo?&lt;br&gt;When BBBY return? &lt;br&gt;I dont care&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857266&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857014&lt;br&gt;BBBY is trading now. BBBYQ was canceled, and no longer exists. If you had BBBYQ when it was canceled you lost that investment, it can never be returned. Anyone who says BBBYQ is coming back is a scammer or mentally ill.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857313&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855287&lt;br&gt;What mental illnesses are you diagnosed with?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857321&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857266&lt;br&gt;I dont care of loss my Money.&lt;br&gt;I dont read your shit post.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded><enclosure url="https://i.4cdn.org/biz/1770327356756880s.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0" /></item><item><title>[FAST 208.0/hr] Thread 61850016 — 52 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61850016</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61850016?lm=1771175910</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 17:18:30 +0000</pubDate><description>Open article for full thread</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;[FAST 208.0/hr] Thread 61850016&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61850016'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 52 • Updated: 2026-02-15 17:18 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;know people with multiple six figures but never had a gf&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How is that even possible?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Replies (oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850479&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since 2023 I have been mostly living off credit (while paying obligatory monthly bills) and putting free cash into investments that I thought would push me from 15k to 1 million. Turns out unless you&amp;#x27;re going hard on high risk stuff, this is very hard. I recently realized my credit to assets ratio is now unfavorable and thus have to grind for the next bullrun so I can make it. Keep gambling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851626&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850081&lt;br&gt;I bet your parents are wishing that you had.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851627&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850052&lt;br&gt;i didn&amp;#x27;t realize until much later but i likely have borderline autism and borderline schizoid PD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61852036&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I don’t show off my wealth, most people would assume I have $1000 to my name. In my day-to-day life I engage with 3 women my age who are all in long term relationships. I’m deeply in love with one of them. I’m also socially awkward and probably low test, and broken minded from long term 4chan browsing. &lt;br&gt;Average height, average weight, average dick. Despise fat chicks (phisically and morally).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61852056&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Women are fucking expensive&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61852193&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850105&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yes lol. I’ve listened to women absolutely THRASH the dick size of their exes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61852198&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850077&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;jacking off in the morning&lt;br&gt;suboptimal, you&amp;#x27;ll feel tired for work&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61852199&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850016&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s about genetics, not money&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854346&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850310&lt;br&gt;Height &amp;gt; frame &amp;gt; face &amp;gt; charisma &amp;gt; status &amp;gt; money&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854408&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850105&lt;br&gt;I am pretty inexperienced with women, but my theory is that a her perception of the size is what matters more than the actual size. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The female mind doesn’t really relate to reality directly, there is a buffer, in between themselves and reality and that is their emotional state. This state can massively shift their experience of the same objective thing. Like, if a woman is in love with you, then your dick becomes massive in her eyes, but when the feelings fade, it becomes small. Men have this too but to a much lesser extent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854568&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;women are mossad agents&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854608&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850016&lt;br&gt;Betabuxxing is an outdated strategy. &lt;br&gt;The assumption was always that women naturally wanted to be mothers.&lt;br&gt;What we have learned is that when given the freedom, women will chose to do anything other than be mothers. &lt;br&gt;The assumption tied into myths about female purity and feminine &amp;quot;caring&amp;quot; natures. &lt;br&gt;We are learning that such a thing was strictly socially enforced and doesn&amp;#x27;t actually exist as an emergent property of women.&lt;br&gt;In other words real women have not been invented yet. Foids (men with tits) are an outdated technology that we are rapidly replacing with genetic sciences and robotics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854645&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854408&lt;br&gt;truth nuke&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854663&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850016&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;How is that even possible?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;When women become a second job where you pay to work and potentially have your life destroyed on a whim, it becomes very possible.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;No it&amp;#x27;s not just in my head, two women could be having a full on conversation at a store and when they walk by where I&amp;#x27;m standing looking at some shit on the shelf they immediately shut up and you can feel them tense up like I&amp;#x27;m some kind of predator. It doesn&amp;#x27;t matter what age either except for old grannies. It&amp;#x27;s not just me, it&amp;#x27;s their reaction to any man they don&amp;#x27;t know in general.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854703&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850077&lt;br&gt;theres is nothing like rawdogging a woman, jerking off is just sad.&lt;br&gt;glad it works for you tho, and nice pepe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854704&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850016&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;d rather spend my money on an AI girlfriend, considering how women are these days. I even trust my cummingtonite more than an animal that bleeds for a whole week and doesn&amp;#x27;t die&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m still waiting for the day when robot wives are created&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854713&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850093&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;cut your losses on fantasy like gf and marriage&lt;br&gt;been there, done that, regret will hit you hard in your 50s, but if you dont kys your fine afterwards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854720&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854608&lt;br&gt;Holy based&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854728&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854568&lt;br&gt;eternal honey pot&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854926&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850110&lt;br&gt;small&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855221&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850105&lt;br&gt;6.5 x 5.5 here.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;i don&amp;#x27;t know because i don&amp;#x27;t have a small dick, i also haven&amp;#x27;t had sex in like 10 years lol. im 33 btw. only had sex with 2 girls, one was my ex the other was fuck meat. my ex told me i should be proud of my dick, fuck meat said my dick was thick, both said i stretched them out. I never really spent money on these girls, I attribute that to my dick.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855537&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850016&lt;br&gt;Just become a tutor for high schoolers, if you are in shape and not too old some horny chick will want to live out a fucking her teacher fantasy&lt;br&gt;source: me&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855542&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850016&lt;br&gt;That&amp;#x27;s literally me&lt;br&gt;Also khhv&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855563&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61852036&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;falling in love with a woman&lt;br&gt;You need to stop that shit, immediately. Pairing because of love is the stupidest thing a man can do, just be glad she is taken so she doesn&amp;#x27;t have full control over you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855735&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850237&lt;br&gt;Why though? You can&amp;#x27;t beat toys when it comes to size / girth. 6.4 x 6.25 here, not coping just wanted to share&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856970&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854408&lt;br&gt;This, kinda. &amp;quot;Size&amp;quot; here actually means proportion, or size relative to the rest of the body, not absolute. Reduce the fat everywhere, that will help with the perception of main body parts and overall. Become more athletic for endurance, that will help with expected sex endurance&lt;br&gt;Small woman with great proportions, or a woman with larger ass and larger tits yet she is way larger too?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857045&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850016&lt;br&gt;I have $1.6M nw at 29 and the only reason I have a gf is because I geomaxxed to find a Latina. Even at this nw level, American women want nothing to do with you unless you have the right bone structure (face/height). I have an above avg sized dick too. Literally the ONLY thing they want is bone&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857315&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;poor but frugal&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;not very good looking&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;normies hate my auDHD personality&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;attract all the unusual girls that also don’t fit in&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;only realise it months or years later&lt;br&gt;Autism is hell man, just pure hell and then ADHD makes it even worse&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857324&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850105&lt;br&gt;some woman have a large vagina, they need a big dick. but not every woman has a large one. there are medium and small vaginas too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857327&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;know people who are broke and only have debt or less than 100 bucks in thier bank account&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;they have 2+ children on barely above 3+ min wage jobs&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;really makes you think&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded><enclosure url="https://i.4cdn.org/biz/1771005043719921s.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0" /></item></channel></rss>