<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>/biz/ Active (filtered, with replies)</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/</link><description>Filtered out: general, gme, bbbyq. OP + first 3 replies + last 30 replies.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 20:51:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>&gt;you idiots are holding 1s and 0s on a computer, while my wealth is secure in physical precious meta-ACK — 40 replies — 160.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61863917</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61863917?lm=1771361306</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 20:48:26 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;&amp;gt;you idiots are holding 1s and 0s on a computer, while my wealth is secure in physical precious meta-ACK&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61863917'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 40 • Updated: 2026-02-17 20:48 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;you idiots are holding 1s and 0s on a computer, while my wealth is secure in physical precious meta-ACK&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863927&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;you dumb asses really just keep metals sitting around your zero security home&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864275&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863917&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You have to be extremely stupid to hoard precious metals, as a private citizen. People rob banks, in broad daylight, and these morons are dumb enough to believe that they won&amp;#x27;t show up at their homes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864286&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864275&lt;br&gt;hope they have metal detectors cause i forgot where i burried mine&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864451&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864443&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yes, keep stacking for the US Treasury. The country is going to need that for a food program.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We&amp;#x27;re all in this together.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864455&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The more Jewish crypto / stock shills try to convince me not to buy precious metals, the more I want to buy precious metals.&lt;br&gt;Funny thing is they think they&amp;#x27;re cleverly dissuading people, as if normal people are so concerned about others owning metals, when it&amp;#x27;s extremely obvious these Jews have an agenda to push against owning metals.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;a random nigger is somehow going to know your random house has gold and silver in it out of a million other homes that don&amp;#x27;t, AND HE&amp;#x27;LL KNOW YOUR HIDING SPOT FOR IT TOO because... JUST BECAUSE OKAY!?&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;THE GOVERNMENT WILL TAKE IT SOMEHOW because they&amp;#x27;ll like... go door to door and... JUST STOP BUYING THE RARE EARTH METALS GOY! YOU CAN&amp;#x27;T JUST GET WEALTHY IN THE FUTURE! YOU HAVE TO WASTE YOUR WEALTH ON CRYPTO AND STOCKS!&lt;br&gt;kek... wow&lt;br&gt;smooth&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864462&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864455&lt;br&gt;forgot my image, but at least I got dubs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864463&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864455&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;a random nigger is somehow going to know your random house has gold and silver&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nah, your gf/wife is going to run her mouth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864471&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863917&lt;br&gt;gold coins are weighed in troy ounces (31.1g) you dumb nigger&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864490&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864463&lt;br&gt;Imagine thinking I&amp;#x27;m stupid enough to tell anyone.&lt;br&gt;Kind of like you&amp;#x27;re projecting your own stupidity because that&amp;#x27;s something you would definitely do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864496&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864490&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Imagine being naive enough to believe that you&amp;#x27;re going to be able to hide a stack of gold and silver from your wife.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864497&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863917&lt;br&gt;Always nice when I see a retarded OP neck themselves mid-greentext.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864552&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864496&lt;br&gt;not everyone is a low-test cuck who bends over backwards for their wife and tells her literally everything.&lt;br&gt;You have the mind of a complete loser&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864585&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864455&lt;br&gt;Nobody is cleverly dissuading anybody you stupid retard, if you conceal assets from the tax office they will get a warrant and put you in prison until you talk and you&amp;#x27;ll make number plates for $1 an hour for 10 years. You haven&amp;#x27;t escaped the system you stupid spastic, you&amp;#x27;ve made yourself a target and now all they need is a warrant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864587&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864585&lt;br&gt;And your dumb ass is here explaining that you&amp;#x27;ve hidden sizable assets. Genius.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864598&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863927&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;its a great investment&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;you just need to buy 100lbs of metal 5% over spot and wait for it to ship your house then build a $100k vault and employ armed security to defend it 24/7 and be constantly alert for burglers and when you go to sell it you have to sell it under spot to a dealer and use the same armed security to transport it&lt;br&gt;Meanwhile, cryptochads&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;12 words in my brain&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;copy paste address to trade&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864611&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864552&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why are rock bros the dumbest niggers on /biz/?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Enjoy the people&amp;#x27;s rocks, bro.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864617&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864585&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864587&lt;br&gt;ahaha the jews are triggered so much I absolutely love it.&lt;br&gt;Practically malding over text just because people refuse to stop stacking&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;NOOOOO! AAAAAARGGGHHH! YOU HAVEN&amp;#x27;T ESCAPED THE LAST OF ME, HUMAN!&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;MY JEWY RAT BRAIN WILL SURELY CONQUER YOU AND IMPRISON OR IMPOVERISH YOU FOR LIFE! mweh heh hehh&lt;br&gt;Like clock work lol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864620&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864611&lt;br&gt;They want to larp as based trad larp investors that do as ancient civilization as done, and the irony is grand as the post this on the internet of all places and show how much they love anime and their waifu. Rockfags are just coping with being low status males, and their rocks make them feel special and above it all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864627&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864620&lt;br&gt;I literally don&amp;#x27;t consider myself special. Literally anyone can stack rocks.&lt;br&gt;I just think it&amp;#x27;s hilarious how much it upsets you jews that I&amp;#x27;m not being manipulated into throwing my wealth into the dumpster as you wish I would&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864664&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864627&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Literally literally&lt;br&gt;S.oylenial gamma male detected&lt;br&gt;We all know why you collect rocks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864682&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864451&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hehehe. You got it boss! Got your bullion right here!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;OH SHIT MY BULLION WQS FAKE FUCKKKKKK SRY UNCLE SAM&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864688&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864455&lt;br&gt;This.&lt;br&gt;One of the first times I was buying some silver bullion coins from a store. There we&amp;#x27;re these 2 goblin looking jewish women, I slid over the moeny and before sliding me the coins she started telling me something along the lines of &amp;#x27;&amp;#x27;Make sure to not open up these coins and don&amp;#x27;t touch them and don&amp;#x27;t even breath on them . . . blah blah blah . .. as it can affect the resale value . .. blah blah blah&amp;#x27;&amp;#x27;.I never planned on selling and it made me immediately want to buy more. She hadn&amp;#x27;t even handed the coins over and was already dreaming of getting them back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864689&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Random, worthless corner of the internet discussing stacking physical PMs. All of a sudden, multiple users swarm the thread and are consistently active with sub30 minute replies at odd hours ready to shit on stackers immediately. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Okie dokie. I understand why so many elements of Freemasonry, and secret societies strongly emphasize the lack of even appearing to be banded together behind the scenes. I totally understand why because anyone with a triple digit IQ will recognize when 20 to 30 people who don’t know each other all start, saying the same thing and attacking the same shit. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Once they outsourced all of this talking points to third world to cover online forums, the consistent attacks are essentially assigned that you are over the target.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864694&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864682&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I would hate to be sitting in jail and have all of my wealth just out there, practically unsecured.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864723&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864694&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Notice how this guy avoids all solid discussion, is consistently active, and only replies in quips and trolls.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;His secondary, will play the “reasonable” dissenter. Just pin this thread and watch, anons.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864726&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864723&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What solid discussion would you like to have?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864758&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863917&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;gets hacked&lt;br&gt;AAAAACCCCCK&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864804&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864627&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I literally don&amp;#x27;t consider myself special&lt;br&gt;So then you literally know that literally most governments literally seize money when they want it bad enough and they have literally dealt with countless people who literally thought just because that money was literally in rock form the laws literally don&amp;#x27;t apply to them&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866917&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864804&lt;br&gt;Including your fiat, stocks, and crypto, except yours are way easier for them to confiscate.&lt;br&gt;Your point? OOH you don&amp;#x27;t have one. &lt;br&gt;Oh you&amp;#x27;re retarded? Poor thing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867080&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864723&lt;br&gt;Then why engage? It&amp;#x27;s harder to ignore retards in real life but I still manage, but online there&amp;#x27;s no reason to even pretend. Everyone that gets ventilated by bad advice just makes your assets that much more valuable. Pretend like everyone average and below will face starvation, prostitution, conscription and death; the truth isn&amp;#x27;t far from this. You wouldn&amp;#x27;t spend all day arguing with corpses so why would you spend time on someone that doesn&amp;#x27;t know they are dead yet?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867144&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866917&lt;br&gt;This is really the bull case cry for stacking firearms and putting aside enough to buy sell swords. The government will do anything they think they can get away with which I why I don&amp;#x27;t think even bail ins are certain, you can do those overnight without kicking a single door but there will still be hell to pay in the morning. While stackers are a smaller population most holdings require, or rather will at such time require, going door to door to seize assets in a country in which one can put together an AR for $350-$400 and drop in FRTs can be had for as little as $100. All this against the population and asset class pairing most likely to own firearms. The logistics don&amp;#x27;t make sense. You&amp;#x27;ll see heavy taxes, threats of taxes, capital controls and possibly if briefly bans on sales after a set date. None of this yields as much gold or silver as paying an above market rate. Question is, is there anything worth trading for. If I got a deed to a substantial amount of the land the federal government loves to horde so much I could see myself parting with all (some) of my specie. Nobody can be all stick and no carrot and win. This is why in bank bail ins you atleast get shares in a bank that has recently defaulted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867175&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867144&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;re lucky you&amp;#x27;re but a minnow. For large investors, all of the guns in the world didn&amp;#x27;t stop Uncle Sam knocking on their door for the known vaults of metals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>&gt;mom yells at me for not having a job 5 months after I got laid off from my last one &gt;Complains how we need more money t… — 41 replies — 155.9/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61863594</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61863594?lm=1771360524</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 20:35:24 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;&amp;gt;mom yells at me for not having a job 5 months after I got laid off from my last one &amp;gt;Complains how we need more money t…&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61863594'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 41 • Updated: 2026-02-17 20:35 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;mom yells at me for not having a job 5 months after I got laid off from my last one&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Complains how we need more money to pay the bills and how she can&amp;#x27;t keep working 10 hour shifts to pay our bills&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Look through her purse when she&amp;#x27;s not looking &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;See a $600 receipt for perfume and makeup, and a bank note evidencing a $1800 transfer to her neet sister who also has 2 neet sons and a neet daughter. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Dad gambled away another $10K in stocks. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;He keeps sending me job openings in other states/cities that require 10+ years of experience and he tells me &amp;quot;just walk up to them and ask them to train you, that&amp;#x27;s how we did it back in the old days&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;My own savings are slowly dwindling and I&amp;#x27;ve got no more than a few months left before I&amp;#x27;m officially broke &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;800+ job apps and nothing yet&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m not sure how much more of this I can take bros...&lt;br&gt;Why won&amp;#x27;t the economy get better? &lt;br&gt;Who do I blame for this miserable situation?&lt;br&gt;What are some easy painless ways to check out of this economy earlier don&amp;#x27;t speak?&lt;br&gt;Why are old people all so stupid and contemptible?&lt;br&gt;NGMI?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863604&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863594&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Who do I blame for this miserable situation?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863605&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;See a $600 receipt for perfume and makeup&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;a bank note evidencing a $1800 transfer to&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Dad gambled away another $10K in stocks&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Complains how we need more money to pay the bills &lt;br&gt;what came first?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863607&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863594&lt;br&gt;Meant to say, So to speak, not don&amp;#x27;t speak &lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s been almost a few decades of smartphone development and auto correct still doesn&amp;#x27;t work properly yet AI fags are still like &amp;quot;we&amp;#x27;re totally gonna get agi and self driving cars this year bro!!!&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863786&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863594&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Join ICE.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863791&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863651&lt;br&gt;Most active duty army tried to join a different branch first (bar combat arms), but couldn&amp;#x27;t due to various reasons. Be real this is /biz/.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863810&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Do you live with your parents? That sounds like a lot of the problem&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863822&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863810&lt;br&gt;COL being what it is means even living with asshole parents is better in every circumstance other than them literally being physically abusive or outright robbing you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863846&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;mom seething that she might have to come out of early retirement because her 401k is only up 5% since the start of the year and she spends too much on vacations&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;complains &amp;quot;it&amp;#x27;s not fair, I should get to have a life&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;mfw she used to say this all the time whne I was in highschool when she grounded me -for existing- so she could go out with her friends on fridays, preventing me from ever having a life&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;realize she&amp;#x27;s a narcissist and deserves to suffer and am glad ot be an albatross around her neck&lt;br&gt;Shouldn&amp;#x27;t have stolen 20,000 dollars from me when I was 23, bitch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863852&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863651&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863648&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863782&lt;br&gt;Army is good because it runs weeaboo psyops.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863786&lt;br&gt;I applied for ICE in 2024 before Trump got elected, they&amp;#x27;re hiring beaners instead. Turns out no one will just &amp;#x27;let&amp;#x27; you be useful to society while making 150k a year working 80 hours a week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863856&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863822&lt;br&gt;He&amp;#x27;s just gonna tell you you&amp;#x27;re a loser and to get an apartment with a crackhead roommate or something. Your parents are the problem for not hooking you up with a year of rent and a job if they don&amp;#x27;t want you around. American parents deserve everything coming to them for stealing from their own kids. Who the fuck thinks they can just peace out and retire when society is collapsing lmao. Anyone who says &amp;quot;not my problem, I&amp;#x27;ll be dead by the time it gets REAL bad&amp;quot; is a person I conside rit my duty to cause as much suffering as posible for.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863912&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sounds like your whole family is dead weight except your mom. The perfume and makeup is probably a desperate move to hopefully find a man.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863922&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863856&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Anyone who says &amp;quot;not my problem, I&amp;#x27;ll be dead by the time it gets REAL bad&amp;quot; is a person I conside rit my duty to cause as much suffering as posible for.&lt;br&gt;They&amp;#x27;ll all be abused by Indians in the retirement home while their actual children are estranged. Poetic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864141&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863594&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863622&lt;br&gt;How old are you, OP? Sounds like your family is financially abusive to you. Can you move out on your own (as soon as you find a job, I mean) and cut contact?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864148&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863822&lt;br&gt;It really isn&amp;#x27;t. You can live VERY cheaply in a lot of Asian countries (Thailand, Laos, Indonesia) and do ridiculously low-paying remote work and still come out with net savings every month.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I worked in Taiwan (DON&amp;#x27;T GO THERE) for a while and was able to save over 50% of my pay even though I made half as much as an American would make doing the same job (not ESLosering).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wish I hadn&amp;#x27;t because it completely destroyed my health permanently (they&amp;#x27;re just as bad, maybe worse, about dumping toxic industrial chemicals in food as the mainland chinsects), but it was the only thing available to me after the 2008-12 crash during the Obamaconomy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864222&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863594&lt;br&gt;corner your dad and mom about that 600+1.8k+10k$. That&amp;#x27;ll make them shut for another 1 month.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864358&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863594&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;neet sister who also has 2 neet sons and a neet daughter.&lt;br&gt;nigga how old are you? &lt;br&gt;or are you calling infants neets kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864379&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863594&lt;br&gt;What the fuck does your retarded family have to do with the economy?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864420&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864358&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;her neet sister&lt;br&gt;His aunt is the neet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864425&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863648&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863651&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863643&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;just go get killed for ZOG!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The only military worth joining is the russian one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864429&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864222&lt;br&gt;These are classic case narcissists or sociopaths. They’ll become affronted, say something along the lines of ‘none of your business’ and if they are reticent then it would most certainly be for lip service.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864434&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864425&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;just go get killed for ZOG (east)!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864449&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863643&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863648&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863651&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863852&lt;br&gt;Wow the sõyjack party leaks were true this place is infested with glowies&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864425&lt;br&gt;come on dude&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864740&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864358&lt;br&gt;My neet aunts children are in there fucking 40s and never worked jobs yet live like kings. One of them is 400 pounds and my mom complains about how she needs to keep buying him bigger and bigger gift shirts every year...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864743&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;beat your mother&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864751&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864141&lt;br&gt;I can&amp;#x27;t unfortunately.&lt;br&gt;I tried really hard but it didn&amp;#x27;t work out&lt;br&gt;Got my mom&amp;#x27;s adhd+schizophrenic OCD and my dad&amp;#x27;s autism adhd. I can barely function and the few years I worked a job I was tempted to drive my car into oncoming traffic every single day to and back from work &lt;br&gt;Col is just too high plus I can&amp;#x27;t get a good paying job&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864222&lt;br&gt;Have you read a certain painters description of a certain group of people being like jelly when you argue with them? It&amp;#x27;s impossible to discuss anything with these animals I have for parents. They forget everything the next day and gaslight you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864763&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864743&lt;br&gt;My dad already does and she fucking loves it.&lt;br&gt;Meanwhile I slightly raise my voice to make sure she can hear me and she goes berserk calling me an asshole who&amp;#x27;ll never get women cuz I have no job meanwhile my dad gambled 200k on stock margins in the 90s and lost his job for a decade and she still dutifully stuck with him. It&amp;#x27;s comical how everyday my dad cusses her out and yells at her calling her a dumb bitch at the top of his lungs and she&amp;#x27;ll dutifully have dinner ready for him in an hour while washing all his clothes for him yet she&amp;#x27;ll scold me for not cooking my own food even though I never asked her to cook for me&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864768&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863594&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;He keeps sending me job openings in other states/cities that require 10+ years of experience and he tells me &amp;quot;just walk up to them and ask them to train you, that&amp;#x27;s how we did it back in the old days&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;my dad used to do this&lt;br&gt;holy shit it pissed the fuck out of me&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864788&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864763&lt;br&gt;She loves getting beat?&lt;br&gt;Huh&lt;br&gt;Wonder if she’d love getting her pussy beat into smithereens. Tell your dad to try that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864795&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863604&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863594&lt;br&gt;Ironically the same people who make these demoralisation threads&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864888&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863856&lt;br&gt;Average zoomer blaming everyone but themselves&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865867&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864888&lt;br&gt;explain how he&amp;#x27;s wrong&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865875&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863594&lt;br&gt;She&amp;#x27;s not wrong that you need to contribute just because she&amp;#x27;s also bad with money.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867123&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864751&lt;br&gt;so how does this work, do you pay them a fix amount as your part of rent and costs or do they just siphon off as much as possible or procentual off your incone? you said you have savings so it&amp;#x27;s probably not completely fucked. not sure how much you need a month for them to get off your back. what industry? you drive a car to work so not remote despite crippling autism?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>This shit got me finna kms ONG!!! — 18 replies — 58.4/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61866292</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61866292?lm=1771360361</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 20:32:41 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;This shit got me finna kms ONG!!!&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61866292'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 18 • Updated: 2026-02-17 20:32 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;This shit got me finna kms ONG!!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866346&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866292&lt;br&gt;omg dude imagine sitting by a lake. or you could take a nap on some flowers... whoa that would be so much better than working for shekelberg!!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866589&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866292&lt;br&gt;bros i might have to start waging soon..it..it cant be that bad...r...righ..ACK&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866689&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Let the goyim deal in the real world&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866699&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866689&lt;br&gt;hahaha the files have been so fucking eye opening. everything we said about jews right there&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866707&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866292&lt;br&gt;born to live like an animal! eating and fucking and basking in neurotransmitters!&lt;br&gt;forced to do human bullshit! high-level concerns no animal can even begin to comprehend!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866711&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866292&lt;br&gt;BUMP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866715&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;all you lazy fucking gen alphoids and zoomers don&amp;#x27;t seem to realize that you weren&amp;#x27;t born to lay around fingering your gay assholes.&lt;br&gt;You were born to work even harder just to survive than you need to nowadays, including daily running and chasing down animals for miles with spears, with your tribe to eat, or if you are lucky, fishing and back breaking farming, but thosecame with risks of your shit being plundered or you going hungry if unsuccessful.&lt;br&gt;EVERY DAY was life or death struggles, entitled morons.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866726&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866715&lt;br&gt;We don&amp;#x27;t live in the jungle any more, you boomer rat&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866740&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866715&lt;br&gt;not to mention once you were 30+ years old, you were as good as dead.&lt;br&gt;if a disease didn&amp;#x27;t get you, a competing younger tribe would murder you, or even your own tribe would because your strength, speed, and usefulness ran out, BYTCH&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866752&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866726&lt;br&gt;doesn&amp;#x27;t change the fact that you and OP were born to suffer, struggle and die even more horribly than you are now.&lt;br&gt;No one owes you anything.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866756&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866740&lt;br&gt;I agree everyone over 30 should die horribly&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866770&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866756&lt;br&gt;so do something about it, pussy.&lt;br&gt;your generation are the biggest groups of fags and pussies.&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m 39, and I&amp;#x27;m waaaitiiin&amp;#x27;&lt;br&gt;come on.&lt;br&gt;Do something, BYTCH&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866997&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866292&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t get what I am looking at or missing? Sleeping on flowers and look at the sky?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867010&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866715&lt;br&gt;that actually sounds like living a life, sitting behind a computer for 8 hours in the office isn&amp;#x27;t.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867039&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867010&lt;br&gt;your pampered ass would get tired of running around all day every day REAL fast&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867083&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867039&lt;br&gt;Kill yourself&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867109&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867083&lt;br&gt;You wish I was as miserable as your NEET tranny ass.&lt;br&gt;I actually have a good job, and love that I&amp;#x27;m living in modern times where it&amp;#x27;s never been easier and comfier (except the 90s were better but what can you do?)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>$TSLA @$405 — 11 replies — 38.3/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61866167</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61866167?lm=1771360437</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 20:33:57 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;$TSLA @$405&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61866167'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 11 • Updated: 2026-02-17 20:33 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;What is the fair value for this stock?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866173&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866167&lt;br&gt;$405&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866174&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;$3.50&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866182&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866173&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866174&lt;br&gt;ok, ty. Imma take the average of the two. Wisdom of the crowd&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866274&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866167&lt;br&gt;$60 and that is being generous&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866639&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866167&lt;br&gt;$405&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866174&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866182&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866274&lt;br&gt;wrong&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866757&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866639&lt;br&gt;ok, Imma short it then, because it is overvalued according to you&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866944&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866167&lt;br&gt;uhhhh i&amp;#x27;ll give you a two week old mcdouble for it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867024&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866167&lt;br&gt;1000+ unironically. its not a car company. growth stock. no one cares about p/e ratios, that shit is outdated. elon musk represents the best of us.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867064&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866167&lt;br&gt;20 or 25 pe ratio considering potential chinese competition so 1/15 of the actual price. $25 to $30&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867096&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;0$ until the US kikes get off their ass and cover their debt crisis and give liquidity, and then $5000 per share&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867117&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;0.42$ and that&amp;#x27;s a high estimate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Is it really that much more difficult to start a business in the eu than us? — 27 replies — 35.5/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860796</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860796?lm=1771358733</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 20:05:33 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Is it really that much more difficult to start a business in the eu than us?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860796'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 27 • Updated: 2026-02-17 20:05 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;You guys in the EU make less than us on paychecks, but you get to keep more of your money because you have universal healthcare and PTO while we have to pay for private insurance which chronically denies people&amp;#x27;s health situations. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Are people saying that starting a business in the EU is difficult because of the regulations? What regulations does the European union impose on its citizen&amp;#x27;s than they think it&amp;#x27;s easier to start in the United States instead?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860815&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;Depends enormously on which country are we talking about. Some are easy (Germany) some are very hard (Italy)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860817&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; you get to keep more of your money because you have universal healthcare&lt;br&gt;yeah right&lt;br&gt;good luck getting that &amp;quot;universal healthcare&amp;quot; if you&amp;#x27;re not a boomer, waiting lists are years for even a basic exam/procedure. It&amp;#x27;s either you go private (and pay out of your own pocket) or you die&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; and PTO&lt;br&gt;oh wow, 20 wagie cagie free days a year. Totally worth the 60%+ taxes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;All taxation is theft. It&amp;#x27;s just that. Taxation doesn&amp;#x27;t pay for services. It&amp;#x27;s just the way they control the economy, and here in EU they fucking LOVE to control what you can and cannot do. They print the money, they don&amp;#x27;t need to tax you. They tax you to control you (and to humiliate you)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860822&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;The healthcare thing is too much american leftie argument, it also has been very overcrowded by you guessed arabs and africans, unironically I was better treated when I broke my leg in brazil of all places then in france&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860823&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860815&lt;br&gt;How about the Czech Republic?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860836&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860817&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;waiting lists are years for even a basic exam/procedure&lt;br&gt;we have them too except they&amp;#x27;re called &amp;quot;pre authorization&amp;quot; and we still get to pay for it all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860837&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;What regulations does the European union impose on its citizen&amp;#x27;s than they think it&amp;#x27;s easier to start in the United States instead?&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;re shitting me right? As the other guy said it really varies based on the country, but in places like Italy you need 20 authorizations and 10 certifications (that you pay for) to open something like a bar or a carpentry shop, plus constant &amp;quot;controls&amp;quot; which are basically bribe requests at this point by officials of all kinds. Oh, and good luck filing your taxes. Here&amp;#x27;s how it goes&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; be business owner&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; tax filing time (yay)&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; tax system is so incredibly fucking complex you have to hire people just to calculate how much you own&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; because of course YOU need to tell the state how much the state wants from YOU&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; slightest fuck up? You&amp;#x27;re on the hook for 240% of the original amount&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; they have 5-7 years to come after you&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; &amp;quot;oh hello here&amp;#x27;s a tax bill from 5 years ago cause you filed 3.51 euros less than you were supposed to, plus 1500 eur sanction, plus interest&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; oh btw you pay FIRST, and MAYBE when (after an average of 12 years in court at your expense) you are declared right, you get it back, no interest accrued, your legal expenses still on your back&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; so most people just pay&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; it&amp;#x27;s mafia with a hand of paint on top and the full force of the state behind it&lt;br&gt;EU is completely fucked. Stay away. We can just pray it somehow implodes from within. These bureaucrat jew lover good goyim will kill us all and replace us with shitskin and pajeets and they will feast on top of it all while the continent dies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860842&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860837&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;tax system is so incredibly fucking complex you have to hire people just to calculate how much you own&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; because of course YOU need to tell the state how much the state wants from YOU&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; slightest fuck up? You&amp;#x27;re on the hook for 240% of the original amount&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; they have 5-7 years to come after you&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; &amp;quot;oh hello here&amp;#x27;s a tax bill from 5 years ago cause you filed 3.51 euros less than you were supposed to, plus 1500 eur sanction, plus interest&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; oh btw you pay FIRST, and MAYBE when (after an average of 12 years in court at your expense) you are declared right, you get it back, no interest accrued, your legal expenses still on your back&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; so most people just pay&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; it&amp;#x27;s mafia with a hand of paint on top and the full force of the state behind it&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;EU is completely fucked. Stay away.&lt;br&gt;again this is more or less the same as the US&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860847&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860823&lt;br&gt;A bureaucracy nightmare.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860850&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860842&lt;br&gt;everywhere is completely fucked, but you burgers have weapons and a strong constitution that backs you&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;yeah you&amp;#x27;re retarded pussies and you will never ever use them, we all know. I mean they&amp;#x27;re telling you know that you&amp;#x27;re ruled upon by a bunch of satanist jew pedophiles and there&amp;#x27;s no shooting in the streets, so there you have it. But at least you have the guns. If the Cheka comes knocking at your door demanding your harvest and your daughters, you can shoot back at the fuckers. Here in EU we&amp;#x27;re basically at the mercy of a state that hates us and wants us dead, and we have only our dicks to hold in our hands to defend ourselves from it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860860&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;As far as I keep reading on economic subreddits, negligible, the US just has far more available credit and tax companies a bit less at start allowing them to grow, otherwise its basically the same, sounds legit just a complacency issue from europeans, most of the time they get more unemployment benefits than they would working and have legit no time limit for them so they just don&amp;#x27;t bother lol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860967&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;in my country, the one thing one has to look out for is paying for your own social/healthinsurance, ie, if you have your own business, you need to pay taxes for your own health/socialinsurance, and the taxman wont ask you for the first 3y of that business.&lt;br&gt;After the 3y pass, you will then have to payup all the retrospective social insurance tax costs incurred, which fucks over a lot of retard or unfortunate first business owners&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861032&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860837&lt;br&gt;This is why we need a unified EU business regulation and undermind the corrupt sovereignist that want to keep individual burocratic fuckery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861057&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860815&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Some are easy (Germany)&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; some are very hard (Italy)&lt;br&gt;let me guess italian never tried germany?&lt;br&gt;Germany is known to be a bureucracy hellhole with people fleeing to other countries from it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861032&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;unified will fix it&lt;br&gt;France&amp;amp;germany have been dictating eu lawmaking. You will eat shit as you already do. You have eu wide higher taxes because germany didnt want to compete and made mandatory higher minimum vat a thing.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Not to mention that countries that joined got their industries destroyed by unified regulation and had to import from germany/france what they used to produce themself&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861071&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s the one thing the USA gets right. I personally made a &amp;quot;business&amp;quot; (that never made any profit) in the span of an afternoon. Cost maybe $200 to get my identification numbers for the llc&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861091&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861032&lt;br&gt;yeah let&amp;#x27;s give the EU bureaucrats more power that will fix it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861111&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Is it really that much more difficult to start a business in the eu than us?&lt;br&gt;Depends on the business. If you want to do something shady the US is the place to go. The US has barely any standards and barely any regulations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861113&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860817&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;waiting lists are years for even a basic exam/procedure&lt;br&gt;What are you talking about? I live currently in the EU and have never had to wait for medical care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861119&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Us is easier.&lt;br&gt;I have created 2 corpos and 1 llc for different purposes within the past 8 years. You can do it all online for a few bucks, other regulations depend on specific industry but overall it&amp;#x27;s pretty easy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861128&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860860&lt;br&gt;higher taxation alone puts euros at a disadvantage. Its fine if you do a local job since you compete with locals but anything online / shipped its bad since they have to be more efficient than rest of world to reach same profit margin.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As for amount of bureaucracy its fucking complex and depends on what country and what profession. There is even stupid shit like if you run a repair shop and repair inside your building it counts different than if you decide to drive to your customer and repair locally. In the later case they classify you as a handyman worker and will fine you if you didn&amp;#x27;t register with the craftsman ministry. Also if you do something you didn&amp;#x27;t register for you will also be fined but you can register as &amp;quot; i will do anything&amp;quot; more broadly and dodge it. The amount of bullshit can easily fill a book.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861429&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;Depends on what your goals are, the type of business, your personal goals and the markets you wish to enter. In general it&amp;#x27;s more of an investment in the long run but if you plan to offer your services or products in the EU anyway it makes sense to start your business here and already be compliant&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861441&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860817&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;waiting lists are years for even a basic exam/procedure.&lt;br&gt;Yeah, I remember waiting decades for my appendicitis, it rupturing and me dying because of it. Thankfully they could keep me alive for months despite the extreme difficulties this poses. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861032&lt;br&gt;We need more unified European regulation. Sadly the EU is not an economic alliance anymore.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862545&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860860&lt;br&gt;I love how hard it is to even talk about european economy on reddit, not because of europeans, but because of american lefties, if you so much, and most times you don&amp;#x27;t even need to, mention the US, they will flock like a horde to claim the US lies about everything, that 30% of americans are unemployed and nearly no one in europe, the EU is literal worker&amp;#x27;s paradise and how much they love their welfare policies and hate the US greed, its quite hilarious really how much they want a nanny state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865504&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is, soon it will was once EU Inc comes into play&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865623&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;you have universal healthcare&lt;br&gt;yea but you have to wait 1 year+ because there is a million niggers in queue before you&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865645&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861057&lt;br&gt;Lol this is true.&lt;br&gt;Germany and France made the EU suck with their shit like GDPR etc. Spain happily sniffs every turd. The rest aren&amp;#x27;t better.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866460&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If your efforts are starting to go anywhere, your own government will make sure, you won&amp;#x27;t get any further.&lt;br&gt;They hate nothing more than citizens that are not dependent on them. That&amp;#x27;s why they are allowing third world people in to the maximum extent physically possible, that are never going end up being a &amp;quot;plus&amp;quot; on the balance sheet, but that they hope will be cheap voting sheep for their party. The people pay for them after all, not the party.&lt;br&gt;Effectively: If Elon Musk was a citizen of a EU-country, he&amp;#x27;d already be in jail waiting for the sentence to be sent to prison. You probably don&amp;#x27;t want to get into that situation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866966&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865645&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Le GDPR sucks because uhm JUST LET ME HAVE YOUR DATA&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>I made 30k in a Day — 8 replies — 32.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61865072</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61865072?lm=1771361299</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 20:48:19 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;I made 30k in a Day&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61865072'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 8 • Updated: 2026-02-17 20:48 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;it was enough&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;find out about RAM bubble&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;have dozens of servers for homelab&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;make meme eBay listing&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;sell 6TB of RAM for $30k after taxes and fees&lt;br&gt;Same sticks sold for double at the time&lt;br&gt;Same sticks now 70% less per stick&lt;br&gt;I saw the bubble and did a flip off the top into profit&lt;br&gt;Once the payment cleared I quit my jerb&lt;br&gt;Been making more per day not working&lt;br&gt;2026 is van life friendly&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865094&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Should i sell my 4060 rtx?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865134&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865094&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Should i sell my 4060 rtx?&lt;br&gt;NvidiAI is bleeding money on AI and going to restart consumer GPU production soon&lt;br&gt;so, yes&lt;br&gt;I am currently in the process of selling ALL my Nvidia GPU&amp;#x27;s&lt;br&gt;From professional cards to 40 series&lt;br&gt;already bought AMD replacements&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865873&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865072&lt;br&gt;But RAM prices are still at ATH?....&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865929&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865873&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;But RAM prices are still at ATH?....&lt;br&gt;This, i&amp;#x27;m work at a VAR. A customer of mine wanted to add 128GB DDR5 RDIMMs to server, our quote was $10k. Dell&amp;#x27;s retail site lists it for like $13k&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865979&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865072&lt;br&gt;This meme again. These broads are like 40 by now&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866110&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865979&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;emma roberts is 35&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866360&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865979&lt;br&gt;post meme with renewed thots then&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867173&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865072&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What movie is this meme from?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>US is in recession — 7 replies — 28.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61866972</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61866972?lm=1771361425</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 20:50:25 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;US is in recession&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61866972'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 7 • Updated: 2026-02-17 20:50 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;US is in recession&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866978&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866972&lt;br&gt;I graduated collage and got a job. Must be a skill issue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867094&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866972&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Criminal justice less useful than an art degree &lt;br&gt;Wow&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867095&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866972&lt;br&gt;buy an ad&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867099&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;fell for the computer science meme and now I have to work at Goodwill for $13/hr&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867136&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867094&lt;br&gt;Performing arts. That means that what most people think of when they think &amp;quot;arts major&amp;quot; (fine arts, animation, etc.) are better-employed than criminal justice majors. They&amp;#x27;re better employed than med techs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Marinate on that for a minute.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867150&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867099&lt;br&gt;Have you tried walking into google and giving Sundar a firm handshake, kiddo... That&amp;#x27;s what we used to do back in our day... Look him in the eyes and let him know you&amp;#x27;ll do whatever in takes... Extra hours, sleeping at the office... Kids these days just don&amp;#x27;t have the grit we used to have... That&amp;#x27;s why we sent men to the moon, 6 times at that, yes sir...&lt;br&gt;You gotta pay your dues, and you gotta be in it to win it...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sent from my iPhone&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867192&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867094&lt;br&gt;A lot of people who do Criminal Justice degrees are people who watched CSI etc and want to solve murders or do forensics rather than law or general policing or whatever. The actual amount of jobs available for that field is extremely small&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>NIGGER LIFE — 12 replies — 18.3/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61863888</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61863888?lm=1771359107</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 20:11:47 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;NIGGER LIFE&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61863888'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 12 • Updated: 2026-02-17 20:11 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;PUMP... AND DUMP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863890&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;it&amp;#x27;s over for buttcoin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863896&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863888&lt;br&gt;SUPER NIGGER GALAXY&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863903&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Looks fine to me&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864134&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863888&lt;br&gt;NIGGER CZ!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864323&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NIGGER NIGGER&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865150&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IT&amp;#x27;S JUST ONE THOSE DAYS WHEN YOU DON&amp;#x27;T WANNA WAKE UP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865752&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A most blessed thread on /biz/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Good morrow fine and friendly gentlemen of non-reflective skin tones!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866571&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;NIGGER JOCKEY!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866593&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;crypto is for niggers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866664&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863888&lt;br&gt;checked melanin individuals!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866990&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;its all one big nigger epoch innit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>it's crazy to me that there's a TG full of deranged porn addicted "people" who spend every waking moment trying to dissu… — 3 replies — 12.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61867085</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61867085?lm=1771361336</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 20:48:56 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;it&amp;#x27;s crazy to me that there&amp;#x27;s a TG full of deranged porn addicted &amp;quot;people&amp;quot; who spend every waking moment trying to dissu…&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61867085'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 3 • Updated: 2026-02-17 20:48 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;it&amp;#x27;s crazy to me that there&amp;#x27;s a TG full of deranged porn addicted &amp;quot;people&amp;quot; who spend every waking moment trying to dissuade people from buying and holding specific assets to the point where even legitimate discussions about the asset is swarmed with comments aimed at derailing it. all because another group of ((people)) can&amp;#x27;t stand the idea that people they never wanted to make it got in on the ground floor. really activates the old almonds doesn&amp;#x27;t it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867125&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Based. Got 12,000 of those shitty little tokens so far and I&amp;#x27;m buying $5000 worth every week for the next six weeks. Suck it, juden&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867153&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867085&lt;br&gt;This is false. We are not deranged.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867180&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867085&lt;br&gt;take your meds schizo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;No additional replies in the latest window.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Privacy Coins — 90 replies — 201.6/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61849447</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61849447?lm=1771359864</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 20:24:24 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Privacy Coins&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61849447'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 90 • Updated: 2026-02-17 20:24 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whether you like it or not, BTC is dying. Which way anons?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849481&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gold and silver.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849898&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849447&lt;br&gt;XMR as always. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849481&lt;br&gt;Acceptable but unusable for internet transactions and too easily stolen. Also makes smaller or spontaneous transactions harder unless the governments were to issue gold coins again and that would be bearish.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849958&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849447&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;BTC is a pedo coin&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;most used currency for CP is not however&lt;br&gt;quit the infighting, monegro.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864948&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864897&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I don&amp;#x27;t care if it stays as long as you stop smearing XMR and spamming our threads&lt;br&gt;The only spammer is you, in both this thread and the xmr general. You came here to start shit and have done so in every privacy thread that has popped up. You also accuse everyone of being a poojeet and promoting nerva. Again, the only person promoting (xmr in your case) and causing a stink has been YOU. So fuck off back to your little monero hole, jeetbot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865014&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864948&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The only spammer is you,&lt;br&gt;I wish that were true but sadly the nervajeets constantly try to shit up our thread and this board. There&amp;#x27;s a reason all of these anti-Monero threads pop up when they lose the discussion in the general. Notice how quiet they&amp;#x27;ve become after &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860646 was posted. All of their anti-Monero arguments (which was the entire value proposition for nerva) are gone. Their questions they claim never were answered poofed up into air. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;You came here to start shit&lt;br&gt;OP literally accuses XMR of being some freemason bullshit. You&amp;#x27;re the perfect representation of the jew asking what harm he has done to us. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;You also accuse everyone of being a poojeet and promoting nerva.&lt;br&gt;No, I say that the ones that copy all of the points the nervajeets make to be a nervajeets. That&amp;#x27;s because the only people interested in nerva are jeets.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Please don&amp;#x27;t challenge me when I smear the only functional crypto currency please just go away I can&amp;#x27;t handle it please please please&lt;br&gt;No sar, you wish to talk about XMR? I&amp;#x27;ll be there and refute each on of your pathetic claims.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865124&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864651&lt;br&gt;Holy shit, XMR to a fucking T anon...&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865014&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;bot programmed to hate random shitcoin&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;even if not true, makes it look like hes funded by masons/jews because he literally cannot stop promoting monero&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;becomes a meme in and of himself here&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864651&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;he seriously cant stop&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;he will bring nerva up in random threads every chance he gets even when no one is talking about it&lt;br&gt;Just fucking stop and go away monegro. Maybe they didnt stop after that was posted, because they were never spamming up your threads in the first place you pathetic fucking loser. Only you were, they were just asking questions, something anyone can do. I scoured your xmr generals, and your clearly the psychopath across every fucking one. Non stop blogposts of text that do nothing but go in circles, and now youre doing it here. Save yourself some time and go shit up someone elses thread. Oh right, you cant, because youre a monegro botnet that works for monero glowies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I started this thread to discuss privacy coins and all youve done is shit up my thread you piece of shit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865161&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865014&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;bot&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865268&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862698&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862796&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864651&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864866&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865161&lt;br&gt;good morning nervasaaars&lt;br&gt;truly xnv is the most aryan bharatoken superior peer-to-poop privacy coin xnvsaars redeem asap&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865595&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865268&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;i cant stop sucking monero dick, am i gay enough yet? Somebody like me pleeease!!&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;Back to your xmr general faggot shill&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865847&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865268&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;nooo not my heckin fedcoin noo all other privacy coins are jeetcoins noooo&lt;br&gt;CryptoNight-Adaptive &amp;gt; RandomX for decentralization&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865956&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865869&lt;br&gt;Have you tried bumping your generel thread so it stays up like everyone else does&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865998&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865956&lt;br&gt;Wasnt my general. I got the screenshot someone snapped of it off the discord. No way a thread gets bumped off this board that fast. There is shit on here for days that no one replies to. Mods are afraid of it. Idk why. Glowies or bagholders probably.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866158&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865869&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;This thread has been pruned or deleted &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865998&lt;br&gt;How do you know that it wasn&amp;#x27;t deleted by the OP?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866337&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865998&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;discord&lt;br&gt;very true sar discord is perfect for our poo privacy coin, better stay there, 4chan is an anti-indian glowie honeypot benchod site&lt;br&gt;btw ser remember to send your designated face scan/ID to discord for better compliance nervasaars&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866373&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866158&lt;br&gt;Well for one, that thread was only posted a few hours ago. Threads dont die that quick. The other reason is because his thread is back&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865946 and hes asking why his shit got deleted. Oh and 4chan is now blocking me. Yet the mods and XMR fags are the ones who started all this. Ask about nerva, get banned. Buy the JDIF coin goy. Maximumkekles&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;btw since my block, they deleted his thread again. So yea, jannies are deleting anything nerva related.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866384&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866337&lt;br&gt;See pic related here&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864948&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;(thats you faggot.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866402&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849447&lt;br&gt;BTC died when it forked away from BCH (the Bitcoin) and broke from the design being an unbroken chain of hashes of digital signatures. That chain doesn&amp;#x27;t exist at all on BTC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866407&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866384&lt;br&gt;why so mad saar&lt;br&gt;the nerva discord isn&amp;#x27;t paying (you) enough to raid 4chan?&lt;br&gt;do not redeem the mod ban saar stop evading bans saar&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866583&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866407&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;the nerva discord isn&amp;#x27;t paying (you) enough to raid 4chan?&lt;br&gt;do not redeem the mod ban saar stop evading bans saar&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;stop evading bans&lt;br&gt;Their discord isnt paying me shit, i started stealing memes from there because its obvious youre all fucking jeet jannies that doesnt want anyone posting about Nerva at all. Stop evading bans? Why are you banning them or me in the first place? You dont ban xmr, zcash, ltc, btc, xrp, or any of that other shit. Yet here you are, admitting to being the jannie whose banning them. Youre pathetic. Pretending that their threads just &amp;quot;fell off the board,&amp;quot; and even having the gall to pretend to ask about it. I knew the mods had a hand in the fucking XMR general, and that anon that said you followed him to /pol/ wasnt lying. Fuck you you pieces of shit. Screencap this and start posting it in other /biz/ threads. This place is corrupt as is XMR.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866671&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849447&lt;br&gt;they all go to zero if btc dies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866688&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;bitch about Nerva shills on XMR threads&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;ban/delete whenever they make a Nerva general&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;leave countless shit threads untouched&lt;br&gt;This is exactly why Nerva exists.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If your “decentralized privacy coin community” is so threatened by the existence of a CPU-only alternative that mods have to memoryhole any discussion, that’s not confidence, that’s insecurity and gatekeeping. You can’t preach censorship resistance while censoring competition like a reddit janny.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Monero is the king today, nobody denies that. But watching a Monero mod rageban any Nerva thread while allowing endless garbage posts just proves the point. A privacy movement that can’t tolerate parallel projects is already compromised.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cope harder. Nerva isn’t going away.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866695&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866583&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866688&lt;br&gt;ChatGPT moment&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866712&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866695&lt;br&gt;Cope. Also trips and dubs of truth. &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866688&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866728&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866712&lt;br&gt;Getting rugged by Zcash jews is one thing but imagine getting rugged by Nerva jeets I would kms lmao&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866805&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865124&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;go away monegro.&lt;br&gt;Stop talking about my coin and stop coming to my general and I will tolerate your kind&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;because they were never spamming up your threads in the first place you pathetic fucking loser.&lt;br&gt;We had this argument already. Over 40 pro-nerva posts in just the current XMR general. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;they were just asking questions&lt;br&gt;All of their questions were already answered, I asked them multiple times to ask any unanswered questions and it&amp;#x27;s been a few days since then. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;something anyone can do.&lt;br&gt;How come they never can answer my questions then? &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;your clearly the psychopath across every fucking one.&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;d rather be a psycho than a jeetcoin shill&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Non stop blogposts of text that do nothing but go in circles, and now youre doing it here. Save yourself some time and go shit up someone elses thread. Oh right, you cant, because youre a monegro botnet that works for monero glowies.&lt;br&gt;Or maybe stop smearing Monero and actually try to have some arguments? &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I started this thread to discuss privacy coins&lt;br&gt;Yeah, I always also start a discussion by posting schizo BS criticizing the only proven tool. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;all youve done is shit up my thread you piece of shit.&lt;br&gt;And you don&amp;#x27;t like it? Looks like I&amp;#x27;m justified in my behavior towards the jeets. Of course I am. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865161&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;picrel&lt;br&gt;See &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61809820 and &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860646 Your questions already have been answered. Please let me know if you have any other questions. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865595&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;re literally sucking off nerva and the current govt. The best part is that all of your arguments regarding epstein and monero are easily extrapolated towards nerva too. It wouldn&amp;#x27;t be too hard to invite your devs to the island considering 40% of them publicly dox themselves and the other ones use discord which always required PII to sign up. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865847&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;CryptoNight-Adaptive &amp;gt; RandomX for decentralization&lt;br&gt;How do you prevent CPUs being clustered locally? Furthermore, how do you plan to detect a 51% attack?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866813&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865869&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Nerva generals get took down immediately.&lt;br&gt;Your jeetcoin is just Monero but no dev work since 2018. It hasn&amp;#x27;t even been maintained. Literally all you do is shill your bags and all of this started because you got relisted by jews. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Your jewish glowcoin is gonna hit zero,&lt;br&gt;Oh I&amp;#x27;m sure all of the DNMs will switch from Monero to your unmaintained mess. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;All you do is advertise monero on here, yet you never get banned.&lt;br&gt;No, all I do is defend Monero against your retarded attacks. That&amp;#x27;s why I&amp;#x27;m always bringing up your fake arguments and refute them. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865998&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;No way a thread gets bumped off this board that fast.&lt;br&gt;Happened a few times with jeetcoin generals now. There&amp;#x27;s simply no interest in your little project. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Mods are afraid of it.&lt;br&gt;What&amp;#x27;s the dangerous part? The low ring size? The lack of development? The lack of any other feature? The ease with which one can 51% it? &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866373&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Yet the mods and XMR fags are the ones who started all this.&lt;br&gt;Just stay out of our general and don&amp;#x27;t smear us and your jeetcoin will be tolerated among the other scams that get posted on this board. Yes, you too can be as beloved as the cheese poster or that guy who posts something that looks like the Yen symbol but with an X. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866384&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;We totally don&amp;#x27;t know about this project&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Anyway I got the screenshot of the general from their discord and weirdly all of my arguments just come from there&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866583&lt;br&gt;Your jeetcoin got relisted. That&amp;#x27;s why some baggie started promoting it in the first place &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Nerva was just relisted (&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61747926)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866821&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866688&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;bitch about Nerva shills on XMR threads&lt;br&gt;Correct, stop pestering us&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;ban/delete whenever they make a Nerva general&lt;br&gt;No need to when they die after two hours anyway lol&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;leave countless shit threads untouched&lt;br&gt;Most shit threads don&amp;#x27;t just push indian coins&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;CPU-only alternative&lt;br&gt;Nigger, RandomX is CPU only. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Monero is the king today, nobody denies that&lt;br&gt;Then why shit on it always? Why even try to move away from it to a clearly inferior product in every metric? Why do you need some community in the first place? We have an economy we care about.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;A privacy movement that can’t tolerate parallel projects is already compromised.&lt;br&gt;So can you tolerate our general not existing to push your cowshit coin?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866825&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866688&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;If your “decentralized privacy coin community” is so threatened by the existence of a CPU-only alternative that mods have to memoryhole any discussion, that’s not confidence, that’s insecurity and gatekeeping.&lt;br&gt;This thread has been up for 4 days now. This narrative of &amp;#x27;le jannies are out to get me!&amp;#x27; isn&amp;#x27;t holding any water. So far the only posts that keep getting removed are the ones that literally break the rules of 4chan&lt;br&gt;https://www.4chan.org/rules&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Complaining about 4chan (its policies, moderation, etc) on the imageboards may result in post deletion and a ban.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Evading your ban will result in a permanent one. Instead, wait and appeal it!&lt;br&gt;Have any of you tried not calling the mods glownigger XMR shills and not changing your IP so you can continue calling the mods glownigger XMR shills?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;You can’t preach censorship resistance while censoring competition like a reddit janny.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Looks like this post is gonna get deleted, unless the jannies like being compared to reddit jannies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866885&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Let&amp;#x27;s make a deal. Let us have our Nerva General and we&amp;#x27;ll stay out of XMR Generals. I think it&amp;#x27;s a pretty simple and straightforward solution. If everyone is so worried about this &amp;quot;jeetcoin&amp;quot; then let us have our containment thread and fuck off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866961&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866885&lt;br&gt;1. Not up for us to decide&lt;br&gt;2. You already had your generals, they die out anyway and you still feel a need to infiltrate our generals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867008&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866825&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;4days&lt;br&gt;And they started spamming and shitting on nerva here&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866825 right at the beginning, and this isnt a nerva thread and never was, as if OP was a nerva shill and they werent. They are shitting up other threads and advertising XMR, and abusing their cuck jannie powers to ban people who disagree with them, then his little buddy starts asking me to &amp;quot;stop evading bans&amp;quot; and pretending theyre not deleting actual nerva threads. They can go fuck themselves. I hope their rainbow shit covered dildos break off in their asses. Youre the only ones who are really evading bans with your jannie powers while advertising and spamming and harassing users across boards you worthless piles of shit.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Have any of you tried not calling the mods glownigger XMR shills and not changing your IP so you can continue calling the mods glownigger XMR shills?&lt;br&gt;Maybe if they would stop being exactly that, everything can go back to normal, but they wont. They started it the day they took a shit on someone asking about nerva and have been shitting up every non monero thread since. Im sick of seeing them shit everywhere every time a privacy coin thread pops up. Either remove the XMR general for advertising, or leave privacy threads and nerva threads/anons alone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867018&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866805&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Stop talking about my coin and stop coming to my general and I will tolerate your kind&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;doesnt know where hes at or what hes doing, apparently&lt;br&gt;Also, I started this general and one of the jannies banned me. Why? ban these monegros.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867055&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867008&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;and this isnt a nerva thread and never was&lt;br&gt;Oh yeah OP just stole the picture from a nervajeet and pretends to be oblivious to it despite being in the general in which nerva had to be mentioned over 140 times already&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;They are shitting up other threads &lt;br&gt;We got inspired by you it seems. Maybe stop trying to psyop people regarding our coin.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;and advertising XMR, &lt;br&gt;We&amp;#x27;re refuting your FUD and asking you questions which you can never answer. That&amp;#x27;s because all you do is literally just put out ads for your jeetcoin&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;and abusing their cuck jannie powers to ban people who disagree with them, then his little buddy starts asking me to &amp;quot;stop evading bans&amp;quot; and pretending theyre not deleting actual nerva threads.&lt;br&gt;How about the generals that don&amp;#x27;t get deleted and then die from your community consisting solely of five jeets?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;They started it the day they took a shit on someone asking about nerva and have been shitting up every non monero thread since.&lt;br&gt;Funny thing to say when nerva jeets admit to being in multiple threads not related to nerva and even pol to promote their cowshit coin&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Im sick of seeing them shit everywhere every time a privacy coin thread pops up.&lt;br&gt;Stop spreading FUD&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Either remove the XMR general for advertising,&lt;br&gt;It isn&amp;#x27;t. It&amp;#x27;s refuting your claims. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;leave privacy threads and nerva threads/anons alone.&lt;br&gt;Your kind infiltrated our thread. You are supposed to leave us alone. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867018&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;doesnt know where hes at or what hes doing, apparently&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m in the thread that just spreads fud about Monero from the very beginning.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Why?&lt;br&gt;Because you&amp;#x27;re an obvious nervajeet that spreads FUD so his bags get bought.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>When did you realize that you were NOT going to make it? — 68 replies — 99.8/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61862922</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61862922?lm=1771359018</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 20:10:18 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;When did you realize that you were NOT going to make it?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61862922'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 68 • Updated: 2026-02-17 20:10 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862935&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;is he ok&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862944&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862935&lt;br&gt;just some minor scratches (on his brain)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862956&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;the funniest part is that you think &amp;quot;maybe he survived the crash, just barely&amp;quot; but then it erupts in flames and he&amp;#x27;s cooked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864714&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863183&lt;br&gt;you&amp;#x27;re not supposed to drive there&lt;br&gt;play stupid games, win stupid prices&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864734&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863411&lt;br&gt;When I got my permit in the EU the first evasion maneuver you learn is the quick jerking of the handle to swerve and avoid this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864738&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863681&lt;br&gt;Should we just back china then?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is this the only way to topple the status quo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864767&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;Why do you care what other people are thinking? Does it hurt your feelings when Jesus leaves you on read? You still don&amp;#x27;t have to be atheist.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864769&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864709&lt;br&gt;not starting with &amp;gt;riding a motorcycle&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864775&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;I BOUGHT SHINY ROCK @ $120 &lt;br&gt;BIZ TOLD ME IT WAS GOING TO $5000 EOY&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864842&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864092&lt;br&gt;No it&amp;#x27;s not dumbass. Nearly all roads in Asia are like this and they all have motorbikes that drive on it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864852&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864842&lt;br&gt;Well then it&amp;#x27;s a retarded design if you have to give way to vehicles turning every 2 seconds - and it has no markings to indicate as such.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864870&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;That finishing final destination touch&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865341&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864842&lt;br&gt;Just because people abuse the emergency lane it illegal doesn&amp;#x27;t mean that&amp;#x27;s what it is designed for.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865399&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862935&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;he&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865412&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864842&lt;br&gt;they have roads where motorcycles try to front brake doing 70mph? lol, this chink deserved what he got, like it or not.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865437&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s not tragic to die doing what you love&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865490&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;When the NSA broke fisa and used Pegasus on me whilst on vacation and upon arriving home and getting a new phone being threatened in person after dodging a SWAT attempt through someone using back doors on my hardwired internet connection. Just the tip of the icerberg but I would strongly advise leaving the united states, it’s only gonna get worse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865508&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;cutting across 2 lanes just to go 5 mph in a turn&lt;br&gt;motorcyclist shouldn&amp;#x27;t have been there but white car is a fucking retard&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865611&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865490&lt;br&gt;There&amp;#x27;s nowhere to go. We have to take a stand where we are.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865639&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;When did you realize that you were NOT going to make it?&lt;br&gt;I looked at the conditions of the people who had made it to the wealthiest tiers of society. They all had generational wealth behind them, and they all operated on insane levels of exploitation to generate that wealth. Realized that &amp;quot;making it&amp;quot; means screwing over so many people that you alienate yourself from most people, except the likes of musk, epstein, trump, etc.&lt;br&gt;I realized that though the club was small and that I wasn&amp;#x27;t in it, that the people in the club were not the kind of person I wanted to be. I&amp;#x27;d rather disband the club.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865646&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865611&lt;br&gt;Nope, I’m out - fuck this third world country in disguise. The problem is thresholds were crossed and stupid people who shouldn’t have power drag you into shit that doesn’t even matter. This whole entire country is rotten, the corrupt local cop is just an extended phenotype of the so called “elite”. Shut off the news, delete all media and just get up and fucking go. Don’t lift a finger for this surveillance prison social credit score algorithm hellscape.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865657&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863529&lt;br&gt;Beautifully put.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865848&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865437&lt;br&gt;Ok Alesteir&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865901&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863924&lt;br&gt;Yes those entities actually exist. In history, people were religious because they were uneducated and most couldn&amp;#x27;t read. now people can read and are educated, but they aren&amp;#x27;t religious, but they also told that spiritual or religious hoo-hah is bull, the only thing that exists is what you see in front of you with your basic senses blah blah. When in fact, people should be using their educated brain to dig deeper. but it&amp;#x27;s all by design by the elites to continue obscuring the truths. they did it hundreds of years ago, and they continue to do it today just in a different way. READ THINGS. start with the bible. answers for a lot of things are in there. you don&amp;#x27;t need to be religious to read the bible and think critically.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;then move upwards throughout history and you&amp;#x27;ll notice the pattern. these people are extremely, extremely religious/spiritual themselves. They are Yahwists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865913&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864842&lt;br&gt;Because the chinks are all retarded insects, its not supposed to be driven on&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866587&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;it really is amazing how you can just go from fully alive, lots of possibilities to fully dead and nothing can be done about it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866704&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866587&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Could practice something called&lt;br&gt;&amp;quot;Defensive driving&amp;quot; &lt;br&gt;or &lt;br&gt;&amp;quot;Not recklessly speeding on the shoulder&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;But yea nothing could have been done, the cagies claimed another scalp&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866754&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864685&lt;br&gt;Pretty much this&lt;br&gt;I’m simultaneously never going to sell and never expecting it to go up&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866776&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863681&lt;br&gt;I have to admit I wasn&amp;#x27;t a noticer but now I am kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866784&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864699&lt;br&gt;I need to re read the Art of War in this context&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866977&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863529&lt;br&gt;Something about if people breed fast, they die fast.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866980&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863681&lt;br&gt;this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866986&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866704&lt;br&gt;or just dont fucking ride a motorcycle. dumbest activity there is&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>/smg/ - Stock Market Gambling — 380 replies — 67.5/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861684</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861684?lm=1771341198</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:13:18 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;/smg/ - Stock Market Gambling&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861684'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 380 • Updated: 2026-02-17 15:13 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Casino Economy Edition&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Some helpful links to numb the pain&lt;br&gt;https://findahelpline.com/&lt;br&gt;https://www.nvidia.com/refunds/&lt;br&gt;https://www.whitehouse.gov/refunds&lt;br&gt;https://jlingz.com/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Educational sites:&lt;br&gt;https://www.investopedia.com&lt;br&gt;https://www.khanacademy.org/economics-finance-domain&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Financial TV Streams:&lt;br&gt;https://www.newslive.com/american/cnbc.html&lt;br&gt;https://www.livestreamy.net/bloomberg/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Charts:&lt;br&gt;https://www.tradingview.com&lt;br&gt;https://www.finscreener.com&lt;br&gt;https://www.portfoliovisualizer.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Screeners: so you feel like in the movies&lt;br&gt;https://finviz.com/&lt;br&gt;https://etfdb.com/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Gambling:&lt;br&gt;https://www.optionsplaybook.com/options-introduction/&lt;br&gt;https://www.optionsprofitcalculator.com&lt;br&gt;https://optionstrat.com/&lt;br&gt;https://www.optionistics.com/quotes/option-prices&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Pre-Market and Live data:&lt;br&gt;https://www.investing.com/indices/indices-futures&lt;br&gt;https://finance.yahoo.com/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Calendars&lt;br&gt;https://www.marketwatch.com/economy-politics/calendar&lt;br&gt;https://www.earningswhispers.com/calendar&lt;br&gt;https://www.cmegroup.com/trading/interest-rates/countdown-to-fomc.html&lt;br&gt;https://www.mortgagenewsdaily.com/data/building-permits&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Boomer Investing 101: so zoomers with meme stocks can outperform you&lt;br&gt;https://www.bogleheads.org/wiki/Getting_started&lt;br&gt;https://www.sec.gov/search-filings&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Misc smg:&lt;br&gt;https://www.financialjuice.com/home&lt;br&gt;https://finance.yahoo.com/trending-tickers&lt;br&gt;https://market24hclock.com/&lt;br&gt;https://www.dividendchannel.com/drip-returns-calculator&lt;br&gt;https://brokerchooser.com/&lt;br&gt;https://www.chathamfinancial.com/technology/us-market-rates&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Previously on /smg/: &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858740&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861716&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m an American, I have extreme anxiety that i can&amp;#x27;t sell or buy right now&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;so me, and my fellow americans formally decided were panic selling everything Tuesday&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;sorry euros&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861738&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861716&lt;br&gt;i just watch the spot silver chart and get either mad or relieved when it doesnt move very far from 75&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864779&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This europoor just bought 70k USD worth of a global index fund and an ex-USA fund. Feel sick desu but I can’t sit on this cash forever&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864791&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864756&lt;br&gt;I dunno... what portion of nearly 50% of John Q Investor&amp;#x27;s assets are going to go into gold after he capitulates between now and August?&lt;br&gt;What is it they were saying 6 months ago? 60/20/20?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864794&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864791&lt;br&gt;forgot pic&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864805&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864588&lt;br&gt;enjoy your anal lysis&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864818&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;it&amp;#x27;s over.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864862&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;anyone know how to get fidelity to display my port value in premarket it doesn&amp;#x27;t update until market open and i need to aaaaaaaaaaahhhhhh more accurately right now&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864869&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864862&lt;br&gt;Have you tried to do math, you nigger gorilla?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864875&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864869&lt;br&gt;shiet wypipo be making computers hard to learn and shit to keep the black man down&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864876&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861707&lt;br&gt;ETOR&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864877&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864750&lt;br&gt;LEMEOW&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864887&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862034&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862207&lt;br&gt;DOSH&lt;br&gt;LOADS O MONE&lt;br&gt;SMG BTFO AGAIN&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864895&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864887&lt;br&gt;ok but how does that affect you personally?&lt;br&gt;post your profits big boy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864940&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864877&lt;br&gt;That&amp;#x27;s your 47% tariff doing it&amp;#x27;s job&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864953&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864895&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;GME baggie coping&lt;br&gt;go back to your containment thread&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864962&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ready for the bloodbath?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864974&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;soxl down 10%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864975&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;everyone&amp;#x27;s expecting it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864982&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The nurse at the psychs office called after out appointment today saying she was worried about me and asked if I wanted to get institutionalized.&lt;br&gt;While on one hand it feels good that someone cares about me, fuck no give me pills to survive [society] or stfu.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;what are the market implicaitons of this?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864986&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864777&lt;br&gt;I hope you guys bought hopium when I said. up another 20%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865002&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864982&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;asked if I wanted to get institutionalized&lt;br&gt;newby here. is this common in finance?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865011&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864411&lt;br&gt;hi bob&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865015&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865002&lt;br&gt;if you aren&amp;#x27;t getting wellness checks from the county health system or your female broker you probably aren&amp;#x27;t taking enough risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865028&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALL HANDS ON DECK&lt;br&gt;GET READY TO DEPLOY THOSE V&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865049&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865002&lt;br&gt;Yes. Saying &amp;quot;getting balls deep in leverage to see green or red numbers is the only thing that makes me feel anything&amp;quot; was the wrong answer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865127&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Well my mining portfolio has just been raped&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865178&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;jesus christ&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865184&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;bought google at 300 &lt;br&gt;how bad of an idea was that?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865241&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864986&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864777&lt;br&gt;Hopium currently up 324%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865274&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is today the day to slurp google&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865308&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865274&lt;br&gt;For me it&amp;#x27;s XOM&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>The US is in recession — 97 replies — 51.4/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61857490</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61857490?lm=1771354682</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 18:58:02 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;The US is in recession&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61857490'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 97 • Updated: 2026-02-17 18:58 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US is in recession&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857499&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White collar recession comes before regular recession 100% of the time. We&amp;#x27;ve been in a white collar recession since 2020.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857500&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;Always was, its depression for over a year now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857508&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;GDP is growing, recession is fake.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nothing ever happens. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stop putting your vibes and feelings into your job search, learn to get better skills and be more marketable to employers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;McDonalds is always hiring&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861729&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858084&lt;br&gt;The fantasy is better than the reality&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861769&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857805&lt;br&gt;We should be bombing Mexico.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861811&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861711&lt;br&gt;No I wasn’t. I don’t feel like explaining it to you so I’ll just let AI do it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863135&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858023&lt;br&gt;Pam Bondi was such a hot piece of ass when she was young. She&amp;#x27;s still sorta cute give that she&amp;#x27;s sixty years old. It&amp;#x27;s too bad she&amp;#x27;s protecting Jewish pedophiles and cannibals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863175&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;BUMP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863206&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And the burger gov is again burning absolutely everything in the market, including themselves to make a smoke screen to cover the crashing dollar.&lt;br&gt;Nobody wants that shit yet it is going up with not only no buyers but countries constantly throwing it into the market. Absolute shitshow from a drowning in shit man.&lt;br&gt;Funny isn&amp;#x27;t it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863218&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860719&lt;br&gt;The boat that is jewsa has been sinking for a while. The orange nigger is actively making more holes in it and setting it on fire&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863252&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What&amp;#x27;s the polymarket for that??&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863679&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857500&lt;br&gt;Try since 08. Things have never actually genuinely recovered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864332&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;End of the Juglar cycle. Overproduction crisis. Fed interest rates plunging toward zero. Soon an other Capital idling necessary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864333&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863679&lt;br&gt;Capital final crisis since 2008.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864989&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863206&lt;br&gt;2006 was giving out loans like candy to people who had absolutely no way of ever servicing them&lt;br&gt;this then resulted in a lot of forced selling into a no bid market as all of this inventory was cleared when the bubble popped&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;right now we dont have excessive loans, quite the opposite retards arent given insane loans this is legit existing money bidding up hard assets because so much money got printed and it has to go somewhere&lt;br&gt;you dont get a crash in housing without forced selling and who is going to force sell his real estate at low prices without the bank margin calling them&lt;br&gt;unlike stocks which are completely fungible and its price is set at the margin, housing isnt and the owner can just sit on the asset forever and not be forced to take any offer being made at market price&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;to disrupt this &amp;#x27;bubble&amp;#x27; you need the government unprinting the money supply (lol, lmao even) or you need a large section of boomers dying off and leaving their heirs with no way to pay the taxes/upkeep and force dump it&lt;br&gt;the second one is the only realistic option, tho there is also the risk that the heirs can pay for the inheritance and real estate is now permanently locked up in magnate hands and the nation reduced to permarenting slave&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865001&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It really isn&amp;#x27;t mentioned enough that our &amp;quot;recovery&amp;quot; after 2008 was just setting interest rates to 0 for 10 years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865048&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864989&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;...a large section of boomers dying off and leaving their heirs with no way to pay the taxes/upkeep...real estate is now permanently locked up in magnate hands....&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;ve laid out exactly what&amp;#x27;s been going on since 2008&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865068&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865048&lt;br&gt;yes thats the point, the implication here is that real estate is now permanently priced out of the middle class income range&lt;br&gt;not that a crash is imminent like the anon i was replying to seemed to suggest&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865501&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;I knew it was really over when Wendy&amp;#x27;s and pizza Hut announced theyre closing hundreds of stores.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865585&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;Idk these terms, and economics is a fraudulent science anyways, so I&amp;#x27;ll just say what I see.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;My life sucks.&lt;br&gt;Its getting worse.&lt;br&gt;I am watching generational decline among my family (each new set of kids struggle more than their parents).&lt;br&gt;People seem unhappy.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Call that recession, depression, or economic boon! Idc, US is a shithole.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m sure people will respond saying I&amp;#x27;m cherry picking. Dishonesty is rampant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865659&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857779&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Foreign money taking investments out of the US because trump is an unpredictable fucking moron being puppeteered by unironically evil people&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;American dollar has lost 10% of its value over the course of 2025&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Constant tariff bullshitery that is objectively hurting American industries that rely on imports&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Nuked basedbean deal with China on top of farmers needing a fucking bailout because of the retard they voted in (again)&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Tourism industry cratering every day as we speak so even less money being injected into the economy &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;ICE operation have caused businesses across the country to shut down because either no one&amp;#x27;s willing to go out, or because they don&amp;#x27;t want random goons in masks harassing employees&lt;br&gt;Dude it&amp;#x27;s actually impressive how hard these retards just destroyed the entire reputation of america abroad and fucked us over domestically, but his cult fan base and circle of wannabe oligarchs who own media outlets will continue telling you that there is no war in ba sing se&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865663&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861063&lt;br&gt;We really need to do what the Chinese do with making sure household consumption as share of GDP is increasing. Actually reflects living standards instead of billions of dollars getting spitswapped between 3-4 different AI companies constantly. Then again, most of the people hear would just ree hearing the term “5 year plan” or “stability focused infrastructure development.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865674&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865585&lt;br&gt;MIGAtrannies will happily eat shit if a libtard has to smell their breath.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865800&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865585&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;US is a shithole&lt;br&gt;and the usa still gives you about the best chance in the world to improve your life if you come from humble beginnings&lt;br&gt;altho it also offers you every temptation possible to make you drive yourself over the financial cliff at every turn at the same time it offers you opportunity&lt;br&gt;just know its far worse everywhere else as society in general is reverting back to medieval style caste based system of neither hope nor escape&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865942&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865800&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;and the usa still gives you about the best chance in the world to improve your life if you come from humble beginnings&lt;br&gt;this has not been true in at least 20-25 years&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866035&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865942&lt;br&gt;lol, lmao&lt;br&gt;then give me the list of countries that you think arent just better today but were better 20 years ago and i&amp;#x27;ll have a good laugh&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;and to clarify we are specifically talking about giving chances to poor unconnected people so dont say retarded shit like liechtenstein&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866071&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865800&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;he fell for the meme&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866130&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860705&lt;br&gt;None of these are necessary. We could be totally self-sufficient, even for things like rare-earths. The Epstein class decided that would be bad for them so we aren&amp;#x27;t.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866186&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866130&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;pharmaceuticals are not necessary &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;input goods for new tech are not necessary &lt;br&gt;Uh huh. So what’s necessary? Shovels, canned food and farmland? If you want to be Amish so badly just do it, nobody is stopping you. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the real world, though, self-sufficiency would entail access to pharmaceuticals and the ability to evolve technologically and keep up with the first world. We can sing songs all day about how the US could be self-sufficient one day and that’s fine. The point is that we aren’t.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866312&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866130&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;re retarded if you actually believe this. Even IF we could be self sufficient, and make everything we need ourselves (we can&amp;#x27;t) the price of everything would fucking skyrocket to the point that most people wouldn&amp;#x27;t be able to afford common items that we have now like tvs and phones.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866376&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857508&lt;br&gt;THE DOW IS AT 6 MILLION!!!!!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866632&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866312&lt;br&gt;Key difference was that things lasted and were repairable, only people what would suffer would be consoomer types.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;TVs&lt;br&gt;No one would complain if smart TVs stopped existing, and anything above 4k is a meme&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Smartphones&lt;br&gt;Make them with weaker specs and optimize.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866648&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;anyone who isn&amp;#x27;t low iq or the most subhuman subspecies on the planet (miggers) already knew this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>GERMANY TO END BURGERGELD PROGRAMS — 76 replies — 31.3/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858970</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858970?lm=1771352737</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 18:25:37 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;GERMANY TO END BURGERGELD PROGRAMS&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858970'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 76 • Updated: 2026-02-17 18:25 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;WILL BE REPLACED WITH A STRICTER PROGRAM IF YOU REFUSE WORK. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEXT STOP, PRIVATIZED HEALTHCARE.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858974&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Uh oh, Europeans actually have to work for a living now? Aw shucks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858980&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858974&lt;br&gt;They will soon legalize 12 hour work days much like Argentina has done. Even contributing 5% of their GDP to NATO has ultimately bankrupted them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859007&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858970&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wait you could get NEETbux in Germany this whole time by simply “refusing to work”? WTF&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860591&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860550&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;it&amp;#x27;s either the whip or picking cotton&lt;br&gt;That false dichotomy is sure proof of wageslave brainrot. I don&amp;#x27;t blame you, though. The whole system is rigged against you from birth and every aspect of your human nature is weaponized against you by the very thing you&amp;#x27;re meant to worship as a social animal, i.e. society.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860601&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858970&lt;br&gt;They just gave away all our money to Ausländers and now that the social systems are running dry they are simply getting rid of them kek.&lt;br&gt;Nothing they do will fix this. Humanity is doomed.&lt;br&gt;Accelerationism is the only way.&lt;br&gt;Let the third world starve and divert fund into AI datacenters.&lt;br&gt;The wolf will chew its own leg off to survive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860612&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860601&lt;br&gt;third world is the biggest net exporter of food to the point frenchoids were crying it would kill their overpriced artistical wine or something, they aint starving bro&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860626&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860591&lt;br&gt;Sorry chief, I find the idea of opening a business to be enticing but I don’t see any sort of moat I could pursue with it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860651&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858970&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858974&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860660&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860612&lt;br&gt;Africa imports a lot of food&lt;br&gt;And France was rightfully complaining that imposing huge restrictions on European agriculture while signing free trade agreements with countries having little restrictions is retarded&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860678&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859446&lt;br&gt;a 10% reduction? kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860682&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860422&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;10 year gap&lt;br&gt;I tell them it is due to the government forcing employers to lower standards to hire the affirmative action subhumans. They never call me back, because they are off giving useless lazy meritless and sometime convict affirmative action subhumans jobs. &lt;br&gt;Enjoy paying to taxes to niggers, spics, and cunts that hate you, just in the vain hopes they one day stop calling you a racist and sexist. Get back to work wagie... the whole economy rests on you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860686&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860191&lt;br&gt;Gas?!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860707&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860422&lt;br&gt;kek, they won&amp;#x27;t work at all, german economy will implode and as merz said they already can&amp;#x27;t afford the welfare + pensions, it will just shrink till it gets too low to live then they will just kys as by now they are legit unable to live at all&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860723&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859099&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;this nigga thinks German economy circa 1988 is anything like today&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lol&lt;br&gt;Lmao even&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860724&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860401&lt;br&gt;a drooly retard eh? yeah that sounds just perfect for our new expanded military, the bundeswehr needs you to pick this uniform, this little sign and just stand there to block the evil russian drones with your face for us&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860758&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;tfw the only time in my life where I might receive neetbux for a few months is the exact time this happens&lt;br&gt;fucking lol my entire life is me getting fucked by the universe. Nothing good ever happens to me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860764&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860626&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;moat&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;he fell for Buffett boomer brain rot &lt;br&gt;The only moats Buffett had were his generous throat and his congressman daddy. And let&amp;#x27;s not forget about being lucky enough to be born in close proximity to swollen jewish nuts in Israel&amp;#x27;s 2nd state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860766&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860758&lt;br&gt;join a gang, sell weed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861462&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858970&lt;br&gt;NooOoOO&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861576&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858970&lt;br&gt;thats gut. not because of the money, it wont help in any significant way but because its a statement. fuck bürgis, fuck ausländer&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861599&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858970&lt;br&gt;They have been rebranding the same system for almost 25 years now. The previous government eased up on some of the welfare restrictions because they were largely pointless. The new(old) sanctions don&amp;#x27;t really change anything because even with them you can be permanently on welfare in Germany as long as you show up to your jobcenter appointments. Nobody in Germany is going to hire someone who hasn&amp;#x27;t worked for years and is clearly just applying because the jobcenter is pressuring them. This is just a huge waste of everyone&amp;#x27;s time and part of Germany&amp;#x27;s soviet-tier obscuring of unemployment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861817&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860422&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;It&amp;#x27;ll be hard to explain the 10+ year gap&lt;br&gt;16 years gapmaxxer here, would you hire me?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862208&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Every nation has 10% unemployable retards. What to do with them?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;send them into the meatgrinder&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;employ them for the least possible payment&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;give them fake jobs&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;giver them life long gibs payed by everyone else&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A nation can do any of these without problems. BUT: If you open your borders and let the 10% retards of the entire third world in, you can not give them gibs anymore or you risk financial collapse. Especially if you destroy your own industry and energy security. The meatgrinder is then the only viable solution. Prepare for a war.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862662&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860724&lt;br&gt;getting out from Bundeswehr cuckery is even easier than getting welfare.&lt;br&gt;just fake mental illness and you cant work there. ez.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862678&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862662&lt;br&gt;that&amp;#x27;s for now buddy, things will change pretty fast when we attack those pesky russians to save EVROPA, our poor refugees can&amp;#x27;t go, so its time for private retard from munich to catch a drone, you are legit stupid and not only faking if you believe all that goodwill shit won&amp;#x27;t dissapear from the constitution as soon as they need meat, you will be the retard brick to the new EU federation, be glad&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862777&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862678&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;tfw only germans have to serve in the Volksfront&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;12% of our pop doesn&amp;#x27;t even have a german pass&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;tfw they are getting welfare and Neetmax while i&amp;#x27;m send off to the grinder after taxing the shit out of my market gains&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862781&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;why would you give people free money for burgers? lazy europoops.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862784&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859975&lt;br&gt;reminder the leaders are all boomers but when you point this out some tranny will start screaming to stop blaming the boomers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;All it takes is for non-elderly people to rise up and say &amp;quot;get the fuck out of my way grandpa or I will cave your head in&amp;quot; and there&amp;#x27;s nothing they can do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862797&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860147&lt;br&gt;it&amp;#x27;s despicable. these assholes come here, shit up our culture and behave like the are welcome here. cultures should be kept separate. you have to go back to /pol/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863548&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862678&lt;br&gt;nothing will happen.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;muh WW3&lt;br&gt;is a nothingburger like covid.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863561&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860422&lt;br&gt;your cat&amp;#x27;s litterbox needs changing, roastie&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863615&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859111&lt;br&gt;but not civil rights (since they invaded)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866483&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859010&lt;br&gt;/thread&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;otherwise politicians would actually have to do something. news cycle is 50% immigration and 50% buergergeld which is not a gigantic slice of the money pie, then they bicker 3 years and rename the thing and change one integer, just like launching a shitcoin and changing the port. then they&amp;#x27;ve done enough work for one legislative period and resume partying on epstein island&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Fun fact: RLUSD only has a 4x smaller market cap than Chainlink — 13 replies — 27.9/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61866834</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61866834?lm=1771359791</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 20:23:11 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Fun fact: RLUSD only has a 4x smaller market cap than Chainlink&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61866834'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 13 • Updated: 2026-02-17 20:23 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Won&amp;#x27;t be long until RLUSD is also above Chainlink kek baggies what a humiliation ritual when XRP chads dab on you not once but two times looool&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866848&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;aw honey, you angry again?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866857&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866834&lt;br&gt;That requires people actually locking up their value onto XRPL directly instead of using ripple&amp;#x27;s ethereum virtual machine.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Which they won&amp;#x27;t.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866859&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866848&lt;br&gt;What kind of weird cope is this lmao &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866857&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s growing every day. You nervous there stinky?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866865&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866859&lt;br&gt;No, its just odd that ripple&amp;#x27;s XRPL chain has 1% of the total value with XRP&amp;#x27;s ethereum side chain. Especially since they have been around longer than LINK.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866867&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866834&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;file name&lt;br&gt;Thanks for stirring the pot spammy. Now we know you&amp;#x27;re the sole individual trying to create beef between XRP &amp;amp; LINK.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866872&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866867&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s not me i&amp;#x27;m someone else, i&amp;#x27;ve just saved this picture from another thread I saw earlier today and figured i&amp;#x27;d name it the same when I saved it back then.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866873&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866859&lt;br&gt;Its also like saying that the release of ISO200022 would ultimately skyrocket the price of XRP .... which it wouldnt. Same thing is going to happen with the opening of the clarity act.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Except when you consider that the TVL held by their oracles are 15x the current market cap of LINK.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866879&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866872&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866867&lt;br&gt;I mean when that person saved it back then whoever it was, nobody knows it&amp;#x27;s all a mystery on 4chan where everybody is anonymous.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866887&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866872&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;It&amp;#x27;s not me i&amp;#x27;m someone else&lt;br&gt;Kek, never change. Stinks deserve it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866915&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866887&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;sole individual&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;there&amp;#x27;s probably a whole lot people doing it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866965&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866873&lt;br&gt;yeah well&lt;br&gt;fuck stinks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867027&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866965&lt;br&gt;I like the concept that LINK is a litmus test for the overall inflated market of cryptocurrencies. If the creator has been elected to the CFTC and is spearheading one of the most important clarity laws for currency adoption. What does that say for the broader market overall?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;My theory is that institutions are stalling as much as possible so they can create their own private solution rather than using whats publicly available. Because that would allow for the broader market to win instead of participating in a zero sum game.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867043&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866965&lt;br&gt;Being open source is one of the biggest memes where private investors can just steal what&amp;#x27;s been established and carbon copy to keep all the benefits. It&amp;#x27;s actually a tale as old as time when it comes to innovation. Edison didn&amp;#x27;t get rich off of ingenuity, he got rich off of stealing patents and publicly humiliating his competition, IE tesla.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>