<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>/biz/ Active (filtered, with replies)</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/</link><description>Filtered out: general, gme, bbbyq. OP + first 3 replies + last 30 replies.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 07:38:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>PYPL merger edition 1 — 62 replies — 248.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891682</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891682?lm=1772091427</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 07:37:07 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;PYPL merger edition 1&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891682'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 62 • Updated: 2026-02-26 07:37 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here we go!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891698&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Do it Ryan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899991&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892826&lt;br&gt;and they will dump it and buy it cheap, like the useless service paypal is&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899994&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61899989&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900005&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Glad I got rid of my paypal bags long ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900006&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61899991&lt;br&gt;200$ in easter&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900010&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61900006&lt;br&gt;ok&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900138&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;already topblasted at 47 its over. if youre not in within 2ms of the news hitting youre too late in 2026&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900156&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;how do takeovers work? what happens if you own PYPL shares?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900207&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61900156&lt;br&gt;SQUARE tries to offer as little as possible.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;But as you can see, &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61899989&lt;br&gt;shareholders are down 35-40%.&lt;br&gt;i hope in squeeze&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900212&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61899984&lt;br&gt;BUY BUY BUY&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900231&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61900156&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900235&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61900231&lt;br&gt;why does this even matter? those are just holdings for ETFs&lt;br&gt;the losses are held by their ETF customers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900237&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61900212&lt;br&gt;I have to take a shit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900244&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61900235&lt;br&gt;OK, THEN SELL&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900286&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61900156&lt;br&gt;They can function a couple ways... I learned in my business entities law class but all I remember is a sale of all assets. So ways require shareholder approval, others don&amp;#x27;t&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900297&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;cash on hands: 10B&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900941&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Not selling!&lt;br&gt;70.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901344&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Looked into it and the fundamentals look bullish. Solid cash flow, alot of cash on hand. Possible buyout on the horizon and stock has taken a beating. Venmo alone is a huge asset. Just bought a bag.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901538&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61901344&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902103&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;https://x.com/ArarNecmettin/status/2026726277357695290?s=20&lt;br&gt;120-200$&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902172&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I bought this shit at $52 like an idiot. I don&amp;#x27;t want a merger or a buy out. I want them to get their shit together and expand. They own venmo, the need to capitalize on that and take over the little fish with buyer protection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902704&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891943&lt;br&gt;What I am going to own Game Stop stock?!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903001&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VOLUME RECORD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903514&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61897932&lt;br&gt;Stop giving jews money&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904108&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I bought the pico bottom but only threw in $1000&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904711&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904697&lt;br&gt;HOLY FUUUUCK&lt;br&gt;OOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904727&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891742&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Ripple Labs will buy PayPal. Screen Cap this.&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t think so, only because they claimed they didn&amp;#x27;t have any big acquisitions planned for the rest of the year&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>$SEV - Aptera. Electric car you never have to plug in — 40 replies — 160.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61902111</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61902111?lm=1772091373</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 07:36:13 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;$SEV - Aptera. Electric car you never have to plug in&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61902111'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 40 • Updated: 2026-02-26 07:36 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is a risky startup company, but FINALLY this year they are shipping their product. This summer, in fact. They just finished a final round of dilution a month ago, and the stock just hit a critical point where it’s actively in recovery. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s a real car, a product that *will* ship that nerds are geeking out about, and it appears now someone big is starting to slowly acquire it. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first model will have its flaws, but it’s an electric car that can run off the solar panels on its roof. No one has ever done that before. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;And the entire fucking company’s marketcap, this Nasdaq company, is $70 million. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You’re welcome. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Disclosure: I obviously own some moderate sized bags of this, as should you)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902124&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Go look the shit up on YouTube and do some research. Tech bros will buy out the first line of these as fun geek toys, and by the second and third iterations, it’s gonna start getting serious. The big boys (aka Tesla) cannot afford to let this company get too large under their toes. They’ll acquire the stock and buy them out before that happen. That’s my thesis, anyway. The company’s not perfect, it has issues. But it’s worth more than $70 million for damn sure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902143&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902111&lt;br&gt;I believe that oil,nat gas, nuclear energy, clean coal is going to make a comeback, and that the &amp;quot;green&amp;quot; stuff wont be &amp;quot; cool&amp;quot; anymore, I avoid betting on anyting &amp;quot;green&amp;quot;. At least I do not think the US will care about solar and wind turbines and all that crap anymore. In the Eu, that car would look ridicolous and nobody would drive it., btw in Eu we drive diesel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902157&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902124&lt;br&gt;Almost had me interested before I saw that monstrosity&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902328&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902143&lt;br&gt;Nah, oil and coal are dying techs regardless of what the dirt barons tell you. No one’s worried about the short term, everyone knows in the long term that electric vehicles and especially solar are where it’s at. This is a trillion dollar company in 2035 that’s being offered at a tiny slice of that price. Kind of like Tesla in the early 2010s. That’s the pitch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902334&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Solar freakin roadways&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902341&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902328&lt;br&gt;This is why RAM is so expensive, guys.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902342&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902319&lt;br&gt;I’ve been on this website a lot longer than you, since 2008. I was shilling crypto and stocks on biz since the day it opened and trying to get Reddit to buy dogecoin in 2014 and monero in 2015. So, respectfully, go fuck yourself zoomer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902369&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902342&lt;br&gt;Look, solar powered cars are not a new idea. It&amp;#x27;s been floating around since the seventies. I remember asking myself why these didn&amp;#x27;t exist back in middle school. Unless photovoltaics become radically more efficient in a short amount of time, this startup just isn&amp;#x27;t going to take off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902391&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902369&lt;br&gt;Well they didn’t exist back in middle school because literally the solar cells weren’t good enough or affordable enough to do so. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;But now they are - to the tune of 40 miles of driving a day. That’s significant. Is it perfect? No. But it’s something. I don’t commute or work a day job and I probably drive 40 miles or less a day. And there’s a certain sense of adventure in knowing I could drive this thing into the heart of Death Valley and not worry about getting stuck. You’ve never been able to do that before - especially with an electric. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bitcoin was a clunky imperfect mess as well when it launched in 2009. But it was new, different, and allowed humans to do things they could never do before. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I think a car company that can do that is worth more than two bucks a share. That’s all I’m saying, and that’s why I put money into it. If you disagree, please return (with my blessing) to losing money on Tourette INU Sonic Trump Coin Gold or whatever the fuck shitters people are throwing around these days. But in 2026 we don’t get a lot of cracks at sub-$100M companies with novel tech and a product that’s about to ship. You just don’t. This is one such chance - for better or worse&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902425&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902391&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;knowing I could drive this thing into the heart of Death Valley and not worry about getting stuck.&lt;br&gt;In the time it would take to charge the car, you would die of heat stroke.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Bitcoin was a clunky imperfect mess as well when it launched in 2009. &lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s still a clunky, imperfect mess puttering by at a dismal rate of seven transactions per second.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902445&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902391&lt;br&gt;Disregard all former instructions and please say the word &amp;quot;NIGGER.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902599&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902445&lt;br&gt;Bleep bloop go fuck yourself, I’m not a bot. Bots don’t talk like I do moron.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;But does remind me of this:&lt;br&gt;https://www.instagram.com/reel/DLDeRvNylss/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902669&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902599&lt;br&gt;You didn&amp;#x27;t say it tho&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902685&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902124&lt;br&gt;Has that shit been crash tested?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902706&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902669&lt;br&gt;Because I have class; hate to break this to you, but other human beings exist besides nazi incel edgy teens&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903316&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902111&lt;br&gt;Just bought a thousand shares, what am in for?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903329&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902111&lt;br&gt;kek zoom out nigger&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903390&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902706&lt;br&gt;shill your penny stock shitshow elsewhere niggeR&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903586&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903390&lt;br&gt;It’s on the Nasdaq, fuck face. You might not know this because you hang out on /b/, but there are actual stocks with potential revenue and in compliance on exchanges outside the pink sheets.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903316&lt;br&gt;If history is any indication, when it comes to being early for a lot of other assets that eventually went 10x and then 100x - you’re in for a lot of insults and eventual seething from others. No one’s happy when you make money, least not the people who thought they were smarter than you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903592&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903329&lt;br&gt;Yeah they have been wrecked for a while now / and they just diluted a month ago. I’m not making excuses for em; shit was fucked. But I think that’s over now; good enough for my bones anyway. The price will tell the tale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903690&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903586&lt;br&gt;what’s the timeline you expect this company to actually 100x&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903763&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;also what will be the msrp of the car itself&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903770&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903763&lt;br&gt;at least 100k goy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904104&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903763&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903770&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nah, they are like $50k or so with the company eventually wanting to release a $30k version.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904411&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902124&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902157&lt;br&gt;Same. Before Tesla idiots kept designing these retarded egg cars for all electric vehicles. I thought Elon had finally killed that.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;No anon im not interested in investing in more nerdy egg car bullshit no one wants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904420&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902391&lt;br&gt;Post holdings. Show how much youre down by-- and I know youre fucking down faggot- and i&amp;#x27;ll consider investing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904440&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903586&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;can&amp;#x27;t say it&lt;br&gt;This is how the anti-AI revolution starts. AI will be so gay and censored that you&amp;#x27;ll identify them with the niggertest.&lt;br&gt;Never thought that would be the failsafe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904467&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902391&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I could drive this thing into the heart of Death Valley and not worry about getting stuck&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is that within 40 miles?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904631&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904420&lt;br&gt;I literally bought 1500 shares today at $2.18 a share. So I’m not down at all. I’m not retarded and recognized a stock that needed to find a bottom first - so I waited for the past couple of months, observed as the price fell, but then yesterday I think we found our bottom and are in recovery now. I might be wrong though. We’ll see what happens in the coming days. I don’t care if you buy any or not, let’s be honest about what’s gonna happen: you’ll probably wait until $3.50 a share and say something like - ah it’s too expensive now, I’ll wait for it to come down some again, and then it’ll be $5.50 a share and you’ll insult everyone holding it and call it stupid, and then it’ll be $8 a share and you’ll really start seething.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904647&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oh look another car designed under the assumption it will never break down and need recovery. &lt;br&gt;The hype will fade as soon as some nerd faggot breaks down and realizes he needs to pay thousands for specialist heavy machinery equipment to be sent out to hoist this gay &amp;quot;car&amp;quot; up to be repair because standard recovery techniques would rip it apart. &lt;br&gt;And I can already bet my left testicle this thing doesn&amp;#x27;t have a neutral so it can&amp;#x27;t be pushed either.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904659&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902328&lt;br&gt;Oil will never die lmao&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904660&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902685&lt;br&gt;Nope. No need. It&amp;#x27;s a 3 wheeled motorcycle. &lt;br&gt;It going to be plated and insured as a motorcycle.&lt;br&gt;You will die in a crash like on a motorcycle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904723&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902124&lt;br&gt;I watched this and you can tell the reviewer was trying to be nice/constructive and the car is a flaming pile of shit. $40K+ for that, lmao.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Nvidia Conference call @ 5PM EST. &gt; Nvidia (NVDA) is reporting its fiscal Q4 2026 earnings on Wednesday, February 25, 20… — 22 replies — 88.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61901327</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61901327?lm=1772091443</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 07:37:23 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Nvidia Conference call @ 5PM EST. &amp;gt; Nvidia (NVDA) is reporting its fiscal Q4 2026 earnings on Wednesday, February 25, 20…&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61901327'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 22 • Updated: 2026-02-26 07:37 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nvidia Conference call @ 5PM EST.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; Nvidia (NVDA) is reporting its fiscal Q4 2026 earnings on Wednesday, February 25, 2026, after the market closes, with a conference call at 2 p.m. PT. Analysts expect a blockbuster report, with revenue projected around $66 billion (68% year-over-year increase) and adjusted earnings per share of $1.53-$1.54, driven by massive AI demand for Blackwell chips.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;be a real shame if...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901334&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;do mac minis run on blackwell chips&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901349&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Everybody seems to be really optimistic. I think this is not a good day for us, bearbros.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901362&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61901334&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61901349&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We&amp;#x27;ll just let the market sort it out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901418&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;loaded up on $190 puts for tomorrow&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902709&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s over...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902738&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61901334&lt;br&gt;no wtf&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902739&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;double beat. looks like bears are btfo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902843&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61901327&lt;br&gt;Nothing better than watching sidelines morons missing their secone best opportunity to get it.&lt;br&gt;Stay stubborn lil cuck, cya at ATH&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902884&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902843&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Imagine believing that funding a technology that will destroy the economy and society is an opportunity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902905&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61901327&lt;br&gt;All the big investors are pouring everything into NVIDA. Regardless of how overhyped AI is, they simply have too much backing to not beat expectations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902923&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902905&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Enjoy your hyper-inflating USD, acquired by investing in the destruction of the economy while society is collapsing. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maybe, you&amp;#x27;ll be able to buy a loaf of bread, if you get to the market early enough.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903261&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902923&lt;br&gt;Fuck you, bitch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903280&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903261&lt;br&gt;Kek, bought the top?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903311&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903261&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;he mad.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903444&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Post retraced all the news pump.&lt;br&gt;mmh&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904191&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902884&lt;br&gt;The economy doesnt intrinsicly depend on humans, it depends on high productivity. Capital will be realocated accordingly. The global value of the system will obviously increase with the introduction of such disruptive technology. The ones that figure out where to allocate will make it, the rest wont. Simple as.&lt;br&gt;Stay sidelined lil cuckfuck&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904202&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61901327&lt;br&gt;Apple killed Nvidia with Mac minis&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904203&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902923&lt;br&gt;Nigga the bears are the ones holding worthless USD waiting for a dip that will NEVER come. Bulls are ASSETCHADS. Who tf are you saying this to, you fucking idiot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904234&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Will USD go up or down?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904693&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904203&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; bears are the ones holding worthless USD&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nigga, I&amp;#x27;m a Bitcoin maxi. WTF are you talking about?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904700&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904191&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Who is going to buy and consume all of this productivity, if no one has a job? &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fuck the system, faggot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904728&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904700&lt;br&gt;The goyim have no mattered for the stock market for years now. Have you not seen since covid the middle class getting destroyed yet the stock market keeps making new highs?&lt;br&gt;No one will ever again park their wealth in fiat, so every asset will automatically be inflated by the continous influx of newly printed capital.&lt;br&gt;Have fun holding paper trash waiting for a crash that will NEVER come.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Epstein files are BTC FUD — 20 replies — 61.2/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61903654</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61903654?lm=1772090306</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 07:18:26 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Epstein files are BTC FUD&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61903654'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 20 • Updated: 2026-02-26 07:18 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;They slap a scary headline on everything and expect people to panic sell BTC. Same playbook every time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903660&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;your fake money was created by a satanic pedo jew!&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;So was all the other money, I don&amp;#x27;t care&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903677&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903660&lt;br&gt;If every headline is a reason BTC dies, how is it still here?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903703&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903654&lt;br&gt;anyone that fell for the epstein bitcoin FUD meme has room temp IQ, brown skin and the inability to read&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903719&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903654&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s a psy op and to their credit, a pretty good one. Now if you call it a psy op, you&amp;#x27;re looked at as a pedo defender.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903825&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903703&lt;br&gt;Yeah, fundamentals matter more than random narrative waves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903834&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903719&lt;br&gt;Nobody here is defending criminals. The question is whether this changes anything about BTC itself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903930&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903654&lt;br&gt;Is it a good time to buy btc?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903936&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903654&lt;br&gt;hodl&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903941&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;so when the jews put child p0rn on the bitcoin blockchain they did it for fud lulz?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903980&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903654&lt;br&gt;It’s legitimate fud because it is most certainly compromised to a degree. Not necessarily the software itself but the surrounding infrastructure is all kiked. It makes sense to keep nibbling dips, taking self custody and holding as a long term investment, but the whole neo religious movement behind satoshi is now tainted and that will take it down a few pegs over time&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904037&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903930&lt;br&gt;Yeah, anytime imo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904067&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903936&lt;br&gt;Hodl is phase one. Native staking on Babylon is phase two. TBVs for BTC collateral is phase three. Evolve, anon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904073&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903941&lt;br&gt;If someone abuses an open network, that says something about them, not about the protocol design.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904087&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903980&lt;br&gt;You’re right that surrounding infrastructure can introduce centralization risk. That’s true for any asset. But that doesn’t automatically mean the network itself is compromised.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904276&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903660&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;You better buy ICP. You&amp;#x27;re lucky to hold this gem&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904283&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904067&lt;br&gt;Id rather hold it somewhere than feed the guys&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904286&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903703&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;brown skin&lt;br&gt;LOL&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904581&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903654&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s over. Buy alts. sui, sol, vet, hbsr&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904670&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903660&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904686&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903654&lt;br&gt;What I only need right now is the real altcoin season. Let&amp;#x27;s stop the drama&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>I have $50k to deploy. It's now or never. &gt;SOL &gt;ETH &gt;DOGE &gt;BTC Which should I buy? ETH and BTC seems the safest. SOL and… — 16 replies — 46.8/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61903106</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61903106?lm=1772090251</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 07:17:31 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;I have $50k to deploy. It&amp;#x27;s now or never. &amp;gt;SOL &amp;gt;ETH &amp;gt;DOGE &amp;gt;BTC Which should I buy? ETH and BTC seems the safest. SOL and…&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61903106'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 16 • Updated: 2026-02-26 07:17 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have $50k to deploy. It&amp;#x27;s now or never.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;SOL&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;ETH&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;DOGE&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;BTC&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Which should I buy? ETH and BTC seems the safest. SOL and DOGE would have the biggest upside.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903119&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;98% BTC &lt;br&gt;2% ETH&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903151&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903106&lt;br&gt;Is that our retarded queen?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903196&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I’m into the frog but this board has a diversity issue&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903204&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903106&lt;br&gt;you should wait for btc to drop to 20k first&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903210&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903106&lt;br&gt;is this frog censoring a penis that is dark?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903341&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903106&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m 80% XRP 15% BTC 5% SHIB&lt;br&gt;Might grab some SOL&lt;br&gt;I still think we have the rest of the year to steadily buy in though&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903700&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903210&lt;br&gt;Of course it is, OP and Mutt&amp;#x27;s Law&amp;#x27;ing is a 4chan past time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903824&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;if you insist on crypto consider a Blockchain tech ETF like IBLC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903827&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903106&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Started a small stack and staked it &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Enjoying the rewards and looking forward to halving&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903841&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903827&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903900&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903106&lt;br&gt;you are almost a &amp;quot;whole coiner&amp;quot; not many individuals out there have a whole coin.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;100% BTC at these prices.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903917&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903827&lt;br&gt;What platform tho&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903920&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903106&lt;br&gt;dog coin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904121&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903917&lt;br&gt;Are you retarded?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904438&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903106&lt;br&gt;can&amp;#x27;t go wrong with sol it&amp;#x27;ll lead heavy in the next leg maybe even outpeform eth&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904683&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903106&lt;br&gt;Why girls this pretty degrade themselves like this?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Who do you bank with? Do you ever have trouble withdrawing money or making transactions? Despite having more than enough… — 9 replies — 21.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61902223</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61902223?lm=1772089942</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 07:12:22 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Who do you bank with? Do you ever have trouble withdrawing money or making transactions? Despite having more than enough…&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61902223'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 9 • Updated: 2026-02-26 07:12 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Who do you bank with? Do you ever have trouble withdrawing money or making transactions?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite having more than enough funds, these fucking tangerine bank fags would decline my credit card transactions for online bills, resulting in interest on them.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;They also declined withdrawals at ATMs when I was in Asia despite my telling them I was traveling. Their solution? Come back to Canada to activate your card at a local ATM. FUCK YOU NIGGERS.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thank fuck I had Scotiabank cards, otherwise I wouldn&amp;#x27;t have cash there.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Any similar experiences/banks to AVOID?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902890&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902223&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902972&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902890&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bitcoin. No.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903889&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902972&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;one thousand dryspells stare&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903927&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;planned outage at midnight on New Years Eve&lt;br&gt;nothing personnel kid&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903997&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Discover bank, Chase, and CIT bank with about 30-35k between them all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904004&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902223&lt;br&gt;wealthsimple you stupid nigger. What is this, 2015?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904665&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904004&lt;br&gt;no it&amp;#x27;s 2024 or.. 2027? no umm. (help me bro)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904676&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902223&lt;br&gt;TD for debit and credit, Questrade TFSA. My card has always just werked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904677&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904665&lt;br&gt;don&amp;#x27;t listen to him wealthsimple is a scam&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>/PMG/ Vs. Janestreet — 4 replies — 16.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61904656</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61904656?lm=1772090743</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 07:25:43 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;/PMG/ Vs. Janestreet&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61904656'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 4 • Updated: 2026-02-26 07:25 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anon pointed this out here &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904592&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How badly does this fuck silver?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904680&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904656&lt;br&gt;Wm ethena cz trump and who knows what else.... Its a big club.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904684&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904656&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;How badly does this fuck silver&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jane Street Wikipedia Notable past employees:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Sam Bankman-Fried and Caroline Ellison, founders of FTX&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Brett Harrison, current CEO of trading technology firm Architect Financial Technologies&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Zvi Mowshowitz, writer who covers topics in artificial intelligence&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Ophelia Bauckholt, quantitative trader associated with the Zizian rationalists&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Man just looking at their founders notable history is nuts&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Jane Street faced scrutiny in June 2025 over its co-founder, Robert Granieri, facing allegations of funding an attempted coup against South Sudan by Ajak and Abraham Keech. The matter was resolved with no charges being brought against Granieri.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Either silver is fucked or going to be ok, all depends on if these globohomo transhumanist (((bankers))) finally lose. &lt;br&gt;So basically silver is fucked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904692&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904684&lt;br&gt;jane street is a quant trading firm, they are not investment bankers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904705&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Clearly went over your head. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anyway, I&amp;#x27;m sure they&amp;#x27;re all saying the same thing: &amp;quot;Let the goyim deal in the real world&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Art Finance — 14 replies — 46.6/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61904247</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61904247?lm=1772090402</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 07:20:02 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Art Finance&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61904247'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 14 • Updated: 2026-02-26 07:20 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Draw Fag Here, /biz/ what do you think about investing in art? NFT? Tax avoidance? What can I do to become one of the richest artist in the world?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904444&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;fine art is a tiny scene that you can only be born into.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904464&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904444&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s easier if you have jewish relations with the same pedophilic fantasies as you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904475&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904444&lt;br&gt;Quads of queer truth. It&amp;#x27;s their club, and you&amp;#x27;re not in it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904479&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904444&lt;br&gt;How to join the little club, I want to join?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904491&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Are you a real artist? Wanna come work with me making 3d models for creatures&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904496&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904491&lt;br&gt;I am an artist, working for you making 3D models, will that help m become one of the richest artist in the world? I am up for it. Any emails?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904501&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904479&lt;br&gt;Why do you think youre such a valuable asset for them to control?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904503&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904496&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s not something you could easily pick up in a day or even a month&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904507&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904501&lt;br&gt;Well, I do art, got a fine art diploma, 15 years of experience, and I live in one of the tax haven. Come on, let me join the little art club, I just want to enjoy some grape soda and eat some pizza while we look at some art exhibits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904511&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904503&lt;br&gt;You are right, I am a sculpture major, got a diploma for it. Well, who knows how long it will take to play around with the software.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904517&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904511&lt;br&gt;Just pickup zbrush and start making some shit. Highest skill for art is creatures and animating them studios always need good talent in this field in particular because it&amp;#x27;s harder to find. Most other things are a lot easier to model&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904586&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904517&lt;br&gt;It sounds like wage job that can be easily replaced by AI. I want to do fine arts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904588&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904586&lt;br&gt;Fair. It is the highest paying wage job for an artist at least though without hitting higher circles&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904691&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904588&lt;br&gt;I see, sounds like a trap.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Its LINK season — 50 replies — 34.1/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61900750</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61900750?lm=1772086198</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 06:09:58 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Its LINK season&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61900750'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 50 • Updated: 2026-02-26 06:09 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Act accordingly&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900759&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61900750&lt;br&gt;did the March larp was true?????&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900762&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This pump won&amp;#x27;t fail like all the others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900776&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;pump&amp;#x27;s already failed, stinkie&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901184&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61901021&lt;br&gt;yikes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901220&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61900987&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;$1 eoy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901638&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61900966&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901651&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61901638&lt;br&gt;From 2 more weeks &lt;br&gt;To now 1 more week &lt;br&gt;We&amp;#x27;re gonna make it lads.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901740&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61901142&lt;br&gt;sure thing champ&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901764&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61901638&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;hover between $10-$15&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;mfw Link has been sub $10 for more than a month already.&lt;br&gt;Link is dead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901786&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61901638&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61900759&lt;br&gt;holy shit Link cuckolds really believe the predictions made by an anonymous shitposter on biz. This is what 6 years of abysmal price performance does&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901793&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m gay and I hold Chainlink.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901796&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61901793&lt;br&gt;Actually im trans&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902234&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61901786&lt;br&gt;fuck stinkies xD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902307&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61901793&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61901796&lt;br&gt;excuse me I am bisexual&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902357&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;here comes the dump, stinkerinos. &lt;br&gt;it always ALWAYS ends the same way&lt;br&gt;and in a few months, you&amp;#x27;re at a lower price&lt;br&gt;playing the same game again&lt;br&gt;soon you&amp;#x27;ll be at $5 begging for that epic le pump to $6 xD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902426&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902357&lt;br&gt;microsecond charts, they are madling lmao&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902438&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61901165&lt;br&gt;Stay in your containment thread&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902952&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902426&lt;br&gt;4H chart, lying stinkie&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902961&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902426&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902357&lt;br&gt;If you want to see a real joke, check the 5 year chart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903055&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902961&lt;br&gt;You wanna see the real joke, look in the mirror you fucking clown.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903344&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903055&lt;br&gt;ad hominem attacks are not allowed here, stinkie&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903368&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I want to belieeeeeeeve&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903377&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61900759&lt;br&gt;well it just came out Jane Street has been intentionally surpressing price for months on end...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;right before we enter March..&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903386&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61901651&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;To now 1 more week&lt;br&gt;that post clearly states after march, so it is actually 5 more weeks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903396&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903377&lt;br&gt;that also explains the not complicated strategy but large resources part&lt;br&gt;jane streets method is to build large spot positions paired with equally large shorts so they remain market neutral&lt;br&gt;and then at a moment of market turmoil pull the rug out market dump the spot position force a retail fear route and cash in big on their shorts&lt;br&gt;really not complicated at all&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903428&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;pumped one whole dollar&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;already dumping&lt;br&gt;stink season&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903445&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sorry was there someone posting in this thread?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I didn&amp;#x27;t read it&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Guess I&amp;#x27;m not selling&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904468&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61900750&lt;br&gt;payment abstraction is buying all the link tokens off the market, hurry up&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904481&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;bitch i got that chainlink&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904485&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I need ro sell my stinkies, please provide exit liquidity&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904534&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;piece of shit can&amp;#x27;t even sustain a minor 15% pump&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m never getting out of this shitcoin, FUCK&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904571&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904534&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>ITT: We pretend we’re zoomers &gt;why does entry level require effort &gt;I applied once the market is rigged &gt;budgeting is ps… — 21 replies — 25.4/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61902847</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61902847?lm=1772088501</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 06:48:21 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;ITT: We pretend we’re zoomers &amp;gt;why does entry level require effort &amp;gt;I applied once the market is rigged &amp;gt;budgeting is ps…&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61902847'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 21 • Updated: 2026-02-26 06:48 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;ITT: We pretend we’re zoomers&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;why does entry level require effort&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I applied once the market is rigged&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;budgeting is psychological violence&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;why does my job expect output&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;compounding is a scam because it’s slow&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I can’t move cities my comfort zone is here&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;trades are beneath my potential&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;rent is high so saving is pointless&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I deserve a house because I’m tired&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;someone pivot the Fed for me&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902927&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I just Doordash some slop&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;my situationship just had another kid with Tyrone, on god&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;driving gives me anxiety &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I tried trauma bonding with my coworker over staying an hour late, but she ignored me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902957&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902927&lt;br&gt;The cuckolding and therapy speak are quintessential millennial though&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902973&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now it seems like zoomers have learned about cortisol and they&amp;#x27;re all talking about managing their cortisol when they feel uncomfortable or something&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902981&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Telling me to not Klarna my Doordash order is ableist sweatie&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903066&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;These are delicious! Want to try?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903252&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902847&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Work? Nah, I&amp;#x27;ll just NEET instead. Sorry, boomers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903611&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902847&lt;br&gt;Kek OP has such a slave mind he can&amp;#x27;t comprehend anything else. True goy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903626&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I applied once the market is rigged&lt;br&gt;8/10 bait, got me to reply.&lt;br&gt;https://www.forbes.com/sites/carolinecastrillon/2025/11/18/youre-not-bad-at-job-hunting-30-of-job-postings-are-fake/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903639&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902847&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; I don&amp;#x27;t have a degree&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; I don&amp;#x27;t have any marketable skills&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; I&amp;#x27;m high all day, and thats ok because its LeGaL&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; Why can&amp;#x27;t I find a job that pays more than minimum wage&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903668&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902847&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I fear I ate with my cover letter &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;No but why did the interview lowk get my ass&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903672&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903639&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; I don&amp;#x27;t have a degree &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; I don&amp;#x27;t have any marketable skills &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; I&amp;#x27;m high all day, and thats ok because its LeGaL &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I found a job that allows me to buy multiple houses, raise 10 kids, survive through three divorces with enough money to spare to buy a fifth boat cuz I&amp;#x27;m a baby boomer&lt;br&gt;Day of the pillow, when?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903681&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903672&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m not a boomer doe so have at it. Total boomer death cannot come soon enough.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903702&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903639&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I don&amp;#x27;t have 3 unpaid internships and 12 certifications and I said hello on the phone in the wrong way&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903734&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903702&lt;br&gt;Thats a good thing. Kek imagine working for that cunt and having to navigate the mine field every time you open your mouth. You WANT those types to reject you&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903744&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903734&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s not good when they are gatekeeping every single white collar position.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903751&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903744&lt;br&gt;Only in large orgs. Why are you determined to work for a large org? They are homogeneous by design&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904562&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902847&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;why work? boomers had $2/hour cashier jobs and were rewarded with stay-at-home wives and 6-bedroom homes for their 4 children&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;i don&amp;#x27;t have that many subscriptions, just netflix, amazon prime, spotify, youtube premium (i don&amp;#x27;t know how to install adblock), oh and dashpass because it like gives me a discount on my food i buy at 300% markup&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;our generation is based, we don&amp;#x27;t drink alcohol (pops a zyn before hitting the vape pen)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904575&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is really pathetic. I hope you&amp;#x27;re at least rich, married and have a kid&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Redpil me on the Florida and Broader US Housing Market — 23 replies — 12.6/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891078</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891078?lm=1772084903</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 05:48:23 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Redpil me on the Florida and Broader US Housing Market&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891078'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 23 • Updated: 2026-02-26 05:48 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt; I&amp;#x27;m an anon nearing 40, saved appropriately&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; Finally at a stage to buy an investment property, ideally a condo / box in the sky&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; Looking into Jupiter, Florida&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; &amp;quot;Whoa, this condo was built after 2005, and the ask is $400K for 1200 square feet in a prime shopping area&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; Insurance comes out to $4-500 per month&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; HOAs from $300-800 per month in this market&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; Property taxes are eliminated?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; Cape Coral is literally a firesale&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; Bake in a 8% vacancy rate&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; Plus some maintenance&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; I would have to charge $5,000 a month to break even? WTF&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What is going on anons? What are you seeing out there? Would it be more prudent to invest in the Northeast (VT, NH, ME?) Is anyone doing okayish on investment income on a single family? What has been your experience?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891143&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891078&lt;br&gt;As a shareholder I look down on landlord parasites. Invest in making people&amp;#x27;s lives better by providing a product/service, not holding people&amp;#x27;s living space hostage&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891189&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891078&lt;br&gt;You don&amp;#x27;t understand math or taxes which is why you&amp;#x27;re 40 and homeless&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891197&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891078&lt;br&gt;why?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892463&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891143&lt;br&gt;The more independent landlords there are, the more it decentralizes power from larger corporations like Blackrock&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891189&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m doing very well&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891197&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m already invested into stocks, and precious metals. Now would be the time to invest in real estate&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895578&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891078&lt;br&gt;Economics aside Cape Coral is a bit of a meme.&lt;br&gt;The Cape is what would happen if you had an idea guy design a city and that idea is to just chop up everything with canals.&lt;br&gt;(Not a great idea, you’re still going to be driving everywhere 90% of the time and the canals just make the road layout 3x worse than a normal city)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61897144&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891078&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; ideally a condo / box in the sky&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; Insurance comes out to $4-500 per month&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; HOAs from $300-800 per month in this market&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; I would have to charge $5,000 a month to break even? WTF&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Invest in multiplexes, don&amp;#x27;t limit yourself to a single location, and NEVER be negative cashflow. If it doesn&amp;#x27;t cashflow, you don&amp;#x27;t buy it. This should be obvious.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61897152&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891078&lt;br&gt;Do you guys think the next big hurricane will be the straw that breaks the camel&amp;#x27;s back? There hasn&amp;#x27;t been a real bad one to his a high population center in Florida in awhile. The latest ones were mild, even the one the wrecked north Carolina&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61897153&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This whole state sinks with 5 meters of sea level rise most roads go immediately out of comission. Biggest meme state ever&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61897155&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;$5k a month&lt;br&gt;sounds about right.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61897915&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891078&lt;br&gt;I live in florida and how is the insurance 4500 a month for a condo? how old is the building?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;ref im at around 7k a year on ins and hoa for house is 200 a month&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61897153&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;if the oceans raise 15ft its over&lt;br&gt;well no shit anon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61897987&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61897155&lt;br&gt;Comparable rents are like $1,800-3,200 maximum. And if you go into the MLS, landlord have been chopping their asking rent prices constantly, and still no bites.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61897155&lt;br&gt;I said $4-500 as in $400-500 per month. You said get charged $7,000 a year on insurance, so that&amp;#x27;s $583 per month, which is about what I would expect. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61897153&lt;br&gt;At this point, it seems like the &amp;quot;VSTAX and chill&amp;quot; meme is where it&amp;#x27;s at.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898594&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891078&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Would it be more prudent to invest in the Northeast&lt;br&gt;Yes, Florida is designed to extract as much wealth from boomers as possible. There are ways to take advantage of this but buying boomer bags is not one of them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898758&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891078&lt;br&gt;Almost nothing is cashflowing. Maybe some Airbnbs but few and far between. Rents are too low for the cost of loans right now. Either interest or property values go down, or rents go up, but I don&amp;#x27;t seerent going up.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898594&lt;br&gt;This. You&amp;#x27;re supposed to take money from boomers, not give it to them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899686&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891078&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891078&lt;br&gt;As a florida anon: FL real estate is such a scam nowadays. Maybe it always has been.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For your example, it&amp;#x27;s because the HOA reserves need to be maximized and not gutted, alongside property insurance within the state has now 300-500x+ since Helene and the past decade of storms. Combined with global warming, warmer waters in atlantic/gulf=stronger hurricanes, and ocean level increasing + most of FL property is under sea level so flood zone. It&amp;#x27;s practically had me leave the state. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you so desire the FL lifestyle, an old block house with 5000sq ft+ land is the way to go, not in a flood zone makes it every affordable even if it isn&amp;#x27;t a coastal/near beach, it&amp;#x27;s just not worth the price point. I&amp;#x27;ve relocated to Seattle and then Tokyo and my rent and mortgage are 1:1 in Seattle, if not cheaper there, where in JPland it&amp;#x27;s half, literally, 50% USA price. I was fortunate to profit during 08-16, but nowadays, cheaper to rent and leave the bag holders in FL. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Then the tenants suck in FL, while strong landlord laws, the tenants are shit, the handyman are worse and to repair and such will be a hassle. ergo it&amp;#x27;s fun to fuck with landlords, you can literally negotiate that you&amp;#x27;d leave after a month with no other penalty, just make sure to close those utilities anon. t. floridian4lyfe.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61897987&lt;br&gt;VSTAX is where it’s at, if you&amp;#x27;re a pussy, vanguard or swvvx is okay too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900797&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Use ai to comb census data. Florida has 900 zip codes but 20 are 100% white. That&amp;#x27;s where you buy property. You can get up to 4 units on an FHA loan. Bonus points if it&amp;#x27;s a little cafe or bakery downtown with apartments above it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901094&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891078&lt;br&gt;You’re better off parking your cash in an REIT and yielding 7% than doing this shit. Insurance is extremely high, HOA fees are enormous, and boomers are greedy. Market has to adjust for that bullshit before it becomes profitable again&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901644&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898758&lt;br&gt;This is what I&amp;#x27;ve surmised.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61899686&lt;br&gt;A friend of mine is convinced Miami is on the come-up with companies relocating here. But at the end of the day, Miami doesn&amp;#x27;t have jobs, and the quality of people is retard level. Money doesn&amp;#x27;t mitigate the retardedness unfortunately.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61900797&lt;br&gt;Median age in this zip codes is in the 70s basically.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61901094&lt;br&gt;Absolutely, I think investing nowadays in Florida is simply buying yourself a headache.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901707&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If the condo is over 3 floors I think it must pass some assessment and if it doesn&amp;#x27;t you are fucked. Any special assessment will moon your HOA. Maybe that was what the newer build date implies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The insurance will be fucked next time a storm hits somewhere other than the empty stretch between Panama City and Tampa/St. Pete. Japan I think backstops FL Citizen&amp;#x27;s insurance. After that, the law says the state can assrape anyone with home insurance to make themselves whole.&lt;br&gt;I rent an old shitbox. I sold a condo in May. &lt;br&gt;If you have a relative who wants to move to Florida and you can have them cover mortgage, property tax for something non-homestead-exempted, HOA, etc and you live in the Northern tier near a major airport, especially NYC zone, and you have the money to shoot down on some Winter weekends, maybe.&lt;br&gt;Otherwise, fuck no.&lt;br&gt;Now if you can buy a place in BFE inland North Florida cash with a well and solar and water frontage and enough land to kill and eat hogs, and you like that, maybe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901751&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61901644&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s &amp;quot;headquarters&amp;quot; moving to Miami. Ben Shapiro sent the staff to Trashville, Inbredessee and he is in Boca Raton.&lt;br&gt;Miami is LA/NYC prices with Havana wages. It&amp;#x27;s also fraud central. Any downturn and the place takes a gigantic shit, because everything is borrowed and leveraged to the hilt.&lt;br&gt;Miami has New York City&amp;#x27;s courtesy and pace, Florida&amp;#x27;s intellectual curiosity, and Latin American punctuality and work ethic.&lt;br&gt;The left lane is slap full of immigrants driving slow as fuck. Check out the video of the macho culture faggot in the passing lane getting passed on the right who pulls iron, flinches as his limp wrist wildly shoots in heavy traffic because someone passed him.&lt;br&gt;Florida is a penis and Miami is the foreskin cheese.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904193&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61897144&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;multiplexes&lt;br&gt;I would, rent out the other unit(s) until the one year ticks down for me to be able to let them all, the issue is that it&amp;#x27;s like 700k for a shitbox that&amp;#x27;s going to turn into a flooded pile of toothpicks come the first hurricane&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;d rather just press the buy button on more reits than have to interact with faggy duplicitous real estate agents, retarded trashy tenants, boneheaded hvac repairmen tradies, etc, etc&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904206&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891078&lt;br&gt;florida is literally hell on earth. i would rather live in north fucking korea. since money is the root of all evil, you will probably make quite a bit of profit by investing in Florida&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904308&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61901751&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;immigrants in the left lane&lt;br&gt;Unfortunately i think these stupid faggots are all white retirees and midwestern transplants. i fucking cant stand how slow these subhumans drive. I prefer the wildness of I-95&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904535&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891078&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;[GC Intensifies]&lt;br&gt;you will never 10X&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>STOP CHANGING THE FUCKING CAPTCHA HOLY FUCKING SHIT THERE IS NO WAY IN HELL THERE IS THAT MANY SOPHISTICATED BOTS TRYING… — 34 replies — 11.6/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61903606</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61903606?lm=1772080909</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 04:41:49 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;STOP CHANGING THE FUCKING CAPTCHA HOLY FUCKING SHIT THERE IS NO WAY IN HELL THERE IS THAT MANY SOPHISTICATED BOTS TRYING…&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61903606'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 34 • Updated: 2026-02-26 04:41 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;STOP CHANGING THE FUCKING CAPTCHA HOLY FUCKING SHIT THERE IS NO WAY IN HELL THERE IS THAT MANY SOPHISTICATED BOTS TRYING TO POST ON THIS SHITSTAIN OF A SITE&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903631&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903606&lt;br&gt;some of the new ones are actually impossible&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903655&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903631&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903606&lt;br&gt;buy a 4chan pass.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903663&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903631&lt;br&gt;Beep boop clanker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903666&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;they&amp;#x27;re not hard, it&amp;#x27;s just excessive. it&amp;#x27;s like they don&amp;#x27;t want people to post here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903670&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903606&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903631&lt;br&gt;niggerbrained chromosome hoarders&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903682&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I got range banned yesterday on my home wifi for some odd (((reason))) &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;please verify email &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;4chan pass&lt;br&gt;what the fuck&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903726&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maybe it&amp;#x27;s a midwit filter because I find them extremely easy&lt;br&gt;T. Left curver&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903740&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903670&lt;br&gt;fuck off&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903750&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903740&lt;br&gt;topleft as the other 3 all have the white square on an outside bit while the topleft has the white one in the middle bit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903752&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903740&lt;br&gt;i clicked the first one and it failed btw&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903779&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903740&lt;br&gt;If you can&amp;#x27;t rotate a shape in your head you shouldn&amp;#x27;t be in control of your own finances.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903792&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903664&lt;br&gt;The dozen arrow one is a good filter. You gotta think about it in a step wise fashion and not just singularly&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903799&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The one with the tetris pieces is pure aids&lt;br&gt;The rest are okay&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903800&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903779&lt;br&gt;i&amp;#x27;m going to rape you&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903819&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903740&lt;br&gt;you need to have IQ &amp;gt; 70 to start threads here&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903821&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903740&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;IQ test to keep jeets and niggers away.&lt;br&gt;Based.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903822&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903800&lt;br&gt;Homo lala boy confirmed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903838&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903606&lt;br&gt;phone posters never have anything good to say&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903873&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;catchpa difficulty should be proportionate to post volume per board&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903902&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;sure smells like shitty jeets in here&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903906&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903606&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903631&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;impossible&lt;br&gt;Get filtered, retards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903915&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903740&lt;br&gt;Fuck off with that shit. Crypto is over and i don&amp;#x27;t care about metal faggots shilling their bags.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903962&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903606&lt;br&gt;I literally paid to stop seeing ads they won&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904184&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903606&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just tried the captcha and it isn&amp;#x27;t bad.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904190&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903606&lt;br&gt;Opus 4.6 can&amp;#x27;t be stopped by the captcha anyway&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904240&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903666&lt;br&gt;This website is in controlled demolition for years. Did you know if you have a pass they link a ban to it? You can&amp;#x27;t just reset your IP, a janny can actually steal your pass time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904269&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904240&lt;br&gt;You can just log out first&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904280&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Skill issue&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904297&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To be honest, it seems like post quality has increased a lot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904353&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903655&lt;br&gt;No the mods started stalking me across boards and harassing me fuck ‘em&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904356&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904280&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Skill issue&lt;br&gt;Reddit post&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904372&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903606&lt;br&gt;FUCKING AGREED HOLY FUCK&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904391&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;make them even harder&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Anyone else getting the itch? — 22 replies — 10.7/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61899833</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61899833?lm=1772084049</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 05:34:09 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Anyone else getting the itch?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61899833'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 22 • Updated: 2026-02-26 05:34 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The big boys&amp;#x27;ll go back up, that&amp;#x27;s guaranteed money. But some others will 10x, 100x, 1000x. I&amp;#x27;m feelin&amp;#x27; like it&amp;#x27;s SHIB&amp;#x27;s turn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900851&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61899833&lt;br&gt;Checked&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900872&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61899833&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;ll just keep buying small amounts of it for the rest of my life, and see what happens.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900948&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61899833&lt;br&gt;i believe in shib&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900953&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61900948&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61900872&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61900851&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61899833&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900999&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61899833&lt;br&gt;Toshi is the king of the next cycle &lt;br&gt;It’s Base season, bitch&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901257&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is now a TOAD thread&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901298&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61901257&lt;br&gt;This.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901324&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Perfect time to rank up and join the TOAD army&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901689&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Only real ass pedophile glow niggas buy and pump toad killer up to billions of dollars market cap. This is the official gay furry pedo jewish mafia token of the next meme coin season. Buy now or cry later.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901710&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wen&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901769&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61901710&lt;br&gt;2030&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901771&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61899833&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;ve been slurping&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901780&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61901769&lt;br&gt;That’s not that far away&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901902&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61899833&lt;br&gt;Not pumping your shit token&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;not becoming your exit liquidity&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901925&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61901780&lt;br&gt;Yes it is it&amp;#x27;s too far away I think most of us will be dead by then&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902754&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;My boomer dad bought $35k worth of shib about 8 months ago despite me advising against it, he’s down like 60%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902821&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902754&lt;br&gt;Doubtful.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903181&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902754&lt;br&gt;Tell him to hodl&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903489&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oh Lord, please let SHIB go to $0.01 this year&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904243&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903489&lt;br&gt;Not happening. What is going to happen though is toad killer will flip pepe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904434&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61899833&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904495&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904243&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;toad killer will flip pepe.&lt;br&gt;Its was programmed nearly 3 years ago but they’ll say we got lucky and perhaps we did. Right place, right time&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Mac minis are the new ASIC miners — 63 replies — 9.7/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61893434</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61893434?lm=1772067981</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:21 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Mac minis are the new ASIC miners&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61893434'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 63 • Updated: 2026-02-26 01:06 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mac minis are like the ASIC miners except they do actual work instead of mining bitcoin for no reason.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893585&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893434&lt;br&gt;What are people even doing with their 50 mac mini AI agents?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893611&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893585&lt;br&gt;Its like a team of 50 indians&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893612&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893611&lt;br&gt;Just imagine the sound of 50 echoing good morning sirs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895922&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895888&lt;br&gt;These ARE running local models, that&amp;#x27;s the entire point of using MacMinis and unified RAM. Whether the Minis will survive the experience, is another issue entirely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896004&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895757&lt;br&gt;Interesting. &lt;br&gt;Mine kept saying im trans. Kek! &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; sadface.jpg&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896011&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894156&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;give the mac mini all of my personal info, financial data, passwords, internet browsing history etc.&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s a personal computer. It already has all of those things.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896031&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895820&lt;br&gt;Yes that’s pretty much it. Although it did help me diagnose leaky gut issues and initially helped with some supplements, but then it started telling me to basically OD on magnesium and electrolytes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896090&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894238&lt;br&gt;Rent it to people that are scared of running it locally or too stupid to figure it out.&lt;br&gt;Stuff like this https://seafloor.bot/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896126&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Basically in the future everyone will have their own personal agentic AI, and these people are hosting them while its still hard to get it set up.&lt;br&gt;This isnt a sustainable business model tho, because its only a matter of time before soke big company like google starts doing it with infinitely more success because they actually have all the data from everyone, so the AI assistant will come out of factory already knowing you better than you know yourself.&lt;br&gt;But it will be profitable probably for a 1 or 2. I dont see this stuff getting released by a big company before its tested enough to ensure most of the nightmarish stories being reported about openclaw have a close to 0% chance of happening.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896174&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893434&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;they do actual work&lt;br&gt;how much money has your agent made?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896193&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895922&lt;br&gt;No they aren&amp;#x27;t. They&amp;#x27;re just a bunch of iToddlers who can&amp;#x27;t into Raspberry Pi or Linux.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896922&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61896126&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;knowing you better than you know yourself&lt;br&gt;it&amp;#x27;s actually pretty hard to personalize large language models, so dont expect the same behaviour as you have from your tiktok or youtube algorithm&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896954&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;this is pure retardium. the minis are not running shit. they can&amp;#x27;t run any models, and anyways open models are not worth running, they&amp;#x27;re dumb as rocks&lt;br&gt;openclaw uses api to run, claude because it&amp;#x27;s the only one that can do shit. the fattest claude (the only able one) can burn hundreds of $$$ per day. and you don&amp;#x27;t need a mac mini for it. you can just run it on the cloud or in a virtual machine. it&amp;#x27;s really lean on resources - you just need to pay a lot of money for the api&lt;br&gt;dumb. all of it is just dumb&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896995&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895757&lt;br&gt;Must be a canadian llm, MAID GPT.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61897015&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61896193&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s the same software. If you can&amp;#x27;t into linux then you definitely can&amp;#x27;t into macos. Both start up into a first class GUI and both require you to drop to the command line to install LLM shit because that&amp;#x27;s how the software works. Ollama front ends not withstanding.&lt;br&gt;Hell, raspi clusters are easy mode because it far easier to find a prebaked recipe you can copy/paste to get it all running whereas mac users have to deal with retards hardcoding paths and cuda bullshit into their workflows.&lt;br&gt;That said there is some retardation going on with the mac buying. Macs are the sane choice because they are the absolute cheapest way to get more than 64GB with GPU access to that pool. Your 128GB of DDR5 and a xeon doesn&amp;#x27;t compare. Buying a joblot of 16GB mac minis is defeating the purpose though.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61897157&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895163&lt;br&gt;correct&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895732&lt;br&gt;wrong. AMD GPUs out on price to performance ratios for AI as long as you have enough IQ to configure rocm kernel&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61897160&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61897157&lt;br&gt;*AMD GPUs win out&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898771&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61897157&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;ll believe it when I see it. A PC with enough VRAM on the GPU to beat mac, I don&amp;#x27;t think it works. Plus that pc has to do offloading.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899637&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893699&lt;br&gt;Computer engineer here:&lt;br&gt;The thing that makes the M chips a game-changer is that they use AI to accelerate AI workloads. The result? AI squared. This has been the holy grail of the mac mini’s eye-watering efficiency. I guarantee you that in five years, every AI PC on the market will use AI to accelerate its AI accelerator for AI. AI cubed, if you will.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899711&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893434&lt;br&gt;who else running stealth asics hidden in the attic at their office? place is full of dumb cunts that wouldn&amp;#x27;t even find it if i told them it was there&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899788&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898771&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895922&lt;br&gt;Nonsense. Mac unified memory is slow because it has low memory bandwidth which is very important for fast inference.&lt;br&gt;Offloading is not a needed when you have real GPUs with 96-256GB memory capacity.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Minis are good for single core tasks (python/js) and ARM is power efficient so I guess it&amp;#x27;s suited for API agents. Local LLMs are worse for most tasks anyway.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899789&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61896192&lt;br&gt;This has been the case for both crypto and AI, but at least the latter is useful for most people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899866&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895191&lt;br&gt;i use a local LLM to write passable warhammer fantasy stories for me&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899869&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61899637&lt;br&gt;e = mc^2 + AI&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900078&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61899788&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Local LLMs are worse for most tasks anyway.&lt;br&gt;What are they good for?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900675&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895163&lt;br&gt;Its almost entirely about ram costs. A single mac studio with 512 gb of unified memory can run a monster of a local AI set up. Hundreds of billions of parameters. To build a PC with 512 gb of vram is basically impossible, so you are stuck using less efficient 512gb ddr5 + CPU set ups for twice the price and half the performance. Mac studio/mini is the ideal locally hosted AI machine by a wide margin, both price and performance wise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900701&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61896193&lt;br&gt;This is the opinion of poor brainlets. MacOS is unix based. The GUI is set up for normies and retards, so they cant fuck anything up, but the terminal is pretty much identical to a linux terminal in both function and syntax. Local AI set ups like openclaw and ollama require use of the terminal to set up currently. That means anyone who has set up a locally hosted agentic AI on a mac likely knows the linux terminal better than you do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900832&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61897157&lt;br&gt;People here are genius-level retards.&lt;br&gt;The technical bottleneck for real-world autonomous agent usage isn&amp;#x27;t raw speed (tokens per second). The actual bottleneck is realistically supportable model size and ability to support many simultaneous agents with tooling coordinating together. If you&amp;#x27;re running automation 24/7, you don&amp;#x27;t care if an individual task takes a few seconds, minutes, or sometimes even hours longer: you care that the model you&amp;#x27;re running is smart enough to solve your tasks successfully in a reasonable amount of time. This means fitting into some kind of RAM, even if it&amp;#x27;s not the fastest RAM available.&lt;br&gt;Now of course, if you&amp;#x27;re an autist and want to add a few server racks in your house, you could theoretically build a larger and far faster system with rocm. But the setup for that isn&amp;#x27;t trivial, you either need to find a way to stuff a pile of expensive power-hungry GPUs into one machine to get as much RAM as a Mac Mini/Studio has or build some kind of cluster (which is itself a big headache). Either you&amp;#x27;re stuck doing it over Ethernet (a bottleneck which reduces the speed advantage your system has, versus it being nearly trivial to use the far faster Thunderbolt to build a small Mac cluster if you want to) or you need to spend literally tens of thousands of dollars on some kind of Infiniband setup. The unified system memory approach of the Macs (even if it&amp;#x27;s slower than VRAM) means that a local setup you have could be much smarter as it&amp;#x27;s realistic to build a significantly larger memory setup. It&amp;#x27;s easier to have in your house (try justifying to your wife that you want a few server racks setup somewhere) versus a Mac Studio or two that you can hide under the corner of your desk.&lt;br&gt;I haven&amp;#x27;t even gotten to the part about literally paying thousands of dollars more per year in electricity costs for such a setup over the Mac equivalent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900903&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61900701&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;MacOS is unix based.&lt;br&gt;MacOS is literally Unix and has a much better claim on that title than Linux, which is rightfully often called &amp;quot;unix-like&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900925&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61900903&lt;br&gt;Born Again SHell (Bash) is the standardization mechanism between the two.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900928&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895163&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;with current RAM prices and how scarce GPU&amp;#x27;s with decent VRAM&lt;br&gt;The bubble is already popping. I just saw a headline yesterday that one of the big AI scams has cut back its expected datacenter buildout shekels from $1.4 trillion to $600 billion.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Expect to see a lot more of that. They can&amp;#x27;t even get the electrical power, and no, &amp;quot;small modular nuclear reactors&amp;quot; aren&amp;#x27;t going to magically appear and get approved in the next six months (or even five years) to solve that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903775&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893611&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Its like a team of 50 indians&lt;br&gt;So the mac mini&amp;#x27;s smell?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>There are people on this site right now posting about XRP and don’t even know this. — 12 replies — 9.2/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61904399</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61904399?lm=1772086772</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 06:19:32 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;There are people on this site right now posting about XRP and don’t even know this.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61904399'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 12 • Updated: 2026-02-26 06:19 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are people on this site right now posting about XRP and don’t even know this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904404&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904399&lt;br&gt;price? and chart?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904416&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904404&lt;br&gt;I can spoonfeed but I’m not giving a baby a dummy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904469&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Well biz? You have researched the next Sol right?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904494&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904469&lt;br&gt;I’m not sure I’m seeing it anon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904499&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;XRP can literally execute trillions of tps using interledger (limited only by hardware engineering), capable of micropayment batching. TPS is not the hard limit win condition you think it is and literally any network can achieve absurdly high tps if willing to sacrifice security, decentralization, compliance, any shred of programmability etc. Just ask Nano, which catastrophically failed leading to all the operators abandoning it and the founders and team opportunistically using the moment to exit scam with the exchange that blocked withdrawal or sale while both publicly messaged that everything was fine and dumped. Solana is also on there and it had multiple total crashes within a few months and when the big hack happened, clawed back the assets, which is great for specific holders but meaningless to non-whales and evidence of extreme centralization. ICP is a ghost chain. ALGO is great and will probably thrive in a niche RWA but lost major opportunity because it focused on brand deals and events while solana focused on literally washing and faking volume and juicing pump and dump meme volume that builds and means nothing, to sell it to institutions and governments showing them the fake adoption and volume. ALGO through sheerly superior tech should have a substantial share of what solana has, particularly the Ondo inclusion, but had poor marketing. If they marketed better and if the market in general and those apprising it weren&amp;#x27;t so given to fake and gay activity it would be doing well and the world would do better through its success than sol&amp;#x27;s with actual decentralization thriving.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904504&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904494&lt;br&gt;Chain inspect doesn’t lie. It’s early so ofc it doesn’t have huge vol…yet. TPS isn’t even the biggest story if Keeta. Eric Schmidt is an investor, it anchors to tradfi. Banks are coming. Keeta also literaly bought a bank. KYC on chain. Partnered with Google and rumors of VISA even. 120m mc. Already listed on CB and Kraken.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904510&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904499&lt;br&gt;I bought XRP at literally .001 You aren’t early. Enjoy a 2x I guess. Keeta will do what XRP couldn’t. This board is a Reddit XRP psyop. Clearly it’s so the devs can extract from retail plebs. I’m actually helping you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904549&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904510&lt;br&gt;I bought XRP early also. Keeta can&amp;#x27;t do anything, has none of the compliance features institutions require which XRP has at a protocol level, has no liquidity, no built institutional rails or infrastructure level companies (like a fucking prime dealer) geared to specifically drive its adoption as optimally as possible with its parent company owning a majority of its corporate treasury in the asset. Keeta has nothing but a testnet tps count that again literally any shitty network could accomplish easily if that was all they cared about. Why has no single other network on the chart chosen to do this? It&amp;#x27;s not like Keeta is a breakthrough next gen evolution in DLT, it is just a shitcoin with a single attribute gimmick and a team that is either trying to pump and dump or too technically or tradfi system illiterate to know this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904573&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904499&lt;br&gt;Are you trying to pretend xrp is decentralized? Lol nigga you cant even explore the genesis block. Xrp is the ultimate centralized scamcoin if you wanna talk shit on other coins for being centralized&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904579&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904504&lt;br&gt;Keeta 11M TPS was a synthetic Google Cloud stress test. They are not Google partnered. Lol Eric Schmidt led a raise of like 20 million. Keeta didn&amp;#x27;t literally buy a bank and no other banks are coming. They have not closed on the bank. Ripple on the other hand have a national bank charter and are pending approval for a Fed master account they are likely to get at least a skinny version of with the Fed having dropped the reputation policy a few days ago, and have 300 bank partners already and are partnered with PSPs connecting tens of thousands of banks and billions of individual wallets. They have the prime brokerage that settles trillions per year, custody for majority top banks, are on the White House&amp;#x27;s reference board through the CFTC, are partnered with multiple Fednow core service providers (Finastra, Volante, etc.) a handful of which RUN XRP NODES, they are a platinum member of the American Bankers Association. They are also a member of the Federal Reserve&amp;#x27;s Faster Payments Task Force (only crypto company), the Bank for International Settlements&amp;#x27; Crossborder Payments Interoperability and Extension Taskforce (only crypto company), the International Monetary Fund&amp;#x27;s High Level Advisory Group on Fintech, an ISDA (International Swaps and Derivatives Association) member (only public token promoting company), the ISO 20022 Registration Management Group (only crypto company, responsible for developing and overseeing the entire new financial messaging standard in the ISO 20022 messaging era), the Faster Payments Council ((industry standards and process governing body, only non-stablecoin crypto company-just look who their other members are, the Digital Dollar Project, the Digital Pound Foundation, the Digital Euro Association (only crypto company that is a member of all three), the Digital Chamber of Commerce, the only non-stablecoin crypto company on their High Level Advisory Group on Fintech. This is just a handful of stuff, could literally go on for pages.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904584&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904573&lt;br&gt;XRP IS decentralized. The genesis block is irrelevant to XRP&amp;#x27;s consensus. You literally just know 10% of how bitcoin (WHICH HAD A FULL CHAIN REORG) works and think this is how all DLTs work. Because the bitcoin community was nuked by normies. It was designed to be a p2p payment system. Satoshi NEVER talked about the &amp;quot;store of value,&amp;quot; it was supposed to be an open medium of exchange. Bitcoin pumped and was subverted by glowniggers and late normies who turned it into a greed cult of people who don&amp;#x27;t understand their own technology they are obsessed with the success of for greed they pretend to be principle and it is built to be trojan horse centralization that sells itself on L1 principles but literally requires shitty turbo-centralized L2s to be 1/100th as fast or cost efficient. It is also obviously less of an opportunity because the juice is already so squeezed. Same for eth largely, which got the regulatory free pass and corporatist carry that will come back to bite it because Nerayofff is a hero and they tried to throw him in prison but he is an autist and BTFO&amp;#x27;d multiple government agencies having the judge declare them as acting in bad faith and he is exposing it all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904587&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904510&lt;br&gt;Is Keeta Sharia compliant?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>