<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>/biz/ Active (filtered, with replies)</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/</link><description>Filtered out: general, gme, bbbyq. OP + first 3 replies + last 30 replies.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 16:00:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Buy Gold ASAP and stay away from Silver. — 22 replies — 88.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890123</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890123?lm=1771862096</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:54:56 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Buy Gold ASAP and stay away from Silver.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890123'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 22 • Updated: 2026-02-23 15:54 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gold will skyrocket when Trump bombs Iran.&lt;br&gt;Kikes and Glowies advertising the silver scam.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890127&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890123&lt;br&gt;Begone jew&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890130&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890123&lt;br&gt;You must be a zogbot trying to keep the goyim away from holding silver which is an essential component of milspec electronics, batteries, radars, primary explosives and so on. There&amp;#x27;s approximately 500 ounces of silver in every tomahawk cruise missile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890139&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890123&lt;br&gt;There are 90 tonnes of silver in a blackhawk tank you filthy jew!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890143&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890127&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890130&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Silver has no real value because it can be corroded.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;There&amp;#x27;s no central bank around the world who buys silver. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KKKXVTZAk9s&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890147&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890127&lt;br&gt;Love this execution tool that killed the criminal Jew. Christianity is a Jewish psyop&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890156&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890147&lt;br&gt;Another jew&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890159&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890147&lt;br&gt;Its the real world™, everything is a jewish psyop.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890169&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890147&lt;br&gt;best post&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890273&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890143&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;There&amp;#x27;s no central bank around the world who buys silver.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890280&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890273&lt;br&gt;All of that metal that should be used for electronics, stored in vaults because jews are retarded dwarven larping faggots.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890289&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890273&lt;br&gt;those are chicken eggs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890290&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890123&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;buy the generational top&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890293&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890290&lt;br&gt;the return to normal of the gen top.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890304&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890273&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;There&amp;#x27;s no central bank around the world who buys silver.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is how Gold is stored in Russia.&lt;br&gt;I hope you understand the difference.&lt;br&gt;Silver is a shitty common metal that can be easily found.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890403&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890273&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;pallets &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;No way this is actually Russian&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890408&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They are both going to go up this year. Gold because it has always been a hedge against geo-political instability and de-dollarisation, and silver because it is so obviously being suppressed and is running out of supply in March. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m in gold personally as it&amp;#x27;s less volatile, I don&amp;#x27;t want to deal with the stress of silver.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890455&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Please buy chinks and ivans same asset re-leveraged ponzi bag to make line go up so the collateral doesnt devalue&lt;br&gt;niet. Russia is going to lose 75% of its population, china likely up to 90%. Enjoy the cannibalism&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890470&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890123&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890581&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;OP destroyed in one image&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890792&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890143&lt;br&gt;retard&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890810&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890143&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;because it can be corroded&lt;br&gt;That&amp;#x27;s just wrong. Silver doesn&amp;#x27;t corrode.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890911&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890810&lt;br&gt;it can if it remain for a very long time (at least few centuries) in seawater. Silver is chalcophile while gold is siderophile (like all platinum group metals). Silver doesn&amp;#x27;t react much to anything, but still more than gold, who react to nothing but aqua regia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Link vs XRP — 19 replies — 76.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889600</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889600?lm=1771861764</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:49:24 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Link vs XRP&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889600'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 19 • Updated: 2026-02-23 15:49 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;When will the gap close? Link came within a hair of flipping xrp in January ‘21. We all know that Link is everything Xrp fraudulently claims to be so it makes sense that this chart should flip soon enough. Will it be gradual or violent? Will it flip because xrp crashes or because Link moons? &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most importantly where are some places you can use Link as collateral to borrow Xrp to take full advantage of the trade of the century?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889606&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m so tired.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889622&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889600&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889606&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889620&lt;br&gt;Link is scam&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Buy XRP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889634&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889606&lt;br&gt;Xrp is like chainlink if all the nightmares came true: no use case, no revenue, an ipo that formally cuts token holders out of the picture etc.. and we need over a 10x to reach their market cap. This fact always gives me energy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889799&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889634&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889823&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889600&lt;br&gt;It won&amp;#x27;t. Even RLUSD will pass link&amp;#x27;s marketcap in a matter of a few months.You invested poorly in a project with the only purpose of jewishly injecting fees for literally no reason and assuming people will allow you to entrench in core services. It is a bad financial and moral investment&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889827&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889634&lt;br&gt;XRP had no ICO. Link sells to retail at every pump and drains operator rewards it claimed it wouldn&amp;#x27;t. Link has literally zero use case outside arbitrary jewish rent seeking crypto toll boothing. It solves no problem and has no use outside ADDING frictions. XRP from Ripple alone has: &lt;br&gt;https://ripple.com/insights/institutional-defi-on-xrpl-scaling-real-world-finance-with-xrp-at-the-core/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889841&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889600&lt;br&gt;not gonna happen, jews will reward retard boomers once again, they are the golden generation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890083&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889600&lt;br&gt;strongly believe 2026-2027, hopefully you&amp;#x27;re ready. won&amp;#x27;t be instant, but still swift. cant believe there are anons who actually think like this &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889827, i hope they dont disappear and comment a little longer so we can have fun with them. chainlink wont be the only crypto that will flip xrp either&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890125&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;xrp&lt;br&gt;BOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOM&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890250&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889827&lt;br&gt;always funny to see them gloating with their &amp;quot;MPT&amp;quot; and permissioned dex when literally all of that has been absolute standard and normal for the rest of crypto&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;XRP retards are even saying wrapped assets on their chain is something novel like lmao&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890307&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889600&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;We all know that Link is everything Xrp fraudulently claims to be&lt;br&gt;Since when did sergoy claim link was a bridge currency? &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The bigger issue you&amp;#x27;ll have saying it&amp;#x27;s &amp;quot;everything&amp;quot; XRP claims to be&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Is it a security or not? &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Which honestly give me an idea, which maybe will settle things in the USA. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Holding this piece of shit token + writing the previous statement out made me realize, we can probably class action chainlink and find out legally. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Is security or not? &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Has it or has it not been advertised as one?&lt;br&gt;Might be able to recover these -50% bags and get the SEC involved to settle things. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;No more waiting on the pool to open. No more cope on clarity act. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anyone willing to get this started?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890390&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;What AI thinks&lt;br&gt;Argument That LINK Is a Security&lt;br&gt;Under the Howey test (SEC v. W.J. Howey Co.), an asset is a security if there is:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;An investment of money&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;In a common enterprise&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;With a reasonable expectation of profit&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Derived from the efforts of others&lt;br&gt;LINK can arguably meet all four elements:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Investment of money: &lt;br&gt;People buy LINK with capital.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Common enterprise: &lt;br&gt;The value of LINK rises and falls with the success of the Chainlink ecosystem.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Expectation of profit: &lt;br&gt;Many buyers hold LINK expecting price appreciation, not immediate utility use.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Efforts of others: &lt;br&gt;The value of LINK depends significantly on the continued development, partnerships, and ecosystem growth driven by Chainlink Labs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additionally, the original token distribution helped fund development, which resembles capital formation typical of securities offerings.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thoughts anons? Is this class actionable?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890519&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889823&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889827&lt;br&gt;Oh hey I remember this deranged plebbit shitbag peddling cripple marketing material unironically&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;if you make fun of me or my fat jew goblin xrp shitcoin youre a LITERAL &amp;quot;pharisee&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;youre LITERALLY &amp;quot;abstracting&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;mirroring&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;xrp is LITERALLY a force of objective good guys, for real&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;xrp is gonna LITERALLY save the banks FROM usury &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I LITERALLY have no idea how swift fees work on a basic level and all of my hopium relies on my failure to comprehend this&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;muh LITERAL saudi prince&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890539&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biepum is in this very thread, seething at the standard.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;All and every progress regarding the &amp;#x27;&amp;#x27;flippening&amp;#x27;&amp;#x27; that they have been praying for can be found here&lt;br&gt;https://link-flip.alwaysbeshipp.ing/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;RLUSD will sooner overtake chainlinks mcap than chainlink xrp&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890828&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889600&lt;br&gt;It will be violent, and partly due to xrp crashing, but in no small part due to link pumping. Its going to happen after Clarity act + full staking release and neet nodes. So 2050 at this rate&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890840&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890828&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;dude, le clarity&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;le full staking&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;le neet nodes&lt;br&gt;never happening, sweetie&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890870&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889600&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889606&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889620&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889622&lt;br&gt;the only usecase any of these has is XLM; because africans are still trading phone minutes as currency and XLM is a reasonable replacement&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;XRP and LINK are complete LARPs that nobody even trusts&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;and i don&amp;#x27;t even give a shit about giving africans currency. but its literally the only thing your larp does in the physical world&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890891&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890390&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;common enterprise&lt;br&gt;You bought a product, not a share. Everything you just wrote proves this is a speculation and not an investment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Ai is about to crash the economy — 9 replies — 36.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889737</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889737?lm=1771861884</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:51:24 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Ai is about to crash the economy&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889737'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 9 • Updated: 2026-02-23 15:51 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was released today by citrini&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI gets good. Companies lay off workers. Margins expand. Stocks rip. S&amp;amp;P hits 8,000. Everyone celebrates.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;• But fired workers stop spending. Companies weaken. They buy more AI to cut costs. More layoffs. Less spending. A negative feedback loop with no natural brake.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;• The top 10% of earners drive 50%+ of all consumer spending. They&amp;#x27;re the ones getting replaced. A $180K product manager ends up driving Uber for $45K. Multiply that across every major city.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;• Ghost GDP emerges - the economy is &amp;quot;growing&amp;quot; on paper, but the money never reaches real people. Productivity is booming. Wages are collapsing.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;• Then it hits housing. $13 trillion in mortgages, all underwritten on one assumption: you keep your job for 30 years. In 2008, the loans were bad on day one. In 2028, the loans were good. The world just changed after they were written.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;• S&amp;amp;P crashes 38% from highs. Unemployment hits 10.2%. Markets barely react anymore.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;• The punchline: you&amp;#x27;re not reading this in 2028. You&amp;#x27;re reading it in February 2026. Every domino they describe has already started falling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889750&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WAOW! Link me to this guy&amp;#x27;s substack payment page immediately!!!!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889754&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There&amp;#x27;s over a billion jeets you can just keep vacuuming up the top 10% of them to always have an american middle class&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889766&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is this from that monotone Chinese guy on youtube&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889795&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889737&lt;br&gt;nigga, I am 400K deep into PLTR, you don&amp;#x27;t have to sell me on it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889802&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889737&lt;br&gt;the crazy part no ones even trying to stop it, what you are saying here isn&amp;#x27;t some major breakthrough its plainly obvious to anyone with a brain. another plainly obvious problem with a.i that most people are missing is that its not creative in the same way a person is, a.i cannot invent the airplane so you aren&amp;#x27;t just replacing a high value earner but someone that has tools that a.i doesn&amp;#x27;t have, intuition, creativity all things a.i cannot do and will never be able to do with any accuracy its a complete meme.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889812&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889737&lt;br&gt;None of that has happened, it&amp;#x27;s a fake cover story for the drunken spending companies did post covid. They hired way too many people for bullshit jobs and are now cutting back while saying it&amp;#x27;s because of AI.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rest of the shit is due to inflation, first from covid supply shocks, then companies trying to squeeze every last dollar they could out of the consumer and now trump tariffs. AI hasn&amp;#x27;t even begun to displace people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889814&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Melanin inclined individuals all in on ai are so screwed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889824&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889814&lt;br&gt;America fixed this problem already&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890898&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889750&lt;br&gt;This one is free https://www.citriniresearch.com/p/2028gic&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>I don't think BTC is how Satoshi described Bitcoin to be in 2008/9. — 7 replies — 27.8/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890488</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890488?lm=1771861524</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:45:24 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t think BTC is how Satoshi described Bitcoin to be in 2008/9.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890488'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 7 • Updated: 2026-02-23 15:45 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890544&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;you can&amp;#x27;t read c++&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890560&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890488&lt;br&gt;satoshi was kind of retarded about scaling, remember he actually envisioned that people were grinding hashes on their home CPU and be competitive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890570&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890488&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I don&amp;#x27;t think BTC is how Satoshi described Bitcoin to be in 2008/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was created as an alternative back then. A decentralized tool that cannot be sanctioned taxed or stolen by governments.&lt;br&gt;Until the Governments stepped in and convinced the people to start mining it and shorting it for them. Small miners were replaced by big corporations and venture capitals.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kikes are gifted. They always find ways to destroy good ideas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890647&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890488&lt;br&gt;Bitcoin doesn&amp;#x27;t even work that way, only difficulty scales not transaction rate. The fact the supposed creator would say something completely wrong about it shows it wasn&amp;#x27;t actually created by a single person but an organization consisting of individuals with varying levels of understanding of how it works&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890651&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890544&lt;br&gt;Don&amp;#x27;t need to unc, I have claude&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890835&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890651&lt;br&gt;claude will tell you that nothing has fundamentally changed &lt;br&gt;aside from the P2P hardfork and code cleanup&lt;br&gt;you probably don&amp;#x27;t even know that a 0.8 can still participate in the network &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890570&lt;br&gt;you don&amp;#x27;t even know what &amp;quot;decentralization&amp;quot; means, astroturf jew&lt;br&gt;you are blockchain illiterate&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890882&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890560&lt;br&gt;This, Bitcoin has evolved to becoming a kwh futures market backstopping the grid with 0 chance of a 51% attack. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890647&lt;br&gt;Even Hal Finney suggested Bitcoin banks to address scaling, but everyone has their own opinions and hybrid models. &lt;br&gt;What&amp;#x27;s more interesting than outdated blocksize drama is the op_return drama. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;There&amp;#x27;s a little civil war going on how big the op_return data field should be and what should be allowed in it. &lt;br&gt;Tether started on BTC only and now utilizes a few different chains &lt;br&gt;There are a bunch of projects arguing how much data should be allowed to be inscribed into the op_return field that is causing arguments in the community. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is because some op_return data is just garbage, but it has to be validated. &lt;br&gt;On the other hand some data in that field will open up a great deal of security for these projects to reference. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;So OP is a fag, but there are still arguments on how this project is going develop.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Buy Chainlink at $8.50 is a literal gift from God to poorfags everywhere. — 6 replies — 24.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890506</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890506?lm=1771861604</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:46:44 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Buy Chainlink at $8.50 is a literal gift from God to poorfags everywhere.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890506'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 6 • Updated: 2026-02-23 15:46 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Buy Chainlink at $8.50 is a literal gift from God to poorfags everywhere. Don’t listen to the satanic fudfaggots. Accumulate NOW or be poor forever.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890516&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I like chainlink but it doesn’t seem like the technology and its adoption directly relates to the appreciation of the coin’s value. Almost makes me wish I could buy stock instead of a coin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890592&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890506&lt;br&gt;You said the same thing at $15 and then $12.50 and then $9.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890599&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;if bitcoin goes down again then link is going down with it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890689&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890592&lt;br&gt;No I didn’t. I bought at $5 and $6. You’re a gay Reddit nerd faggot. Also your pic is about GME you gay Reddit nigger. Suck my cock.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890779&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890599&lt;br&gt;checked and buy order set for $4.50&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890884&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;reserve dca is getting juicy, almost up to 14 makeit stacks a week&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>European funds for an american — 7 replies — 22.4/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890472</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890472?lm=1771861308</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:41:48 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;European funds for an american&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890472'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 7 • Updated: 2026-02-23 15:41 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;I want to put 20% of my account in foreign, but not all foreign is created equal. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I predicted the rise in the polish economy. It&amp;#x27;s very simple, a homogenous white country free from communism is always going to become rich. A diverse country full of communists like Canada and South Africa is going to get worse and worse. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I also predicted that the real-estate market in Croatia would sky rocket due to whites fleeing countries like the UK. I was right. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;So.... are there any good mutual/index funds that target the white regions of Europe, that an American can invest in? Is there a Balkans fund? A Baltic fund? Norway/Finland fund (not Sweden or Denmark)? I do not want to invest in the UK, France, Germany, or Spain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890485&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;finland&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;white&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890499&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;please buy my bag&lt;br&gt;nein. Death to every communist, that includes every single member of a political party, everyone over 50, every bureaucrat and every single subsidized &amp;quot;private&amp;quot; which in europe is every company.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890518&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No fucking way those numbers on finland are right. I live in Helsinki and it’s like 25% brown.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890524&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890472&lt;br&gt;You are correct about Poland but everybody knew and knows about Poland but nobody wants to talk about why they&amp;#x27;ve been the hottest economy in Europe for 15 years (white and Christian).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anyway. You&amp;#x27;ve never heard of EPOL?&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;ve owned the Polish index tracker ETFs for 8 years and it has done nicely.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Otherwise, Baltics do have stock markets but they are Frontier markets (this is below emerging markets) and you basically can&amp;#x27;t buy them if you&amp;#x27;re not in the country.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Norway invests in U.S. stocks. So does Sweden and their banks. Hottest Swedish bank stock is 100% invested in NYSE traded companies. So it&amp;#x27;s circular. If you invest in European banks or Norway you&amp;#x27;re actually buying U.S. stocks with extra steps. EPOL is heavily weighted towards Polish banks and you guessed it - they all hold U.S. company stocks.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;European Bank customers are just a source of capital to invest in the New York Stock Exchange. And I&amp;#x27;m an insider so I know.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you want an actual good EU based investment buy WDEF. European defense spending will be hot for 15 years. Otherwise buy Spotify and the upcoming revolut IPO.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890543&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890524&lt;br&gt;Any funds for manufacturing from the regions I mentioned in the OP, or medical services?&lt;br&gt;Medical services will always be the last to go even under socialism since Europeans will bankrupt their country with debt before they let a hospital go bankrupt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890855&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890543&lt;br&gt;You clearly don&amp;#x27;t understand the region. You&amp;#x27;re way out of your depth and element. I&amp;#x27;m sorry but it would take me hours to explain this to you.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;t. American in Latvia who knows Poland pretty well (dated a Polish chick and been there many times).&lt;br&gt;You assume Eastern Europe has the economic model of America or Germany, just poorer and white. You&amp;#x27;re way off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890868&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890472&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;France &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;85%&lt;br&gt;lmaoooo&lt;br&gt;this is the 1972 census?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Is this biz approved? — 4 replies — 16.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890765</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890765?lm=1771862364</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:59:24 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Is this biz approved?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890765'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 4 • Updated: 2026-02-23 15:59 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;Making myself stand out in the freezing cold and pouring rain when I&amp;#x27;m too tired to study so I know how it feels to be homeless if I fail&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Should she instead play a violent pvp video game then take a nap to know how it feels to hurt evil people in a game and then be asleep for a really long time?&lt;br&gt;Should she instead message a random anonymous man through an encrypted messaging app and send him a couple hours worth of pics, videos and video calls doing whatever he requests of her so she knows how it feels to have an OF and be a camgirl?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890875&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890765&lt;br&gt;Women and social media were such a mistake, holy fucking shit why would anyone make a video like this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890903&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She should suck my dick behind a dumpster while I finger her asshole until I cum in her throat to know how it will feel to be a $20 street hooker when she NGMI&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890927&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890765&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;making myself listen to a woman talk for one entire minute when I&amp;#x27;m tired of looking at charts so I know how it feels to work for a female middle manager if I don&amp;#x27;t make it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890931&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890765&lt;br&gt;that particular approach seems retarded for sure.&lt;br&gt;but in general it&amp;#x27;s a good idea to think about what you want out of life, think about how you can reach it, and then simply work through that plan.&lt;br&gt;otherwise you end up aimlessly dicking around never really getting anywhere. look at how many cryptoshitters sat through their rise and peak all the way to the bottom again, because they didn&amp;#x27;t even have any clear goals for what target they want to hit.&lt;br&gt;it was always just &amp;quot;even more would be even nicer&amp;quot; and then &amp;quot;well, at least back to the prior ATH!&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890875&lt;br&gt;also this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>GET YOUR MONEY OUT OF US STOCKS — 7 replies — 13.9/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890686</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890686?lm=1771860622</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:30:22 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;GET YOUR MONEY OUT OF US STOCKS&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890686'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 7 • Updated: 2026-02-23 15:30 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890699&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;please buy my communist EU bags&lt;br&gt;nein&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;how about &amp;quot;international&amp;quot; ponzi etf&lt;br&gt;nein&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nobody wants to buy the boomerX bags. Choke on your same asset re-leveraged ponzi collateral.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890721&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890686&lt;br&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XpSOWfFtKJE&amp;amp;list=RDXpSOWfFtKJE&amp;amp;start_radio=1&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890723&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890699&lt;br&gt;god damn, how many more days in a row can you be proven wrong? This must be some record cope&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890730&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Not buying your scam wick&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890796&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890723&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Please by my greatest fool&lt;br&gt;The March 2026 to Q4 2029 uncovered sovereign ponzi bond ice shelfs hitting is deterministic; on a global scale&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890803&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890699&lt;br&gt;shut the fuck up you fat fuck&lt;br&gt;Europe won&lt;br&gt;Social Democracy won&lt;br&gt;Human Rights won&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890812&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890803&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Europe&lt;br&gt;dead, old and dying&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;socialism&lt;br&gt;looking at the polling on average under 20%, in parts under 5%&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Human rights&lt;br&gt;Doesn&amp;#x27;t exist. The enforcer can only write reports and scrap bodies off the floor&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Wut Gud out of Pumped Dead Coins? — 2 replies — 8.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890886</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890886?lm=1771862422</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 16:00:22 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Wut Gud out of Pumped Dead Coins?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890886'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 2 • Updated: 2026-02-23 16:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;HBAR - seems to actually do something, though I am not sure what. Something about Lemon and all the crypto problems being solved - nobody uses it though. Least embarrassing price action on list&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALGO - tranny dump already happened, was leading DiFi platform and was pretty decent for dApps. Dead now that all of that is dead.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;ICP - muh Caffeine app builder and distributed compute. Only &amp;quot;real&amp;quot; token to do a 1/1000x (2k -&amp;gt; $2)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;LINK - honestly, I am not sure what LINK does, something about oracles and sending JSON objects&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;GOLD - more gooder if Iran bombed?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;XRP - I don&amp;#x27;t know what XRP does, is it like a replacement for USDC for replacing FedWire? Banks aren&amp;#x27;t ready to adopt it yet and still use USDC. Also not sure what it does.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;???&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Serious question though, which of these or similar can pump?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Also, if you want to tell me what they do, I would genuinely appreciate it. I only really understand ALGO and ICP.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890916&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890886&lt;br&gt;definitely not QNT&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890935&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890886&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;tfw no clussy&lt;br&gt;Also&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;LINK - honestly, I am not sure what LINK does, something about oracles and sending JSON objects&lt;br&gt;We&amp;#x27;re still so fucking early&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;No additional replies in the latest window.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Financial independence / retire early — 36 replies — 9.8/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61884958</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61884958?lm=1771849270</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:21:10 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Financial independence / retire early&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61884958'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 36 • Updated: 2026-02-23 12:21 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;How&amp;#x27;s FIRE going for you, anons?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884964&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884958&lt;br&gt;Well I&amp;#x27;m looking into LCOL countries I can retire to because waiting until I&amp;#x27;m a multi millionaire in the states is not viable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884966&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884958&lt;br&gt;Just need a 7x then I&amp;#x27;m good. Already have rope if ready if I don&amp;#x27;t reach the goal in 5 years&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884967&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884958&lt;br&gt;i have about 3m networth but haven&amp;#x27;t quit my job yet. making too much money but want to quit real bad. i took a 4 day weekend recently and got bored because i have no life and hobbies because my job dominates my life and i have no energy left over to develop my personal life after work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884979&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884967&lt;br&gt;They&amp;#x27;ve done an excellent job of trapping you, anon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884983&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884958&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m back to ramen noodle mode.&lt;br&gt;I WILL make this savings last until I get a job again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884986&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884958&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m just living off NEETbux+savings. It doesn&amp;#x27;t completely cover rent, so once my savings are gone I&amp;#x27;m going to just KYS myself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884996&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884974&lt;br&gt;Interesting. I never thought of Japan as having a low cost of living. And I&amp;#x27;ve heard Thailand is not as cheap as it was.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884999&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884976&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884986&lt;br&gt;I listened to a Grant Cardone video on YouTube about pulling IRA retirement money into self-directed fund then you can use it to buy real estate without getting the penalty but you have to go big and do multi-dwelling unit or else IRS flags you. I&amp;#x27;m too chicken shit to try it (yet) but if you&amp;#x27;re going to an hero anyway fuck it try it&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;pull life retirement savings&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;buy 10 unit apartment building&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;give self job fixing toilets&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;collect rent from tenants &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;profit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885003&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ok maybe a 3 unit building&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885030&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884999&lt;br&gt;You literally cannot fix the toilets yourself. Under IRC §4975 you are considered a &amp;quot;disqualified&amp;quot; person. Basically you can own it but you can never touch it. Very gay way to &amp;#x27;own&amp;#x27; something.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885054&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;way ahead of schedule.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Full time job income (104K + 11K in retirement)&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Cost of living 32K&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Fully owned apartment(450K)&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;308K in liquidish assets&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;90K in retirement&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;2K coming in every month from passive revenue from a side business (vidya gaems)&lt;br&gt;In 7-8 years i will probably reach full FIRE. But i&amp;#x27;m releasing new products this year. If i can have similar success i will probably just Barista FIRE living the gamedev dream.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885059&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884967&lt;br&gt;Dude, just quit. You&amp;#x27;ll probably decompress after a month or two, then you can re-evaluate. If you decide you need to work, then you can just go apply to some jobs. Maybe you&amp;#x27;ll decide you want to work in a library or something stupid like that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885062&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885030&lt;br&gt;that fucking sucks what is Cardone talking about then?&lt;br&gt;retirement money is just going to the bank then when I starve to death. maybe that was their plan all along. &lt;br&gt;take the 10% penalty + taxes ? now it&amp;#x27;s a duplex maybe in a cold flyover state&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885102&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just had my 2nd kid.&lt;br&gt;Already gave up and accepted that I&amp;#x27;ll be waging til I die.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885131&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884958&lt;br&gt;Pretty good despite the recent market drawdown. I stopped working 9 months ago and moved to a luxury condo in Thailand. Expenses are relatively low but I&amp;#x27;m still paying my mortgage and car note in America. I get a little bit of income from trading options and renting out my house to my younger sister. I&amp;#x27;m financially set for the rest of my life but I&amp;#x27;m still figuring out what I want to do as far as family, kids, etc.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885135&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885062&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885030&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884986&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;ok I found this. instead of self directed IRA to have to roll it into a business startup&lt;br&gt;so don&amp;#x27;t an hero yet &lt;br&gt;or put me down as your beneficiary first&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;https://www.bankrate.com/loans/small-business/what-are-robs/#:~:text=Key%20takeaways,penalties%20are%20associated%20with%20ROBS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885141&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884967&lt;br&gt;Nigger. Based on the 4% rule you can draw about 120k yearly off investments and statistically never run out of money. Wife and I retired early w/ Lite Fire. No debt. Last year our gross income was $55,000. We bought and sold a RV, Saw the Grand Canyon, Zion, Bryce Canyon, Rushmore. Took a 21 day cruise from west coast through Panama Canal, Cruised out of Florida for 3 weeks and hung out in Fort Lauderdale for 2. Did 2 more week in the Caribbean. Have a 20 day transatlantic cruise from NYC to Sicily booked with stops in 9 ports in April. Tons of midweek short trips seeing cool shit. Leaving work is an adjustment definitely but I have never been happier. See the world, meet people, always with an eye to relocation. Picrel is heading into Cartagena Columbia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885152&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884967&lt;br&gt;I was just like you before I decided to walk away. I call it &amp;quot;golden handcuffs&amp;quot; when a job pays so well that it makes you feel obligated to keep going even though you don&amp;#x27;t need the money. Your job feels like your identity but I promise you&amp;#x27;ll forget about it after you quit and find new hobbies and a gf.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887260&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884974&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884996&lt;br&gt;Japan is not a lcol area. Its cheaper compared to the west but not Thailand/Vietnam cheap. My plan is to live 90 days visa free there a year and live frugally elsewhere for the rest of the year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887270&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884958&lt;br&gt;Closing in on luxury fat FIRE thanks to gold/silver/oil/uranium. Fuck crypto.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887292&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t want to retire early, cuz id probably just be doing the same thing without getting paid for it, but i have enough money to be comfortable for now&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887302&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I am starting to realize the whole game plan of FIRE is just giving me reason to wake up in the morning, something to look forward to. I dont think I will really be that much happier once I achieve my dream of semi financial freedom.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887313&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887292&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;id probably just be doing the same thing without getting paid for it&lt;br&gt;Your job is your hobby? Congrats. What do you do?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887338&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s not really going.&lt;br&gt;Would take me getting my inheritance and buying the bottom of the next global market crash and riding the recovery wave with everything I can throw in during it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887601&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;uhh im 38. been retired since 32. probably unretiring soon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887625&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887313&lt;br&gt;gay prostitute&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890044&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887302&lt;br&gt;frugality is like a game, to see how little i can spend each month&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890071&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885054&lt;br&gt;what&amp;#x27;s your side business anon? reseller?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890085&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;is 1.5M too little to retire?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I round tripped 8 figs being greedy&lt;br&gt;its all i have left&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890089&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890085&lt;br&gt;depends where you live&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890151&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885102&lt;br&gt;My #2 is 4 months old now. Thanks to the fire-induced frugality I was able to reduce my hours for half a year by 10 hours a week which was priceless in itself. Will probably also wage forever but probably only 20 hours or so per week.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884958&lt;br&gt;We managed to pay off the house @32. other than that I only have 15k cash and 50k in the MSCI. &lt;br&gt;The plan was to retire @40 but unrealistic unless I win the lottery ( and I don&amp;#x27;t even play)&lt;br&gt;So yes full fire is impossible right now, but on the plus side: we need less than 2k/ month for a very comfortable life. &lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m converting a part of the house to a rental flat atm which should bring another 600 per month and allow for tax deductions.&lt;br&gt;After installing solar this year my electricity bill should drop from 110 to 40 per month. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;So all in all we can have a cozy lifestyle for an acceptable trade off in lifetime. &lt;br&gt;Wife would like to work 20 hours/week in 10 years or so, I should be able to fully switch to do freelance consultant work in my niche ( or not. Her meager wage combined with the surplus of the next 10 years should easily pay for everything and give the kids a nice tailwind) &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m putting 180 bucks/month per kind into an ETF which should become a nice 150k downpayment (infl.adj.) when they turn 27&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890181&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Never gonna happen on my income. Millennials are fucked out of retirement. At least I own all my shit and have actual children and a loyal wife.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890213&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I dont know what number to stop at..&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Fake and Gay Economy — 94 replies — 8.6/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61871520</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61871520?lm=1771823171</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:06:11 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Fake and Gay Economy&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61871520'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 94 • Updated: 2026-02-23 05:06 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;When will this gay as economy finally collapse and how can i profit from it?&lt;br&gt;Its ridiculous the woman at our workplace contribute nothing to the company and make more money than i do&lt;br&gt;Its infuriating we just had a bunch of lay offs and we lost some of oir best workers but somehow a bunch of HR shits who do nothing all day still work here&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871530&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HR is a necessary function, chud&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871569&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871530&lt;br&gt;For what?&lt;br&gt;Genuinely why do we need it to this extent?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871755&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871569&lt;br&gt;Protect the corp from lawsuits&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883066&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879023&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;If they didn&amp;#x27;t provide value they wouldn&amp;#x27;t be there.&lt;br&gt;75% or more of white collar work literally does nothing, roasties or not.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883243&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;Did they fire itty bitty titties &amp;amp; a bob?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883399&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;When there is an alternative for the money and people to pour over into.&lt;br&gt;Fagmerica&amp;#x27;s slow decline relies on everywhere else being shittier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883616&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;HR while i&amp;#x27;m anxious, waiting for them to communicate their decision about hiring me, being unemployed and thinking about suicide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883644&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882495&lt;br&gt;you know, society almost always makes you think you desire gen z boss and a mini, but fuck that, i&amp;#x27;m gonna say it, loud and proud: i&amp;#x27;m more akin to have a relationship with secret product and a trench, i dont know if its about my selfsteem, i would like to be enough for gen z boss and a mini. Maybe what i need is 5&amp;#x27;3 and an attitude.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883760&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883243&lt;br&gt;They got promoted to Chief Diversity, Equity &amp;amp; Inclusion Officer&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883781&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883644&lt;br&gt;You meant to say inclined. You are more inclined. Akin means &amp;quot;similar to&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883784&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882869&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;incel&lt;br&gt;Im so confused as to what that term means, involuntarily celibate? But its not being celibate if your literally having sex. Such a weird term clearly carrying different meaning. What is the point of using a term that literally has no definition to its meaning, you might aswell speak in baby noises at this point.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884146&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;guys, ALL we have to do is called women like this ugly chopped shit to their face as much as possible and they will lose all motivation to live&lt;br&gt;they are SO fragile in that regard.&lt;br&gt;next time you are walking down the street and see some bitch like this just start yelling “YOURE UGLY”&lt;br&gt;they will spend the next week and a half minimum making reddit posts about it and getting their SSRI prescription upped.&lt;br&gt;don’t ever engage with any ideas or thoughts they have. just pick apart their appearance. you look like a fridge and a stick insect at the same time. your fake dyed hair sucks. you have clown makeup on, you must have learned how to do makeup at the circus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884272&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883066&lt;br&gt;So you&amp;#x27;re saying ceo&amp;#x27;s willingly burn 75% of their money for fun?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884291&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884272&lt;br&gt;he&amp;#x27;s saying the ceo is a fucking retard&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884297&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;I want to shove my cock deep into the first one from behind. Just lift the skirt and blast the pussy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884717&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883784&lt;br&gt;Yes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884737&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871569&lt;br&gt;Without HR you could complete the work, banter and build a genuine camaraderie with your common co-worker, but we cant have unions, and its better if you&amp;#x27;re all divided and conquered, here&amp;#x27;s a harpy to make your life hell&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884742&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873193&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872087&lt;br&gt;These niggers actually get it. All problems flow downstream from jews controlling the issuance of your (since 1913) fake and gay fiat debt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885902&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873611&lt;br&gt;You must be over 18 to use this site&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886326&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882442&lt;br&gt;Yeah this kind of mega über schizos who believe in fe and no nuke use this phrase holy shit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886329&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882442&lt;br&gt;And yes the idea of space is falsifiable you absolute schizo. Satellites wouldn&amp;#x27;t even work without it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886359&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883784&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Such a weird term clearly carrying different meaning. What is the point of using a term that literally has no definition to its meaning&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s just people overusing words or ideas to oblivion, where they lose all context. It&amp;#x27;s like the worst insult was being called gay way back, then it was subverted (actually gay is cool), then it became retarded, then it got subverted (actually retarded is cool because you&amp;#x27;re not trying), then it become autistic, then it became subverted (actually it&amp;#x27;s interesting to be autistic), now it&amp;#x27;s random baby talk by gen alpha (mog, cortisol spike, chopped, unc, lil bro, frame, aura farming, 67, incel, cuk). Now it&amp;#x27;s being subverted by people overusing the terms even if they don&amp;#x27;t apply to anyone or anything in the context at all. Someone not having sex for a week = incel. Someone having a slightly embarrassing moment (cortisol spike), someone better looking walking past (mogged), doing something that&amp;#x27;s barely good (aura farming), having a strong presence even if it&amp;#x27;s completely autistic and retarded (frame). Or like when old people started wearing skateboard shirts having no clue what it was, or everyone and their dog wearing an off white shirt. People make shit gay eventually, it&amp;#x27;s a universal law.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886363&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;work office job (engineer) with way too many women and diversity hire niggers and Indians who do nothing all day&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;get new (white) South African Vice President&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;calls us all together&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;in his funny accent tells us he’s an engineer and knows the business and there will be changes&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;tells us he will cut 20% of the workforce soon&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;everyone is shit scared and the normie femoids start climbing over each other trying to save their useless asses&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;office girlies start spreading rumours about everyone and everything in desperate attempt to make themselves look better&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;don’t give a fuck, I’m a technician and actually make money for the company unlike them&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Vice President just observes the shit show and never comments on anything while he feels out the office&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;come in one Monday&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;literally all blacks are gone&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;all except the actual useful Indians are gone&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;he culled every single female that we all knew had jewish make believe adult daycare jobs&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;only kept the old hag secretaries that actually do a great job&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kek, based white nigger. Turns out all it takes is some third world coloniser to clean this woke shit up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886555&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872076&lt;br&gt;We are not capitalist.&lt;br&gt;We have been Trotskyist since the end of WW2.&lt;br&gt;Having a central bank is plank #5 of the commie manifesto.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886576&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884742&lt;br&gt;It was a bit delayed until after 1913.&lt;br&gt;They couldn’t go full fakeconomy immediately, or they would have been shut down.&lt;br&gt;They had to wait and boil the frog slowly, using the occasional crisis as a speed boost.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886586&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t ever interact with HR once I&amp;#x27;m hired until I&amp;#x27;m inevitably fired. From where comes the HR hate? Are they the ones who actually make the decisions to fire us?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886684&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;this board is dead as shit holy fuck&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886687&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61886684&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s the weekend. It picks up when the market is open.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886692&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;d fuck all of them. At the same time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887220&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61886363&lt;br&gt;Sounds illegal and fake. This is such an obvious thing to do, there must be a reason it doesn&amp;#x27;t actually happen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889346&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s not going to collapse... bill gates will grow some cheap bug burgers and psyop all the women to think it&amp;#x27;s healthy and great for the environment... so we can continue feeding billions of women to do nothing but work in an office.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889382&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61886363&lt;br&gt;How was he able to be able to gauge who&amp;#x27;s useful and who&amp;#x27;s not in such a short period of time?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889387&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889346&lt;br&gt;Also, paying women to do nothing is one of the best birth controls there is. They are incapable of dating down. Sorry, just the messenger. bullshit jobs, especially for women, will never end until picrel collapses.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unfortunately, the jews also don&amp;#x27;t want picrel to collapse because then their banks would go broke. So we&amp;#x27;re stuck in hell.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>WTF IS HAPPENING - preferably in haiku format — 10 replies — 7.6/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889182</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889182?lm=1771857667</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 14:41:07 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;WTF IS HAPPENING - preferably in haiku format&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889182'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 10 • Updated: 2026-02-23 14:41 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889192&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889182&lt;br&gt;I am holding Tesla shorts&lt;br&gt;Fuck haikus&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889194&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889182&lt;br&gt;It all crashes&lt;br&gt;to zero&lt;br&gt;to fuck us&lt;br&gt;But slowly, slowly!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889198&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Money needs to print&lt;br&gt;Tarriffs will be the excuse&lt;br&gt;When QE returns&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889200&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This shit ass board is dead and has been for years and I’m still broke and FUCK FUCK FUCK FUCK FUCK FUCKKKK&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889208&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cycle doing its thing&lt;br&gt;BTC to 30k&lt;br&gt;Buy the dip you jeet&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889209&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A decision has been made. War is coming&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889252&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889182&lt;br&gt;your asshole is ripped&lt;br&gt;by the cycles you can&amp;#x27;t see&lt;br&gt;because retarded&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889831&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889252&lt;br&gt;Based&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889842&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889182&lt;br&gt;Cryptocurrency is shit&lt;br&gt;Buy metal instead&lt;br&gt;Real money real victory&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889984&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Send it to Zero!&lt;br&gt;Which Coin You Talking About?&lt;br&gt; The One You’re Holding.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>insider here, again. — 30 replies — 7.1/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61879263</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61879263?lm=1771847294</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:48:14 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;insider here, again.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61879263'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 30 • Updated: 2026-02-23 11:48 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;i hope you bought BBBY-WT BBBY-WARRANTS&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879648&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I have a few thousand of these along with shares what am I in for&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879767&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879648&lt;br&gt;getting dumped on by OP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879836&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879767&lt;br&gt;Due to my current occupation, I am prohibited from holding stocks, options, or similar investments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879895&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This you?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879921&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879767&lt;br&gt;idk I mean bed bath was once a huge American retail darling...the historic overstock chart is super schizo/presently quite low...these warrants are trading like a shitcoin which is funny...I also don&amp;#x27;t dislike lemonis. He&amp;#x27;s a media player and if you actually listened to some of his shit there does seem to be an interesting intersection between blockchain capabilities and homeownership etc...not financial advice of course just a variety of things I was peeking at when researching&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879944&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879263&lt;br&gt;no&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879999&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879836&lt;br&gt;What is your current occupation anon? Nothing revealing but in general etc...the exercise price of the warrants is $15...trading currently at less than a dollar it seems like a confusing deal...at this point if one likes the company wouldn&amp;#x27;t shares be the move? I did some modeling around warrant prices if the shares price goes to xyz and that is very interesting...also speaking of interesting what&amp;#x27;s the deal with the alleged cusip similarity to the old bbbyq shares?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880091&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879999&lt;br&gt;Financial system. I am not asking you to hold those warrants until they are exercised. I am asking you to hold them and sell the warrants when we can realize a substantial profit. Nice quads.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881477&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880091&lt;br&gt;Interesting. Wouldn&amp;#x27;t trading the warrants implicitly come with a short term capital gains tax insofar as its impossible to hold them over a year at this point? Would have to be some pretty fair gains to offset that 40% hit...anyways doesn&amp;#x27;t the warrants increasing in price also imply that the shares have gone up in price as well? I ran some informal modeling estimates using black scholes with iv, roughly .65 years to expiry and this is what I came up with: 15.5 bbby share price = 4.50ish warrant price...25 share price/12ish warrant price...60 share price/45ish warrant price...100 share price/85ish warrant price...200 share price 185ish warrant price...I make no claim as to the veracity of these numbers, just for fun. Anyways what do you see happening to the bbby stock price for these warrants to be worthwhile? Am I thinking on the right track in general?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881670&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879263&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881753&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879999&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881477&lt;br&gt;note the digis&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881916&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879263&lt;br&gt;Buy these if you want, but remember, these warrants are not related to the canceled BBBYQ/DK-Butterfly, reguardless of what the BBBYQ schizos say.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881980&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881916&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;nobody tell him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882152&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879263&lt;br&gt;I hold a few&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882389&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;why are americans starting to invest more into VT?&lt;br&gt;isn&amp;#x27;t america the greatest country on earth?&lt;br&gt;for me it has always been VOO&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882429&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;look at NPC holder distribution&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;there&amp;#x27;s no big dumps&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;base still present&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;conviction quietly intact&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884950&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880091&lt;br&gt;So you&amp;#x27;re allowed to buy warrants, won&amp;#x27;t your employer know you bought them?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885366&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get ready everyone. I don&amp;#x27;t think they will be able to kick the can after this sneeze. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885357&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886042&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;what about BBBYQ? i lost all my money. the little i&amp;#x27;ve earned since then i&amp;#x27;ve spent on equipment that will make me a self-made millionaire thanks to my own intellect and blood sweat and tears and not thanks to ryan cohen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886054&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61886042&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886916&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BUY&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887055&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61886042&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;he doesn&amp;#x27;t know what % of powerwash/lawncare businesses fail in their first two years.&lt;br&gt;I appreciate your entrepreneurial spirit, but this isn&amp;#x27;t the flex you think it is.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887380&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887055&lt;br&gt;i&amp;#x27;m not trying to flex i&amp;#x27;m saying the BBBYQ should pay off without having to double down on BBBYW as well. it&amp;#x27;s fucking ridiculous how you can do everything right and run into complete disasters in investing and in other things and getting trolled by random assholes like you as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887389&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ryan cohen and larry cheng are behaving like autistic wankers after making thousands of people lose their life savings and pulte is a clown if he was just grifting BBBYQ investors&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887406&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;and trump is apparently a rapist pedophile murderer who rigged the 2024 election with elon musk and mostly everyone on wall street is getting away with psychopathic scammers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887414&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887380&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;BBBYQ should pay of&lt;br&gt;There will be no payoff for BBBYQ, ever.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887426&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887414&lt;br&gt;then RC should be held accountable for grifting BBBYQ investors, it&amp;#x27;s insulting to everyone&amp;#x27;s intelligence to claimi he did nothing to take advantage of people who looked up to him. though GME maxis are insufferable so they kinda deserve to get scammed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887888&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887380&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m not trolling you, brother. You&amp;#x27;re right, sometimes you do everything right and shit sucks anyways. That&amp;#x27;s what the book of Job is about. You still need to keep the faith, like he did.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889098&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887380&lt;br&gt;BBBYW is more like a lifeboat for people who missed BBBYQ. If you held a fat stack (10,000 plus) of BBBYQ into cancellation then you are good.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890133&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889098&lt;br&gt;2,000 sh @ 038&lt;br&gt;I dont care&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>I sold. 4600 Stinkies, 14.8 ETH. thanks for nothing — 15 replies — 6.7/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889893</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889893?lm=1771854413</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 13:46:53 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;I sold. 4600 Stinkies, 14.8 ETH. thanks for nothing&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889893'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 15 • Updated: 2026-02-23 13:46 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;I sold. 4600 Stinkies, 14.8 ETH. thanks for nothing&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889901&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You are a traitor&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889903&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889893&lt;br&gt;ee sold?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889911&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889893&lt;br&gt;kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889912&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889893&lt;br&gt;Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889925&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889903&lt;br&gt;Literally this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889930&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889925&lt;br&gt;refinance where OP?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889939&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OP set us free&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889961&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889939&lt;br&gt;kek this guy :D &lt;br&gt;reallife wojak&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889983&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I CANT FEEEEEEEEL&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;THE WAY I DID BEFORE&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;TIME WONT HEAAAALL&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;THIS DAMAGE ANYMORE&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889985&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889983&lt;br&gt;You were the only real trader left. We all were waiting for you to sell and now we pump it unitl you fomo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889988&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889983&lt;br&gt;nigger big jew banks predicting 10k btc in tumor weeks™ and u selled?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889994&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889983&lt;br&gt;didnt see those jewtube spams here in the past 4 days about how fucking over for beetkoin and it will never go back up ever again? maybe even negative values in dollars? :D&lt;br&gt;always buy the retard 10iq nigger fud, dont capitulate it!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890002&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889985&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889988&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889994&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I lied. I sold my highest cost basis ETH buys (4.3 ETH total). I have a nice 10k realized loss hole for 2026, but I still think ETH and link make me whole by end of year. I’m expecting a false flag or full scale war with strike on Iran, millions of deaths. So I wanted to pull some out, contemplating selling some more but maybe we get a little fakeout pump. Im hoping to slurp some more if we get one less capitulation, if It runs and I miss out, I still got an ok bag. Also stay frosty for a grid down scenario. Best of luck anons&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890009&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890002&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890397&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890002&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I’m expecting a false flag or full scale war with strike on Iran, millions of deaths&lt;br&gt;wow such market asymmetric information and expectation, you are truly ahead of the curve am i rite lmao&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>how do you guys cope with the fact that OF egirls are making tens of millions a year? — 37 replies — 6.6/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889270</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889270?lm=1771842326</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 10:25:26 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;how do you guys cope with the fact that OF egirls are making tens of millions a year?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889270'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 37 • Updated: 2026-02-23 10:25 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;how do you guys cope with the fact that OF egirls are making tens of millions a year? this shit is really unbelievable man i am seething so hard holy fuck&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889273&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I literally just don&amp;#x27;t care. Nobody will ever love them and I can also make 10 million without displaying my butthole for the world to see&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889278&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s only like top1% creators making millions&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889279&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889273&lt;br&gt;i didnt care too for so long but now im starting to care fml its just so unfair.. Not only are they extremely hot they also get to make 20MM a year for years scamming with bikini pics on OF&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;its just so unfair i feel like crying&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889292&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;Theres literally only been one titty streamer that turned that 5 minute success into owning multiple gas stations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889298&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889292&lt;br&gt;Car washes are where the money is at&lt;br&gt; Once you get your bag idk why people keep doing it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889301&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889283&lt;br&gt;okay this makes me feel better thanks man&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889304&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bro, these bitches don’t “make” money they just receive donations. There’s just as many if not more girls just receiving money from sugar daddies without an OF. These bitches would be getting money from sugar daddies regardless, instead of 1 or 2 sugar daddies giving them tons and tons of money they have thousands of sugar daddies giving them a little bit of money. If anything they are getting a worse deal from OF. Freedom and independence will never make a woman happy so they have no clue what to do with their lives anyways. It’s just one of the perks of being a woman, you get all your shit paid for. Just like women have access to secretary positions where all it takes is a retard to answer a phone and take messages and reply to emails just because they’re attractive and the bosses want them around. There’s a price on beauty and it’s a very short window to capitalize on. All they have to do is take a few pictures and videos, it could be all in the same day, and those pictures can be rolled out for years so they literally don’t have to do any work and can just let an agency handle everything. Almost all these bitches use an agency so they are giving up almost 50% of the profits to men. So there is an easy way for you to capitalize on these bitches profits you just aren’t doing it. This shit has been going on for centuries. It’s nothing new it’s just online.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889315&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are thousands of whores that lose their dignity on OF without making any money at all&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889322&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;You know there are criminals, corrupt politicians, and mindless corporate drones making more than that, right? Perhaps you imagine an economy in which people are compensated for the value they provide to society. That&amp;#x27;s only an ideal, not the economy that exists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889335&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;I am still a virgin at 35 and over my entire life I have wasted only 2.40 CHF on women. I&amp;#x27;m proud of myself that I&amp;#x27;m not a cuck.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889339&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;a girl I knew from school started an onlyfans. everyone she grew up with saw her getting fucked. she made like $200 and deleted it a couple months later. I feel like this is probably pretty common&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889347&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889339&lt;br&gt;Is she hot? You gonna share with the class?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889349&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889335&lt;br&gt;Was that 2.40 CHF for a cup of coffee? Bus fare?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889354&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889339&lt;br&gt;Girl I knew in the office years ago had hers leaked by one of the bitchy HR ladies. Like 14 people paid 5 bucks to sub to it and watched her rail herself with a 7 inch hog.&lt;br&gt;Eventually it got to her and started impacting her work and she was put on a PIP.&lt;br&gt;She quit like a month later. Think about that. At best she made the equivalent of a few burgs at Wendy&amp;#x27;s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889368&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889354&lt;br&gt;You made that up in your head. Why would HR have her porn videos&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889372&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889347&lt;br&gt;yea she was hot. she was also one of my good friends sisters. i didnt save any of the videos though&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889354&lt;br&gt;yep&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889378&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889368&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s not really difficult to understand if you understand how women work. Her being HR just happened to be where she worked. Office gossip is unfortunately how office wagies fill their day. Men aren&amp;#x27;t much different desu. We just talk about we railed so and so on the weekend. &lt;br&gt;Office women are vile and will say the most endearing things to your face before finding ways to tell your wife at the Christmas party how she heard you got blown by your manager&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889392&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;Are they?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;rented cars&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;leased jets&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;AirBNBs in Dubai for two days&lt;br&gt;All the illusion of being rich. Even if they did make a few shekels, they are definitely beholden to the pimp that is laundering money through them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889405&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;grow boobs then if you don&amp;#x27;t like it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889409&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;Barely any of them do, pretty much just the hottest ones that are willing to get their brains fucked out on camera. If you aren&amp;#x27;t one of the hottest guys willing to have your dingle out for the world to see it really isn&amp;#x27;t comparable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889429&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889409&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s an enormous amount of work too when you get big enough to make decent cash but not enough to sustain yourself. Answering 48 messages in the morning yourself because you can&amp;#x27;t afford to pay a guy to do it for and you can&amp;#x27;t not answer because these guys are shelling out 70 percent of your revenue. Then you return. Film more. Do it again and scrape by for maybe 900 bucks a month.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s almost more worth it to end up being worth a few cheeseburgers so you know you aren&amp;#x27;t worth it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889624&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you really cared you would be pimping OF models by now. You think women do anything in their own? They all have pimps.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889631&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s not glamorous but you can go on craigslist whenever you want and make a quick couple hundred getting your dick sucked by lonely old queers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889644&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889631&lt;br&gt;How is that even worth $200? Enjoy your money pox&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889769&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889273&lt;br&gt;Holy cope. Obviously most men will love them because men are horny dogs. Its 2026, prime time to realize men are the more pathetic gender. This aint the 50s champ.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889773&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889273&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Nobody will ever love them&lt;br&gt;These bitches get BFs all the time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889775&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;how do you guys cope with the fact that OF egirls are making tens of millions a year?&lt;br&gt;Only the top 1% do, the rest make around few hundred USD or few 20-40USD a month.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889273&lt;br&gt;Lot of them have BFs and lot of them don&amp;#x27;t do porn with other men just sell their nudes but most aren&amp;#x27;t making enough to retire on not by a longshot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889777&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;1. They don&amp;#x27;t receive all that money, they are hired under an umbrella corporation, they are just models for hire.&lt;br&gt;2. They are women, they don&amp;#x27;t know how to invest their money (see amouranth, it was her husband who put her in front of the camera, managed her socials and invested her money)&lt;br&gt;3. I can&amp;#x27;t see what you would do with that much money, unless you are hyper-dependent on people doing things for you...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889804&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;They aren&amp;#x27;t. The vast majority have sold their souls for triple digit profits&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889830&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Comparing yourself to women is one of the first steps on the tranny pipeline lmao&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889840&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;Go sell your asshole to strangers and lookmax then you lazy cunt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889979&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;Nothings stopping you from doing gya shit on onlyfans&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889986&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;Doesn&amp;#x27;t bother me in the least.&lt;br&gt;Firstly, it causes tons of women to throw their lives away being whores. So is hardly a victory for women.&lt;br&gt;Secondly, what does that money do other than ruin their lives? Women crave a man higher on the totem pole than they are, now they can&amp;#x27;t find one for two reasons.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>