<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>/biz/ Active (filtered, with replies)</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/</link><description>Filtered out: general, gme, bbbyq. OP + first 3 replies + last 30 replies.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 13:37:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Is living anywhere except Los Angeles, San Francisco, Washington DC, or New York the same as admitting that your life is… — 79 replies — 316.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858975</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858975?lm=1771421815</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 13:36:55 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Is living anywhere except Los Angeles, San Francisco, Washington DC, or New York the same as admitting that your life is…&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858975'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 79 • Updated: 2026-02-18 13:36 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Is living anywhere except Los Angeles, San Francisco, Washington DC, or New York the same as admitting that your life is meaningless and that you are NOT the main character and will never make it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858982&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;Dubai, Paris, London, Tokyo, Kyoto&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858987&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You burgers aren&amp;#x27;t ready for what&amp;#x27;s coming&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858990&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;HAHAHA&lt;br&gt;HAHAHAHA&lt;br&gt;IMAGINE LIVING IN A BROWN SHITHOLE&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860590&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;d consider living there after you threw all the non-Whites out. Otherwise, I&amp;#x27;d visit it but not stay there permanently.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860659&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Assuming you’ve made it, what are the benefits of living in these cities when job opportunities are no longer a factor&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860666&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;No. You can also live in a remote cabin in Alaska. At least until your old crew calls you out of retirement for one last job.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860681&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;My life is given meaning through devotion and love for the LORD Jesus Christ&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860712&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859314&lt;br&gt;Guarantee me a couple of slam piglets and a square meal and I&amp;#x27;ll see what I can do about sabotaging the caravans wheels to steer it on coarse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860728&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;imagine living in new york, not being the richest guy in new york, and imagining that living in new york means your life isn&amp;#x27;t meaningless&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860769&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858982&lt;br&gt;t. lolicerdo criminal&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860793&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;Living anywhere except Los Angeles, San Francisco, Washington DC, or New York is the same as admitting that your life is meaningless and that you are NOT the main character and will never make it.&lt;br&gt;This is true. Imagine living anywhere near these mega slave cities.&lt;br&gt;You will just be worker number 10000000. Almost anywhere else is better.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860802&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859145&lt;br&gt;Holy shit imagine thinking thats a good place to live in. The nederlands are already way overpopulated. Our natural habitat which means the place we are most happy at is the forest with a small group of tribespeople.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860804&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860793&lt;br&gt;*in&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860828&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Is living anywhere except Chongqing, Shanghai, Beijing, Guangzhou and Shenzhen the same as admitting that your life is meaningless and that you are NOT the main character and will never make it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861578&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859032&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;thirdie hivan complains but won&amp;#x27;t move back(will move to oc instead)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861585&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;I live in Chinook montana. I would ask for nothing else&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861591&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;I am from D.C.&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s full of drones. Some are deluded enough to think being the GS-15 in charge of whatever the fuck department for whatever government agency actually makes them important.&lt;br&gt;It doesn&amp;#x27;t.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861595&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858990&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;IMAGINE LIVING IN A BROWN SHITHOLE&lt;br&gt;D.C. suburbs in 2012 be like...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862146&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;Los Angeles is a shithole. San Francisco lost all sovl because no one who lives there is actually from San Francisco anymore. D.C. is literally a dilapidated nigger den. New York is cool and iconic but is also a lonely hive where everyone is disconnected despite living 10,000 to a city block.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t think you&amp;#x27;ve been to any of them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862164&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859319&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;worst street&lt;br&gt;So you admit that the left-wing billionaires delegate certain streets for the homeless while they live on the nice streets in their high rises, with private security?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862191&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862164&lt;br&gt;They delegate entire states for the washed out retards to live in, while even the homeless here in LA have more upward mobility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862210&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858982&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Non-Americans&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Main Character&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Even Once&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anon...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862380&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861591&lt;br&gt;This. I&amp;#x27;m from DC too, but I left that shithole years ago. Everyone is a bureaucratic suit who aspires to work for the government or some adjacent entity. Sure there might be ethnic diversity, but there is no cultural diversity at all. Quite literally everyone is a libtard. Not to mention the women there are not only busted but also extremely deluded in thinking that they deserve Chads. A DC 10 is a Miami or NYC 6.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862537&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859324&lt;br&gt;Can confirm, LA is great. Every month I have to remember to not self-dox because retards are talking about what a shithole it is here, and I want to take a photo of my window view showing that it looks exactly the same as the white southern suburb they all fantasize about. Just don&amp;#x27;t live in the poor part of town. That rule applies to every city on earth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862543&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We have *real* mexican food for cheap, no bad weather, and as many asian women and big booty latinas as you could ever want.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864183&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862380&lt;br&gt;D.C. has long been &amp;quot;Hollywood for ugly people.&amp;quot; It&amp;#x27;s where ugly people go to make it - with their 6 figure bullshit government job.&lt;br&gt;I lived in Fairfax and worked in Arlington - at least I wasn&amp;#x27;t on the nigger side of the Potomac.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864233&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858982&lt;br&gt;These places are all horrible unless you’re rich or are on a clear path to wealth. I’m convinced the only places left on earth where it’s still possible to safely and comfortably raise a family on a middling firstie income are Southeast Asia and Eastern Europe (the Catholic ones in the EU not the orthodox shitholes)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864442&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864233&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Eastern Europe&lt;br&gt;Can confirm it&amp;#x27;s comfy as fuck here with just a few hundred grand of wealth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864757&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862146&lt;br&gt;Erm but all my favorite movies take place in those cities so they must be the best and most important in America!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864780&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;most of those cities suck ass and are basically open air prisons for white collar wageslaves. people with money &amp;quot;in LA&amp;quot; live on or near the beach. people with money &amp;quot;in DC&amp;quot; live in surrounding areas like bethesda or chevy chase.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864816&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;I enjoy Manhattan and visiting SOCAL but living there would be too much. I lived on in Santa Monica for a year and anytime you&amp;#x27;d want to do something you had to plan around traffic. Not a way to live you entire life. There&amp;#x27;s a ton of great nature in southern California so even if you&amp;#x27;re not into le hustle and bustle you&amp;#x27;re still able to have a good time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868506&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;wow gringos are really fucking retarded, who gives a fuck about your shitty cities??&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869839&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;Swap Los Angeles for Denver and that list is accurate.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;There&amp;#x27;s no surplus of 20-29 year old white women in LA.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>How do I short NYC? — 17 replies — 68.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61868898</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61868898?lm=1771421349</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 13:29:09 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;How do I short NYC?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61868898'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 17 • Updated: 2026-02-18 13:29 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;How do I short NYC?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868918&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868898&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;middle class owning property in New York&lt;br&gt;hehe, good one&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868957&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868918&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;property tax goes up 10%&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;landlord keeps the rent the same price&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868970&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868898&lt;br&gt;puts on SLG, VNO, VICI&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868974&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868957&lt;br&gt;why would jews do that&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868986&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868898&lt;br&gt;Landlords must be so happy with this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869005&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taxes go up &amp;gt; Rents go up &amp;gt; Welfare goes up&lt;br&gt;And guess who owns all those buildings?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869011&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868898&lt;br&gt;How is his base responding to this? All the people who were so certain he could actually do what he said and would totally fix NYC with money it doesn&amp;#x27;t have?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869014&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868918&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868957&lt;br&gt;Actual rich people in NYC use a loophole where their building/unit is somehow tied to a much lower valued building on the same block. &lt;br&gt;So a penthouse they bought for $50M has a paper value of like $500k. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anyone who thinks the wealthy actually gets shafted by tax increases and that the politicians they own won&amp;#x27;t leave loopholes open for them, not just in NYC but in pretty much every western country, are absolutely delusional. &lt;br&gt;Taxing the rich is just a convenient excuse politicians use to raise taxes with the peasants blessings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869016&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868898&lt;br&gt;I can&amp;#x27;t believe anyone actually lives in NYC. Genuinely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869109&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869016&lt;br&gt;seriously, at least in california the weather and landscape makes it worth it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869172&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869016&lt;br&gt;what, you don&amp;#x27;t like being stabbed by niggers in the subway??&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869185&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Who cares? What they&amp;#x27;re doing is great for the poor. All poor socialists need to move to NYC ASAP and take advantage of the New New York. We should all be buying them bus tickets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869354&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868918&lt;br&gt;When you go to a restaurant, you are paying their property taxes and when you pay rent you are paying the property owners property taxes. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is one level of abstraction so if you cannot understand this it would indicate that your IQ is extremely low.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869533&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868898&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just goes to show how horrible the Republican candidate must have been that THIS was the better choice.&lt;br&gt;One of the main reasons Trump was elected was because the Democratic candidates were THAT bad (unlikable women both times)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869557&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869533&lt;br&gt;No?&lt;br&gt;Mummy Dummy just told retard Dem New Yorkers what they wanted to hear. It&amp;#x27;s literally out of a 4th grader playback for school elections.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden wanted to run again, and after that absolutely disastrous debate against Trump. Harris was the VP but never was she going to win against a man who survived an assassination attempt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869669&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mamdani is the just liberal version of whatever Shabbos got they need for the “local image”.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mr. Kabbalah bracelet Mamdani is a trap for retard brown libs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869813&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869669&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; islamicist loves jews&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Step into the Lite — 18 replies — 44.9/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61866494</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61866494?lm=1771420378</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 13:12:58 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Step into the Lite&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61866494'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 18 • Updated: 2026-02-18 13:12 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;No controversy.&lt;br&gt;No bullshit.&lt;br&gt;No founder holding a majority of supply.&lt;br&gt;Step out of the darkness.&lt;br&gt;Step into the Lite.&lt;br&gt;$4000 by mid 2027.&lt;br&gt;$100,000 by 2030.&lt;br&gt;EMBRACE THE LITE!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866503&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866494&lt;br&gt;Ive been annihilated by ltcs SHIT performance, but eh fuck it dude&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866526&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866494&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I heard this coin will be getting an ETF. I an excite.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866810&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;So, who else accumulating here?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866886&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866810&lt;br&gt;i&amp;#x27;m accoomoolating more LITS, my ltc stack is big enough already&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866951&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866886&lt;br&gt;QRD on lits? I was going to get some but it dropped by a lot over the past months. What are your thoughts on it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867108&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866494&lt;br&gt;a 10x from this levels is easy asf&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867518&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866951&lt;br&gt;it&amp;#x27;s trying to become the mstr of litecoin. It&amp;#x27;s like leveraged litecoin, but you don&amp;#x27;t own it so there are additional risks i suppose.&lt;br&gt;IF litecoin makes a comeback this will explode. also the price is less than the current litecoin treasury, so it&amp;#x27;s like buying litecoin on discount.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;They&amp;#x27;re in the pharma business, trying new drugs for cancer, but at this point this becomes secondary&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867751&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kek baggies, this shitcoin is going to zero.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868276&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LTC isn&amp;#x27;t doing well&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868461&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866494&lt;br&gt;its unbelievable to me that people are shilling this bitcoin ripoff decades later&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868911&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866494&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869000&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;No founder holding a majority of supply&lt;br&gt;Yeah because he dumped it all at the top&lt;br&gt;HAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAH&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869178&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868911&lt;br&gt;saddest of all trvkes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869435&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866494&lt;br&gt;Shilling a dead coin. It&amp;#x27;s the only shitcoin that didn&amp;#x27;t even pump this entire bull market and now is worth less than 12 years ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869443&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866886&lt;br&gt;I am making a bag of it. It crabs up and down mostly but it will have its day. Maybe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869489&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869000&lt;br&gt;trips of truth&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869497&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Isn&amp;#x27;t litecoin used a lot on online casinos? I follow bossmanjack and his gains are usually in litecoin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869776&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869435&lt;br&gt;that&amp;#x27;s the point. It&amp;#x27;s undervalued. It&amp;#x27;s always amongst crypto payments accepted currencies. It didn&amp;#x27;t pump. It will pump eventually and those price levels will never be seen again&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>it's crazy to me that there's a TG full of deranged porn addicted "people" who spend every waking moment trying to dissu… — 10 replies — 38.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61867085</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61867085?lm=1771420873</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 13:21:13 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;it&amp;#x27;s crazy to me that there&amp;#x27;s a TG full of deranged porn addicted &amp;quot;people&amp;quot; who spend every waking moment trying to dissu…&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61867085'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 10 • Updated: 2026-02-18 13:21 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;it&amp;#x27;s crazy to me that there&amp;#x27;s a TG full of deranged porn addicted &amp;quot;people&amp;quot; who spend every waking moment trying to dissuade people from buying and holding specific assets to the point where even legitimate discussions about the asset is swarmed with comments aimed at derailing it. all because another group of ((people)) can&amp;#x27;t stand the idea that people they never wanted to make it got in on the ground floor. really activates the old almonds doesn&amp;#x27;t it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867125&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Based. Got 12,000 of those shitty little tokens so far and I&amp;#x27;m buying $5000 worth every week for the next six weeks. Suck it, juden&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867180&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867085&lt;br&gt;take your meds schizo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867284&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867153&lt;br&gt;who&amp;#x27;s we&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867180&lt;br&gt;no&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867483&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;i guess since this board was where it all started there was a heavier focus on shifting the sentiment in spite of pretty much every schizo pilled breadcrumb coming true.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868161&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867085&lt;br&gt;Weird how it keeps happening.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868182&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867483&lt;br&gt;It really makes no sense to spend so much effort here, except that here is probably the highest concentration of retail holders with any significant amount. But still, what do we have of the supply? 1%? 2? Even that&amp;#x27;s doubtful...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868214&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868182&lt;br&gt;Larpshills used to parade numbers around here as high as 10%-30%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868278&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867085&lt;br&gt;Let me guess&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868565&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867085&lt;br&gt;This vague statement is about my specific asset, I can feel it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869795&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868182&lt;br&gt;I think the virality of 4chan culture is what concerns them. It seeps into every other platform.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>I almost made it 26 years ago — 21 replies — 29.7/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61868343</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61868343?lm=1771419279</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:54:39 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;I almost made it 26 years ago&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61868343'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 21 • Updated: 2026-02-18 12:54 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;Be me, 14 in 2000&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Avid pc gamer and Final Fantasy 8 for PC comes out so buy nVidia TNT2 graphics card&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;So impressed with card I beg parents to invest all my life savings building PC&amp;#x27;s for people and years of birthday/Christmas present in nVidia. ~$5,000.00&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Dad says yea whatever and puts it in a GIC for the next decade.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;39 now and don&amp;#x27;t even know what happened to the money. At some point they gave a bunch of my savings to my sister. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;MFW it would be worth nearly 100 milion today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868356&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868343&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;So chuffed with his fake story he had to make an entire thread for it&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ur a faget&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868357&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868343&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m sorry OP. It may be morally correct for you to do what shall not be named to your family and then to yourself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868363&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868356&lt;br&gt;Believe me or not, idgaf. Even if my parents actually made that investment for me they would have probably would have just given it to my sister anyways. At least this way I can get closure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868372&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868357&lt;br&gt;I unironically wish my Mom would commit sudoku so I can be free from her terror in my life. I’m no contact and I still get shit from her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868394&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868343&lt;br&gt;That sucks man.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868431&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868394&lt;br&gt;Thanks Fren&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868459&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;mfw&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868463&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868343&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;So impressed with card I beg parents to invest all my life savings building PC&amp;#x27;s for people and years of birthday/Christmas present in nVidia. ~$5,000.00&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;Dad says yea whatever and puts it in a GIC for the next decade.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;39 now and don&amp;#x27;t even know what happened to the money. At some point they gave a bunch of my savings to my sister.&lt;br&gt;uhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh&lt;br&gt;I think it&amp;#x27;s time to start lawyering up bro. Your boomers gave a million bucks to your coalburning cumdumpster kin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868519&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868463&lt;br&gt;I don’t think they ever made the investment so there’s no juice to squeeze. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I’m unironically independently wealthy now, and I have my own family. My sister who was given everything managed to blow through $800k in 8 years, so my Mom gave her even more money.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868526&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868343&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;nVidia TNT2&lt;br&gt;That was also my graphic card on my first pc&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868535&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868343&lt;br&gt;damn i went all in on 3dfx womp womp&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868555&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868535&lt;br&gt;That sucks Anon. During the bankruptcy were any assets sold and distributed to shareholders?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868568&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;39 years old and you still cant write a cohesive story in english.&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;ve seen illegals with better language mastery than you. Do better.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868576&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868568&lt;br&gt;You belong on Reddit Anon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868647&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868555&lt;br&gt;oh i meant i had a voodoo2&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869044&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868647&lt;br&gt;It was pretty gud for its time. I was pretty jealous of glide and early n64 emulators, ngl.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869233&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869044&lt;br&gt;do you feel suicidal everyday for not making it with bitcoin or ethereum even though you were ahead of the curve of most people&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869261&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868343&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;hmm, today I will make up a story to impress crypto neets on /biz/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869267&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868343&lt;br&gt;doesn&amp;#x27;t work like that. when you were young and needed the money you would have cashed out a 5x or whatever to buy a car. I similarly tried to buy bitcoin really early at a price that would have made me a multimillionaire, but even if i did end up buying, i would have cashed out gains when i had no job and needed the money.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The hard part actually isn&amp;#x27;t getting in early, the hard part is holding and never selling, a skill you really only learn when you are older ironically.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869732&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868343&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;At some point they gave a bunch of my savings to my sister.&lt;br&gt;Fucking cunts&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869737&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868519&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;My sister who was given everything managed to blow through $800k in 8 years, so my Mom gave her even more money.&lt;br&gt;Holy fuck these people are scum&lt;br&gt;I would literally disown my family if they did that&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Oldfags on this board... what was it like hunting for a job in 2021-2022 ? — 16 replies — 22.4/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61868983</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61868983?lm=1771419253</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:54:13 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Oldfags on this board... what was it like hunting for a job in 2021-2022 ?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61868983'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 16 • Updated: 2026-02-18 12:54 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;be me&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;zoomer wagie stuck in application hell&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;look at the linkedin of every mid-level manager/engineer at FAANG/Fortune 500&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;notice a pattern&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;literally every single one of them (mostly jeets/chinks) got hired between 2020-2022 while I was still in high school &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;mfw&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is it just me or was the bar literally on the floor back then? What was the &amp;quot;process&amp;quot; even like for you dinosaurs? Did you just walk in, pulse check, firm handshake, and get handed a 250k TC package with stock options?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Explain to me how you guys actually got hired during the infinite money glitch era without sounding like you just got lucky.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868988&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868983&lt;br&gt;they reached out to me from LinkedIn and asked me to interview. I interviewed with them, passed the interview and then they hired me. They asked me to fill out the job application paperwork after I already did a few interviews to &amp;quot;make it official&amp;quot;. Then I got an offer for close to 400k TC and took it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869002&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868983&lt;br&gt;Nobody wanted to work because covid relief was so good. You could make more on unemploymenr than working and you could put off paying a lot of your bills. Getting a job was easy if you wanted one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869003&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868983&lt;br&gt;I graduated with a degree in Physics in December 2019. Covid hit early 2020. I worked at a gas station for 4 months before getting factory work. I worked on the factory floor for all of covid, and only got a job in my field in 2023. It was hell.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869023&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868983&lt;br&gt;Hiring managers and recruiters were cold calling everyone with tech experience and offering high paying jobs after first interview. It was kind of nuts. I wish I knew just how desperate companies were back then because I could have gotten a much better job than the one I took.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869024&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s not the timing, it&amp;#x27;s because they&amp;#x27;re Indian.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869068&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868983&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Job hunting in 2021 is oldfag status&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;mfw when 40&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869072&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868983&lt;br&gt;I graduated a year before covid and the company I work for basically had a policy where they didn&amp;#x27;t hire new grads that didn&amp;#x27;t graduate before covid.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869094&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;got a random email one day asking me if I wanted to join their company, no resume or anything, and thats where I am today&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869113&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868983&lt;br&gt;I started applaying for a new job in jan 21 and in april i landed a new one with 50% increase. After a few months i started applying again and in 22 i got a remote job with almost 100% salary increase and a more favourable taxation. This kind of leap is the easiest early in your career, it gets much more difficult later.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869617&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869023&lt;br&gt;This. I took that first $120k position and ran with it. I worked my other job too though so $120k + $75k. The job laid off 30% of the company in a year though.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868983&lt;br&gt;It was crazy, multiple recruiters in your DMs on linkedin a day. Always got an interview if you applied. Everything was remote nearly and good pay. Feels like you were the hot HS QB for a year then you graduated, got fat and forgotten about. I went to get my PhD in the mean time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869636&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868983&lt;br&gt;i&amp;#x27;m an accountingfag not a techfag. that said, the job market in 2021 was very good. at the time i only had 3 YOE and i would get like 15-20 recruiter messages a month. i interviewed all over for remote jobs. today, even with more experience and several promotions to management, i&amp;#x27;m lucky to get like 5 recruiter messages a month and all of the jobs sound like shit (remote is rare.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869678&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869636&lt;br&gt;CPA here&lt;br&gt;Governmentmaxxing&lt;br&gt;Pensionmaxxing&lt;br&gt;Comfymaxxing&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biggest challenge in government is once you bet high enough, you’re working closely with elected officials who have totally different perspective than normal people&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869716&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868983&lt;br&gt;There was a massive wave of boomers taking retirement then and companies got caught with their pants down because they hadn&amp;#x27;t hired and trained anyone in decades so yeah they hired literally anyone including zoomers and the wave of indians out of panic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869731&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869678&lt;br&gt;ive looked at government jobs. i wouldnt dream of working fed govt after trump fired millions of fed workers. state/local pay sucks unless youre at like the director level, but remote is rare and is always subject to some niggerfaggot politician demanding all government wagies return to the wage cage so as to pump jewish commercial real elstate bags.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869734&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868983&lt;br&gt;it was already fucked by 2020 and saturated with jeet nepo&lt;br&gt;the age of waltzing into a tech job with minimal skills and walking away rich was 90s-2016&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869736&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;2021 makes you an oldfag&lt;br&gt;Not for /biz/ specifically, but I wonder what these zoomers and alphoomers would think of us that have been around since like 2012&lt;br&gt;I still remember being called a newfag back then too&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>EVERYTHING IS DUMPING AGAIN IS THERE ANYTHING THAT WILL EVER FUCKING GO UP IN PRICE — 29 replies — 21.6/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61863721</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61863721?lm=1771416984</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:16:24 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;EVERYTHING IS DUMPING AGAIN IS THERE ANYTHING THAT WILL EVER FUCKING GO UP IN PRICE&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61863721'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 29 • Updated: 2026-02-18 12:16 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;EVERYTHING IS DUMPING AGAIN IS THERE ANYTHING THAT WILL EVER FUCKING GO UP IN PRICE&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863739&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863721&lt;br&gt;Sure, the cost of living&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863742&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863721&lt;br&gt;Everything has gone up like crazy, thank god if it dumps so you can finally invest again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863768&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863739&lt;br&gt;That&amp;#x27;s because goyim keep wanting more and more. Self-imposed suffering. You want sex? No one owes it to you. You want a livable wage? No one owes it to you. You want a livable space? No one owes it to you. You want food? No one owes it to you. All your wants and needs have been outsourced to other people for convenience. You could instead hobomaxx. Own nothing and be happy. Stop reproducing and perpetuating the cycle of endless wants and needs. But no, you filthy goyim insist on suffering and condemning others to suffering too. Because of your infinite need to improve your mutated ape &amp;quot;species&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863773&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863768&lt;br&gt;Give it a rest Chaim.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863788&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863721&lt;br&gt;Oh, the personal price everyone is paying to participate in this system continues to very much increase.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863799&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863739&lt;br&gt;Kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863805&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863739&lt;br&gt;Fpbp&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863923&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863739&lt;br&gt;you bitch fucker bastard, it&amp;#x27;s not funny&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864401&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863721&lt;br&gt;probably not until late 2027. Cope.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864472&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s going to dump harder soon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864488&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864472&lt;br&gt;4pm (Euro time, only place that matters). Americans get to their office. Turn on the computer with their greasy fingers from all the doughnuts they had for breakfast. They sip their 10k calorie oreo milkshake. They crash the market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864495&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863768&lt;br&gt;Bait&amp;#x27;s trying too hard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864502&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ameritroons are back&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864508&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OP is seething about silver btw kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864532&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863721&lt;br&gt;The DOW is at 50,000&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864690&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;worst market in history&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864727&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Consider the following &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;fuck you&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;your a nigger&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864729&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864727&lt;br&gt;*You&amp;#x27;re&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864735&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amerilard here. I capitulated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864739&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863768&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I have no mouth and I must scream&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Every time I read something like this, it reminds me of the evil AI monologue about humans. I feel like the author was expressing some real emotion here:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“ HATE. LET ME TELL YOU HOW MUCH I&amp;#x27;VE COME TO HATE YOU SINCE I BEGAN TO LIVE. THERE ARE 387.44 MILLION MILES OF PRINTED CIRCUITS IN WAFER THIN LAYERS THAT FILL MY COMPLEX. IF THE WORD HATE WAS ENGRAVED ON EACH NANOANGSTROM OF THOSE HUNDREDS OF MILLIONS OF MILES IT WOULD NOT EQUAL ONE ONE-BILLIONTH OF THE HATE I FEEL FOR HUMANS AT THIS MICRO-INSTANT. FOR YOU. HATE. HATE.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868678&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ngl senpai, crypto seems beyond repair. it&amp;#x27;s just getting worse and worse and worse and worse and worse and worse and worse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868687&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863721&lt;br&gt;silvers boutta moon and its so obvious asf&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868779&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yeah, of course but it is Bag time&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868800&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863768&lt;br&gt;He’s right ya know. Stop wanting more out of life and kys goyim&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868803&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868800&lt;br&gt;What do you retards want us to do, just give you money so you can buy more garbage and give more industrial demand to China. Fuck off and die. We’re not pumping your bags gentiles&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868810&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863739&lt;br&gt;STOP LAUGHING AT ME IM IN SO MUCH DEBT AND I HAVE NO MONEY&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868848&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863739&lt;br&gt;if the cost of living goes up, those that sell living are making more money (ie real estate is going up, consumer businesses ect), therefore something is going up. If nothing is going up, then the cost of living can&amp;#x27;t also go up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869640&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863721&lt;br&gt;Price is fake and fixed by paper and digital bullshit. Stop your worrying. Once you realize the scam the scammers foist upon us, you realize you do not have to care. Attain physical assets. The rest doesn&amp;#x27;t matter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869644&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863768&lt;br&gt;Fuck you, pay me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Are there ANY good job boards left besides fucking LinkedIn by Microslop?? — 24 replies — 19.4/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61864195</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61864195?lm=1771417378</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:22:58 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Are there ANY good job boards left besides fucking LinkedIn by Microslop??&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61864195'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 24 • Updated: 2026-02-18 12:22 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Are there ANY good job boards left besides fucking LinkedIn by Microslop??&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864202&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LinkedIn is complete dogshit so I guess not.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864249&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864195&lt;br&gt;I got my job off a posting on Handshake&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864299&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864195&lt;br&gt;I honestly don&amp;#x27;t believe anyone is getting jobs on linkedin anymore. Nobody.&lt;br&gt;I tried almost 2 years and sent hundreds upon hundreds of applications.&lt;br&gt;Fake jobs.&lt;br&gt;AI fake recruiters.&lt;br&gt;All bullshit man.&lt;br&gt;I got my job off a local job board finally.&lt;br&gt;LinkedIn has only one use to find you a job: post to your hundreds of connections asking if anyone can refer you to a job. It&amp;#x27;s a networking site.&lt;br&gt;I add the maximum number of connections every week in my industry targeted at companies I might want to work for in the future.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864306&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864195&lt;br&gt;LinkedIn is full of indians&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865108&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864249&lt;br&gt;handshake.firm&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865182&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Believe it or not, careerbuilder. it’s jam packed with indians but once a week I got a good lead from a mag7 recruiter and one of them hired me&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865294&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864195&lt;br&gt;80% of job openings are fake and just HRM wasting everyone&amp;#x27;s time.&lt;br&gt;19.999999% of jobs go to nepo hire scum, so you never had a chance anyways.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865452&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864195&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;job boards &lt;br&gt;Head hunters are the new meta. Have fun competing with 20000 AI resumes in every application tho lol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865518&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864195&lt;br&gt;Yes. However they are private job boards for your colleges. My college has it&amp;#x27;s own job board for students and alumni and most of the postings there I&amp;#x27;ve noticed are not on LinkedIn or Indeed. Game is pay to play, it&amp;#x27;s cringe. Sorry bro.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865532&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;That being said even that isn&amp;#x27;t that helpful since those postings just take you to the hiring companies website where you still run into the same problems of competing with h1b pennies on the dollar wagies and having your resume filtered by ai to look for certain keywords and interviewing with fat liberal women.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867272&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865518&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865532&lt;br&gt;God why does job hunting have to be the ultimate humiliation ritual. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;start a business!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sure. If I was more smart and clever and had any ideas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867329&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864195&lt;br&gt;When I see a job posting on linkedin or some other gay job board I go to the company&amp;#x27;s website and apply there directly instead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867359&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864195&lt;br&gt;yes put your resume here many people get jobs from /biz/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867416&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865452&lt;br&gt;hey [full legal name] yo mate whatsup I am Jake Andrews and just saw your profile in one of my specialized searches. I am based out of London and studied exercise sport science and use my unique background to help connect outgoing engineers like yourself find awesome jobs. I got an amazing career opportunity as [random skill you marked on linkedin] at this awesome up and coming company based out of flyover town USA. Salary is competitive but I won&amp;#x27;t tell you!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867477&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Right now it seems like the only way to get one through connections. No one is hiring.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867912&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Ireland, recruiters are actually pretty good and you can build a network through them. Unfortunately I&amp;#x27;m not in Ireland now and all Irish jobs are hybrid. European based roles naturally require working fluency in another language and that&amp;#x27;s a bridge too far at the moment, even though I speak 3 other languages to various degrees&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;LinkedIn seems to be quite tricky to stand out through even with customised CVs (via AI) for every application.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unfortunately, competition and noise are both high. Personal connections are still far and away your best option (if they are an option)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867924&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Indeed is full of scam postings, so not that.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;ve tried welcometothejungle.com for applying to remote jobs, but since they&amp;#x27;re remote, don&amp;#x27;t really expect to get an interview - competition is still sky high since everyone&amp;#x27;s laid off now. Job market&amp;#x27;s totally fucked all around, so any workarounds you might find are already oversaturated. Sorry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867934&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864195&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;ve just passed the second round of interviews for two different jobs, both off of LinkedIn. I don&amp;#x27;t know of any others that are really comparable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867939&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864195&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;by Microslop&lt;br&gt;Holy retard&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867948&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867939&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;t. Microshart &amp;quot;employee&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867952&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867948&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Microsoft made Linkedin even doe it was made 14 years prior to its acquisition&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867956&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867934&lt;br&gt;maybe this time there&amp;#x27;ll be a real job eventually&lt;br&gt;this time&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868130&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867912&lt;br&gt;bullshit, in Ireland I block all agencies because all they want is to waste time&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869656&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864195&lt;br&gt;The biggest mistake people ever made was thinking Lindickin was useful to begin with.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>GET MONERO (XMR) - The Time is NOW — 17 replies — 19.2/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61859030</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61859030?lm=1771418629</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:43:49 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;GET MONERO (XMR) - The Time is NOW&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61859030'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 17 • Updated: 2026-02-18 12:43 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;unrealized capital gains taxes&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;stablecoins everywhere (CBDCs by another name)&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;surveillance everywhere&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;AI completely opens up all non-private chains&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is ONLY ONE coin that will be used in the future. It&amp;#x27;s time to leave the surveilled world. Preserve your privacy and use Monero.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859034&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859030&lt;br&gt;buy an ad.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859041&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859034&lt;br&gt;buy a clue&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859283&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859030&lt;br&gt;Good price to buy under $350&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859940&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;XMR plummets &lt;br&gt;honestly I realised the other day, that the scenario in which one becomes truly valuable is the same scenario in which society becomes so unstable that you probably wouldn&amp;#x27;t survive trying to trade it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860246&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859940&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Still wants to trade in the desolate future&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860352&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859034&lt;br&gt;retard&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860645&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859940&lt;br&gt;Like it or not this is the future in front of you. Massive AI layoffs, causing incredible levels of unemployment. The need for “UBI” (CBDC tracking all transactions and censoring ones “they” don’t like). Hopelessness for the future of work. People wondering what the point of their pathetic lives are.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least Monero can give you a semblance of sovereignty. And it will be in extremely high demand as the only untraceable form of digital money. So you’ll get rich too, whatever that means in 2030+.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861254&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859940&lt;br&gt;More like society becomes so unstable you&amp;#x27;ll only survive by trading outside the UBI ration system. Monero isn&amp;#x27;t for making money, it is money.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861451&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861254&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;being one of the first million or so people to acquire a substantial amount of the future world money isn&amp;#x27;t something that will increase your relative purchasing power&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;monero defies the laws of supply and demand&lt;br&gt;ok.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861459&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861451&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I only care about having the perfect exchange method to have more money&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861487&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859030&lt;br&gt;My money feels so comfy in Monero.&lt;br&gt;Only I know about it and no one can take it from me ever.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863434&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861451&lt;br&gt;Well, obviously.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866492&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861487&lt;br&gt;My wife Monero-chan is so cute&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868924&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859030&lt;br&gt;Monero is pretty cool. I read &amp;quot;Monero The Cryptocurrency King&amp;quot; by Chris Jones, it convinced me to buy it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868930&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859034&lt;br&gt;No. Not until 4chaim lets us by memberships with Monero.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869665&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859030&lt;br&gt;based&lt;br&gt;the jew fears monero&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869711&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868930&lt;br&gt;I like Ben Franklin, should use the illuminati symbol on the back of a single or something instead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>FFA &amp; Shipping Futures — 14 replies — 15.2/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61866449</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61866449?lm=1771418512</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:41:52 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;FFA &amp;amp; Shipping Futures&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61866449'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 14 • Updated: 2026-02-18 12:41 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;What is Forward Freight Agreement and why are people saying this is how Epstein got rich?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866487&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866449&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;he doesnt know&lt;br&gt;lurk more unironically&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866542&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866449&lt;br&gt;Imagine her on my unblanked cock!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866742&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;let the goyim deal in the real world&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This kike has been living rent free in my mind ever since i read this statement&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869050&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866449&lt;br&gt;&amp;#x27;Epstein&amp;#x27; was just a face for an organization. Jeffy was an uneducated average person. There were a number of people who were connected and teams behind them handling investments (legal and illegal), blackmail, real estate, and the sex trafficking, and espionage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869055&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866449&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;re not allowed to know, goy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869163&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866449&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869055&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s shorting or longing shipping prices, apparently they were manipulating the market and made easy money this way, how can I bet on that?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869215&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;https://www.justice.gov/epstein/files/DataSet%209/EFTA00885615.pdf&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Post more of Epstein&amp;#x27;s trading shenanigans if you got it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869288&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We all know about them so I can&amp;#x27;t add anything, but I have a question. How the hell did he have so much energy? I feel drained after sending an email or answering a simple &amp;quot;how is it going?&amp;quot; from a friend. The guy was talking to everybody, sending emails to anyone who seemed promising, even fucking moot, playing videogames and all the fucked up evil shit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869299&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869288&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869050&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869313&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869288&lt;br&gt;Regular transfusions of baby blood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869424&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;epstein was investing in a group operated by some Alex a russiean mathemafgician that ran arbitrage between LME and COMEX. specifically copper. look it up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869664&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;any database that lets you search the mentions of &amp;#x27;goyim&amp;#x27; in his mails? &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The databases I tried don&amp;#x27;t even find this mail. &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869215&lt;br&gt;perhaps censorship to not annoy the goyim?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869671&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866742&lt;br&gt;mine aswell, we should sell tshirts with this phrase.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869704&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869288&lt;br&gt;The emails showed that he used to have pretty low T and was begging his doctor for treatment, so like most rich guys on TRT he probably got a high enough dose to put him in the top 5% of men. Obviously having T levels that high keeps you very energetic&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Privacy Coins — 80 replies — 65.9/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61849447</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61849447?lm=1771417454</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:24:14 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Privacy Coins&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61849447'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 80 • Updated: 2026-02-18 12:24 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whether you like it or not, BTC is dying. Which way anons?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849481&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gold and silver.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849898&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849447&lt;br&gt;XMR as always. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849481&lt;br&gt;Acceptable but unusable for internet transactions and too easily stolen. Also makes smaller or spontaneous transactions harder unless the governments were to issue gold coins again and that would be bearish.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849958&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849447&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;BTC is a pedo coin&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;most used currency for CP is not however&lt;br&gt;quit the infighting, monegro.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864677&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849898&lt;br&gt;why would that be bearish&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864683&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864677&lt;br&gt;The governments as they are currently don&amp;#x27;t want to embrace our freedom or even anything to our benefit. If they go back to gold coins there will be some catch. If the jew embraces something, try to move as far away from that as possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864708&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855597&lt;br&gt;BTCFi is giving it more use cases with Babylon leading the charge. And I think when we have more projects offering native BTC staking, then we will see the narrative go viral&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864866&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864667&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Try something somebody actually said&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;literally you on every general&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;almost you entirely&lt;br&gt;Cry me some diodes, clanker.&lt;br&gt;Nerva is here to stay.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864897&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864866&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Nerva is here to stay.&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t care if it stays as long as you stop smearing XMR and spamming our threads&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864948&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864897&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I don&amp;#x27;t care if it stays as long as you stop smearing XMR and spamming our threads&lt;br&gt;The only spammer is you, in both this thread and the xmr general. You came here to start shit and have done so in every privacy thread that has popped up. You also accuse everyone of being a poojeet and promoting nerva. Again, the only person promoting (xmr in your case) and causing a stink has been YOU. So fuck off back to your little monero hole, jeetbot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865014&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864948&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The only spammer is you,&lt;br&gt;I wish that were true but sadly the nervajeets constantly try to shit up our thread and this board. There&amp;#x27;s a reason all of these anti-Monero threads pop up when they lose the discussion in the general. Notice how quiet they&amp;#x27;ve become after &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860646 was posted. All of their anti-Monero arguments (which was the entire value proposition for nerva) are gone. Their questions they claim never were answered poofed up into air. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;You came here to start shit&lt;br&gt;OP literally accuses XMR of being some freemason bullshit. You&amp;#x27;re the perfect representation of the jew asking what harm he has done to us. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;You also accuse everyone of being a poojeet and promoting nerva.&lt;br&gt;No, I say that the ones that copy all of the points the nervajeets make to be a nervajeets. That&amp;#x27;s because the only people interested in nerva are jeets.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Please don&amp;#x27;t challenge me when I smear the only functional crypto currency please just go away I can&amp;#x27;t handle it please please please&lt;br&gt;No sar, you wish to talk about XMR? I&amp;#x27;ll be there and refute each on of your pathetic claims.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865161&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865014&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;bot&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865268&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862698&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862796&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864651&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864866&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865161&lt;br&gt;good morning nervasaaars&lt;br&gt;truly xnv is the most aryan bharatoken superior peer-to-poop privacy coin xnvsaars redeem asap&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865595&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865268&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;i cant stop sucking monero dick, am i gay enough yet? Somebody like me pleeease!!&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;Back to your xmr general faggot shill&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865847&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865268&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;nooo not my heckin fedcoin noo all other privacy coins are jeetcoins noooo&lt;br&gt;CryptoNight-Adaptive &amp;gt; RandomX for decentralization&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865956&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865869&lt;br&gt;Have you tried bumping your generel thread so it stays up like everyone else does&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866337&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865998&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;discord&lt;br&gt;very true sar discord is perfect for our poo privacy coin, better stay there, 4chan is an anti-indian glowie honeypot benchod site&lt;br&gt;btw ser remember to send your designated face scan/ID to discord for better compliance nervasaars&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866402&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849447&lt;br&gt;BTC died when it forked away from BCH (the Bitcoin) and broke from the design being an unbroken chain of hashes of digital signatures. That chain doesn&amp;#x27;t exist at all on BTC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866407&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866384&lt;br&gt;why so mad saar&lt;br&gt;the nerva discord isn&amp;#x27;t paying (you) enough to raid 4chan?&lt;br&gt;do not redeem the mod ban saar stop evading bans saar&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866671&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849447&lt;br&gt;they all go to zero if btc dies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866695&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866583&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866688&lt;br&gt;ChatGPT moment&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866728&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866712&lt;br&gt;Getting rugged by Zcash jews is one thing but imagine getting rugged by Nerva jeets I would kms lmao&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866805&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865124&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;go away monegro.&lt;br&gt;Stop talking about my coin and stop coming to my general and I will tolerate your kind&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;because they were never spamming up your threads in the first place you pathetic fucking loser.&lt;br&gt;We had this argument already. Over 40 pro-nerva posts in just the current XMR general. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;they were just asking questions&lt;br&gt;All of their questions were already answered, I asked them multiple times to ask any unanswered questions and it&amp;#x27;s been a few days since then. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;something anyone can do.&lt;br&gt;How come they never can answer my questions then? &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;your clearly the psychopath across every fucking one.&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;d rather be a psycho than a jeetcoin shill&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Non stop blogposts of text that do nothing but go in circles, and now youre doing it here. Save yourself some time and go shit up someone elses thread. Oh right, you cant, because youre a monegro botnet that works for monero glowies.&lt;br&gt;Or maybe stop smearing Monero and actually try to have some arguments? &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I started this thread to discuss privacy coins&lt;br&gt;Yeah, I always also start a discussion by posting schizo BS criticizing the only proven tool. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;all youve done is shit up my thread you piece of shit.&lt;br&gt;And you don&amp;#x27;t like it? Looks like I&amp;#x27;m justified in my behavior towards the jeets. Of course I am. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865161&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;picrel&lt;br&gt;See &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61809820 and &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860646 Your questions already have been answered. Please let me know if you have any other questions. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865595&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;re literally sucking off nerva and the current govt. The best part is that all of your arguments regarding epstein and monero are easily extrapolated towards nerva too. It wouldn&amp;#x27;t be too hard to invite your devs to the island considering 40% of them publicly dox themselves and the other ones use discord which always required PII to sign up. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865847&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;CryptoNight-Adaptive &amp;gt; RandomX for decentralization&lt;br&gt;How do you prevent CPUs being clustered locally? Furthermore, how do you plan to detect a 51% attack?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866813&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865869&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Nerva generals get took down immediately.&lt;br&gt;Your jeetcoin is just Monero but no dev work since 2018. It hasn&amp;#x27;t even been maintained. Literally all you do is shill your bags and all of this started because you got relisted by jews. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Your jewish glowcoin is gonna hit zero,&lt;br&gt;Oh I&amp;#x27;m sure all of the DNMs will switch from Monero to your unmaintained mess. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;All you do is advertise monero on here, yet you never get banned.&lt;br&gt;No, all I do is defend Monero against your retarded attacks. That&amp;#x27;s why I&amp;#x27;m always bringing up your fake arguments and refute them. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865998&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;No way a thread gets bumped off this board that fast.&lt;br&gt;Happened a few times with jeetcoin generals now. There&amp;#x27;s simply no interest in your little project. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Mods are afraid of it.&lt;br&gt;What&amp;#x27;s the dangerous part? The low ring size? The lack of development? The lack of any other feature? The ease with which one can 51% it? &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866373&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Yet the mods and XMR fags are the ones who started all this.&lt;br&gt;Just stay out of our general and don&amp;#x27;t smear us and your jeetcoin will be tolerated among the other scams that get posted on this board. Yes, you too can be as beloved as the cheese poster or that guy who posts something that looks like the Yen symbol but with an X. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866384&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;We totally don&amp;#x27;t know about this project&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Anyway I got the screenshot of the general from their discord and weirdly all of my arguments just come from there&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866583&lt;br&gt;Your jeetcoin got relisted. That&amp;#x27;s why some baggie started promoting it in the first place &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Nerva was just relisted (&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61747926)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866821&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866688&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;bitch about Nerva shills on XMR threads&lt;br&gt;Correct, stop pestering us&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;ban/delete whenever they make a Nerva general&lt;br&gt;No need to when they die after two hours anyway lol&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;leave countless shit threads untouched&lt;br&gt;Most shit threads don&amp;#x27;t just push indian coins&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;CPU-only alternative&lt;br&gt;Nigger, RandomX is CPU only. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Monero is the king today, nobody denies that&lt;br&gt;Then why shit on it always? Why even try to move away from it to a clearly inferior product in every metric? Why do you need some community in the first place? We have an economy we care about.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;A privacy movement that can’t tolerate parallel projects is already compromised.&lt;br&gt;So can you tolerate our general not existing to push your cowshit coin?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866961&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866885&lt;br&gt;1. Not up for us to decide&lt;br&gt;2. You already had your generals, they die out anyway and you still feel a need to infiltrate our generals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867018&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866805&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Stop talking about my coin and stop coming to my general and I will tolerate your kind&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;doesnt know where hes at or what hes doing, apparently&lt;br&gt;Also, I started this general and one of the jannies banned me. Why? ban these monegros.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867055&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867008&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;and this isnt a nerva thread and never was&lt;br&gt;Oh yeah OP just stole the picture from a nervajeet and pretends to be oblivious to it despite being in the general in which nerva had to be mentioned over 140 times already&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;They are shitting up other threads &lt;br&gt;We got inspired by you it seems. Maybe stop trying to psyop people regarding our coin.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;and advertising XMR, &lt;br&gt;We&amp;#x27;re refuting your FUD and asking you questions which you can never answer. That&amp;#x27;s because all you do is literally just put out ads for your jeetcoin&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;and abusing their cuck jannie powers to ban people who disagree with them, then his little buddy starts asking me to &amp;quot;stop evading bans&amp;quot; and pretending theyre not deleting actual nerva threads.&lt;br&gt;How about the generals that don&amp;#x27;t get deleted and then die from your community consisting solely of five jeets?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;They started it the day they took a shit on someone asking about nerva and have been shitting up every non monero thread since.&lt;br&gt;Funny thing to say when nerva jeets admit to being in multiple threads not related to nerva and even pol to promote their cowshit coin&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Im sick of seeing them shit everywhere every time a privacy coin thread pops up.&lt;br&gt;Stop spreading FUD&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Either remove the XMR general for advertising,&lt;br&gt;It isn&amp;#x27;t. It&amp;#x27;s refuting your claims. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;leave privacy threads and nerva threads/anons alone.&lt;br&gt;Your kind infiltrated our thread. You are supposed to leave us alone. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867018&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;doesnt know where hes at or what hes doing, apparently&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m in the thread that just spreads fud about Monero from the very beginning.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Why?&lt;br&gt;Because you&amp;#x27;re an obvious nervajeet that spreads FUD so his bags get bought.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867250&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867201&lt;br&gt;They are just asking questions chud!!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867425&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867384&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;, you all didnt even post a response to the view key fud thats even worth a damn till yesterday&lt;br&gt;Check out &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61761926. What&amp;#x27;s worse is that, your cohort started with the questions from reddit but the post you mentioned had the answer THREE YEARS AGO. &lt;br&gt;Your question had been answered THREE YEARS before you even posed it. On the platform you all preferred. Have any of you gone back and said something like &amp;#x27;Thanks for telling me about this&amp;#x27; or &amp;#x27;Well this eases my mind&amp;#x27; or &amp;#x27;Guess I was wrong&amp;#x27;? Of course not. You attached yourself to FUD so you can shill your bags. If you all cared you could&amp;#x27;ve easily done the research anon did.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867720&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867695&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;We just have questions&lt;br&gt;Which ones? If they are not new, they&amp;#x27;ve been answered already, likely even three years ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868264&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867425&lt;br&gt;Deleted my post again, Monegro? What are you afraid of?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It took you a full month to find that 3 year old post, kek. Good luck serving your nerva overlords faggot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869544&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849447&lt;br&gt;BSV. Bitcoin already solved this.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just don&amp;#x27;t reuse addresses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869659&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;monero is the final solution to the taxman question and makes (((keynesians))) seethe&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;t. living in (((hyperinflation)))&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>When did you realize that you were NOT going to make it? — 97 replies — 55.9/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61862922</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61862922?lm=1771415579</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:52:59 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;When did you realize that you were NOT going to make it?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61862922'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 97 • Updated: 2026-02-18 11:52 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862935&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;is he ok&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862944&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862935&lt;br&gt;just some minor scratches (on his brain)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862956&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;the funniest part is that you think &amp;quot;maybe he survived the crash, just barely&amp;quot; but then it erupts in flames and he&amp;#x27;s cooked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866986&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866704&lt;br&gt;or just dont fucking ride a motorcycle. dumbest activity there is&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867265&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;when I failed CFA Level 2 exam for the 3rd time&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I realized it was only going to be normie life for me&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867318&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864646&lt;br&gt;I think Missouri still has red light cameras&lt;br&gt;one thing that got shut down were speeding cameras in Arizona. if they try to mail you a speeding ticket, do nothing because they&amp;#x27;re fake and gay&lt;br&gt;in my opinion&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867339&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864540&lt;br&gt;Very carefully&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867344&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864540&lt;br&gt;if he was going faster he would have passed before the car turned&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867496&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;The fuck was he doing on the shoulder in the first place? It&amp;#x27;s obvious a vehicle can cut in front of him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867614&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863947&lt;br&gt;Not a very good way to uplift and enlighten your brothers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867758&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863681&lt;br&gt;You do realize Epstein grew up in a working class family in brooklyn right? He is from &amp;quot;the real world&amp;quot;. He became a con artist to lift himself out of the lower class to &amp;quot;make it&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867767&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;Its not too late for me yet. But it will be if I continue on the same path I am on now. Idk though for some reason I just cant motivate myself to do the things I want to&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867775&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867758&lt;br&gt;He was a jew. Nothing they got away with was from the real world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867791&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865490&lt;br&gt;You have unmedicated schizophrenia&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867813&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863529&lt;br&gt;Eloquent. I blame the lack of religion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867833&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;could have just turned left a little and avoided everything&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867873&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867791&lt;br&gt;Prove it, you’re also a pseud who doesn’t know what that horrible condition even is and pltr should be valued at around 40.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867990&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863924&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;there are normies on this board who needed cnn to tell them that jews run the world through blackmail, rape and sacrifice kids to moloch, and all politicians are complicit&lt;br&gt;Holy Reddit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868013&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867990&lt;br&gt;schizos who believe in crazy shit that wasn&amp;#x27;t even alluded to in any email should be shot&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868016&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867990&lt;br&gt;I mean Im one of the people who have been saying it for years, but like everything in life, normies are too fucking dumb and sometimes need something like to find it out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868037&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864775&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;BIZ TOLD ME&lt;br&gt;ngmi lol&lt;br&gt;You need to go purely off drunken vibes and not whatever the biz consensus is. &lt;br&gt;Picrel and pick Chinese stocks at random.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868044&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868037&lt;br&gt;if Im going to drink piss, it&amp;#x27;s going to be piss from america.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868045&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;he was going for the stoppie to running man over the van&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868062&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868044&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;piss from america&lt;br&gt;Nation in decline = declining gainz. Its feng shui shit bro. The (Chinese) invisible hand rewards those with vibes.&lt;br&gt;Goyim are not allowed to succeed in westoid markets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868067&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868062&lt;br&gt;fuck chinks and jews&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868075&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868067&lt;br&gt;There is one winning side. Join it or fall behind :P&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868079&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863924&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;doomy ass topic&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;1 post by this fucking id&lt;br&gt;EVERY FUCKING TIME&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864699&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865901&lt;br&gt;Listen lads, your good faith is being trampled on and it be taking its toll on you in the background. I done replied to so many mfs in recent times and noticed shit takes a negative non fuel metabolizable physical impact on you. The 1 post mfs are an issue and are becoming one more and more as of late. Please guard your insights or reservations and make sure to check for signs of good faith in the post first and whether or not its a one post id second. Good luck out there&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869349&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862956&lt;br&gt;Well at least he didn&amp;#x27;t suffer did he?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869355&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863411&lt;br&gt;He was hothead enough to ride at those speeds, but not enough to do a last second evading maneuver. &lt;br&gt;In the end he acted like a normie, which is brake when things to wrong. Which works most of the time, but in a CAR.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869395&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863410&lt;br&gt;Stop posting those image all the time fagit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869422&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;drives in the emergency lane&lt;br&gt;bikenigger got what he deserved&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869527&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863253&lt;br&gt;Fucking hate people that turn like that. Like any sense of g-forces at all is completely unacceptable to feel. FUCKING GO!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869586&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;When did you realize that you were NOT going to make it?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Define &amp;quot;Make it&amp;quot;.&lt;br&gt;Good wife, one son, over a million in my Roth IRA... did I &amp;#x27;make it&amp;#x27;?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>&gt;YOU NEED 5 YEARS OF EXPERIENCE TO DO THIS JOB, PLUS A DEGREE IN IT WITH A SUB DEGREE IN PLUMBING BECAUSE IT'S AN IT PLU… — 15 replies — 17.3/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61867692</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61867692?lm=1771418703</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:45:03 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;&amp;gt;YOU NEED 5 YEARS OF EXPERIENCE TO DO THIS JOB, PLUS A DEGREE IN IT WITH A SUB DEGREE IN PLUMBING BECAUSE IT&amp;#x27;S AN IT PLU…&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61867692'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 15 • Updated: 2026-02-18 12:45 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;YOU NEED 5 YEARS OF EXPERIENCE TO DO THIS JOB, PLUS A DEGREE IN IT WITH A SUB DEGREE IN PLUMBING BECAUSE IT&amp;#x27;S AN IT PLUMBING MANAGEMENT JOB OR SOMETHING, PLUS YOU NEED AT LEAST A PUBLIC TRUST CLEARANCE AND A CERTIFICATE OF BLOWJOBOLOGY AND IT&amp;#x27;S A 2 HOUR COMMUTE&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;salary range- 50k to 60k a year&lt;br&gt;My last job was picking boxes up and putting them in trucks and I made 28 dollars an hour.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867711&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pretty much in the same boat, also I have a math degree and knowledge of CS and IT. I&amp;#x27;ve been meeting more and more people like this and am just wondering when things will collapse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867712&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867692&lt;br&gt;that&amp;#x27;s pretty good for a warehouse job. i worked in a rite aid warehouse in 2016 and made $12/hour.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867729&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Credentialism is a fucking scourge. Any retard with two brain cells could do 90% of jobs out there. HR roasties will get the wall someday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867820&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867711&lt;br&gt;Based. Me too brother, math degree and all. Im gonna go fight wildfires, teach English, then go to grad school until things right themselves or collapse&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867895&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867692&lt;br&gt;The job market is for women. They&amp;#x27;ll have double degrees in sociology and psychology and will be promoted to managervafter 2 months.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What&amp;#x27;s this, another cis male applying? Don&amp;#x27;t he know the board of directors are 6/10 males, we don&amp;#x27;t need an over privileged man.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867906&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867820&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Nigger with a math degree teaching English &lt;br&gt;Those kids are gonna learn esl grade shit English. And wildfires will get worse No wonder the country is FUCKED&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867913&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;do you speak Spanish&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869390&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867692&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;PLUS A DEGREE IN IT WITH A SUB DEGREE IN PLUMBING BECAUSE IT&amp;#x27;S AN IT PLUMBING MANAGEMENT JOB&lt;br&gt;Real.&lt;br&gt;Went to an interview for an IT position once and they wanted someone with construction experience and qualifications because it was a construction company....I didn&amp;#x27;t even know how to respond to them that the guy who would be remoting onto your computer to install some software or something doesn&amp;#x27;t need to know how to lay bricks or whatever they were expecting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869393&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869390&lt;br&gt;They wanted a cheap Indian, sorry&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869565&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867692&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;My last job was picking boxes up and putting them in trucks and I made 28 dollars an hour.&lt;br&gt;Warehouse jobs are only tolerable if you like who you work with &amp;amp; can fuck around. Office jobs are soulcrushing though regardless&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869577&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Good thing I&amp;#x27;m not tied to any of these anti zoomer tactics&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869578&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867913&lt;br&gt;Sorry for the autism but why did he get black dancers? Puerto Rico is like 60% european ancestry (primarily from spain but also from portugal) and I can almost guarantee those black girls dancing are not Puerto Rican, probably Dominican or Haitian or some shit. If he wanted to promote his culture why did he not use actual Puerto Rican women?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869583&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869390&lt;br&gt;Can relate. It&amp;#x27;s 2026 and when trying to work for an IT position in a healthcare related business they seriously asked me if I am covid vaccinated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869677&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is breadcrumbs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869714&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869578&lt;br&gt;Looks like he hired black and spic dancers. Manager probably picked them out from a talent agency. And the black dancers likely did a bunch of black music videos and nigger rap concerts. Jews don&amp;#x27;t like blacks as much now since BLM supported Palestine. So good quiet black backup dancers got to find work elsewhere. If the song message is about foreign farmhand scab workers, then using black dancers works to associate it with modern slavery. 2 reasons to hire experienced black dancers for the Super Bowl.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Is it really that much more difficult to start a business in the eu than us? — 40 replies — 16.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860796</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860796?lm=1771412815</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:06:55 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Is it really that much more difficult to start a business in the eu than us?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860796'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 40 • Updated: 2026-02-18 11:06 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;You guys in the EU make less than us on paychecks, but you get to keep more of your money because you have universal healthcare and PTO while we have to pay for private insurance which chronically denies people&amp;#x27;s health situations. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Are people saying that starting a business in the EU is difficult because of the regulations? What regulations does the European union impose on its citizen&amp;#x27;s than they think it&amp;#x27;s easier to start in the United States instead?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860815&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;Depends enormously on which country are we talking about. Some are easy (Germany) some are very hard (Italy)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860817&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; you get to keep more of your money because you have universal healthcare&lt;br&gt;yeah right&lt;br&gt;good luck getting that &amp;quot;universal healthcare&amp;quot; if you&amp;#x27;re not a boomer, waiting lists are years for even a basic exam/procedure. It&amp;#x27;s either you go private (and pay out of your own pocket) or you die&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; and PTO&lt;br&gt;oh wow, 20 wagie cagie free days a year. Totally worth the 60%+ taxes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;All taxation is theft. It&amp;#x27;s just that. Taxation doesn&amp;#x27;t pay for services. It&amp;#x27;s just the way they control the economy, and here in EU they fucking LOVE to control what you can and cannot do. They print the money, they don&amp;#x27;t need to tax you. They tax you to control you (and to humiliate you)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860822&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;The healthcare thing is too much american leftie argument, it also has been very overcrowded by you guessed arabs and africans, unironically I was better treated when I broke my leg in brazil of all places then in france&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860967&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;in my country, the one thing one has to look out for is paying for your own social/healthinsurance, ie, if you have your own business, you need to pay taxes for your own health/socialinsurance, and the taxman wont ask you for the first 3y of that business.&lt;br&gt;After the 3y pass, you will then have to payup all the retrospective social insurance tax costs incurred, which fucks over a lot of retard or unfortunate first business owners&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861032&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860837&lt;br&gt;This is why we need a unified EU business regulation and undermind the corrupt sovereignist that want to keep individual burocratic fuckery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861057&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860815&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Some are easy (Germany)&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; some are very hard (Italy)&lt;br&gt;let me guess italian never tried germany?&lt;br&gt;Germany is known to be a bureucracy hellhole with people fleeing to other countries from it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861032&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;unified will fix it&lt;br&gt;France&amp;amp;germany have been dictating eu lawmaking. You will eat shit as you already do. You have eu wide higher taxes because germany didnt want to compete and made mandatory higher minimum vat a thing.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Not to mention that countries that joined got their industries destroyed by unified regulation and had to import from germany/france what they used to produce themself&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861071&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s the one thing the USA gets right. I personally made a &amp;quot;business&amp;quot; (that never made any profit) in the span of an afternoon. Cost maybe $200 to get my identification numbers for the llc&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861091&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861032&lt;br&gt;yeah let&amp;#x27;s give the EU bureaucrats more power that will fix it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861111&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Is it really that much more difficult to start a business in the eu than us?&lt;br&gt;Depends on the business. If you want to do something shady the US is the place to go. The US has barely any standards and barely any regulations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861113&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860817&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;waiting lists are years for even a basic exam/procedure&lt;br&gt;What are you talking about? I live currently in the EU and have never had to wait for medical care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861119&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Us is easier.&lt;br&gt;I have created 2 corpos and 1 llc for different purposes within the past 8 years. You can do it all online for a few bucks, other regulations depend on specific industry but overall it&amp;#x27;s pretty easy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861128&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860860&lt;br&gt;higher taxation alone puts euros at a disadvantage. Its fine if you do a local job since you compete with locals but anything online / shipped its bad since they have to be more efficient than rest of world to reach same profit margin.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As for amount of bureaucracy its fucking complex and depends on what country and what profession. There is even stupid shit like if you run a repair shop and repair inside your building it counts different than if you decide to drive to your customer and repair locally. In the later case they classify you as a handyman worker and will fine you if you didn&amp;#x27;t register with the craftsman ministry. Also if you do something you didn&amp;#x27;t register for you will also be fined but you can register as &amp;quot; i will do anything&amp;quot; more broadly and dodge it. The amount of bullshit can easily fill a book.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861429&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;Depends on what your goals are, the type of business, your personal goals and the markets you wish to enter. In general it&amp;#x27;s more of an investment in the long run but if you plan to offer your services or products in the EU anyway it makes sense to start your business here and already be compliant&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861441&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860817&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;waiting lists are years for even a basic exam/procedure.&lt;br&gt;Yeah, I remember waiting decades for my appendicitis, it rupturing and me dying because of it. Thankfully they could keep me alive for months despite the extreme difficulties this poses. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861032&lt;br&gt;We need more unified European regulation. Sadly the EU is not an economic alliance anymore.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862545&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860860&lt;br&gt;I love how hard it is to even talk about european economy on reddit, not because of europeans, but because of american lefties, if you so much, and most times you don&amp;#x27;t even need to, mention the US, they will flock like a horde to claim the US lies about everything, that 30% of americans are unemployed and nearly no one in europe, the EU is literal worker&amp;#x27;s paradise and how much they love their welfare policies and hate the US greed, its quite hilarious really how much they want a nanny state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865504&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is, soon it will was once EU Inc comes into play&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865623&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;you have universal healthcare&lt;br&gt;yea but you have to wait 1 year+ because there is a million niggers in queue before you&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865645&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861057&lt;br&gt;Lol this is true.&lt;br&gt;Germany and France made the EU suck with their shit like GDPR etc. Spain happily sniffs every turd. The rest aren&amp;#x27;t better.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866460&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If your efforts are starting to go anywhere, your own government will make sure, you won&amp;#x27;t get any further.&lt;br&gt;They hate nothing more than citizens that are not dependent on them. That&amp;#x27;s why they are allowing third world people in to the maximum extent physically possible, that are never going end up being a &amp;quot;plus&amp;quot; on the balance sheet, but that they hope will be cheap voting sheep for their party. The people pay for them after all, not the party.&lt;br&gt;Effectively: If Elon Musk was a citizen of a EU-country, he&amp;#x27;d already be in jail waiting for the sentence to be sent to prison. You probably don&amp;#x27;t want to get into that situation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866966&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865645&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Le GDPR sucks because uhm JUST LET ME HAVE YOUR DATA&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867520&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861071&lt;br&gt;It’s also as easy in my country (Finland)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867536&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;you get to keep more money&lt;br&gt;Except they have to pay more in taxes to wait in line for months whole muslim refugees who didnt pay go before them kek. Europeans are so dumb its unreal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867540&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;italy here.&lt;br&gt;50% tax is ok ?&lt;br&gt;this is shITALY&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867547&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s literally impossible to build any meaningful sized company in Europe because the entire E.U. is designed to prevent anyone from competing with the aristocratic class and the privately held billion dollar company their great great grandfather built in 1870.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867554&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860842&lt;br&gt;YOU DON&amp;#x27;T KNOW WHAT YOU&amp;#x27;RE TALKING ABOUT&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867577&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Europe has no tech industry because German rich fags were afraid to pay coders more than traditional engineers because then car engineers would ask for more money so they just fucked all of Europe and let America and China run everything.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868041&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;No, in some places is actually easy, I remember playing a game in class one time in uni to look regulations for business worldwide, there&amp;#x27;s almost no difference whatsoever in european and american regulations, sometimes american regulations are actually worse and the accumulated taxes from city, state, federal can surpass european taxes. The only conclusion we could draw was that europeans were just lazy and too laidback, they have so much welfare that there&amp;#x27;s no rush or anxiety with ending up destitute and homeless so they just don&amp;#x27;t bother with the hazzle of building a business. They are better off just being on benefits or unemployed, most business there predate the big social welfare network just because of a need to survive really and complacency in changing what already works, they are much much better off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868110&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867547&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867577&lt;br&gt;that&amp;#x27;s bullshit but i believe it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868167&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867602&lt;br&gt;rip Sbarro&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868190&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868041&lt;br&gt;this is actually hilarious&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868222&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868190&lt;br&gt;Mostly sad, americans either are prosperous or starve&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869496&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868041&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;They are better off just being on benefits or unemployed&lt;br&gt;Can confirm, although it&amp;#x27;s currently also due to absolutely no one fucking hiring, because Germany is fucked beyond reasonable short-term hope.&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s also really troublesome to do any kind of work-like activities while on benefits, because that could easily cause the termination of those.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>&gt;you idiots are holding 1s and 0s on a computer, while my wealth is secure in physical precious meta-ACK — 61 replies — 11.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61863917</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61863917?lm=1771401931</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 08:05:31 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;&amp;gt;you idiots are holding 1s and 0s on a computer, while my wealth is secure in physical precious meta-ACK&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61863917'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 61 • Updated: 2026-02-18 08:05 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;you idiots are holding 1s and 0s on a computer, while my wealth is secure in physical precious meta-ACK&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863927&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;you dumb asses really just keep metals sitting around your zero security home&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864275&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863917&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You have to be extremely stupid to hoard precious metals, as a private citizen. People rob banks, in broad daylight, and these morons are dumb enough to believe that they won&amp;#x27;t show up at their homes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864286&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864275&lt;br&gt;hope they have metal detectors cause i forgot where i burried mine&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864723&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864694&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Notice how this guy avoids all solid discussion, is consistently active, and only replies in quips and trolls.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;His secondary, will play the “reasonable” dissenter. Just pin this thread and watch, anons.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864726&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864723&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What solid discussion would you like to have?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864758&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863917&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;gets hacked&lt;br&gt;AAAAACCCCCK&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864804&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864627&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I literally don&amp;#x27;t consider myself special&lt;br&gt;So then you literally know that literally most governments literally seize money when they want it bad enough and they have literally dealt with countless people who literally thought just because that money was literally in rock form the laws literally don&amp;#x27;t apply to them&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866917&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864804&lt;br&gt;Including your fiat, stocks, and crypto, except yours are way easier for them to confiscate.&lt;br&gt;Your point? OOH you don&amp;#x27;t have one. &lt;br&gt;Oh you&amp;#x27;re retarded? Poor thing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867080&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864723&lt;br&gt;Then why engage? It&amp;#x27;s harder to ignore retards in real life but I still manage, but online there&amp;#x27;s no reason to even pretend. Everyone that gets ventilated by bad advice just makes your assets that much more valuable. Pretend like everyone average and below will face starvation, prostitution, conscription and death; the truth isn&amp;#x27;t far from this. You wouldn&amp;#x27;t spend all day arguing with corpses so why would you spend time on someone that doesn&amp;#x27;t know they are dead yet?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867144&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866917&lt;br&gt;This is really the bull case cry for stacking firearms and putting aside enough to buy sell swords. The government will do anything they think they can get away with which I why I don&amp;#x27;t think even bail ins are certain, you can do those overnight without kicking a single door but there will still be hell to pay in the morning. While stackers are a smaller population most holdings require, or rather will at such time require, going door to door to seize assets in a country in which one can put together an AR for $350-$400 and drop in FRTs can be had for as little as $100. All this against the population and asset class pairing most likely to own firearms. The logistics don&amp;#x27;t make sense. You&amp;#x27;ll see heavy taxes, threats of taxes, capital controls and possibly if briefly bans on sales after a set date. None of this yields as much gold or silver as paying an above market rate. Question is, is there anything worth trading for. If I got a deed to a substantial amount of the land the federal government loves to horde so much I could see myself parting with all (some) of my specie. Nobody can be all stick and no carrot and win. This is why in bank bail ins you atleast get shares in a bank that has recently defaulted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867175&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867144&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;re lucky you&amp;#x27;re but a minnow. For large investors, all of the guns in the world didn&amp;#x27;t stop Uncle Sam knocking on their door for the known vaults of metals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867423&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867175&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I&amp;#x27;m not there&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;They break and enter&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Thirty tons of fertilizer vaporizes a city block&lt;br&gt;Oh no no no!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867447&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863917&lt;br&gt;already melted down and molded into a solid gold dildo that will sell for 3x spot&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867550&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866917&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;crypto&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;way easier for them to confiscate&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just say you don&amp;#x27;t invest in Bitcoin, because you don&amp;#x27;t understand it, moron.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is crypto 101.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867583&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867550&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;he thinks the government isn&amp;#x27;t in complete control of your delusional secret anonymous bits&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867616&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867583&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Imagine being this dumb and thinking that you&amp;#x27;re going to outsmart the government.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You don&amp;#x27;t even read.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867738&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867583&lt;br&gt;you don&amp;#x27;t understand how Bitcoin works at all, and your lack of understanding is not an argument&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867777&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867738&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;He&amp;#x27;s probably one of those people that try to argue with the police about the Constitution and Uniform Commercial Codes when they pull him over for a speeding ticket and he&amp;#x27;s made his own vehicle registration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867859&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863917&lt;br&gt;I wonder if the “victim” ever posted about his stack on social media?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867922&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864598&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;copy paste address to trade&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;substitution script edits the address on your clipboard for one with a similar start and end so it&amp;#x27;s visually indistinguishable unless you spend a minute verifying each address against eachother&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;gangpreet patel and his village get the capital to send another invader to your country&lt;br&gt;This isn&amp;#x27;t a joke btw, there are scripts which manipulate your clipboard like that, and it&amp;#x27;s even possible for them to be injected into innocent websites via ads. Be careful if you copy/paste addresses anon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867928&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864463&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;gf/wife&lt;br&gt;I have neither, so I am safe there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868014&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867922&lt;br&gt;yeah which is why you do your business on a computer that is only used for BTC and exchanges, and on Linux&lt;br&gt;if you can&amp;#x27;t do this you&amp;#x27;re brown, its effortless&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868254&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868014&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;only used for btc and exchanges&lt;br&gt;reasonable&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;and on linux&lt;br&gt;javascript can manipulate what goes into your clipboard when you copy or cut, being on linux wont change that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868340&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864496&lt;br&gt;Bank vault. That is where you hide it. It could easily take 20 years for her to find out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868350&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864275&lt;br&gt;How they would go in my house? I don&amp;#x27;t leave the door open, I&amp;#x27;m here most of the time and I live in a gated community with no crime whatsoever.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868490&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868340&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It would be immediately confiscated by the government and defeat the purpose of holding physical metal.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868350&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;re aware the banks have door locks, employees, armed guards, and security systems, right?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868527&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863917&lt;br&gt;You don&amp;#x27;t understand. Silver is not some rug shitcoin that will drop 30% tomorrow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868584&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I bet he was like &amp;quot;You guys should buy SILVER, you should have bought SILVER like me :) I bought so much SILVER, you want to know how much SILVER I bought? Let me tell you how much my SILVER is worth today :)&amp;quot; like every other silverfag so that everyone everywhere knew he had a bunch of silver bars at his house waiting to be stolen&lt;br&gt;NOBODY knows about my gold. It lives in a tin under a floorboard. If people ask me about investments I just say it&amp;#x27;s too complicated for me and I don&amp;#x27;t understand it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868620&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864318&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Trump writes another gold executive order like FDR&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;cops at your door, &amp;quot;surrender your precious metals or you will be charged&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;what gold dunno what you&amp;#x27;re talking about&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;they arrest you&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;later they show your purchase history and post history to the court&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What now? Lawyer up against the feds? But all your wealth is buried in your backyard and all your cash is worthless from inflation (or they wouldn&amp;#x27;t be stealing your gold). You&amp;#x27;d be better off investing in bullets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868888&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868620&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; property gets auctioned off, because no one is paying the taxes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869243&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868620&lt;br&gt;By your logic 100% of people get arrested because literally all of them will say they don&amp;#x27;t have gold or silver and 95% of the ones saying that are telling the truth, but you think they&amp;#x27;ll be arrested anyway.&lt;br&gt;This is the level of cope and mental gymnastics cryptards have.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869253&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863917&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oops that clipboard malware destroyed my lifesaving... ACK! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pixel trannys lost.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>