<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>/biz/ Active (filtered, with replies)</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/</link><description>Filtered out: general, gme, bbbyq. OP + first 3 replies + last 30 replies.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 09:31:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>theyre STILL buying this — 8 replies — 32.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889884</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889884?lm=1771839080</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 09:31:20 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;theyre STILL buying this&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889884'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 8 • Updated: 2026-02-23 09:31 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;theyre STILL buying this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889888&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;un &lt;br&gt;fucking &lt;br&gt;believable&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889891&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;this is the biggest crime and scam EVER HOW THE FUCK IS IT AT 240 HOW DO THEY KEEP DOING THIS&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 1MIN CANDLE ON SPOT IS 400K$ VOLUME AND ON PERPS ITS FUCKING 10M$&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889892&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;how CAN IT BE PROFITABLE who the FUCK BUYS THIS???????????????&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889894&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;first it goes from FUCKING 180 TO FUCKING 320 and it STILL WONT DIE!!!!!!!!!!!!!!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I CANNOT BELIEVE THIS PIECE OF MOSSAD SHIT&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889895&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889892&lt;br&gt;Israel spambots&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889899&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889895&lt;br&gt;its FUCKING UNBELIEVABLE how the fuck can this work. the only way is by controlling the CEX its binance and mossad together&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889904&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HOW THE FUCK IS THIS PIECE OF SHIT THE SAME PRICE AS FUKCKING YESTERIAIYDIYDYAIDYADYAI I FUCKING HATE YOU MOOSSAD NIGGERSIFJSOIHFJSOGJISGAEPJIRG UFUICCKOYU&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889906&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AND IM THE ONLY NIGGER ON THE INTERNET WHO NOTICES IT BECAUSE EVERYTHING IS SO FAKE AND GAY NOW THAT LITERALLY NOBODY REALIZES THE CRIMETHEFT GOING ON ON THIS FUCKING PIECE OF SHIT&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;FOR 4 &lt;br&gt;FUCKING&lt;br&gt;MONTHS&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;FOUR!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>TICK TOCK WAGIE — 22 replies — 28.9/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61884227</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61884227?lm=1771836362</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 08:46:02 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;TICK TOCK WAGIE&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61884227'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 22 • Updated: 2026-02-23 08:46 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;MONDAY WILL BE HERE BEFORE YOU KNOW IT!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884234&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;bezos will laugh at me for 30 years until I retire and am too old to enjoy it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884271&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;ve not worked in two years now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884444&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884227&lt;br&gt;total wagie death. &lt;br&gt;retired at 28.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884609&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NOW THE PARTY DON&amp;#x27;T START TILL I WALK IN&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885590&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Don&amp;#x27;t forget to set you alarm and back up alarms tonight, wagie. cannot have you being late for the 06:00 standup&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885594&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884227&lt;br&gt;foh nigga you keep offering VTO&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885608&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885590&lt;br&gt;Winter storm, no one will be in the office, faggot!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885622&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884227&lt;br&gt;that&amp;#x27;s ok Jeff, i have become desensitized to waging&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885626&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885608&lt;br&gt;Acts of god will be docked from your pay&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885888&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884227&lt;br&gt;Joke&amp;#x27;s on you Archon, cause I got fired. Can&amp;#x27;t own my soul if I starve myself to death on purpose now can you? Who can take my Monday mornings from me when I can&amp;#x27;t even afford a calender? Jeff Bozos.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885921&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Monday is my day off though, Jeff.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886102&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884227&lt;br&gt;your 48-hour trial of living is nearly over, wagie. the weekly humiliation ritual about to kick off once again&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886324&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884227&lt;br&gt;Wagies, don&amp;#x27;t forget to pack your little plastic lunch container and bring a snack&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886327&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stay strong, wagies. That 2% annual raise is definitely coming this time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888158&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;grow up wagie&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888163&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888158&lt;br&gt;i already have a routine&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888177&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884227&lt;br&gt;Only soft millenials complain about work. Real men do what needs to be done to make enough to solidify yourself in life and make your mark. Living in mommy&amp;#x27;s basement and trading bitcoin doesn&amp;#x27;t make you cool or edgy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888219&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61886102&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;those chicken legs&lt;br&gt;Stop skipping legs day you nigger&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888304&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884227&lt;br&gt;uh ohh wagie&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889294&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888158&lt;br&gt;He&amp;#x27;s just like me&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889305&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884227&lt;br&gt;Hey Jeff, one of your little faggot drivers didnt follow my instructions to put the box of quaker instant oat meal(maple flavor packets) on my porch. Instead they left them at my gate..in the rain..in a cardboard box...cardboard jeff..&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889850&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;four to go&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Why not Start an Online Casino? — 7 replies — 28.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889846</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889846?lm=1771838674</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 09:24:34 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Why not Start an Online Casino?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889846'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 7 • Updated: 2026-02-23 09:24 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;What exactly is stopping me?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;buy a license for $15k in XYZ island&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;only take crypto to avoid KYC on burgerbros&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;run some clean poker games&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;collect money&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889851&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889846&lt;br&gt;Basad, be the cz killer!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889853&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Owning a casino is one way that putting all your profits back into it can go wrong.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889866&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How big is the crypto gambling audience even?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889869&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889846&lt;br&gt;I like your idea. But I find it hard to believe you just pay for your license and you’re free to do whatever you please. Prob too much red tape/ rules/regulations to. Can’t let the goyim get a step up at all. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You think you can get away with non KYC? I’m interested in hearing how&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889883&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889869&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;you think you can get away with non-kyc?&lt;br&gt;There are already sites that are doing this operating in the US today. Ignition, ACR. and Coinpoker notably on the crypto side and WPT gold on the sweepstakes side. only coinpoker and WPT shill via ecelebs and in general US noncompliance sites seem like an underserved area of the market. I don’t get why there aren’t more players.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889886&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889866&lt;br&gt;Considering GGPoker takes direct crypto deposits, it’s presumably massive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889896&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Because the Australian government only allows poker machines. No poker or games outside of casinos, polymarket is banned. Online poker banned. Two up (coin flip game) is unbanned one day a year but banned for the rest of the year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>I sold. 4600 Stinkies, 14.8 ETH. thanks for nothing — 2 replies — 8.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889893</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889893?lm=1771838972</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 09:29:32 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;I sold. 4600 Stinkies, 14.8 ETH. thanks for nothing&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889893'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 2 • Updated: 2026-02-23 09:29 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;I sold. 4600 Stinkies, 14.8 ETH. thanks for nothing&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889901&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You are a traitor&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889903&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889893&lt;br&gt;ee sold?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;No additional replies in the latest window.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>how do you guys cope with the fact that OF egirls are making tens of millions a year? — 35 replies — 41.3/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889270</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889270?lm=1771836056</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 08:40:56 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;how do you guys cope with the fact that OF egirls are making tens of millions a year?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889270'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 35 • Updated: 2026-02-23 08:40 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;how do you guys cope with the fact that OF egirls are making tens of millions a year? this shit is really unbelievable man i am seething so hard holy fuck&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889273&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I literally just don&amp;#x27;t care. Nobody will ever love them and I can also make 10 million without displaying my butthole for the world to see&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889278&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s only like top1% creators making millions&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889279&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889273&lt;br&gt;i didnt care too for so long but now im starting to care fml its just so unfair.. Not only are they extremely hot they also get to make 20MM a year for years scamming with bikini pics on OF&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;its just so unfair i feel like crying&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889284&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;retard women live retard woman experience. you care about money?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889287&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;OF&lt;br&gt;Literally who?!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889292&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;Theres literally only been one titty streamer that turned that 5 minute success into owning multiple gas stations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889298&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889292&lt;br&gt;Car washes are where the money is at&lt;br&gt; Once you get your bag idk why people keep doing it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889301&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889283&lt;br&gt;okay this makes me feel better thanks man&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889304&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bro, these bitches don’t “make” money they just receive donations. There’s just as many if not more girls just receiving money from sugar daddies without an OF. These bitches would be getting money from sugar daddies regardless, instead of 1 or 2 sugar daddies giving them tons and tons of money they have thousands of sugar daddies giving them a little bit of money. If anything they are getting a worse deal from OF. Freedom and independence will never make a woman happy so they have no clue what to do with their lives anyways. It’s just one of the perks of being a woman, you get all your shit paid for. Just like women have access to secretary positions where all it takes is a retard to answer a phone and take messages and reply to emails just because they’re attractive and the bosses want them around. There’s a price on beauty and it’s a very short window to capitalize on. All they have to do is take a few pictures and videos, it could be all in the same day, and those pictures can be rolled out for years so they literally don’t have to do any work and can just let an agency handle everything. Almost all these bitches use an agency so they are giving up almost 50% of the profits to men. So there is an easy way for you to capitalize on these bitches profits you just aren’t doing it. This shit has been going on for centuries. It’s nothing new it’s just online.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889315&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are thousands of whores that lose their dignity on OF without making any money at all&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889322&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;You know there are criminals, corrupt politicians, and mindless corporate drones making more than that, right? Perhaps you imagine an economy in which people are compensated for the value they provide to society. That&amp;#x27;s only an ideal, not the economy that exists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889335&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;I am still a virgin at 35 and over my entire life I have wasted only 2.40 CHF on women. I&amp;#x27;m proud of myself that I&amp;#x27;m not a cuck.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889339&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;a girl I knew from school started an onlyfans. everyone she grew up with saw her getting fucked. she made like $200 and deleted it a couple months later. I feel like this is probably pretty common&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889347&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889339&lt;br&gt;Is she hot? You gonna share with the class?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889349&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889335&lt;br&gt;Was that 2.40 CHF for a cup of coffee? Bus fare?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889354&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889339&lt;br&gt;Girl I knew in the office years ago had hers leaked by one of the bitchy HR ladies. Like 14 people paid 5 bucks to sub to it and watched her rail herself with a 7 inch hog.&lt;br&gt;Eventually it got to her and started impacting her work and she was put on a PIP.&lt;br&gt;She quit like a month later. Think about that. At best she made the equivalent of a few burgs at Wendy&amp;#x27;s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889368&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889354&lt;br&gt;You made that up in your head. Why would HR have her porn videos&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889372&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889347&lt;br&gt;yea she was hot. she was also one of my good friends sisters. i didnt save any of the videos though&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889354&lt;br&gt;yep&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889378&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889368&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s not really difficult to understand if you understand how women work. Her being HR just happened to be where she worked. Office gossip is unfortunately how office wagies fill their day. Men aren&amp;#x27;t much different desu. We just talk about we railed so and so on the weekend. &lt;br&gt;Office women are vile and will say the most endearing things to your face before finding ways to tell your wife at the Christmas party how she heard you got blown by your manager&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889392&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;Are they?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;rented cars&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;leased jets&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;AirBNBs in Dubai for two days&lt;br&gt;All the illusion of being rich. Even if they did make a few shekels, they are definitely beholden to the pimp that is laundering money through them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889405&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;grow boobs then if you don&amp;#x27;t like it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889409&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;Barely any of them do, pretty much just the hottest ones that are willing to get their brains fucked out on camera. If you aren&amp;#x27;t one of the hottest guys willing to have your dingle out for the world to see it really isn&amp;#x27;t comparable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889429&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889409&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s an enormous amount of work too when you get big enough to make decent cash but not enough to sustain yourself. Answering 48 messages in the morning yourself because you can&amp;#x27;t afford to pay a guy to do it for and you can&amp;#x27;t not answer because these guys are shelling out 70 percent of your revenue. Then you return. Film more. Do it again and scrape by for maybe 900 bucks a month.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s almost more worth it to end up being worth a few cheeseburgers so you know you aren&amp;#x27;t worth it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889624&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you really cared you would be pimping OF models by now. You think women do anything in their own? They all have pimps.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889631&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s not glamorous but you can go on craigslist whenever you want and make a quick couple hundred getting your dick sucked by lonely old queers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889644&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889631&lt;br&gt;How is that even worth $200? Enjoy your money pox&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889769&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889273&lt;br&gt;Holy cope. Obviously most men will love them because men are horny dogs. Its 2026, prime time to realize men are the more pathetic gender. This aint the 50s champ.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889773&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889273&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Nobody will ever love them&lt;br&gt;These bitches get BFs all the time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889775&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;how do you guys cope with the fact that OF egirls are making tens of millions a year?&lt;br&gt;Only the top 1% do, the rest make around few hundred USD or few 20-40USD a month.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889273&lt;br&gt;Lot of them have BFs and lot of them don&amp;#x27;t do porn with other men just sell their nudes but most aren&amp;#x27;t making enough to retire on not by a longshot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889777&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;1. They don&amp;#x27;t receive all that money, they are hired under an umbrella corporation, they are just models for hire.&lt;br&gt;2. They are women, they don&amp;#x27;t know how to invest their money (see amouranth, it was her husband who put her in front of the camera, managed her socials and invested her money)&lt;br&gt;3. I can&amp;#x27;t see what you would do with that much money, unless you are hyper-dependent on people doing things for you...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889804&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;They aren&amp;#x27;t. The vast majority have sold their souls for triple digit profits&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889830&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Comparing yourself to women is one of the first steps on the tranny pipeline lmao&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889840&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;Go sell your asshole to strangers and lookmax then you lazy cunt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>When the AI bubble pops and all those GPUs go to BTC you will see a rally like never before. — 12 replies — 32.8/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889497</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889497?lm=1771837786</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 09:09:46 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;When the AI bubble pops and all those GPUs go to BTC you will see a rally like never before.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889497'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 12 • Updated: 2026-02-23 09:09 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the AI bubble pops and all those GPUs go to BTC you will see a rally like never before.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889501&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889497&lt;br&gt;ASIC is superior in every way. Buy Canaan stock while it’s still criminally undervalued&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889545&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;That sounds boomerific wait until he finds out the massive warehouses filled with bitcoin miners&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889550&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889497&lt;br&gt;Price increase leads to hash rate increase.&lt;br&gt;Hash rate increase doesn&amp;#x27;t lead to price increase.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889553&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;That&amp;#x27;s nice. In the meantime moners are capitulating and selling their hardware. It&amp;#x27;s telling that Bitcoin prices are so dependent on moninf profitability. When you can&amp;#x27;t mine anymore it&amp;#x27;s going to die isn&amp;#x27;t it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889567&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889501&lt;br&gt;Sources say Charlie is stable, please God&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889714&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889497&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;ve used more ai than btc, in fact i havent used btc for a singular thing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889721&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889553&lt;br&gt;Ether!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889723&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889721&lt;br&gt;I mean btc blockchain could be an l2 anytime they hardfork it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889829&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889497&lt;br&gt;Nah Bitcoin lacks a clear narrative on why I&amp;#x27;m supposed to be supporting it going to 1 million. All the old ones failed so now it&amp;#x27;s a tech stock without any tech.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889833&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889497&lt;br&gt;Normies seem to hate AI more than BTC because BTC is straight up useless to them and thus harmless to their jobs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889843&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;everyone uses AI everyday&lt;br&gt;&amp;lt;nobody uses crypto&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;sorry to break it to you, anon...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889875&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889843&lt;br&gt;I have never used ai, only in gugli search.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>2026 is THE year of the Link token. You'll see. Check 'em. — 46 replies — 30.9/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61882840</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61882840?lm=1771833738</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 08:02:18 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;2026 is THE year of the Link token. You&amp;#x27;ll see. Check &amp;#x27;em.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61882840'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 46 • Updated: 2026-02-23 08:02 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;2026 is THE year of the Link token. &lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;ll see. Check &amp;#x27;em.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882854&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882840&lt;br&gt;Great year for Sergey. Horrible year for baggies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882857&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882840&lt;br&gt;you have nothing to check, not even dubs, you will fail&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882865&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Uh, I&amp;#x27;ma put my cat on the keyboard. Meow meow meow, meow, meow meow. Meow meow. Meow meow? Meow. (Financially speaking)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884132&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;digits and link is $100 eoyt 2026&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884172&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884132&lt;br&gt;You are low energy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884202&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882840&lt;br&gt;linkies are THE cuckolds of crypto xD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884230&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882840&lt;br&gt;Zero digits in this thread. SAD!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884400&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884230&lt;br&gt;How is that even possible?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884841&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883854&lt;br&gt;how embarrassing&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884942&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;$500 EOY CHECKEM&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885073&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;$10,000 EOY. Check em niggers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885105&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;$20 in April, digits confirm&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885130&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882840&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;whitnessed&lt;br&gt;$120 eoq&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885795&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is known&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885804&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885795&lt;br&gt;I hate these niggers so much. Every financial opinion piece they spew out is complete dog shit on crypto. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;...And for that reason goy, BUY BITCOIN! Just because!&amp;quot; &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;And PLEASE pay for a subscription to our stock picks!&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;Everytime. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;They made retards generational baggies the last run.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886478&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882895&lt;br&gt;It hasnt even begun yet&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886491&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882857&lt;br&gt;check the chart&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886642&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882840&lt;br&gt;Depends on how badly the US starts to tank because crypto is designed to step in once the dollar begins to collapse.&lt;br&gt;The alternative is the complete collapse of the global economy and a new dark age for humanity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886644&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882865&lt;br&gt;kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888654&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;pool remains closed&lt;br&gt;stack remains unsold&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888690&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;$120 eoy &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;clarity starts the next bull run, check em&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888705&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Linky remains stinky, check ‘em&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888709&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Poo poo pee pee caca doo doo wee wee, check em&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888754&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Okay hear me out&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The potential for 81K is possible though ironically. When you account for staking locking up 95% or even more of the circulating supply(350 Mil, the rest are spoken for on nodes already). I suspect by 2026 BTC will only have around 35-40% dominance as well, projects with specific applications will begin to take hold. Oracles, various layer 1&amp;#x27;s that enable Smart contracts, DEFI, decentralized cloud computing, decentralized cloud storage, and probably other things that haven&amp;#x27;t even been conceptualized yet.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We are supposed to see at least 8 Trillion MCAP by 2025 of all crypto according to the experts. Klaus Schwab mentions this in his book.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I think we will see 4-5 Trillion at the peak of the next bullrun easy. That will probably be early to mid 2022. Next peak bull run will probably mid to late 2026 which could easily run 16-20 Trillion MCAP of all crypto. In the scheme of things that is only around 18-25% of the global GDP. Its honestly not that much.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now lets say LINK network protocol captures 4 Trillion by 2026 peak bull run. At even 80% staking saturation (70 Million circulating supply) the price is close to 60,000 per LINK, around 57,000. At 15% circulating supply, its 52.5 Million LINK with a 4 Trillion MCAP is 76,000 per LINK.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;These numbers sound ridiculous at first or to the uniniated but again when you understand what LINK is/does its honestly not. We are buying a share of the fat protocol that will monetize Web 3.0. I mean think if HTTPS would have been monetized. The Internet itself is worth around 19 Trillion and when you add in data accumulated from the &amp;quot;Internet of Things&amp;quot;, it adds a 5-10x multiplier roughly.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Internet is more or less 25 years old for the masses as a whole. If there were 350 Million shares circulating, they would be worth just under 54,000 each at its current estimated value.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pic related is fun and entertaining but ironically achievable in the time frame suggested&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Discuss&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888841&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888754&lt;br&gt;Sounds good I hope it’s true&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888850&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888754&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;now let&amp;#x27;s say that [impossible thing] could happen&lt;br&gt;nice ass though&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888854&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;$1000 EOY&lt;br&gt;It has always been and always will be&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889104&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884400&lt;br&gt;kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889172&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888754&lt;br&gt;mental illness :/ if only we had a place to put you people that did not have internet access&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889312&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Something something it’s like a mental asylum or something and there is a locker or something and you have like the locker code or something but not really and the locker will open in a few years and there’s like heaps of money or something? Anyway, that’s how holding LINK feels like, or something&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;just hold for another decade bruv&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889341&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The First Reptilian Bank of Canada just aped 300 GLNK and you&amp;#x27;re bearish???&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889715&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889341&lt;br&gt;based reppies finna save us no cap. trust&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889793&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884942&lt;br&gt;Triple and link will hit $502&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Fake and Gay Economy — 94 replies — 21.2/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61871520</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61871520?lm=1771823171</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:06:11 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Fake and Gay Economy&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61871520'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 94 • Updated: 2026-02-23 05:06 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;When will this gay as economy finally collapse and how can i profit from it?&lt;br&gt;Its ridiculous the woman at our workplace contribute nothing to the company and make more money than i do&lt;br&gt;Its infuriating we just had a bunch of lay offs and we lost some of oir best workers but somehow a bunch of HR shits who do nothing all day still work here&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871530&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HR is a necessary function, chud&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871569&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871530&lt;br&gt;For what?&lt;br&gt;Genuinely why do we need it to this extent?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871755&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871569&lt;br&gt;Protect the corp from lawsuits&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883066&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879023&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;If they didn&amp;#x27;t provide value they wouldn&amp;#x27;t be there.&lt;br&gt;75% or more of white collar work literally does nothing, roasties or not.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883243&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;Did they fire itty bitty titties &amp;amp; a bob?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883399&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;When there is an alternative for the money and people to pour over into.&lt;br&gt;Fagmerica&amp;#x27;s slow decline relies on everywhere else being shittier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883616&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;HR while i&amp;#x27;m anxious, waiting for them to communicate their decision about hiring me, being unemployed and thinking about suicide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883644&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882495&lt;br&gt;you know, society almost always makes you think you desire gen z boss and a mini, but fuck that, i&amp;#x27;m gonna say it, loud and proud: i&amp;#x27;m more akin to have a relationship with secret product and a trench, i dont know if its about my selfsteem, i would like to be enough for gen z boss and a mini. Maybe what i need is 5&amp;#x27;3 and an attitude.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883760&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883243&lt;br&gt;They got promoted to Chief Diversity, Equity &amp;amp; Inclusion Officer&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883781&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883644&lt;br&gt;You meant to say inclined. You are more inclined. Akin means &amp;quot;similar to&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883784&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882869&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;incel&lt;br&gt;Im so confused as to what that term means, involuntarily celibate? But its not being celibate if your literally having sex. Such a weird term clearly carrying different meaning. What is the point of using a term that literally has no definition to its meaning, you might aswell speak in baby noises at this point.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884146&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;guys, ALL we have to do is called women like this ugly chopped shit to their face as much as possible and they will lose all motivation to live&lt;br&gt;they are SO fragile in that regard.&lt;br&gt;next time you are walking down the street and see some bitch like this just start yelling “YOURE UGLY”&lt;br&gt;they will spend the next week and a half minimum making reddit posts about it and getting their SSRI prescription upped.&lt;br&gt;don’t ever engage with any ideas or thoughts they have. just pick apart their appearance. you look like a fridge and a stick insect at the same time. your fake dyed hair sucks. you have clown makeup on, you must have learned how to do makeup at the circus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884272&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883066&lt;br&gt;So you&amp;#x27;re saying ceo&amp;#x27;s willingly burn 75% of their money for fun?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884291&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884272&lt;br&gt;he&amp;#x27;s saying the ceo is a fucking retard&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884297&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;I want to shove my cock deep into the first one from behind. Just lift the skirt and blast the pussy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884717&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883784&lt;br&gt;Yes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884737&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871569&lt;br&gt;Without HR you could complete the work, banter and build a genuine camaraderie with your common co-worker, but we cant have unions, and its better if you&amp;#x27;re all divided and conquered, here&amp;#x27;s a harpy to make your life hell&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884742&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873193&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872087&lt;br&gt;These niggers actually get it. All problems flow downstream from jews controlling the issuance of your (since 1913) fake and gay fiat debt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885902&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873611&lt;br&gt;You must be over 18 to use this site&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886326&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882442&lt;br&gt;Yeah this kind of mega über schizos who believe in fe and no nuke use this phrase holy shit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886329&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882442&lt;br&gt;And yes the idea of space is falsifiable you absolute schizo. Satellites wouldn&amp;#x27;t even work without it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886359&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883784&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Such a weird term clearly carrying different meaning. What is the point of using a term that literally has no definition to its meaning&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s just people overusing words or ideas to oblivion, where they lose all context. It&amp;#x27;s like the worst insult was being called gay way back, then it was subverted (actually gay is cool), then it became retarded, then it got subverted (actually retarded is cool because you&amp;#x27;re not trying), then it become autistic, then it became subverted (actually it&amp;#x27;s interesting to be autistic), now it&amp;#x27;s random baby talk by gen alpha (mog, cortisol spike, chopped, unc, lil bro, frame, aura farming, 67, incel, cuk). Now it&amp;#x27;s being subverted by people overusing the terms even if they don&amp;#x27;t apply to anyone or anything in the context at all. Someone not having sex for a week = incel. Someone having a slightly embarrassing moment (cortisol spike), someone better looking walking past (mogged), doing something that&amp;#x27;s barely good (aura farming), having a strong presence even if it&amp;#x27;s completely autistic and retarded (frame). Or like when old people started wearing skateboard shirts having no clue what it was, or everyone and their dog wearing an off white shirt. People make shit gay eventually, it&amp;#x27;s a universal law.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886363&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;work office job (engineer) with way too many women and diversity hire niggers and Indians who do nothing all day&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;get new (white) South African Vice President&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;calls us all together&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;in his funny accent tells us he’s an engineer and knows the business and there will be changes&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;tells us he will cut 20% of the workforce soon&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;everyone is shit scared and the normie femoids start climbing over each other trying to save their useless asses&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;office girlies start spreading rumours about everyone and everything in desperate attempt to make themselves look better&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;don’t give a fuck, I’m a technician and actually make money for the company unlike them&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Vice President just observes the shit show and never comments on anything while he feels out the office&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;come in one Monday&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;literally all blacks are gone&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;all except the actual useful Indians are gone&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;he culled every single female that we all knew had jewish make believe adult daycare jobs&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;only kept the old hag secretaries that actually do a great job&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kek, based white nigger. Turns out all it takes is some third world coloniser to clean this woke shit up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886555&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872076&lt;br&gt;We are not capitalist.&lt;br&gt;We have been Trotskyist since the end of WW2.&lt;br&gt;Having a central bank is plank #5 of the commie manifesto.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886576&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884742&lt;br&gt;It was a bit delayed until after 1913.&lt;br&gt;They couldn’t go full fakeconomy immediately, or they would have been shut down.&lt;br&gt;They had to wait and boil the frog slowly, using the occasional crisis as a speed boost.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886586&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t ever interact with HR once I&amp;#x27;m hired until I&amp;#x27;m inevitably fired. From where comes the HR hate? Are they the ones who actually make the decisions to fire us?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886684&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;this board is dead as shit holy fuck&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886687&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61886684&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s the weekend. It picks up when the market is open.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886692&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;d fuck all of them. At the same time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887220&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61886363&lt;br&gt;Sounds illegal and fake. This is such an obvious thing to do, there must be a reason it doesn&amp;#x27;t actually happen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889346&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s not going to collapse... bill gates will grow some cheap bug burgers and psyop all the women to think it&amp;#x27;s healthy and great for the environment... so we can continue feeding billions of women to do nothing but work in an office.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889382&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61886363&lt;br&gt;How was he able to be able to gauge who&amp;#x27;s useful and who&amp;#x27;s not in such a short period of time?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889387&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889346&lt;br&gt;Also, paying women to do nothing is one of the best birth controls there is. They are incapable of dating down. Sorry, just the messenger. bullshit jobs, especially for women, will never end until picrel collapses.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unfortunately, the jews also don&amp;#x27;t want picrel to collapse because then their banks would go broke. So we&amp;#x27;re stuck in hell.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Why do people on this board whine piss and moan about having six-figs? — 58 replies — 13.7/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61883830</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61883830?lm=1771823889</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:18:09 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Why do people on this board whine piss and moan about having six-figs?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61883830'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 58 • Updated: 2026-02-23 05:18 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Do any of you realize how unbelievably lucky you are compared against most in even 1st-world countries? Your average person is tens of thousands in credit card debt and struggling to pay off their klarna these days. Even worse, they&amp;#x27;re a few months behind on their mortgage and about to lose their house.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meanwhile, your lot go &amp;quot;WAAAAAA WOE IS ME I&amp;#x27;M ONLY WORTH $475K AT 23 YEARS OLD I&amp;#x27;LL NEVER BE RICH!!!!!&amp;quot; Even if you&amp;#x27;re larping, I mean fuck you don&amp;#x27;t&amp;#x27; realize how spoiled rotten and ridiculous you sound, you&amp;#x27;re not even funny nor cute when you whine like that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883852&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883830&lt;br&gt;yea but crypto went down&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883873&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883830&lt;br&gt;because im still a wageslave you retarded cockgargling faggot&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883874&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883830&lt;br&gt;There are no 1st world countries anymore. It goes:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Switzerland, Northern Italy, Poland, and everybody else&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884765&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884755&lt;br&gt;You are kinda free if you are in the top 10% ig. They are the group still spending in usa.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884780&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883830&lt;br&gt;Another day another poorfag trying to drag me into his crab bucket.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;FUCK OFF YOU PIECE OF SHIT LOSER STOP TRYING TO MAKE EVERYONE SUFFER WITH YOU&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884789&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884780&lt;br&gt;He isn’t wrong. American median household income is 60k.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885028&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883830&lt;br&gt;Six figs isnt enough to retire. Anyways Im at very low 6 figs one slight dump in stocks and Im back to 5 figure hell.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I want out of the wagecage and its not luck when the average person in the US probably buys fast food 10 times a week, goes out to a restuarant once a week at $200 per visit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885045&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;it called being tongue-and-cheek you stupid fucking retarded fucking nigger&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885049&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885045&lt;br&gt;oops meet to say tongue in cheek but whatever&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885051&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884789&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;median household income&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;household&lt;br&gt;Kek they try so hard to giving a realistic number. Show me median individual income, emphasis on median. Don&amp;#x27;t feed me &amp;quot;average&amp;quot; which is easily skewed upwards.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;you live in a nation of 100 people&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;1 person makes $1b&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;99 people make $10k&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;average houshold size is 10 people&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;median individual income $10k&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;median household income $100k&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;average individual income ~$10m&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;average household income ~$100m&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885310&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885051&lt;br&gt;by your own math median is just as misleading as mean&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885331&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883830&lt;br&gt;500k is nothing. If you have this, congrats. You can spend your entire net worth and buy a decent house. Now what? &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;There has to be more than this, op. People who are &amp;quot;doing well&amp;quot; should be able to actually make a change in this world, yet they can barely afford to buy a house. The system is broken&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885340&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885331&lt;br&gt;Back in muh day we just gathered sticks of wood and nailed cardboard&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885350&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883830&lt;br&gt;The majority of people in first world countries are boomers, they own multiple houses, have had multiple wives, multiple kids, multiple cars, multiple pension plans. I literally have nothing in comparison.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885360&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885350&lt;br&gt;Dont go there just stay where you are. When they send their drones china will just hack them and make them crash. And thats how the white cookie crumbles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885501&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885310&lt;br&gt;But far more accurate to reality than the supposed reality they try to paint. In both median individual and household income the amounts are more accurate than average while median individual income bears the most accuracy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885512&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m about to enter 6 figure hell next week, what am i in for?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885530&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883830&lt;br&gt;My 300k is literally nothing&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885562&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885512&lt;br&gt;5 figure hell after trump&amp;#x27;s tariff tirade&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885855&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883830&lt;br&gt;Lucky? I&amp;#x27;m a fucking wage slave. Having 600k usd means fuck all when houses cost 2 million AUD in Sydney and I&amp;#x27;m 30 years old. I don&amp;#x27;t want to work the rest of my life (I won&amp;#x27;t anyway as AI is about to take me out)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885862&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885512&lt;br&gt;Depends on your age and savings rate&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885873&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883830&lt;br&gt;Nope. Not good enough.&lt;br&gt;Sense of accomplishment is relative. We want to go up in life, not down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885878&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883830&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s good that I was born when and where I was. It is a good thing. I greatly appreciate being born on a scaffold.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885983&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885051&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;what is law of large numbers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885987&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885331&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;muh house&lt;br&gt;Kys retard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886585&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885512&lt;br&gt;Obsessively watching your portfolio everyday, and realizing you’re still broke. I eased off the gas and just started spending a little and enjoying life more when I hit 100k. If it’s gonna be another 30 years to retire, I might as well the ride.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886699&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885350&lt;br&gt;Wait 50 years and you&amp;#x27;ll be even richer than boomers unless you fuck it up&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886704&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885855&lt;br&gt;You can always rope&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886984&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;over 500k at 32&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;165k safe public sector income&lt;br&gt;Never gonna make it ;_;&lt;br&gt;Forever angry at myself for buying the chainlink ICO and then selling before it mooned.&lt;br&gt;Shill me your shitcoins and meme stocks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889254&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61886984&lt;br&gt;$500k at 32 is a lot. If you simply invest in an index fund you could get 10% per yeat. Doubling every 7 years. You will have $2 million cash by age 46, which is good. Purely through passive investment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889285&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889254&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s 7% per year normally, but we are likely entering a decade of stagnation in stocks now after the 2 decade megabull we&amp;#x27;ve had&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889380&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884630&lt;br&gt;Meh, I sold 12 BTC for $40 each&lt;br&gt;Now I&amp;#x27;m broke, but debt free and 300 link&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889424&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61886984&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;meme stocks&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For 165k income? SCHD.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>WTF IS HAPPENING - preferably in haiku format — 9 replies — 10.8/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889182</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889182?lm=1771836115</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 08:41:55 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;WTF IS HAPPENING - preferably in haiku format&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889182'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 9 • Updated: 2026-02-23 08:41 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889192&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889182&lt;br&gt;I am holding Tesla shorts&lt;br&gt;Fuck haikus&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889194&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889182&lt;br&gt;It all crashes&lt;br&gt;to zero&lt;br&gt;to fuck us&lt;br&gt;But slowly, slowly!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889198&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Money needs to print&lt;br&gt;Tarriffs will be the excuse&lt;br&gt;When QE returns&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889200&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This shit ass board is dead and has been for years and I’m still broke and FUCK FUCK FUCK FUCK FUCK FUCKKKK&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889208&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cycle doing its thing&lt;br&gt;BTC to 30k&lt;br&gt;Buy the dip you jeet&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889209&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A decision has been made. War is coming&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889252&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889182&lt;br&gt;your asshole is ripped&lt;br&gt;by the cycles you can&amp;#x27;t see&lt;br&gt;because retarded&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889831&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889252&lt;br&gt;Based&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889842&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889182&lt;br&gt;Cryptocurrency is shit&lt;br&gt;Buy metal instead&lt;br&gt;Real money real victory&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Link vs XRP — 8 replies — 9.4/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889600</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889600?lm=1771836056</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 08:40:56 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Link vs XRP&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889600'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 8 • Updated: 2026-02-23 08:40 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;When will the gap close? Link came within a hair of flipping xrp in January ‘21. We all know that Link is everything Xrp fraudulently claims to be so it makes sense that this chart should flip soon enough. Will it be gradual or violent? Will it flip because xrp crashes or because Link moons? &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most importantly where are some places you can use Link as collateral to borrow Xrp to take full advantage of the trade of the century?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889606&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m so tired.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889622&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889600&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889606&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889620&lt;br&gt;Link is scam&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Buy XRP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889634&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889606&lt;br&gt;Xrp is like chainlink if all the nightmares came true: no use case, no revenue, an ipo that formally cuts token holders out of the picture etc.. and we need over a 10x to reach their market cap. This fact always gives me energy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889799&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889634&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889823&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889600&lt;br&gt;It won&amp;#x27;t. Even RLUSD will pass link&amp;#x27;s marketcap in a matter of a few months.You invested poorly in a project with the only purpose of jewishly injecting fees for literally no reason and assuming people will allow you to entrench in core services. It is a bad financial and moral investment&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889827&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889634&lt;br&gt;XRP had no ICO. Link sells to retail at every pump and drains operator rewards it claimed it wouldn&amp;#x27;t. Link has literally zero use case outside arbitrary jewish rent seeking crypto toll boothing. It solves no problem and has no use outside ADDING frictions. XRP from Ripple alone has: &lt;br&gt;https://ripple.com/insights/institutional-defi-on-xrpl-scaling-real-world-finance-with-xrp-at-the-core/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889841&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889600&lt;br&gt;not gonna happen, jews will reward retard boomers once again, they are the golden generation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>CRYPTO IS DEAD — 33 replies — 8.3/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61880718</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61880718?lm=1771824753</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:32:33 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;CRYPTO IS DEAD&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61880718'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 33 • Updated: 2026-02-23 05:32 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Crypto is dead. So I&amp;#x27;m looking into buying again, maybe lump sum maybe DCA. What do you think, anons? Some think that the bear market is just starting so maybe it&amp;#x27;s better to wait... but idk, the sentiment seems rather depressed already. Anyone else also accumulating rn or ar you waiting for october? Alts or BTC?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880730&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;rn&lt;br&gt;Tiktok negrobabble gets your thread filtered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880848&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880730&lt;br&gt;You answered tho?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881053&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880718&lt;br&gt;all other macro bottoms took several months of crabbing before the markets went up again, we havent done that yet&lt;br&gt;probably better to wait it out and only deploy capital when its clear the trend has shifted&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;like last macro bottom in late 2022, if you waited till conformation you bought at 18k instead of 16k, a marginal difference&lt;br&gt;i&amp;#x27;ll assume that nobody actually nabbed the 60k bottom here for how short it was&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881059&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881053&lt;br&gt;My fear is that the bull run was kinda front runned so what if the bear is also like that, leading to a shorer bear market&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881187&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881059&lt;br&gt;very reasonable assumption but again wait for the turn&lt;br&gt;unless you believe the snap back up will be violent, which is hard to do with sentiment this bad&lt;br&gt;even on the fakest V-est of v-dips during corona you had a good while to buy at 4k&lt;br&gt;and like i said you already missed the 60k window&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881266&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880718&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;ve been DCAing for that past two months. My instinct tells me this year is going to be really bad for crypto. Lots of crashing, crabbing, doom and gloom. So I&amp;#x27;ll slurp up as much bloody water as I can and hope that in the next few years we either finish collapsing or I&amp;#x27;m incredibly wealthy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881505&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880718&lt;br&gt;I voted for this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883131&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881187&lt;br&gt;That&amp;#x27;s not true, pic related is the covid dip. You had a total of 5 days at 5k, then it started a pretty steep recovery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883135&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881266&lt;br&gt;Pretty much this, except things will probably turn suddenly when CLARITY passes in a month or 2&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883290&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880718&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883374&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883135&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Polity is going to make my bag go line up&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;BUY MY BAG NOW&lt;br&gt;no&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883380&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;btc behaves like a more volatile leveraged spy. I thought the whole idea is crypto being a hedge against fiat and being decentralized. now american companies like mstr and blackrock own huge chunks and the whole crypto movement depends on american regulations. I dont own crypto and I never will. Everyone still being heavily into crypto at this moment must be desperate as fuck otherwise I dont get it. Last 5 years btc couldnt even outperform the s&amp;amp;p lol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883384&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883380&lt;br&gt;Everyone being into ponzi asset, including every single ponzi paper in the spx is desperate &lt;br&gt;You can&amp;#x27;t print yourself out of a demographic deflation. Your advertising is futile&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883390&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880718&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Polkadot crypto&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;https://www.figment.io/insights/polkadots-dynamic-allocation-pool-dap-an-evolution-in-issuance-and-staking/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883398&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883390&lt;br&gt;Go advertise somewhere else freak jeet/chink&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883516&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883290&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;buy my stockbags and metalbags&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;don&amp;#x27;t you dare buy decentralized currencies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883562&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880718&lt;br&gt;Wait, its going lower. Experts think 40k is the bottom&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883576&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883398&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Im Korean not Indian&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883624&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883576&lt;br&gt;What&amp;#x27;s the difference?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883631&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;cryptoniggers still DCAing into crypto in the midst of crypto winter&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;completely ignoring asset classes that have momentum like AI, space tech, precious metals, energy, etc.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The definition of insanity is doing the same thing over and over again and expecting different results.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883636&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883631&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;buy my bags at ath&lt;br&gt;No thank you&lt;br&gt;I always made the most money when faggots like yourself tell me crypto is dead and chase assets hitting multi decade highs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883645&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883636&lt;br&gt;Everything that&amp;#x27;s been doing well, and that means not crypto, will keep doing very well until May. Then we get bust and people will rotate into treasuries and cash, ready to buy the next bottom. Watch and learn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883665&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883645&lt;br&gt;So I should buy the tippy top and sell in about 2 months? Are you fucking retarded?&lt;br&gt;Yeah I don&amp;#x27;t play chicken with assets, I DCA when there&amp;#x27;s fear and I sell when there&amp;#x27;s greed.&lt;br&gt;Once again, not buying your bags, nigger.&lt;br&gt;Sold my silver @103 as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883782&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883631&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;like AI&lt;br&gt;buying ai here is about the most retarded investment strategy possible&lt;br&gt;ai credit is cracking all over the place and the mag 7 are going to spend 90% of their revenue on capex this year&lt;br&gt;who is left to incinerate trillions of dollars now, we are about to hit the minsky moment on the ai build out&lt;br&gt;considering the regular economy isnt doing too badly might not even be bad for other assets as the retarded overspend on infrastructure build out is curtailed&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;and also this isnt even touching on the rather hard physical limits that even if they keep exponentially building more datacenters there doesnt exist the electricity surplus to actually turn the things on&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883866&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The value of a company is based on its ability to split its profits between its owners, aka shareholders.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What is the value of Bitcoin based on?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883974&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880718&lt;br&gt;Brics, Banks and Billionaires only buying one thing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884007&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883866&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The value of a company is based on its ability to split its profits between its owners, aka shareholders.&lt;br&gt;lol.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884025&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880718&lt;br&gt;Did crypto ever have life in the first place? When you consider the (((forces))) at play behind normalizing CBDCs and tokenization of everything - the entire crypto concept becomes just another homosexual ponzi used to control people, track their purchases, and control their rates in order to reward the good goyim, and punish the bad. Unbacked digital tokens on a screen never had any value to begin with. Some people still think the jew.s. dollar has value even though it is literally unbacked and printable monopoly game board paper. It&amp;#x27;s &amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;VALUE&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot; comes from the jew.s. AIPAC government forcing its usage through tyranny and semitic organizations like the FED. Unbacked paper that the state prints could never be an actual wealth instrument, just fake currency for a fake economy in a fake two-party &amp;quot;&amp;quot;democratic&amp;quot;&amp;quot; nation. Press S to spit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885137&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883631&lt;br&gt;What if I am doing the same thing that always worked and expecting the same result too? Buying assets that &amp;quot;have momentum&amp;quot; is just a different way to say you&amp;#x27;re buying tops, it&amp;#x27;s a retarded strategy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886530&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880718&lt;br&gt;If you didn&amp;#x27;t make it in 2021 or 2017 you are ngmi&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crypto needs a major flush out reset or its cooked for good this time. I have never been more bearish for the future of crypto.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888075&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880718&lt;br&gt;If you are buying alts at this point then you are foolish and deserve to die poor. Go all in on BTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888148&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881059&lt;br&gt;Alts saw no bull run desu, BTC on the other hand pump over 5X. Its a smart choice to go for BTC in case this will happen again. I see a lot of anons are into staking now and that&amp;#x27;s a good sign for long term holding&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889468&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here&amp;#x27;s the chart of the tulip bubble. Hope it helps you bros out. Unfortunately, unlike tulips which grow on solar power and have their own solar cells, your Bitsteins need electricity too, which of course is not distributed. Have fun!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>WHAT IS HAPPENING — 35 replies — 7.5/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61888550</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61888550?lm=1771822297</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 04:51:37 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;WHAT IS HAPPENING&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61888550'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 35 • Updated: 2026-02-23 04:51 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHAT IS HAPPENING&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888557&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888550&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;he still thinks being saylors exit liquidity is a smart hold&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888558&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bitcoin is going to zero, for real this time&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888570&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;is something happening in iran?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888582&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888550&lt;br&gt;worst case scenario: this becomes the 50k waiting room &lt;br&gt;but really i think the crab will continue for another month or two&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888592&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get buttfucked you crypto cucks!!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888644&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888570&lt;br&gt;Hot Muslim sex&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888664&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888570&lt;br&gt;mexico ol’ donnie trumpie is doing more distractions. el mencho is a cia mexican american plant&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888679&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;G A P E D &lt;br&gt;A&lt;br&gt;P&lt;br&gt;E&lt;br&gt;D&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888720&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maybe you should have got real money instead instead of 1s and 0s&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888727&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Finally... the real bottom...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888738&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;linkbtc needs to go down at any cost&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888756&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;WHAT IS HAPPENING&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Took a screenshot for you, fren. Your BitCorns are going to zero, fren. You fell for the digital casino scam for the zillionth time, fren.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888805&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888720&lt;br&gt;You don&amp;#x27;t understand&lt;br&gt;Bitcoin allows you to securely transfer ledger space associated with your wallet, to someone else&amp;#x27;s wallet&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888814&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888756&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;late sunday&lt;br&gt;chinks are dumping again&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888818&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888814&lt;br&gt;le chings aren&amp;#x27;t even awake yet you ree-ree&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888821&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888814&lt;br&gt;binance piss snake dump on the weekend during low liquidity&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888852&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888550&lt;br&gt;Going to Zero as we&amp;#x27;ve told you.&lt;br&gt;Then it will go to 750k and will go up forever 5-15% a year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888863&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;bitpoop status: GAPED + RAPED&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888979&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888550&lt;br&gt;Trump hit the blockchain with the Discombobulator&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889033&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hope it goes to zero soon. This ponzi has lasted way too long.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889152&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889033&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;ponzi&lt;br&gt;You don&amp;#x27;t even know what that word means you dumb gook jeet&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889159&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889152&lt;br&gt;It is a ponzi&lt;br&gt;Bitcoin generates no revenue, produces nothing, has no unique properties that can&amp;#x27;t be perfectly cloned.&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s a fungible collectible, by definition&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889195&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888570&lt;br&gt;Based on supply and personnel movements they were definitely planning a full on invasion this week, but the interview with Huckabee might have ruined it. Now a lot of middle eastern allies are coming out of the woodwork opposing an invasion. Personally I think they will still go through with it today or tomorrow&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889201&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889159&lt;br&gt;But enough about gold.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889202&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889159&lt;br&gt;Even if true, still wouldn&amp;#x27;t make it a ponzi, brainlet&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889204&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889159&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;i use words i dont understand to describe things i dont like&lt;br&gt;good luck, anon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889245&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889201&lt;br&gt;Gold is an element of the universe, by definition it has unique properties &lt;br&gt;Bitcoin can be perfectly cloned in like 15 minutes, the reason the clone would be worth zero is because humans would think that other humans don&amp;#x27;t value it&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As far as what makes Bitcoin a ponzi, it&amp;#x27;s zerosum, there&amp;#x27;s no revenue, earnings, or use cases, yet people talk it up like it&amp;#x27;s an investment, because they know the price only goes up if new suckers get in.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889248&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889245&lt;br&gt;At this price I don&amp;#x27;t think whales even care if price goes up, they just need exit liquidity on the way down&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889250&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888550&lt;br&gt;I voted for this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889259&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888550&lt;br&gt;I also voted for this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889272&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888550&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;fkn 0&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;micro second&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;VR00M&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889327&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889245&lt;br&gt;Bitcoin is the relationship of currently existing btc miners running a shared protocol. You cant replicate that quickly. There has to be a huge amount of decentralized effort, it is in its nature to slowly emerge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889332&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888550&lt;br&gt;i wanted this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Ai is about to crash the economy — 8 replies — 6.9/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889737</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889737?lm=1771834912</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 08:21:52 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Ai is about to crash the economy&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889737'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 8 • Updated: 2026-02-23 08:21 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was released today by citrini&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI gets good. Companies lay off workers. Margins expand. Stocks rip. S&amp;amp;P hits 8,000. Everyone celebrates.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;• But fired workers stop spending. Companies weaken. They buy more AI to cut costs. More layoffs. Less spending. A negative feedback loop with no natural brake.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;• The top 10% of earners drive 50%+ of all consumer spending. They&amp;#x27;re the ones getting replaced. A $180K product manager ends up driving Uber for $45K. Multiply that across every major city.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;• Ghost GDP emerges - the economy is &amp;quot;growing&amp;quot; on paper, but the money never reaches real people. Productivity is booming. Wages are collapsing.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;• Then it hits housing. $13 trillion in mortgages, all underwritten on one assumption: you keep your job for 30 years. In 2008, the loans were bad on day one. In 2028, the loans were good. The world just changed after they were written.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;• S&amp;amp;P crashes 38% from highs. Unemployment hits 10.2%. Markets barely react anymore.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;• The punchline: you&amp;#x27;re not reading this in 2028. You&amp;#x27;re reading it in February 2026. Every domino they describe has already started falling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889750&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WAOW! Link me to this guy&amp;#x27;s substack payment page immediately!!!!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889754&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There&amp;#x27;s over a billion jeets you can just keep vacuuming up the top 10% of them to always have an american middle class&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889766&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is this from that monotone Chinese guy on youtube&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889795&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889737&lt;br&gt;nigga, I am 400K deep into PLTR, you don&amp;#x27;t have to sell me on it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889802&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889737&lt;br&gt;the crazy part no ones even trying to stop it, what you are saying here isn&amp;#x27;t some major breakthrough its plainly obvious to anyone with a brain. another plainly obvious problem with a.i that most people are missing is that its not creative in the same way a person is, a.i cannot invent the airplane so you aren&amp;#x27;t just replacing a high value earner but someone that has tools that a.i doesn&amp;#x27;t have, intuition, creativity all things a.i cannot do and will never be able to do with any accuracy its a complete meme.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889812&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889737&lt;br&gt;None of that has happened, it&amp;#x27;s a fake cover story for the drunken spending companies did post covid. They hired way too many people for bullshit jobs and are now cutting back while saying it&amp;#x27;s because of AI.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rest of the shit is due to inflation, first from covid supply shocks, then companies trying to squeeze every last dollar they could out of the consumer and now trump tariffs. AI hasn&amp;#x27;t even begun to displace people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889814&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Melanin inclined individuals all in on ai are so screwed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889824&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889814&lt;br&gt;America fixed this problem already&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>BTC dumping? Don’t care. It’s temporary. — 79 replies — 6.3/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61869212</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61869212?lm=1771794293</guid><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 21:04:53 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;BTC dumping? Don’t care. It’s temporary.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61869212'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 79 • Updated: 2026-02-22 21:04 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;If it drops, I buy more. If it goes sideways, I accumulate. If it pumps, I chill. I’m earning yield and stacking long term. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Short term volatility doesn’t change the plan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869234&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869212&lt;br&gt;Crypto and BTC is dead retard &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Everyone knows about it by now&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869237&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869212&lt;br&gt;The niggercattle aren&amp;#x27;t going to pump your epsteincoin bags.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869244&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869212&lt;br&gt;Pixel tranny cope.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878113&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872347&lt;br&gt;It’s got maybe one more bull run left in it, but $150K is never happening. Ethereum is already at the &amp;quot;no new ATHs ever again&amp;quot; stage. Crypto is dead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878176&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869234&lt;br&gt;newfag alert&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878183&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873082&lt;br&gt;you are genuinely retarded, keep making them stronger with your rocks but in the end it won&amp;#x27;t matter&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878193&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878176&lt;br&gt;Yeah and beanie babies as an asset class will come roaring back any day now. Enjoy holding your digital bags.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878207&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878193&lt;br&gt;Not exactly accurate there&amp;#x27;s a few beanie babies still fetching over a million right now anon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878212&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877711&lt;br&gt;FUD only&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878223&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878207&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;fetching&lt;br&gt;Why are they all the same price if they&amp;#x27;re an appreciating asset?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878248&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878207&lt;br&gt;Just because you ask for a price doesn&amp;#x27;t mean you&amp;#x27;ll get it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878256&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877979&lt;br&gt;No. You never share private keys. BTC is locked in a Bitcoin script where spending still requires the staker’s signature. If the platform disappears like I said, the timelock path lets you withdraw using Bitcoin only.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878321&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877722&lt;br&gt;sure anon. why? tech, users, or just hoping for a pump?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878324&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878207&lt;br&gt;Can we make money here? I&amp;#x27;m so tired of negative PNL&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878330&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878248&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s losers trade&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878331&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869212&lt;br&gt;I own a lil bit of btc and eth myself (3% of my entire portfolio) but I would unironically love to see the entire crypto market going to 0. You bitcoin maxi retards need to wake up. Your 5k stack of crypto wont magically 100x in the next 5-10 years and make you rich lol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878347&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878072&lt;br&gt;Nah. I’ve already explained it a bunch. DYOR anon. Either let BTC sleep or look into native, self custody setups and pick what fits you kek.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878349&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869514&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;the elites&lt;br&gt;There are many kinds of elites that compete against each other. Many of them want strategic reserves of BTC to trade with. BTC will never die.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878352&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878331&lt;br&gt;What&amp;#x27;s wrong with btc maxis&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878368&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877734&lt;br&gt;Damn! Taxi drivers don’t call tops and bottoms, they just repeat headlines. Stick to your plan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878374&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878078&lt;br&gt;Not my crowd. Stay poor, anon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878376&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869212&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I&amp;#x27;ve tricked myself with a berg-word for any situation!&lt;br&gt;good for you anon? what do you want me to do with this information?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878386&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869360&lt;br&gt;And yet comex+cme can evaporate 10 trillion in market cap in three days. Going to take one from the xrp schizos and say mcap doesn&amp;#x27;t mean anything. Still hold actual metals and not paper derivatives though...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879258&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878113&lt;br&gt;If crypto is dead, why is the onchain activity, stablecoins, and L2 growth still there? Price isn’t the whole story.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880618&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878349&lt;br&gt;Someone gets it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882946&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878376&lt;br&gt;It depends on you anon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882959&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869212&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is Polkadot decoupling from Bitcoin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883795&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877290&lt;br&gt;Based. We’ve all seen how “temporarily custodial” ends. NGMI if you outsource sovereignty and then act surprised when it rug-pulls itself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883846&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878331&lt;br&gt;the problem with btc is it used to be the gambling outlet than we got kalshi, polymarket, all the sports gambling. no one cares about up down anymore, theres 100000 different things to gamble on. they&amp;#x27;re sucking up all the crypto money. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;god damn tho those 7.10 kalshi stock options. how about build something instead of try to piggy back someone else?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883859&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869212&lt;br&gt;Who thinks ANY crypto is worth it....in 2026!?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Not old stuff then, what NEW crypto will be 100 or 1000 times on Monday, faggots?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885711&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882959&lt;br&gt;it just hasn’t dumped yet. wait for BTC to sneeze and we’ll see how independent it really is&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886601&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883795&lt;br&gt;Finally! Not your keys, not your coins.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887813&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869212&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;Short term volatility doesn’t change the plan.&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;Is a cope created by broke people. Bye, broke person. Enjoy the shift tomorrow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>