<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>/biz/ Active (filtered, with replies)</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/</link><description>Filtered out: general, gme, bbbyq. OP + first 3 replies + last 30 replies.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 22:44:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Is it really that much more difficult to start a business in the eu than us? — 79 replies — 316.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860796</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860796?lm=1771540972</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 22:42:52 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Is it really that much more difficult to start a business in the eu than us?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860796'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 79 • Updated: 2026-02-19 22:42 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;You guys in the EU make less than us on paychecks, but you get to keep more of your money because you have universal healthcare and PTO while we have to pay for private insurance which chronically denies people&amp;#x27;s health situations. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Are people saying that starting a business in the EU is difficult because of the regulations? What regulations does the European union impose on its citizen&amp;#x27;s than they think it&amp;#x27;s easier to start in the United States instead?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860815&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;Depends enormously on which country are we talking about. Some are easy (Germany) some are very hard (Italy)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860817&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; you get to keep more of your money because you have universal healthcare&lt;br&gt;yeah right&lt;br&gt;good luck getting that &amp;quot;universal healthcare&amp;quot; if you&amp;#x27;re not a boomer, waiting lists are years for even a basic exam/procedure. It&amp;#x27;s either you go private (and pay out of your own pocket) or you die&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; and PTO&lt;br&gt;oh wow, 20 wagie cagie free days a year. Totally worth the 60%+ taxes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;All taxation is theft. It&amp;#x27;s just that. Taxation doesn&amp;#x27;t pay for services. It&amp;#x27;s just the way they control the economy, and here in EU they fucking LOVE to control what you can and cannot do. They print the money, they don&amp;#x27;t need to tax you. They tax you to control you (and to humiliate you)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860822&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;The healthcare thing is too much american leftie argument, it also has been very overcrowded by you guessed arabs and africans, unironically I was better treated when I broke my leg in brazil of all places then in france&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870682&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870203&lt;br&gt;ah, i see, you are retarded. just because some laws that are lax exist doesn&amp;#x27;t mean data is protected, you fucking retarded faggot&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870744&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870065&lt;br&gt;it started long before post-WW2 tho, germs bureaucracymaxxed post-reunification during the 2nd Reich, from 1871 onward.&lt;br&gt;At first it was to keep in check all the landers trying to take the lion&amp;#x27;s share of federal credits and centralize power. And it worked gud, but then it progressively became the hellscape kafkaian machine we all know.&lt;br&gt;That&amp;#x27;s how you know the hallofcost never happened, becuz you can be sure nazis would have made endless paperworks addressing the situation, down to the very last jewish pubic hair, but we didn&amp;#x27;t find any document.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870778&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stop eating the commie propaganda. Europeans don&amp;#x27;t have savings for shit, they just have stable expenses but all their wealth is tied to inheriting homes. That&amp;#x27;s why homes are basically untaxed while stocks are treated like financial Nazism. You aren&amp;#x27;t going to spend more a healthy young person in the US, the real benefit of Europe is the private healthcare is very cheap and good &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Starting businesses in Europe sucks because of two factors. The first is low liquidity and consumer spending: unlike the US, people don&amp;#x27;t spend nearly as much, have as much to spend, or make debt. So there isn&amp;#x27;t much room for anyone to buy something new - successful businesses target liquid tourists or B2B, where they write off the huge taxes as expenses. Over regulated financial market also leads to lower liquidity and more difficulty getting loans and investors, you rely on government programs run by middle aged menopausal cunts that have never worked more than 28 hours a week &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other issue is labor laws and public perception. It&amp;#x27;s morally bankrupt to try and get more money, why aren&amp;#x27;t you happy being average, why are you trying to pull ahead. Anyone you hire can&amp;#x27;t be fired, you can&amp;#x27;t have low compensation with offset packages to get high skill labor, you need to suck some blue blooded cock to get money and not wait years for whatever permits you&amp;#x27;ll need, because they were born out of nobility and still have half the money and connections &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eurotards freak out about Epstein but every European politician and rich person rapes babies for breakfast. It&amp;#x27;s just 1) not pedo to them if they&amp;#x27;re over 14 bc muh age of consent and 2) they hide in the shadows unlike Americans, they try to be as unnoticed as possible, give a few concessions to the poor and continue ruling sucking and fucking like they&amp;#x27;ve been doing the past thousand years&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870889&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870103&lt;br&gt;What are the reforms that boomers are blocking?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870915&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869942&lt;br&gt;Yeah i feel the same. Sex, drugs and love are already the ultimate sensations and none of them are expensive. All luxuries are pretty worthless add-ons and don’t feel special. You just have a bigger bed, or a bigger car, not anything you really need.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870937&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860817&lt;br&gt;That&amp;#x27;s complete bullshit, stop making up fantasies in your mind. If there is ONE thing still somewhat running smoothly in western Europe, it&amp;#x27;s free healthcare.&lt;br&gt;Contrary to you i know what i&amp;#x27;m talking about since i was on the operation table just a month ago to fix few lower vertebrae after a bike accident. I never had to wait for anything more than few days, nor did i have to spend a single penny on pre-procedures, examinations or for the hospital stay/operation/anesthesia/post-op medication. And i don&amp;#x27;t have any health mutual.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It probably would have costed me a bazillion goybux in the jewSA.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871000&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870937&lt;br&gt;Why the fuck would it cost bajillions, even shit insurance has a max out of pocket of like 10k. If you don&amp;#x27;t have a job medicaid literally covers everything for free, the real problem is half the people that qualify are too fucking stupid to sign up for it &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Also if the accident wasn&amp;#x27;t your fault you could sue for big money, in Europe they&amp;#x27;re just like meh accidents happen enjoy the lifelong complications faggot. I will agree southern European health systems are pretty decent and their private healthcare is fantastic and cheap, but if you&amp;#x27;re German or some shit I&amp;#x27;d rather have the US system, you guys pay more in healthcare tax than any American if you have a half decent job and if you get anything where you may actually die they just say, yeah you&amp;#x27;re fucked settle your affairs or the bureaucracy will give the rest of your family a stroke, no point trying any more it&amp;#x27;s an inefficient allocation of resources&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871020&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868041&lt;br&gt;This is extremely short-sighted of them, they will end up losing the capacity to compete and fall behind slowly, they actually already are, then when they slowly go on closing business left and right from ever increasing ineficiency. What else can they even do but borrow more and more for the worst possible spending a state can do, paying bills, a budget blackhole, increasing inflation and making money useless and as those countries get poorer the services will also get far far far worse and extremely corrupt, not even talking about how such aging will make it even worse. Honestly this is reading like what happened to argentina, greece and other latam and thirdies socialist govts did, it will work fine as long as the economy can keep it, when it starts to shrink it will be poverty hell. I will agree that america treats us workers pretty bad, but this welfare paradise of the EU won&amp;#x27;t work for long either, they will end up forced to cut things and get closer to us if they want to survive a world with China, India, US and former colonies being no longer mudhutts but mildly developed enough to make raw resources more expensive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871023&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;Lots of retards ITT.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Setting up a business is child&amp;#x27;s play in places like Denmark, Sweden, Estonia. Setting up, doing tax returns and all interactions with gov is handled through online ID and takes seconds.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Places like Bulgaria, Romania, Slovenia are selling themselves as business friendly. Very low taxes. Some places like Bulgaria have extremely low dividend taxes so you pay yourself with dividends. Romania has a corporate setup where you pay a tiny percentage on the turnover. Ideal for freelancers or small business with high margins or just extreme low expense. In all of these places, corporate setups and accountants cost next to nothing.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Then you have some almost offshore jurisdictions still in the EU with insanely beneficial rules for some niches and very low taxes. Like Cyprus and Malta.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now regulations, what regulations? Anything (except guns, booze, some gambling, cigarettes I guess) is traded freely between the states under the same legislation. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Also: we get sued way less over here. Do the math on that one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871050&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; wife started selling her paintings&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; she declared herself first, this was needed to attend some events&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; French government instantly asks her for €800, before she has made her first sale&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; this is what they estimate she&amp;#x27;d owe them at the end of the year based on their estimates of how much she will earn, so they ask for it upfront&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; you can contest it but it&amp;#x27;s actually faster to wait for the year to end so they are proven wrong&lt;br&gt;I hate them so much...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871051&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860860&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;taxes&lt;br&gt;depends where, some places will legit rape your revenue&lt;br&gt;Combined with some insane regulations and you legit can&amp;#x27;t start a company&lt;br&gt;Best example is France, fucked up taxes, and if you want to get into tech, or anything that involves personal data, you need cough up 6 to 7 figures so that your cyber security is in the norm&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871089&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860815&lt;br&gt;This&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871111&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871020&lt;br&gt;I will die long before I see some high tech company or even mid tier industry appear in latam, africa or even india, they will always be turning up cheap raw resources because they are simply brown subhumans with low iq, not even talking about russia post-war. Its an unfounded fearmongering that we will ever have to compete with them lol, you forget europe will never fall to thirdie level of mismanagement simple because we are better educated and white. At the very worst unlikely scenario we will always make money from tourism anyway, but honestly this is all american envy for no reason, we are not stopping you from doing the same.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871116&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871023&lt;br&gt;So you&amp;#x27;re admitting you can only live off arbitrage? Who the fuck are you selling to in Romania or Bulgaria, Romania is actually marginally based because it&amp;#x27;s spread its asshole to US companies for cheap EU labor, those Nordic countries you listed have a smaller economy than Pennsylvania so yeah if you want to sell troon support stickers you&amp;#x27;re good but you&amp;#x27;re not going to make shit otherwise &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Portugal is also kind of based but it fully relies on US and other European investments, as well as inexistent enforcement of labor laws and pathetic salaries. I don&amp;#x27;t get how you&amp;#x27;d start up there without the first 100k being gifted though, or the family having land, or working abroad first &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As I said, Europe is only viable for tourism or B2B, you will never become a millionaire opening a bakery or car wash or hamster fentanyl university of arts like the US, there&amp;#x27;s no consumer spending to eat&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871180&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871116&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Europe is only viable for tourism or B2B, you will never become a millionaire&lt;br&gt;Lmao, just look at economic charts, most european economies have high tech industry as the main economic activity, american bullshit as usual, nobody needs to be a millionaire in europe, we already live better than one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871183&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871116&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Who the fuck are you selling to in Romania or Bulgaria,&lt;br&gt;As I said, you are a fucking retard. Your company is in Bulgaria, but you sell to fucking anyone in EU the same way while paying insanely low corporate tax and next to no admin fees. You ship from anywhere you want in the EU, or have staff in bloody Manila if you wish. What the fuck does that have to do with arbitrage? You incorporate wherever you want since it is your legal right.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I doubt you are entrepreneurial material though, so do not bother grokking the potential here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871191&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871000&lt;br&gt;The suing thing is the biggest AIDS of USA. People are already well compensated enough in europe for their troubles. The ”if you make a honest mistake, someone will see their opportinity and sue you and financially destroy your life” mentality just creates even more stress to an already high stress environment of USA. It just makes people act even more legally defensive at every turn and creates useless bureucracy and slows things down. Getting raped when everything didn’t go 100% nicely is not something to be proud of.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871214&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871020&lt;br&gt;This is the most midwit take and the reason why USA is failing now (it has become a nation of midwits due to poor public education). People have been saying this for decades but right now europe is in a bullrun while USA has been becoming an oligarchic brasil since the 80s. Clearly socialism doesn&amp;#x27;t just lead to inefficiency but instead to more efficiency for all instead of just few hoarding the wealth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871353&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871183&lt;br&gt;Learn to read Fritz, you are saying what I&amp;#x27;m saying while sounding like a mong. You&amp;#x27;re setting up in poor countries to sell to richer countries&amp;#x27; businesses while using the common market, it&amp;#x27;s geographic arbitrage you sausage guzzling troon, and you&amp;#x27;re selling to businesses. All that free education and you&amp;#x27;re still poorer than a fucking car salesman in Pensacola&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871500&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871214&lt;br&gt;What? Excluding Pooland all major eu economies have stopped growing or deacelerated fast, people were saying it for decades with reason, if it wasnt for a miraculous fall of the ussr and a flood of cheap raw resources and energy with negligible transport costs from russia it would&amp;#x27;ve happened earlier as it did post-2008 when europe started to lag more and more behind the US and China.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871533&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867554&lt;br&gt;Nigger&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;give us taxes goy&lt;br&gt;ok, well, how much&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;We don&amp;#x27;t know uwu&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;you tell us&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;but if you&amp;#x27;re wrong we get to take even more of your money lol&lt;br&gt;you just said you don&amp;#x27;t know what I owe&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;thats right &lt;br&gt;so how do you know if I pay wrong?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Don&amp;#x27;t get cheeky with us you little shit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871570&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871500&lt;br&gt;That guy is fucking retarded why even argue. The average European is still a moron, printing useless degrees doesn&amp;#x27;t make people smarter. They still cuck themselves daily. He&amp;#x27;s happy to never own anything so his blue blooded friends can hoard the land and wealth like they&amp;#x27;ve always done &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Muh healthcare muh taxes &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Half of every country is too fucking poor to pay tax, and the top 10% isn&amp;#x27;t stupid enough to pay tax, so the middle class just pays 50% of their income while being happy they can rent a shit hole for life and that they&amp;#x27;re better off unemployed than working in terms of life quality &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I will definitely return to Europe once my nest egg is built, I&amp;#x27;ll just live in 2 different countries 179 days a year and live off US divvies therefore paying no retard tax and just paying private healthcare out of pocket, or if I really make it just pay the flat 100k Italian tax and get private insurance for 300 a month that will pay for top quality coverage while I sip Italian wines and hire high end eastern european hookers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871624&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871570&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;can’t get women otherwise so has to pay for hookers&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thanks for revealing that you’re some dysfunctional weirdo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871681&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871624&lt;br&gt;Thanks for showing why you&amp;#x27;re weak, religious morals won&amp;#x27;t get you anywhere. Also very europilled, way more Europeans use hookers than Americans outside the lower class - but you pretend like it&amp;#x27;s somehow weird while you haven&amp;#x27;t even been to church since your communion &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For now I bang for free, outside working and life only about one chick a week, but you bet your ass I&amp;#x27;ll buy some dimes when I can live off passive income, at least they&amp;#x27;re safe and making good money unlike the daughters you gave away to arabs to be beaten and bred to show how woke you are&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871776&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many countries are gatekept by language.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871778&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;People are doing a lot of grifting and lobby work for deregulation. Starting a business isn&amp;#x27;t really difficult.&lt;br&gt;There are some bad things, in Germany for example financing rounds require a notary to read out the whole contract in person to you. But a lot of these things you and 90% of small business owners won&amp;#x27;t encounter in practice&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860837&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;tax system is so incredibly fucking complex you have to hire people just to calculate how much you own&lt;br&gt;You legitimately think accountants only exist in Europe?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873866&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868110&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s not bullshit. Europeans are smart. The European rich just refused to pay programmers so any good programmer went to America over the past 35 fucking years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875914&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I am right now in the middle of an administrative process in spain which through no error on my side has taken a cumulative 60 - 70 legal work hours to solve for a license for a business unit that generates 15k € in revenue per annum &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;you tell me&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876003&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871776&lt;br&gt;Shouldn&amp;#x27;t you be good if you speak English and French?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876041&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lol. Lmao.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Imagine not living in an offshore tax haven.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We have roads with no potholes and public schools. Hospitals. Low crime and comfy prisons. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Matter of fact, what do you mainlanders get for your tax burden? Other than replacement migration, high crime and crumbling public infrastructure?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Finding a job — 11 replies — 44.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61875447</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61875447?lm=1771540258</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 22:30:58 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Finding a job&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61875447'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 11 • Updated: 2026-02-19 22:30 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;I live near Tampa FL and I&amp;#x27;m wondering what are some viable strategies for actually finding work instead of applying to 1000 ghost job listings and praying someone calls me back?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875498&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875447&lt;br&gt;Head to your nearest mcdonalds and talk to the manager. You&amp;#x27;ll be working by end of day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875501&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875498&lt;br&gt;I have an engineering degree I&amp;#x27;d rather starve and be destitute than work in a factory or retail.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875515&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875498&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m trying to find stuff other than fucking McDonald&amp;#x27;s bro&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875627&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875447&lt;br&gt;Sorry bro FL is literally the worst state in the union for jobs&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our fagnigger governor touts how much money he saves skimming off the annual budget yet the taxes remain insanely high the jobs are shit, the wages are laughable, no fault, right to work state. Its shit but a jewlovers dream&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875634&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875447&lt;br&gt;firm handshake direct eye contact&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875790&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875634&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875821&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875447&lt;br&gt;Church. Social network. LinkedIn by making a post asking your hundreds of connections to point you to a job.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875852&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875447&lt;br&gt;Go to drinking place. &lt;br&gt;Talk to people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875930&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875498&lt;br&gt;This is bullshit boomer advice. McDonalds is full and they only want affirmative action subhumans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875971&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875447&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;ve gotten every job I&amp;#x27;ve had by gaming LinkedIn. Add max number of connections each week.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;search for recruiter &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;filter by target company&lt;br&gt;If they add you back send them a message about how you&amp;#x27;re considering applying to a role at their company and ask them some bullshit questions about company culture or whatever other corporate buzz words are popular at the moment. Hold a conversation instead of being full autistic. Then when you find a role you like start asking questions about the role (even if you already know the answer) with the goal of getting them to put you in direct touch with the hiring manager.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m in engineering (real engineering not SWE) so I ask them about NCEES licensure, inter-state reciprocity of license to practice engineering, or some technical questions for the role that HR would never be able to answer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876007&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875447&lt;br&gt;walk into a dealership. dont look like a weak faggot. profit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>BAT — 10 replies — 40.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61875908</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61875908?lm=1771541030</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 22:43:50 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;BAT&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61875908'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 10 • Updated: 2026-02-19 22:43 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;markets are all fucked&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;global recession &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;nobody is hiring &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;STILL holding 340k of this SHIT&lt;br&gt;The fuck am I even doing bros? Is there any hope for BAT to do literally anything?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875915&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;BAT&lt;br&gt;Holy shit. What year is it???&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875923&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875908&lt;br&gt;why didn&amp;#x27;t brave just give rewards in Ethereum or some shit&lt;br&gt;why did it have to be its own token? All they did was invent a token for the sole purpose of selling&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875927&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875923&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;he now understands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875981&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875923&lt;br&gt;Advertisers were supposed to buy it, I guess. I guess they liked how ads work already where they pay nothing to the end user and get to program them to miscegenate and eat poison.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875982&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875908&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875915&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875923&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875927&lt;br&gt;whats the usecase for this shit when everybody already uses adblockers and doesn&amp;#x27;t wanna watch ads for your 0.00001 cents worth of crypto?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;this is a smart idea on paper but fucking stupid in physical reality&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876018&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875923&lt;br&gt;Good fucking point. The ICO was fucked as well. The longer I hold the more this seems like a cash grab desu&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876025&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875908&lt;br&gt;There’s a reason why Brendan is only casually mentioned in the Epstein files and BAT is a completely and utterly useless memecoin scam. He is actually a principled man and doesn’t wanna get compromised by Jewish sexpest glowniggers. Turns out he really is the biggest brain in crypto and he won’t be doing anything with BAT until all these disgusting uncouth kikes are long gone&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876038&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61876025&lt;br&gt;Trvth Svpernova&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876042&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61876025&lt;br&gt;Wait this ain&amp;#x27;t a nvke how are you defending a guy for being in the files. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yikes that&amp;#x27;s a bad look sweetie&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876043&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875982&lt;br&gt;Jeets will watch SAR, very good customers who doing the needful, please understand sar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Can we collectively decide to pump ROSE please? — 9 replies — 36.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61875510</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61875510?lm=1771540868</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 22:41:08 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Can we collectively decide to pump ROSE please?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61875510'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 9 • Updated: 2026-02-19 22:41 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before you call me a retarded bag holder and that this is a dead coin (I am and am aware), I&amp;#x27;ve seen you deranged retards come together for some miraculous feats for more impractical shit than this. For all the shit you can say about it, ROSE does have a use case. I think it was just too ahead of its time. Like myself, I&amp;#x27;m assuming there&amp;#x27;s many others here who are still left holding a substantial amount, hoping and praying that it will one day go back up. Why couldn&amp;#x27;t we just as a group decide to pump this up and make it the next GME or AMD so that we can all cash out?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875568&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875510&lt;br&gt;pathetic rosechud&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875740&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875510&lt;br&gt;there are newer and better coins. sorry, but nty.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875765&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875510&lt;br&gt;dawn song darpa meta cia nsa mkultra ai nvidia vietnam&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875780&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alternatively, you have &amp;lt;16 months left to join the CRO bros&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875819&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875780&lt;br&gt;wow kys&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875848&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875510&lt;br&gt;Some exchanges freeze your account if they detect that you participated in a pump and dump&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875872&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875848&lt;br&gt;wow kys&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875903&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875848&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m not inherently asking for a pump and dump. Moreso just for sentiment across the internet for ROSE to increase. I mean, even for non bag holders, its at 0.01. The opportunity for the price to increase is there&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876035&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875903&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;its at 0.01&lt;br&gt;holy shit. you&amp;#x27;re telling me every single holder is down on their initial on this shitcoin? i remember this began trading at 3c and the ico price was also 3c.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>your local drug dealer is a multi-millionaire — 12 replies — 21.4/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61873175</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61873175?lm=1771539049</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 22:10:49 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;your local drug dealer is a multi-millionaire&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61873175'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 12 • Updated: 2026-02-19 22:10 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;re download insta cuz friend sent me reel&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;exploring around&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;find some influencer famous escort girl with 600k followers&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;every single post is just&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;on a private jet with a birkin on the table photo&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;on a private jet with LV bag and wrist in photo showing a patek&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;in front of a g wagon&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;in front of a rari&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;on a private jet again&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;at patek store buying another watch&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;some exotic bora bora looking place in the ocean photo&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;nigga is everyone just rich? who is funding these literal prostitutes what is even going on lmao is her sponsor some arab dude? some big shot drug dealer im so confused how are these girls just flying on 60k a trip PJs and buying 100k+ watches like its water hahaha&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873177&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873175&lt;br&gt;Money and taxation is deeply unequal, there are far more people that don&amp;#x27;t flaunt their wealth but are obscenely wealthy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873180&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873175&lt;br&gt;you get a lot of reward for less risk than it seems like&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;but for you personally only dealing weed to the guys you give blowjobs to on grindr will work&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873183&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;1&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873199&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873175&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;is everyone just rich?&lt;br&gt;No retard, almost no one is rich.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873232&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873180&lt;br&gt;fuck you its not fair i wanna fly on private jets to bora bora and get pateks bought for me by a rich sugar mama..&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873199&lt;br&gt;liar everyone is fucking rich, crypto scammers, drug dealers, scammers, your fucking Mexican cleaning lady that charges 200 to a clean a house that takes 1 hour (she can do like 3 -4 a day and make bank)... EVERYONE IN AMERICA IS RICH&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873251&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873175&lt;br&gt;A lot of Insta stuff is staged&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;rented jets and cars&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;travel places just for a few photos&lt;br&gt;I agree a lot of people are rich for no reason, but many of them are just manicuring an experience to make them look rich&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873257&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;i live in LA most of it is fake dont worry &lt;br&gt;yeah some of can be real but more often than not the car is rented, watch is fake, bag is fake, private jet is a photo set, clothes are from china, portfolio isn&amp;#x27;t real, it&amp;#x27;s all a flex to try and scam people with courses or coaching or crypto or some other bullshit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873518&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873175&lt;br&gt;like look at this girl wtf its not fair&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;https://www.instagram.com/gissydoll/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873548&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873257&lt;br&gt;This. It&amp;#x27;s actually pretty insane that there are still people who are dumb enough to fall for it, considering how well known the grift has become&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873646&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873232&lt;br&gt;just get born a beautiful blonde and you will be fine.. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;otherwise the anon earlier said it: knee pads bro jus tlike the rest of us&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875286&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873175&lt;br&gt;first day on the internet, nigga?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875932&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875286&lt;br&gt;shit i guess so foe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>I don't think BTC is how Satoshi described Bitcoin to be in 2008/9. — 5 replies — 20.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61875503</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61875503?lm=1771540823</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 22:40:23 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t think BTC is how Satoshi described Bitcoin to be in 2008/9.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61875503'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 5 • Updated: 2026-02-19 22:40 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875544&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s called Satoshi&amp;#x27;s Vision&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875547&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875503&lt;br&gt;We did it sisters, we actually defeated the jews with buttcorn&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875552&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875503&lt;br&gt;No shit, greed and simping for institutional investment, combined with a total failure to scale has neutered the project. Don&amp;#x27;t come at me with that LN niggotry either, bitcoin wasn&amp;#x27;t supposed to be PayPal 2.0&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875958&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875503&lt;br&gt;It isn&amp;#x27;t. It was supposed to be private money. It was subverted while Epstein&amp;#x27;s MIT lab had majority control over it for a majority of its code build and now it is unscalable and unusable without scaling into shitty, INSANELY centralized L2 end services that are retardedly expensive and slow when better technologies with more functionality that are actually decentralized and have privacy capabilities can scale at L1. Namely the ones Epstein messaged opposing in his emails and then lobbied Gensler to go after when he conditioned him for Chairman of the SEC, XRP.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876034&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;i think moore&amp;#x27;s law was already dead when bitcoin started&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>&gt;max out your 401(k) employer match &gt;max out a Roth IRA &gt;have a reasonable amount of cash in savings for a rainy day &gt;do… — 4 replies — 15.5/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61875968</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61875968?lm=1771540134</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 22:28:54 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;&amp;gt;max out your 401(k) employer match &amp;gt;max out a Roth IRA &amp;gt;have a reasonable amount of cash in savings for a rainy day &amp;gt;do…&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61875968'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 4 • Updated: 2026-02-19 22:28 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;max out your 401(k) employer match&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;max out a Roth IRA&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;have a reasonable amount of cash in savings for a rainy day&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;don&amp;#x27;t make stupid decisions&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;retire as a millionaire&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s that easy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875983&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875968&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;dude just wage slave for 40 years&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875986&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;die at 59&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;or have only 5-10 years to enjoy millions&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;can only enjoy money when you cant move anymore&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;great deal anon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875994&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I lost my virginity in 2005&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875995&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Boomers sold their children and grandchildren into a life of immiserated slavery so they could spend their twilight years living in luxury. It&amp;#x27;s the reason the covid lockdowns happened. They were the only demographic at risk but they had no problem shutting society down and ruining the lives of the youth to prevent themselves from getting a bad cough. We live under boomer communism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Day 217 of snailposting every day until LINK is at $100 — 6 replies — 14.2/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61874340</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61874340?lm=1771539538</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 22:18:58 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Day 217 of snailposting every day until LINK is at $100&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61874340'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 6 • Updated: 2026-02-19 22:18 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Day 217 of snailposting every day until LINK is at $100&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875153&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yeah&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875206&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;fuck stinkies&lt;br&gt;fuck em all yeah&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875210&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874340&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s a literal miracle that it isn&amp;#x27;t yet. A cruel and perverted miracle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875376&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875210&lt;br&gt;soon brother&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875910&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The lower the price, the higher the deposited reserve amount. Cheer up, lads.&lt;br&gt;Imagine the amount when LINK hits $4.90 by EoY.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875963&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I would literally rather marry an Indian than be OP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>How high will the next VIX spike go — 3 replies — 12.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61875921</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61875921?lm=1771540817</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 22:40:17 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;How high will the next VIX spike go&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61875921'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 3 • Updated: 2026-02-19 22:40 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;So we all (at least I hope) know that we are due for a large VIX spike before a buying opportunity. We are at 21 VIX and the market hasn’t even finished topping yet (XLE, XLB, XLI)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;So what VIX level are you buying? 27? 30? 35? &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here’s some potential issues causing elevated VIX&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;iran war&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;bond yields blowing out if oil goes above 80 from war&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;DXY deflationary rally from 6 month dump&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;tariff ruling &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;capex bubble&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;AI bubble&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;AI disruption&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;new deepseek release&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;recession fear&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;growth/inflation from running economy too hot&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;random trump tweets&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875956&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;70&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875993&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;So I don’t know much about trading volatility. Is the play to buy this, set an upper limit sell order, and just forget about it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876032&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some mad cunt has a big load of $80 VIX calls&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lets pray he&amp;#x27;s wrong.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;No additional replies in the latest window.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Vance — 5 replies — 9.8/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61874782</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61874782?lm=1771539221</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 22:13:41 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Vance&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61874782'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 5 • Updated: 2026-02-19 22:13 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt; JD VANCE SAID, “CHINA DOESN&amp;#x27;T LIKE BITCOIN. WE SHOULD BE ASKING OURSELVES, WHY IS THAT?”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;WHY IS OUR BIGGEST ADVERSARY SUCH AN OPPONENT OF BITCOIN?”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;IF THE CCP IS LEANING AWAY FROM BITCOIN, THEN MAYBE THE US SHOULD BE LEANING IN TO BITCOIN.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874791&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874782&lt;br&gt;china hates having gay sex with peter thiel. we should be leaning in to having gay sex with peter theil.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874820&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874782&lt;br&gt;OH MY GOOOOOOOD NO WAY&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875813&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874782&lt;br&gt;china hates 18 year old foids taking fat nasty girl dumps right in my mouth hole&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875936&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874782&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s because they have a closed capital account economy with total firewall over its people and a CBDC. It isn&amp;#x27;t such a profound wonder..&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875943&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875936&lt;br&gt;Bitcoin is western surveillance technology &lt;br&gt;the CCP doesn&amp;#x27;t have majority control over anymore (but used to) with a majority of the code created while Epstein had majority control and subverted it as real money to be unusable without centralizing into shitty L2 end services that are still retardedly expensive and slow and completely contrary to the alleged values of bitcoin which CCP has no problem over but they want control of a system like it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>BITCOIN IS AT 67,000 SIX SEVEN!!! — 4 replies — 6.9/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61875756</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61875756?lm=1771538981</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 22:09:41 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;BITCOIN IS AT 67,000 SIX SEVEN!!!&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61875756'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 4 • Updated: 2026-02-19 22:09 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;BITCOIN IS AT 67,000&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;SIX SEVEN!!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875801&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875756&lt;br&gt;B&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875810&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Really gaining momentum. Bullrun confirmed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875918&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;big if true&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875928&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YES LET&amp;#x27;S GO CHAT&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>IMF calls on China to cut industrial subsidies in half — 74 replies — 41.2/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61872964</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61872964?lm=1771534594</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 20:56:34 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;IMF calls on China to cut industrial subsidies in half&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61872964'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 74 • Updated: 2026-02-19 20:56 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872971&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872964&lt;br&gt;This is a strategic move by the Chinese to kill off the competition in other countries so the Chinese companies can dominate the sectors and then raise the prices&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872974&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;i&amp;#x27;m sure china will get right on that&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872978&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;jews mad&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872971&lt;br&gt;they can do it forever without raising the prices&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874924&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874896&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s literally just convention, you think business boomers want to spend mental energy on trading in more than two currencies? They don&amp;#x27;t give a fuck as long as the currency&amp;#x27;s worth approximately the same amount in between signing the contract and payment being issued&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874936&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874905&lt;br&gt;I do broadly agree, however if it looks like a country is going to debt-nuke the whole world you have to take some action at some point. The US is just as likely to shit the world economy as china is&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874965&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874899&lt;br&gt;Their currency is currently undervalued by roughly 16% and they actively manage its strength. How do you think they have such a ridiculous surplus? .&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874974&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874965&lt;br&gt;No they keep it tied to the dollar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875001&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874974&lt;br&gt;They have one of the most opaque central banks in the world. Nobody outside of China has any idea how they determine their exchange rate. It’s not hard to see the benefits they gain from keeping it low.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875052&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875001&lt;br&gt;Trump admin:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;NO! NO! NO! Only WE&amp;#x27;RE allowed to devalue our currency because WE need WAGESLAVES more than YOU! Y..you can&amp;#x27;t just print to build infrastructure!!! That&amp;#x27;s communist!!!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875074&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875052&lt;br&gt;I think the euros are more upset with china’s devaluation than America is. The guy in that article complaining is German. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;They’re instantiating a levy on small goods in July to combat the yuan that refuses to budge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875077&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875001&lt;br&gt;How it&amp;#x27;s done? They just keep it tied to the dollar. What are you talking about?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875121&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875077&lt;br&gt;It isn’t strictly tied to the dollar. It WAS before 2005, but now it’s a managed float system that is managed by the central bank. The dollar plays a big role, but it isn’t as if the yuan keeps strict pace with the dollar. They can (and do) manage its exchange rate. Exactly how they determine what the exchange rate should be is the opaque part. One way they manage the yuan’s value is by buying/selling dollars with their currency, and this is one reason why the keep so many dollars in reserve. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is also why, earlier in the thread, I argued that the dollar’s role as a reference point for a currency can still cause it to be accumulated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875124&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872964&lt;br&gt;Sour fucking grapes. The Jews running the west are such idiots&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875149&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875074&lt;br&gt;Germans don&amp;#x27;t even believe in debt, they had a rule in their constitution that they couldn&amp;#x27;t borrow more than 0.35% of GDP annually until 2025 when shit hit the fan for needing to build a real military.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Reee we aren&amp;#x27;t taking on debt so you can&amp;#x27;t either reeee&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875160&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873120&lt;br&gt;They’re disgusting gook bugmen that are not human&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875205&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874965&lt;br&gt;A currency cannot be &amp;quot;undervalued&amp;quot;, because there is no &amp;quot;fair&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;inherent&amp;quot; value for a currency.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;China keeps its currency stable relative to other currencies, mainly USD, to avoid currency exchange risk for exporting and importing companies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;China has a ridiculous surplus because (a) Chinese companies are ridiculously competitive, (b) Chinese companies are not allowed to import the kind of things they want to import because of export controls, (c) Chinese companies are afraid an over-dependence on imports will lead to them being rug-pulled by new export controls or piracy, and (d) the CPC has a &amp;quot;minimize China&amp;#x27;s dependence on others, maximize others&amp;#x27; dependence on China&amp;quot; philosophy on how to win trade wars and avoid shooting wars.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875302&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875205&lt;br&gt;Just because there isn’t an underlying physical commodity to back the currency doesn’t mean that the currency can’t still be undervalued (or overvalued). Parity for currencies, even currencies in a fiat system, is one way that this is calculated. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If a basket of various goods in the US goes for 100 dollars and that same basket of goods in Vietnam goes for 10 dollars (ALL ELSE BEING EQUAL), then a fair exchange rate would be 10 dong for one dollar. This is one way that these are calculated—people look at prices for similar goods, adjust for import and other costs, and determine how much that currency can actually purchase. When a country sets their own exchange rate, even if partially like in china’s case, it’s possible to undervalue it. They have an incentive to claim that their currency is weaker than it actually is. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;So, no, that simply isn’t true. I know what you’re trying to say—fiat money has no intrinsic value—but it doesn’t mean that it can’t be undervalued or overvalued relative to other currencies. There’s a reason why economists or even someone casually interested in the economy and trade policy use these terms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875322&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875149&lt;br&gt;Reparations absolutely traumatized Germans in terms of their willingness to take on debt lol. They’ll have to do some serious heavy lifting in the EU soon, so I imagine they’ll start taking some more on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875497&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875322&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s already happened, they got rid of the limit and are doomping into their infrastructure and military&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875505&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873712&lt;br&gt;kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875517&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874965&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;How do you think they have such a ridiculous surplus?&lt;br&gt;by being better than others at everything that matters&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875527&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LMAO. Expecting Chinese to stop subsidising their industry is akin to asking Americans to stop eating Burgers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875528&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875497&lt;br&gt;Huh no kidding, I hadn’t been paying much attention to that. One thing I will be keeping an eye on is the EU pension crisis and how that’s managed because I personally don’t see a smooth exit from that situation, especially in France. Looking into it, I guess Germany has a similar problem, which I wouldn’t have guessed based on their debt. What’s your take?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875554&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875121&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s between 6 and 8 Yuan so it&amp;#x27;s still tied to the dollar&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875563&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875517&lt;br&gt;Well, my point was that by managing the currency in order to keep it low, it makes exports more attractive, which results in a huge surplus. If the yuan floated freely, this would eventually correct. A huge trade surplus would mean more demand for the yuan and it would strengthen the currency. However, China doesn’t let this happen. If the currency strengthens or threatens to strengthen beyond what they deem desirable, they weaken their currency by selling yuan or by setting a lower daily exchange rate. This is the advantage of a managed currency, but it also means that it pisses everyone off when their own exports aren’t as competitive or their domestic industries suffer. China claims that they don’t this to the extent that they’re accused of, and it definitely comes in waves of egregiousness, but it seems like they’re back at it. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;So yeah, it’s true they’re good at exporting, but their insane trade surplus is in part the result of what I’m describing (an undervalued yuan that is kept undervalued by china’s central bank).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875564&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873590&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;call western &amp;quot;social democracies&amp;quot; capitalist&lt;br&gt;We are 10 times more communist than china... with an extra helping of suicidal democracy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875572&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875527&lt;br&gt;China doesn&amp;#x27;t subsidize their industries though&lt;br&gt;They just do things better and have more affordable standards of living&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875583&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873819&lt;br&gt;Wtf I love China now!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875617&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875554&lt;br&gt;It can be undervalued and tied to the dollar. Read my post. You seem to think that because a currency’s exchange rate hasn’t changed that it can’t be undervalued or overvalued. That’s not true. Its real value in terms of purchasing power could rise and the central bank could artificially exert downward pressure (which would mean that the exchange rate would stay roughly the same over time). This is exactly what China has been accused of forever, and the issue is that China issue exactly forthcoming with their economic data. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is obviously tied to the dollar. It is not STRICTLY PEGGED to the dollar. Every day the PBOC sets the exchange rate. The argument is that this rate hasn’t changed and has remained too low for how much demand there is for the yuan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875625&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875528&lt;br&gt;Well they&amp;#x27;re definitely going to bail the pension system out, but it should be kind of mitigated by the military and infrastructure spending because of their domestic industry. Adding money to those sectors should hypothetically cause more younger people to make more money, increasing direct contributions to the pension system. The bet that they&amp;#x27;re taking is that the spending won&amp;#x27;t increase inflation as much as it will improve the economic situation, which has some merit because Germany and even the rest of the EU have considerably lower debt to GDP than China or the US, and the currency has been appreciating broadly over the past few years giving them room for increased spending&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875629&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875572&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most of them are subsidised. They do not call them as subsidies but different names. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Source: Ran a Business sourcing products from multiple suppliers in China.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875657&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873690&lt;br&gt;A communist dictator that values his people and his country will absolutely make any system built on jewish corruption look bad.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875675&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875625&lt;br&gt;Interesting, good take. Definitely a situation to watch, particularly how the bailout happens. Getting a handle on youth unemployment, especially in France, should help, yeah. Realistically, I wonder if the pension system will be continued for much longer moving forward, and I think the French will lose their shit if it’s reformed in any meaningful way.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>NUCLEAR HAPPENING — 17 replies — 25.6/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61874535</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61874535?lm=1771538670</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 22:04:30 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;NUCLEAR HAPPENING&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61874535'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 17 • Updated: 2026-02-19 22:04 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;FED KASHKARI: CRYPTO IS UTTERLY USELESS&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874539&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No shit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874549&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874535&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;CRYPTO IS UTTERLY USELESS&lt;br&gt;We knew&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874557&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874535&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;kashkari&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Minneapolis Fed&lt;br&gt;Don’t care, didn’t ask&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874558&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874535&lt;br&gt;bring back powell!!!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874561&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;who is that&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874565&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874535&lt;br&gt;bullish&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874570&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874535&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Kashkari&lt;br&gt;crypto is useless saar bay silver sar, silver goood&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874571&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874535&lt;br&gt;Thx kaskari, just solded 100k cryptoes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874574&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;*ahem*cough*ahem*&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874773&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874574&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;saar krip toes useless pls put metal in vaults and use IOUs saaar&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874817&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874535&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;guy who famously loves the infinite money printer hates scarce assets&lt;br&gt;Waow&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874825&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874535&lt;br&gt;KASHKARI has never heard of Chainlink&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874841&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;stablecoins can&amp;#x27;t beat venmo&lt;br&gt;he&amp;#x27;s probably not aware that venmo uses stablecoins&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874997&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;that&amp;#x27;s true but listen, you just need someone to buy it off of you at a profit, so while you&amp;#x27;re a fool for buying useless shit in the first place, the other guy is a &amp;#x27;greater fool&amp;#x27;, if you will&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875870&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874535&lt;br&gt;FUCKKKKKKKK&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875900&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A FED KASHKARI JUST FLEW OVER MY HOUSE&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875911&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Based if I may say so, and I may.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Would you have done the same? — 4 replies — 16.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61875715</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61875715?lm=1771541018</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 22:43:38 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Would you have done the same?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61875715'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 4 • Updated: 2026-02-19 22:43 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am a nurse at a large hospital&amp;#x27;s psych unit. I am also a newly graduated psychiatric nurse practitioner. I was about to start an NP job with a guaranteed salary of 150k with good benefits and a decent RVU bonus (bonuses for how many patients I see). However, this job has incredibly shady business practices, terrible reviews from former employees and was far away from home. The job was in a northern suburb of Dallas-Fort Worth, Texas. It was three 12 hour shifts in a row without a lunch break. I was supposed to start in early April.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I resigned last night in favor of a job close to family in a rural area in the southeast USA. This job pays me a 6,000$ a month draw and 67% of my collections. After I pay off the draw in a few months I could make as much money as I want, but that is contingent on the amount of patients I see. I can work as much or as little as I want. Take as much lunch break as I want. Benefits are offered W-2, but the health insurance is expensive. Here I will be doing real psychiatry and not corporate slop crap psychiatry. Also, my family is very happy about me staying close to home.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Basically I am trading certain money at a shit job for uncertain money (albeit a higher ceiling) at a good job. I talked to one of the NPs at the new place and he says that he makes about 24,000$ a month before taxes after working for 5 years. This would be almost double what I would have made in Frisco.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Do you think I made the right choice? Would you have done the same?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875728&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875715&lt;br&gt;so you took a better job, for higher pay, to live in a lower cost of living area with more flexibility and closer to family?&lt;br&gt;wow, just wow anon. you fucked up big&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875759&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No one knows because every fag online claims he makes 300k a year now. No one knows what a good job is anymore.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875878&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875728&lt;br&gt;True, but there is a worst case scenario where I am getting almost no patients and stuck in the draw for much longer than anticipated. Although if I work 5-6 days a week I doubt this will happen. Also, If I somehow get fired while still paying the draw I have to pay it all off in 10 days, which would be nightmare scenario. There is more risk with the good job.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875905&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875878&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;no patients&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;in rural shartmerica&lt;br&gt;you will be overloaded with obese diabetic fentanyl-addicted burgeoids&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Microtragedy — 28 replies — 14.8/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61873618</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61873618?lm=1771534264</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 20:51:04 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Microtragedy&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61873618'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 28 • Updated: 2026-02-19 20:51 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Imagine DCA&amp;#x27;ing for six years for this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873641&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873618&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873651&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873618&lt;br&gt;Bitcoin is a Dyson mound of cryonetic termites and lived for millions of years on a kinetic crash course with fuck YOU.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873656&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873618&lt;br&gt;Because he can only buy when people give him money. And people only want to buy in bull markets. In a few years he will be seen as a genius though.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873658&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873656&lt;br&gt;his stock is collapsing like a shitcoin and diminishing returns will just make the next bullrun even more underwhelming&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873661&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873658&lt;br&gt;good! classic hns!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873664&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873618&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873665&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873658&lt;br&gt;Looks like it&amp;#x27;s still up a lot from 2022 and 2023&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873668&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873658&lt;br&gt;Can survive 4 years at $8,000 price levels &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Will refinance debt if he needs to&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Can&amp;#x27;t stop the cyber hornets&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873670&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873668&lt;br&gt;that&amp;#x27;s bullshit, his voice was cracking when he said that because he knows its not true.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873685&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873668&lt;br&gt;based saylor&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873789&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873668&lt;br&gt;How could BTC at $8000 not trigger a death spiral?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873792&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873618&lt;br&gt;Kek - just DCA bro! In 20 years I&amp;#x27;ll have the last laugh, you&amp;#x27;ll see!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873793&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873668&lt;br&gt;Right - but to repay debtors he has to dilute his baggie shareholders to zero. You always leave that part out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873802&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s not his money tho, right? It&amp;#x27;s his investors&amp;#x27;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873812&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873618&lt;br&gt;Let me tell you how this shit works. Mstr is a front. It&amp;#x27;s a scheme that allows elite whales to cash out at the top. Fed money goes to Blackrock who buys mstr bonds. Mstr buys Bitcoin OTC from those in &amp;#x27;the club&amp;#x27;&lt;br&gt;There wouldn&amp;#x27;t be enough liquidity otherwise. &lt;br&gt;Noone actually buys mstr it&amp;#x27;s just an Epstein type operation to move money around and the goyim are too dumb to notice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873851&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873618&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saylor is well paid to launder funds through his “Bitcoin” management&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875118&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873812&lt;br&gt;If mstr defaulted on those bonds BlackRock is going to be the biggest loser then since &amp;quot;noone actually buys mstr&amp;quot;. But I guess it won&amp;#x27;t hurt BlackRock portofolio if it really dropped to that point.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maybe ~5-10% of mstr shareholders are genuine retail traders I assume.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875148&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873670&lt;br&gt;Why aren&amp;#x27;t those bitcoins in his cup?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875157&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873668&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873658&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873618&lt;br&gt;Are the longs cheap or still way overbought?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875172&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873658&lt;br&gt;LOL&lt;br&gt;X10 is sure&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875219&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873618&lt;br&gt;why is the mNAV &amp;gt; 1.0 to begin with? shouldn&amp;#x27;t it be &amp;lt; 1.0 since their value is basically btc_holdings - debt_obligations?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875222&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873668&lt;br&gt;I hope this faggot&amp;#x27;s bluff gets called so bad&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875246&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873668&lt;br&gt;Holy based cyber hornets&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875254&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is the best thing to happen to crypto. I get to watch this retarded grifter get justed, and I get to buy cheapies once hes gone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875262&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875254&lt;br&gt;Kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875464&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MSTR would have gone to 1600 a share if he himself had not deliberately shorted the stock thinking he could &amp;#x27;sell volatility&amp;#x27; at the same time a bunch of jews launched a coordinated short attack against him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875504&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875464&lt;br&gt;What makes you think there was a coordinated shorting?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875653&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873618&lt;br&gt;When you adjust for inflation he actually did vastly shitter&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>