<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>/biz/ Active (filtered, with replies)</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/</link><description>Filtered out: general, gme, bbbyq. OP + first 3 replies + last 30 replies.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:47:54 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>European funds for an american — 39 replies — 156.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890472</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890472?lm=1771951076</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:37:56 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;European funds for an american&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890472'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 39 • Updated: 2026-02-24 16:37 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;I want to put 20% of my account in foreign, but not all foreign is created equal. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I predicted the rise in the polish economy. It&amp;#x27;s very simple, a homogenous white country free from communism is always going to become rich. A diverse country full of communists like Canada and South Africa is going to get worse and worse. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I also predicted that the real-estate market in Croatia would sky rocket due to whites fleeing countries like the UK. I was right. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;So.... are there any good mutual/index funds that target the white regions of Europe, that an American can invest in? Is there a Balkans fund? A Baltic fund? Norway/Finland fund (not Sweden or Denmark)? I do not want to invest in the UK, France, Germany, or Spain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890485&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;finland&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;white&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890499&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;please buy my bag&lt;br&gt;nein. Death to every communist, that includes every single member of a political party, everyone over 50, every bureaucrat and every single subsidized &amp;quot;private&amp;quot; which in europe is every company.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890518&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No fucking way those numbers on finland are right. I live in Helsinki and it’s like 25% brown.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891003&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890989&lt;br&gt;not at all. Even the smallest, most remote villages are chokefull of shitskins. There isn&amp;#x27;t a single STREET in the countryside not populated with at least 2-3 shitskins/niggers.&lt;br&gt;I know becuz i live in one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891134&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890472&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;a homogenous white country free from communism&lt;br&gt;not Sweden&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891154&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890855&lt;br&gt;I have friends who moved to Croatia. Reason? White flight from the UK. Highly productive middle class white people pouring out of one area and into another, means good things for one economy and bad things for the other. It&amp;#x27;s no different than watching the small cities that surround Akron, Cleveland, Chicago, Detroit, Oakland, Baltimore, etc... All get richer and richer and have better and better economies due to all of the whites in those cities pouring out into the surrounding areas. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You say it&amp;#x27;s not that simple, yet I&amp;#x27;ve told people this will happen and for 30 years, I&amp;#x27;ve been right. I watched the real estate market in Croatia skyrocket into the stratosphere. I&amp;#x27;ve also made a lot of money on real-estate outside of Cleveland and Akron just by investing in the white flight destinations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891164&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890868&lt;br&gt;This is in fact, old data. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891134&lt;br&gt;Yes. That&amp;#x27;s why I said funds that invest in Norway and Finland, but not Denmark and Sweden. I know Finland isn&amp;#x27;t really Nordic but they&amp;#x27;re next door.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891236&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891154&lt;br&gt;That&amp;#x27;s fine but from the average person&amp;#x27;s perspective you can&amp;#x27;t understand the bigger economic picture and appreciate the vast differences in market size and capital flows.&lt;br&gt;Life for average people may be more or less similar in Croatia and England but the English stock exchange is in another universe compared to these small economies.&lt;br&gt;As I said, I&amp;#x27;m an American living in Latvia. My life is better in Latvia. I&amp;#x27;m just a normal guy. The top 1% and .01% would see things quite differently. Where does one park $100,000,000 in the Baltics?&lt;br&gt;Answer: you don&amp;#x27;t. And downstream from that is YOU don&amp;#x27;t get to invest $50,000 in an Estonia market ETF either. These are frontier markets not even as developed as Brazil or India.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891243&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891003&lt;br&gt;Euskadi&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891374&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891236&lt;br&gt;I think real-estate, and downstream from that medical services, are pretty simple by and large because they&amp;#x27;re mostly just a matter of predicting the migration patterns of middle class white people, while avoiding the political behavior of lumpenprole voters. At a bare minimum investing in medical services and realestate are a safe bet in any communist free white flight destination. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Question then becomes, what financial products are available to me that resemble that in any way. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;There&amp;#x27;s a fund called NHCBHFFT that invests in real estate in estonia, for example.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891396&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890472&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I do not want to invest in the UK&lt;br&gt;FTSE100 has been outperforming the S&amp;amp;P500 for a while now but okay&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891622&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891396&lt;br&gt;I want a stock that will perform well long term, the UK, like Canada and South Africa, has not future unless it claws it&amp;#x27;s way back from Weimar conditions. The massive white flight that has already taken place and has been accelerating, looks exactly how things looked for Detroit, Chicago, Oakland, Baltimore, etc... &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ghettofication is an economy killer. Because people ignore it and it makes people irrational, that is the area an investor can exploit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892062&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890472&lt;br&gt;Brown migration is stagnating across Europe and so is the birthrate of migrants of the 2nd/3rd generation. The number of migrants are not big enough to not be outbred in the long run.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892245&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890472&lt;br&gt;This is probably based on early 90s data when Bulgaria was full of gypsies, France was full of North Africans, but the rest of the countries were fine.&lt;br&gt;Now Bulgarian gypsies are also abroad and the roles are reversed, lol (except for France, that&amp;#x27;s only getting worse).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892365&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892062&lt;br&gt;sounds like copium&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892695&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892062&lt;br&gt;White flight is the real economy killer. Again, look at all the places already mentioned. Niggers in america don&amp;#x27;t have exceptional birthrates but once they&amp;#x27;re 20% of a city everyone else runs away. Same as true for states and countries. Most nigger cities in America have half the population they had the in 60s. Akron and Cleveland have lost about half of their population due to white flight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892982&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890855&lt;br&gt;This. &lt;br&gt;I’m polish and I can explain a bit just to give a gist. &lt;br&gt;Poland’s “capitalist” period started in ‘89 so to this day the biggest companies included in WIG20 are completely controlled by National Treasury. So 8 of them constitute about 55% of the index. &lt;br&gt;So mind you by loading up on indexes you’re not really buying innovation rather iron clad businesses that aren’t really growth oriented. &lt;br&gt;Let’ take an example of searching for growth sectors like everyone talks about polish developers so it would be safe to assume that IT stuff has growth potential. &lt;br&gt;And here the biggest IT company is CD project which makes fucking games a dying industry that will be killed by small teams with ai making indie games. &lt;br&gt;Rest of well known IT firms are privately owned or controlled by ventures. &lt;br&gt;It’s hard to really find good stuff I personally think you should search for companies making tangible products or services example solar panels, beauty sector, pharma. &lt;br&gt;We’ve got a lot of ecomerce, construction, pharma/cosmetics, news outlets. Not really innovative stuff. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I mean I wish it was different but really if someone made something meaningful here he would be molested to death by venture capital like CVC Capital Partners and eventually cave in take cash run and live a beautiful trad life in Bielsko Biała.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893067&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892982&lt;br&gt;Cont.&lt;br&gt;So to comparing to the US, Poland is a polar opposite. &lt;br&gt;In the US Capital lobbies politics. In Poland the only people who can lobby are foreign players and people with political power. And this political power has more influence on the stock market while in the US stock market and capital makes politics. &lt;br&gt;The end communist era ripples through Poland up to this day. The people responsible for the transition made themselves very powerful and control the capital to this day. The good news it that their descendants are retarded beyond comprehension and will be unable to maintain power.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895024&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892695&lt;br&gt;They will just flee from one city to another, Germans aren&amp;#x27;t moving from Germany to go to fucking Poopland lol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895226&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890472&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Balkans&lt;br&gt;ha haha hahahahahahaha&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895249&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893067&lt;br&gt;That doesn&amp;#x27;t sound like good news&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895250&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890472&lt;br&gt;South Korea, Japan and Brazil.&lt;br&gt;Lmao if you want to put it into Europe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895308&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890472&lt;br&gt;Check how cucked European stocks are with regards to taxes.&lt;br&gt;The only European stocks i would invest in are stocks listed in London Stock Exchange for this reason.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895312&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895226&lt;br&gt;The Balkans are probably majority white now, because all of the gyppos are here in Finland and other Nordic countries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895890&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890472&lt;br&gt;Look into EU military companies. Saab, Rheinmetall etc. have had huge growth and are still on the rise.&lt;br&gt;Also whatever alternative renewables there are. (Things like synthetic fuels and deep geothermal)&lt;br&gt;Also companies that are processing rare earths and minerals. It is expected that the Europeans will start to extract those resources soon. The usual structure is that companies from outside the EU can mine, but are contractually obligated to sell most of the resources to companies inside of the Union for processing.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Also tech is fine. Plenty of EU countries are turning their backs towards US tech. Many government offices are currently swapping to different software, mostly open source. Expect EU companies to code scaleable European solutions soon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895901&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890472&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Pole pretending to be amerifat in order to brag about his all white country that for some reason has the biggest diaspora of europoors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895911&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now that the Netherlands introduces a retarded tax on unrealized gains (after letting in milliions of low IQ migrants) Switzerland stands alone as an investable country in Europe. Barring a few microstates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895912&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Don&amp;#x27;t invest in Norway even though this is a fake thread made by a pole to brag about his shithole. Anyone wealthy in Norway is looking for an exit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895983&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895901&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m from Ohio.&lt;br&gt;Like 90% of white people in Ohio, I&amp;#x27;m Irish and German. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895912&lt;br&gt;Norway will continue to be a place for whites to move to so long as it remains whiter than sweden. White flight is the biggest predictor that kikes and faggots ignore. You can only beat the market when there is something that makes the professionals behave irrationally. Race and Politics make people behave irrationally. Thus racist investing is the ultimate way to beat the market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895991&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895911&lt;br&gt;Countries that are developing after finally being free from communism, are going to be the countries with the most growth potential. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kind of retarded if you can&amp;#x27;t understand how a country that has only been free for a couple decades has more development opportunity than a mature country where everything has already been built and now there&amp;#x27;s this massive parasitic government that has grown fat off the riches.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896194&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895983&lt;br&gt;You think there will be substantial white flight to Thailand?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896239&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61896194&lt;br&gt;Asia is a different topic. &lt;br&gt;But the high IQ Asian countries that are becoming capitalist later than their neighbors, have the most growth opportunity. So I think Vietnam is the next south Korea.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896307&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895312&lt;br&gt;wrong just like in india there&amp;#x27;s gorilion more to go&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Insider here. Aster will launch its own L1 similar to Hyperliquid in march. It'll give a lot of incentives to attract li… — 14 replies — 56.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61893367</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61893367?lm=1771951300</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:41:40 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Insider here. Aster will launch its own L1 similar to Hyperliquid in march. It&amp;#x27;ll give a lot of incentives to attract li…&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61893367'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 14 • Updated: 2026-02-24 16:41 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Insider here. Aster will launch its own L1 similar to Hyperliquid in march. It&amp;#x27;ll give a lot of incentives to attract liquidity.&lt;br&gt;This is why Aster is the only coin green in this sea of red, and why HYPE is down 10% today. Smart money is accumulating to prepare to farm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893396&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Umm sir, this is 2026.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893425&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893367&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;If the TF2 logo and Super Smash Bros. logo had a baby&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893463&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893367&lt;br&gt;Priced in already. This shit is going sub 50 cents any day now. L1 alone will not move the needle at all&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893479&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893367&lt;br&gt;Peddle your shitcoin somewhere else. Aster had literally six users the other day on it&amp;#x27;s &amp;#x27;perp dex&amp;#x27;. SIX&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893486&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another L1? Man, it’s getting crowded. Interaction between all of these different L1’s sounds like a nightmare. If someone started a company and solved this issue, allowing all of these blockchains to interact with each other seamlessly, I feel like that could be a generational investment opportunity&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893491&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893486&lt;br&gt;that was cubic and it failed horribly&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893501&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;nobody uses Hyperliquid for its l1 lol. it&amp;#x27;s just a no kyc de on Arbitrum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893511&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893367&lt;br&gt;saaaar&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893534&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893367&lt;br&gt;Nobody uses Asster though, Hyperliquid is superior in every aspect.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893542&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893367&lt;br&gt;What are they doing about the fact everyone wants cz to go to jail/die&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893556&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893542&lt;br&gt;there was 6 users on aster yesterday! They dont want!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893625&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893534&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Hyperliquid is superior in every aspect.&lt;br&gt;This and it’s not even close&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893641&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893534&lt;br&gt;Yeap, I&amp;#x27;ve tried both and aster sucked ass. Not many people are using it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896322&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893367&lt;br&gt;Lol, sphincter coin!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>BTC is about to have the by far worst first quarter since COVID. — 5 replies — 20.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61896107</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61896107?lm=1771951631</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:47:11 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;BTC is about to have the by far worst first quarter since COVID.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61896107'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 5 • Updated: 2026-02-24 16:47 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;BTC is about to have the by far worst first quarter since COVID. Massive sell-offs incoming.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896116&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61896107&lt;br&gt;wen moon??&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896133&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61896107&lt;br&gt;The massive selloff already happened&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896140&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61896116&lt;br&gt;250k in mid-late 2028. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61896133&lt;br&gt;lmao&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896278&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;how do I buy?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896346&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61896140&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;250k&lt;br&gt;cope, we will barely hit 150k because of diminishing returns&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Day 222 of snailposting every day until LINK is at $100 — 4 replies — 16.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61895839</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61895839?lm=1771950971</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:36:11 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Day 222 of snailposting every day until LINK is at $100&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61895839'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 4 • Updated: 2026-02-24 16:36 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Day 222 of snailposting every day until LINK is at $100&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895844&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895839&lt;br&gt;lmaoing at this cuckold&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895854&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yeah&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895860&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895839&lt;br&gt;soon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896301&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;they don&amp;#x27;t think it be like it is but it do&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Mac minis are the new ASIC miners — 42 replies — 56.7/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61893434</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61893434?lm=1771949004</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:03:24 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Mac minis are the new ASIC miners&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61893434'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 42 • Updated: 2026-02-24 16:03 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mac minis are like the ASIC miners except they do actual work instead of mining bitcoin for no reason.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893585&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893434&lt;br&gt;What are people even doing with their 50 mac mini AI agents?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893611&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893585&lt;br&gt;Its like a team of 50 indians&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893612&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893611&lt;br&gt;Just imagine the sound of 50 echoing good morning sirs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894324&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There’s a few anecdotal reports of people making money with ai which is driving fomo, but in reality nobody is making money running these bots&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894795&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You cant make money with AI.&lt;br&gt;AI and mac mini is a Rube GoldBERG machine to make unsellable apps like calenders and Diaries&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895001&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893585&lt;br&gt;Its like those Chinese phone farms, only with macs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895139&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893434&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Mac Mini&lt;br&gt;these POS are not designed for this&lt;br&gt;literal ashtrays shortly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895152&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;they are not actually hosting models on those minis lmao, its set up solely so that openclaw doesn&amp;#x27;t disintegrate the OS of your main daily driver computer which often happens&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895163&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894122&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The latest apple minis are 5x faster than equivalent costing PCs at running AI&lt;br&gt;Pure bullshit and you don&amp;#x27;t know shit about technology.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The unified memory bandwith is nice but you only get real benefits with something like M3 Ultra and even then, a properly set up PC inference workstation with real GPU&amp;#x27;s will beat the macs token times by a fair margin&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The problem is with current RAM prices and how scarce GPU&amp;#x27;s with decent VRAM are the Mac is actually a viable alternative to putting a rig together, even if it gets a bit less tokens per second.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895191&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What does AI actually do?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895196&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895191&lt;br&gt;Create asset bubbles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895198&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895191&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895251&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895191&lt;br&gt;What do You actually do?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This message was written by:&lt;br&gt;50 macs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895338&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893611&lt;br&gt;imagine the smell&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895344&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895338&lt;br&gt;jej is make me laugh&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895377&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893611&lt;br&gt;minus the shitting?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895732&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895163&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;even then, a properly set up PC inference workstation with real GPU&amp;#x27;s will beat the macs token times by a fair margin &lt;br&gt;Not at the same price&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895740&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895377&lt;br&gt;Plus they can work 24 hours a day&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895338&lt;br&gt;Apple shouldn&amp;#x27;t actually produce smells because it&amp;#x27;s considered a premium product&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895757&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895191&lt;br&gt;Glorified googling program. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I’ve tried to use AI to diagnose some tricky health issues I’ve had and while it did help at first, I’m pretty sure it eventually tried to kill me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895762&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895732&lt;br&gt;If it was &amp;#x27;the same price&amp;#x27; people would choose the faster option, aka notMac. The problem with the cheap option here being - again - you can cool GPUs and they are somewhat designed to be ran at high temps for extended periods. Mac Minis weren&amp;#x27;t and aren&amp;#x27;t. And these retards are going to fry their Mactrash, abusing them 24/7 as retarded AI agents.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895788&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;you really don&amp;#x27;t need a mac mini, old Lenovo Thinkcenters work perfectly fine and you get get a used one with 32GB of ram and 2 TB of disk space for like $200-300&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I have been using a few with Unbuntu installed to run a bunch of agents on an isolated Vlan at home. (These things are honestly security risks, don&amp;#x27;t give them access to your home network or personal info)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895820&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895757&lt;br&gt;chatgpt is useless now, its a glorified yes man. You can actually trick it into giving horrific advice. Which puts it at the level of a 32 year old life coach, nothing more. Gemini is a good tool if you can get a local unit to run, great for helping map and document trades. But nothing more than that, if you really needed something to bounce ideas off of it isn&amp;#x27;t that. But that is all you can expect out of it, a really good calculator. It&amp;#x27;s when people expect it to be a thinking breathing human is when problems arise&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895868&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895788&lt;br&gt;And what model can you on 32gb ram? Thinkcentres dont have dedicated gpu do they?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895888&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895868&lt;br&gt;no one is running the actual model locally, this is for running the agent and all its tools, most people are running API calls off Openrouter&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895922&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895888&lt;br&gt;These ARE running local models, that&amp;#x27;s the entire point of using MacMinis and unified RAM. Whether the Minis will survive the experience, is another issue entirely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896004&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895757&lt;br&gt;Interesting. &lt;br&gt;Mine kept saying im trans. Kek! &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; sadface.jpg&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896011&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894156&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;give the mac mini all of my personal info, financial data, passwords, internet browsing history etc.&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s a personal computer. It already has all of those things.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896031&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895820&lt;br&gt;Yes that’s pretty much it. Although it did help me diagnose leaky gut issues and initially helped with some supplements, but then it started telling me to basically OD on magnesium and electrolytes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896090&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894238&lt;br&gt;Rent it to people that are scared of running it locally or too stupid to figure it out.&lt;br&gt;Stuff like this https://seafloor.bot/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896126&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Basically in the future everyone will have their own personal agentic AI, and these people are hosting them while its still hard to get it set up.&lt;br&gt;This isnt a sustainable business model tho, because its only a matter of time before soke big company like google starts doing it with infinitely more success because they actually have all the data from everyone, so the AI assistant will come out of factory already knowing you better than you know yourself.&lt;br&gt;But it will be profitable probably for a 1 or 2. I dont see this stuff getting released by a big company before its tested enough to ensure most of the nightmarish stories being reported about openclaw have a close to 0% chance of happening.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896174&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893434&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;they do actual work&lt;br&gt;how much money has your agent made?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896193&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895922&lt;br&gt;No they aren&amp;#x27;t. They&amp;#x27;re just a bunch of iToddlers who can&amp;#x27;t into Raspberry Pi or Linux.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>the future of BTC — 17 replies — 19.7/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61894522</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61894522?lm=1771948563</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:56:03 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;the future of BTC&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61894522'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 17 • Updated: 2026-02-24 15:56 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;screencap this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894525&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;wow cant wait to take on insane amounts of risk for such little gain thanks OP also the past always repeats exactly as before&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894543&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;4x in just 3 short years&lt;br&gt;Zoomers are right&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894560&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894522&lt;br&gt;Doubt it will fall below 200 week MA for that long without a catalyst.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894575&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894543&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;wahhh i only get a 4x wahhhhh&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894588&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;4x on 170,000, or 3x on 240,000 is actually good.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895259&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894575&lt;br&gt;x4 is a horrible performance for an asset that crashes -80% every four years stupid newfag&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895270&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894522&lt;br&gt;I think we&amp;#x27;ll go below 10k&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895280&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894560&lt;br&gt;when will you retards realize the catalyst already happened lol? Kinda sad but I guess you are autistic...The first catalyst was trump and binance fully lifting the ponzi veil, the second catalyst was epstein co-opting bitcoin and tether with types like adam back. so your &amp;quot;200 MA&amp;quot; lol is meaningless. It&amp;#x27;s pretty wild how many of you don&amp;#x27;t realize that it&amp;#x27;s over. Thats what a slow bleed does to a MFer i guess&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895489&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895270&lt;br&gt;Wanting something to be the case isn&amp;#x27;t an argument for it happening.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895550&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894522&lt;br&gt;Bitcoin will never be above Saylor&amp;#x27;s average until he sells at a loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895669&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894522&lt;br&gt;it already dumped, little bro&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896080&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894543&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894560&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895270&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895280&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895550&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895669&lt;br&gt;you retards have been crying for 16 years and I still stack and profit after every single dip&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896092&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894575&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;t. moron who doesn&amp;#x27;t understand risk vs reward calculations&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896096&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895259&lt;br&gt;i make 4x this week&lt;br&gt;BTC unless you are early adopter should be forgoten&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896108&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61896096&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I made a 4x but i&amp;#x27;m not gonna 4x it again&lt;br&gt;imagine being this stupid&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896129&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61896092&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;risk 0&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;reward 4x&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896157&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61896080&lt;br&gt;yes bro&lt;br&gt;buy low&lt;br&gt;but it&amp;#x27;s already oversold&lt;br&gt;niggers waiting for &amp;quot;the real crash&amp;quot; are either delusional or just overthinkers who are always scared of making moves&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Why is Eric Trump deleting all his WLFI and Ethereum posts? — 30 replies — 17.1/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61893430</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61893430?lm=1771945339</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:02:19 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Why is Eric Trump deleting all his WLFI and Ethereum posts?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61893430'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 30 • Updated: 2026-02-24 15:02 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why is Eric Trump deleting all his WLFI and Ethereum posts?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893439&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893430&lt;br&gt;Because the drumpf family is about to be exposed for their crypto crimes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893440&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893430&lt;br&gt;lol xD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893448&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Good disgount obbortunities&lt;br&gt;Low brice&amp;#x27;s de de de&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893504&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893430&lt;br&gt;lol when will these fools realize deleting doesn&amp;#x27;t do shit. once you post, it&amp;#x27;s there forever&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893514&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;should we short WLFI bros&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893518&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893430&lt;br&gt;i hate to break it to you, but the trumps already made their money. they dumped their bags a long time ago and just pretending to still be invested&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893519&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As much as a btc red dildo to 30k would hurt me mentally and physically, it&amp;#x27;s the only way link has a chance at climbing back into the top 5&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893521&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893430&lt;br&gt;i told u about tether dude i warned u&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893576&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893430&lt;br&gt;iran sheaningans&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893620&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893521&lt;br&gt;Explain...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893636&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893430&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893934&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893576&lt;br&gt;and probably more tariff fuckery&lt;br&gt;Or pedophilia&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894002&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;makes me feel good knowing this idiot has no control over the market. its all smoke and mirrors&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894467&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893519&lt;br&gt;So you want Link to be one of the smartest kids in special ed?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894503&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893521&lt;br&gt;lmao tether fud, it really is a bear market&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894504&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893430&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;deleting all his WLFI and Ethereum posts&lt;br&gt;Well mostly because ETH is a dogshit chain. That&amp;#x27;s just a fact.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894634&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893439&lt;br&gt;This&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Trump and his cronies are too stupid to realize once you put it on the internet you can&amp;#x27;t just delete it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894641&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894634&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893504&lt;br&gt;they don&amp;#x27;t care, they&amp;#x27;ve systematically dismantled all legal apparatuses that would hold them accountable for what they&amp;#x27;ve done&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894692&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893430&lt;br&gt;Because ethgate is getting exposed and Zach XBT&amp;#x27;s new report on Ethereum Foundation colluding with CCP and dumping on insider info drops in less than a week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894700&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893430&lt;br&gt;8 hours ago (pic related):&lt;br&gt;https://x.com/EricTrump/status/2026053227108536415&lt;br&gt;15 hours ago:&lt;br&gt;https://x.com/EricTrump/status/2025941658152419412&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894702&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894634&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;you can&amp;#x27;t just delete it.&lt;br&gt;They have succesfully deleted many things anon. Time is all that is needed for even the most heinous crimes to be just a dinner anecdote.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894713&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894641&lt;br&gt;Is that true though? He&amp;#x27;s just going to pardon them when his term is up&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894732&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893439&lt;br&gt;Imagine being dumb enough to provide exit liquidity for Trump&amp;#x27;s kids and saylor&lt;br&gt;Instead of attaining generational wealth, you&amp;#x27;ll be the last of your lineage, as you&amp;#x27;ll be too poor to ever have a family&lt;br&gt;Meanwhile you&amp;#x27;ll stare at a screen, remembering when your useless internet tokens were supposed to be your ticket to freedom&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895168&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;they all should be convicted and the money given back to the american people. Fucking crooks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895190&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anons saw the president of the US of A rug his 80iq base with a memecoin and thought &amp;quot;this is when I should buy&amp;quot;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Top kekkle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895199&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894702&lt;br&gt;This, if you get rich and powerful enough you are untouchable no matter what you do&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895297&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893439&lt;br&gt;Trump will give his whole family a preemptive pardon. They don&amp;#x27;t have to worry about anything&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895451&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893519&lt;br&gt;Link would dump down to $1 if that happened.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895457&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bitcoin was created by the IDF&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895954&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895168&lt;br&gt;A good starting point&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>how do you guys cope with the fact that OF egirls are making tens of millions a year? — 65 replies — 16.5/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889270</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889270?lm=1771937517</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:51:57 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;how do you guys cope with the fact that OF egirls are making tens of millions a year?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889270'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 65 • Updated: 2026-02-24 12:51 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;how do you guys cope with the fact that OF egirls are making tens of millions a year? this shit is really unbelievable man i am seething so hard holy fuck&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889273&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I literally just don&amp;#x27;t care. Nobody will ever love them and I can also make 10 million without displaying my butthole for the world to see&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889278&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s only like top1% creators making millions&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889279&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889273&lt;br&gt;i didnt care too for so long but now im starting to care fml its just so unfair.. Not only are they extremely hot they also get to make 20MM a year for years scamming with bikini pics on OF&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;its just so unfair i feel like crying&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889979&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;Nothings stopping you from doing gya shit on onlyfans&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889986&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;Doesn&amp;#x27;t bother me in the least.&lt;br&gt;Firstly, it causes tons of women to throw their lives away being whores. So is hardly a victory for women.&lt;br&gt;Secondly, what does that money do other than ruin their lives? Women crave a man higher on the totem pole than they are, now they can&amp;#x27;t find one for two reasons.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892313&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;I make faceless straight gay porn. I just ride a bunch of dildos pretending its my first time and they get to pretend they are the ones.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gigs not bad pays about 5k a month. My wife is my manager and hells clean my dildos.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Its not pleasurable by any means just feels like a fat shit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892450&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892313&lt;br&gt;lmao&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893140&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889830&lt;br&gt;everyone compares themselves to women, they are people too after all not some different species&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893380&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Start an only fans account.&lt;br&gt;Show the world your talent.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;My a PBJ using your dick to spread the stuff.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Profit.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Don’t give up until you try.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893392&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Make a PBJ!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Edit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893415&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889279&lt;br&gt;nigga are you stupid, hot girls have always had ez mode, any girl with looks + little brains can hustle money like crazy. I knew a waitress 2 years ago working in a shitty diner that was finessing 3-4 boomers, I remember one time a boomer literally handed her a $3,000 check, no sexual favors or anything, just sweet talk, this chick was spending 5-10,000 dollars a month on clothes and was driving a brand new Jeep luxury model&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893458&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;I know a money laundering scheme when I see one&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893483&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892313&lt;br&gt;Fucking kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893517&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;At least i can coom out of the leaked photos of these e-prostitutes, i can&amp;#x27;t cope with the fact some teenage faggot like barron trump (or Eric i don&amp;#x27;t know who&amp;#x27;s is who in that family of pagan gods worshiper faggots) make billions just because he was born in the &amp;quot;right&amp;quot; family.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893555&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I have never paid for porn or whores in my life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893557&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;the same way I cope with dude getting paid millions to play with balls, I don&amp;#x27;t care. it&amp;#x27;s not me and it doesn&amp;#x27;t impact me, so why should I give a shit?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893569&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;99% of them are making like 20 bucks a month lmfao&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893631&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889354&lt;br&gt;I met a girl who was a friend of a friend of mine at a party when I was younger and she literally handed me a business card with her OF address on it. I didn&amp;#x27;t realize what it was at first but the second I read it I blurted out &amp;quot;What the fuck is wrong with you?&amp;quot; without thinking and she got super offended. I&amp;#x27;m pretty sure I was the first person she handed it to that actually said anything negative about it by the way she reacted, which is very bizarre to me. It&amp;#x27;s kind of crazy how common this shit is.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893680&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;Like everything in the world of money being born a woman was a gamble&lt;br&gt;You just lost it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893688&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t think about women at all anon. They are the worst investment you can make in life&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893708&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889282&lt;br&gt;this right here. tons of people play sports, statistically, 0.000001 get paid well. Image stretching you butthole for a year or two and then finally coming to the conclusion it would have been both easier and more profitable to work a mcjob. add in its a clear red flag so they wont ever get a quality man.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893748&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893140&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;t. tranny&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894411&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889273&lt;br&gt;cope, if i can show my penis for millions i would flex on them hoes bro while being paid.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894435&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s all fake. Yet another demoralization psyop. You really fell for that? LMAO&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894538&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892313&lt;br&gt;You remind me of an anon who was here years ago. Fuck I forget his name but he made like 2k a month selling burping videos. He ended up caving and doing full blown hog cranking after telling anons he was only doing burp fetish shit.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t respect it but I kind of admire the journey desu. Once you&amp;#x27;re on the highway to being a degen there&amp;#x27;s really no off ramp&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894578&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t cope because I don&amp;#x27;t care, but be proud of never contributing to it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895418&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894538&lt;br&gt;Just tell the truth, it was you lol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895453&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;You reek of envy and it&amp;#x27;s pathetic.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;waaaah I&amp;#x27;m unhappy because some people have it better&lt;br&gt;Grow up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895459&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t care. I cannot control it therefore I do not care. They can make 10000 Gorillions every second and I wouldn&amp;#x27;t care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895475&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s upsetting not because I&amp;#x27;m envious but because I pity them. Even the successful ones that are making money I imagine aren&amp;#x27;t happy or fulfilled.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895479&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ai will solve this and make chuds rich at the same time&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895520&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;why does OF cause so much psychic damage to anons? you know guys can make an OF too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895541&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;I guess those egirls are just that much smarter than you, because anyone with millions of dollars compared to a broke bitch must be smart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>insider here, again. — 37 replies — 10.8/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61879263</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61879263?lm=1771939365</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:22:45 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;insider here, again.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61879263'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 37 • Updated: 2026-02-24 13:22 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;i hope you bought BBBY-WT BBBY-WARRANTS&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879648&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I have a few thousand of these along with shares what am I in for&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879767&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879648&lt;br&gt;getting dumped on by OP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879836&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879767&lt;br&gt;Due to my current occupation, I am prohibited from holding stocks, options, or similar investments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880091&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879999&lt;br&gt;Financial system. I am not asking you to hold those warrants until they are exercised. I am asking you to hold them and sell the warrants when we can realize a substantial profit. Nice quads.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881477&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880091&lt;br&gt;Interesting. Wouldn&amp;#x27;t trading the warrants implicitly come with a short term capital gains tax insofar as its impossible to hold them over a year at this point? Would have to be some pretty fair gains to offset that 40% hit...anyways doesn&amp;#x27;t the warrants increasing in price also imply that the shares have gone up in price as well? I ran some informal modeling estimates using black scholes with iv, roughly .65 years to expiry and this is what I came up with: 15.5 bbby share price = 4.50ish warrant price...25 share price/12ish warrant price...60 share price/45ish warrant price...100 share price/85ish warrant price...200 share price 185ish warrant price...I make no claim as to the veracity of these numbers, just for fun. Anyways what do you see happening to the bbby stock price for these warrants to be worthwhile? Am I thinking on the right track in general?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881670&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879263&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881753&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879999&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881477&lt;br&gt;note the digis&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881916&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879263&lt;br&gt;Buy these if you want, but remember, these warrants are not related to the canceled BBBYQ/DK-Butterfly, reguardless of what the BBBYQ schizos say.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881980&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881916&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;nobody tell him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882152&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879263&lt;br&gt;I hold a few&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882389&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;why are americans starting to invest more into VT?&lt;br&gt;isn&amp;#x27;t america the greatest country on earth?&lt;br&gt;for me it has always been VOO&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882429&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;look at NPC holder distribution&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;there&amp;#x27;s no big dumps&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;base still present&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;conviction quietly intact&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884950&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880091&lt;br&gt;So you&amp;#x27;re allowed to buy warrants, won&amp;#x27;t your employer know you bought them?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885366&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get ready everyone. I don&amp;#x27;t think they will be able to kick the can after this sneeze. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885357&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886042&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;what about BBBYQ? i lost all my money. the little i&amp;#x27;ve earned since then i&amp;#x27;ve spent on equipment that will make me a self-made millionaire thanks to my own intellect and blood sweat and tears and not thanks to ryan cohen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886054&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61886042&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886916&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BUY&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887055&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61886042&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;he doesn&amp;#x27;t know what % of powerwash/lawncare businesses fail in their first two years.&lt;br&gt;I appreciate your entrepreneurial spirit, but this isn&amp;#x27;t the flex you think it is.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887380&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887055&lt;br&gt;i&amp;#x27;m not trying to flex i&amp;#x27;m saying the BBBYQ should pay off without having to double down on BBBYW as well. it&amp;#x27;s fucking ridiculous how you can do everything right and run into complete disasters in investing and in other things and getting trolled by random assholes like you as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887389&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ryan cohen and larry cheng are behaving like autistic wankers after making thousands of people lose their life savings and pulte is a clown if he was just grifting BBBYQ investors&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887406&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;and trump is apparently a rapist pedophile murderer who rigged the 2024 election with elon musk and mostly everyone on wall street is getting away with psychopathic scammers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887414&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887380&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;BBBYQ should pay of&lt;br&gt;There will be no payoff for BBBYQ, ever.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887426&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887414&lt;br&gt;then RC should be held accountable for grifting BBBYQ investors, it&amp;#x27;s insulting to everyone&amp;#x27;s intelligence to claimi he did nothing to take advantage of people who looked up to him. though GME maxis are insufferable so they kinda deserve to get scammed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887888&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887380&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m not trolling you, brother. You&amp;#x27;re right, sometimes you do everything right and shit sucks anyways. That&amp;#x27;s what the book of Job is about. You still need to keep the faith, like he did.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889098&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887380&lt;br&gt;BBBYW is more like a lifeboat for people who missed BBBYQ. If you held a fat stack (10,000 plus) of BBBYQ into cancellation then you are good.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890133&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889098&lt;br&gt;2,000 sh @ 038&lt;br&gt;I dont care&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892966&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No one is ever getting shit for canceled BBBYQ shares.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893640&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882152&lt;br&gt;Every asset I own was red today&lt;br&gt;Besides my BBBY warrants&lt;br&gt;Thank you anon schizos for saving my portfolio a month ago with this knowledge&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894969&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893640&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895424&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880091&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;financial system&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just say you&amp;#x27;re the janitor at a bank lmao&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895434&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887426&lt;br&gt;He DID do nothing. You morons were the ones obsessing over him and claiming he&amp;#x27;s still *in* this &amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;play&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895484&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;for how long are you going to continue running this grift?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895609&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895484&lt;br&gt;NEVER SELLING&lt;br&gt;HEDGIE IS A FUCK&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Link vs XRP — 47 replies — 10.5/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889600</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889600?lm=1771935560</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:19:20 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Link vs XRP&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889600'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 47 • Updated: 2026-02-24 12:19 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;When will the gap close? Link came within a hair of flipping xrp in January ‘21. We all know that Link is everything Xrp fraudulently claims to be so it makes sense that this chart should flip soon enough. Will it be gradual or violent? Will it flip because xrp crashes or because Link moons? &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most importantly where are some places you can use Link as collateral to borrow Xrp to take full advantage of the trade of the century?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889606&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m so tired.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889622&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889600&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889606&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889620&lt;br&gt;Link is scam&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Buy XRP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890870&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889600&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889606&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889620&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889622&lt;br&gt;the only usecase any of these has is XLM; because africans are still trading phone minutes as currency and XLM is a reasonable replacement&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;XRP and LINK are complete LARPs that nobody even trusts&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;and i don&amp;#x27;t even give a shit about giving africans currency. but its literally the only thing your larp does in the physical world&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890891&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890390&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;common enterprise&lt;br&gt;You bought a product, not a share. Everything you just wrote proves this is a speculation and not an investment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891011&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889827&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;https://ripple.com/insights/institutional-defi-on-xrpl-scaling-real-world-finance-with-xrp-at-the-core/&lt;br&gt;You keep posting same article like its some kind of mic drop moment. As if linking it over and over suddenly turns it into undeniable proof. It doesn’t lol Youre taking a CEOs words at face value because you think hes personally invested in making you rich. Thats not how this works. CEOs promote their companies and his job is to literally sell you XRP.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891035&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889600&lt;br&gt;Thanks spammy.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889620&lt;br&gt;/thread&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891717&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891011&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m not. It is literally the products they are building and the material they are releasing detailing it to shareholders. Link sell directly to retail every time there is a minor pump. You are literally saying nothing but standing in a way where you think if you come across as affirmative in a direct way it will seem like you are. Lol You are just doing what you accuse me of (which I am not) saying we can&amp;#x27;t trust it to be true because it is relying on the words of someone. It literally isn&amp;#x27;t. They are structuring XRPL core amendment pushes and having their staff code them based on the product suite fit detailed in the article. They made multiple multibillion dollar acquisitions, including a fucking prime broker to actuate it all. And most importantly, the majority of their treasury is in XRP and their products are ALL made more efficient and cost efficient using it and they are incentivized to increase the price of XRP they have in escrow and cannot sell, unlike CLL who dump what was supposed to be operator rewards on retail always and are LITERALLY a fraud designed to milk your savings (exactly what you project Ripple to be, which it isn&amp;#x27;t because the XRPL actually solves efficiencies instead of sticking a tollbooth in the middle of process for literally no reason like a jewish parasite). The entire XRPL is designed to automatically use XRP for auto-bridging between assets etc. Your argument sucks and it is hilarious that it actually applies to link, which you are capable of seeing but literally don&amp;#x27;t care because you are in a literal cult pretending to object but just obsessively committed to a project that is the least morally redeemable or utility having one in all of crypto for literally no reason than ego and entrenched specific coin cultism. Really odd and gay.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891755&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890083&lt;br&gt;Extreme cope. SWIFT said it would take 15 years MINIMUM to even get a product active. I am not sorry to let you know that by that time SWIFT will have 100% missed the boat and payments will have been completely revolutionized, not needing them. You hitched your dingy to a big ship, but it turned out it was the Titanic, which we all always said. Way too little way too late presuming the ethgate lawfare would win but it didn&amp;#x27;t. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890250&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;MPT/permissioned dex is the standard&lt;br&gt;No it hasn&amp;#x27;t. You literally don&amp;#x27;t know what either of those things are. No other ledger at scale has a built in dex and amm and protocol layer compliance like permissioned dex nor the broadness of the MPT standard. It definitely has been The Standard, but not in the way you think. MPT is not &amp;quot;wrapped assets.&amp;quot; Here is an AI slop video that is actually informative which possibly someone at your level of research will be able to be spoonfed by:&lt;br&gt;https://youtu.be/3kYXW_o-N4Y&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890519&lt;br&gt;Top cope in thread&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891887&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890891&lt;br&gt;Everything written proves it&amp;#x27;s a security anon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891914&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890307&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890390&lt;br&gt;The only thing that needs to happen to settle the debate is someone suing. And given chainlink seemingly gives zero fucks about it&amp;#x27;s holders it&amp;#x27;s probably long overdue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892108&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891887&lt;br&gt;It has an etf already bro it’s a defacto commodity and will soon be enshrined in law as a commodity. Also may I just congratulate you on your point that ripple is incentivised to increase the price of Xrp since that is most of their treasury, unlike CLL who also has most of their treasury in Link but is not incentivised to increase the price. I thought that was most salient.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892122&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889600&lt;br&gt;Dunno man, but the best times with link have been when I forgot about it during the bear and came back to big gains&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892185&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891717&lt;br&gt;So other than the CEOs word, what proof do you have they&amp;#x27;re integrating XRP into everything?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892337&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892108&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;CLL who also has most of their treasury in Link but is not incentivised to increase the price.&lt;br&gt;And they never will.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892414&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891011&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Youre taking a CEOs words at face value because you think hes personally invested in making you rich. Thats not how this works. CEOs promote their companies and his job is to literally sell you link&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892515&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892337&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892530&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889600&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;When will the gap close?&lt;br&gt;when the token will be needed for functioning of the network&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892592&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891914&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The only thing that needs to happen to settle the debate is someone suing. And given chainlink seemingly gives zero fucks about it&amp;#x27;s holders it&amp;#x27;s probably long overdue.&lt;br&gt;/thread&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892659&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892185&lt;br&gt;I already mentioned it you fucking retard. You can see the ledger amendment history that they have spent their own dev money and time developing, their acquisitions of Hidden Road, etc. their getting binance listing RLUSD on the XRPL, the fact the early team specifically coded the ledger to explicitly default to its use and to save several percentage points over Ripplenet alone by doing so, the fact that they locked the vast bulk of their corporate treasury up in timed release in it, the fact they fund and partner with multiple large banks to drive and encourage its use and adoption, and the fact the services they are building out literally optimize using it and offer counterparty-less feature that no other asset onchain can, and the fact that they already use it in their business. They literally legally can&amp;#x27;t use it in most contexts yet but with clarity their business can become much more efficient and as a result their core holding increases in value. There is LITERALLY no reason to argue they are not building for its use other than being butthurt that it is true and trying to repress reality like a faggot. They literally have Fednow service providers running XRPL nodes and big banks who are their largest outside investors issuing bonds that reward in XRP (who were celebrated recently in their specific crypto efforts by the financial regulator of Japan) and are partnering with DBS (biggest bank in Singapore (Switzerland of Asia) and Franklin Templeton (trillion plus dollars AUM) building out a repo market on the XRPL. They got ONDO issuing on the XRPL, one of the largest asset managers in Europe/England doing same while basically no one is getting headway in England, Societe General (one of biggest banks in Europe) expanding to include XRP for their euro stablecoin which can bridge to RLUSD using XRP, etc. Literally everything they do builds around corporately driving XRP&amp;#x27;s adoption, literally just fleshing out a business sweet around it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892679&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892659&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892185&lt;br&gt;This isn&amp;#x27;t even 10% of what could be said partnership etc. wise. XRP and link are different in that XRP actually improves business performance and has a reason to exist and incentivizes use in products. Link is literally just a toll booth jew token to insert costs where they would not technologically exist.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892688&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892108&lt;br&gt;The difference is CLL dumps on retail all the time and their business is not improved by the operation of link, it is a technologically pointless token, literally. Ripple hasn&amp;#x27;t sold publicly in over 5 years to retail.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892697&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889600&lt;br&gt;It will most likely be extremely violent the likes of which has literally never been seen before. I am very excited for us.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892933&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891755&lt;br&gt;you&amp;#x27;re practically crying, and they did not say that. I&amp;#x27;m sorry you bet on the wrong horse backed by criminals. to think swift is going to lose is unbelievable amounts of stupidity. haha why am i even talking to you, cya&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892973&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892933&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893028&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892933&lt;br&gt;I mean you&amp;#x27;re retarded and wrong but the cripplets are retarded and right. If that helps at all. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Idk if you link cucks have ever visited the /XSG/ threads but they are hardly ever discussing &amp;quot;muh utility&amp;quot; or even acknowledging other crypto. I&amp;#x27;m pretty sure they&amp;#x27;re currently going /X/ mode and trying to get a retard to be a sacrifice volunteer Mayan style to pump xrp. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Which is hilarious. Anyway buy silver crypto fags.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893103&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892933&lt;br&gt;Really pathetic cope and projection&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893669&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893028&lt;br&gt;Will it work though?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893717&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893669&lt;br&gt;I meaann... it works for the jews&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893824&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893717&lt;br&gt;Kek&lt;br&gt;SACRIFICE SPAMMY 2026&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893980&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;fuck stinks&lt;br&gt;hate &amp;#x27;em&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895158&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892659&lt;br&gt;just look up xrpl code documentation and you will see what a grifter project it is. The hard fact is that no one (relatively speaking) compared to EVM based chains is using it. anything tokenization wise or project wise absolutely PALES against ethereum, thats a hard fact&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;nuh uh, its used by dubai!!!!! and usage will increase 10000000x in the next few months because of institutions!!!&lt;br&gt;yea, sure what if it doesn&amp;#x27;t? &lt;br&gt;Transaction count has been going down overall, just check xrp stats&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895471&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895158&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;and usage will increase 10000000x in the next few months because of institutions!!!&lt;br&gt;Ironic, link has the same problem. At least cripple requires you own some exerpies to do transactions on their network, unlike cucklink.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>I INVESTED IN REAL ESTATE AND ETFs FIVE YEARS AGO AND GOT A 60%+ RETURN — 5 replies — 10.1/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61896003</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61896003?lm=1771949879</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:17:59 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;I INVESTED IN REAL ESTATE AND ETFs FIVE YEARS AGO AND GOT A 60%+ RETURN&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61896003'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 5 • Updated: 2026-02-24 16:17 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile you were trying to scam each other by convincing people to buy crypto and precious metals. For years I had to It seems I won in the end.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Any good thing that your stupid fake money could have achieved was compromised the nanossecond people began to use it as an investment. Reserve value assets are not supposed to be even considered investment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investments are bonds, real estate, stocks, and so on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896009&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;fuck off you childish shizophrenic spammer&lt;br&gt;KYS&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896036&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A lot of tradefi cheerleading today across the mongolian dice gambling board&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896087&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I made 114k YTD trading crypto. Cope harder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896237&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;based boomer etf enjoyer. slow and steady wins the race.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896240&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61896003&lt;br&gt;My overall portfolio return was 80% last year, with PMs &amp;amp; miners being up 3x though?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>any old fags/multi cyclers in here? &gt;class of 2015 &gt;initial 10k &gt;ath 12M (arguably less though due to liquidity) &gt;curren… — 30 replies — 8.8/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61894267</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61894267?lm=1771939392</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:23:12 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;any old fags/multi cyclers in here? &amp;gt;class of 2015 &amp;gt;initial 10k &amp;gt;ath 12M (arguably less though due to liquidity) &amp;gt;curren…&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61894267'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 30 • Updated: 2026-02-24 13:23 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;any old fags/multi cyclers in here?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;class of&lt;br&gt;2015&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;initial&lt;br&gt;10k&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;ath&lt;br&gt;12M (arguably less though due to liquidity)&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;current&lt;br&gt;1.3M&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;biggest fumble&lt;br&gt;had a lot of BNB I sold way too early&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;biggest disappointment&lt;br&gt;ETH&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894562&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894267&lt;br&gt;class of 2008&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;initial was 20k in 2017, ATH was 2.1M (dec 2022)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;i have bought (4) coins - BTC, ETH, LINK, PEPE... everything has made me money&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;biggest disappointment... i guess ETH because it&amp;#x27;s only done a 2x/3x for me?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;the biggest fumble was just selling too early... i cashed out LINK at a 17x and it did a 290x... cashed out PEPE at an 8x and it did a 25x&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;i still think to this day about how the LINK marines spamming dumb memes in 2017 was the best financial advice i ever received in my life&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894566&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894562&lt;br&gt;correction, ATH was dec 2024&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894633&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894566&lt;br&gt;what are you sitting at now?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894682&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894267&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;class of&lt;br&gt;2017&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;initial&lt;br&gt;60k or so&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;ath&lt;br&gt;30M (would have been about 19M after taxes if I&amp;#x27;d realized it all) in jan 25&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;current&lt;br&gt;7.2M&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;biggest fumble&lt;br&gt;Not selling t r u m p at 60 (had bought at 3, ended up selling at 20. 10M upnl &amp;#x27;made&amp;#x27; and gone in under a week). Runner-up: getting hooked on perps after 10/10 and gambling away another 5M trying to make back my summer port highs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;biggest disappointment&lt;br&gt;Being an 8 figga nigga well into last summer and still staying 90% in crypto instead of just socking a few mil into VT and finally relaxing. It&amp;#x27;s incomprehensible to me that I could realize and even vastly surpass my dream of 9 years (to retire, to be fuck you rich) and then have so much time (9 months or so in 2025) to lock in any of those gains and still to utterly fail to do so. Thinking about my taxes was an achilles heel for me because I would keep seeing my port at an ATH, then do the mental math on the taxes I&amp;#x27;d owe if I realized it all, then be mad that my real net worth after taxes was really 30% lower than it was on paper, and then I&amp;#x27;d resolve to make another 1.3x so I could &amp;#x27;make back&amp;#x27; the money I just felt I&amp;#x27;d lost doing the mental math. But doing that would just create another paper ATH that taxes would eat into again, so the chase never ended.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894771&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894682&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Being an 8 figga nigga well into last summer and still staying 90% in crypto instead of just socking a few mil into VT and finally relaxing.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;It&amp;#x27;s incomprehensible to me that I could realize and even vastly surpass my dream of 9 years (to retire, to be fuck you rich) and then have so much time (9 months or so in 2025) to lock in any of those gains and still to utterly fail to do so.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;iktfb&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I think about the same thing multiple times a day&lt;br&gt;could have just clicked out and been done with it&lt;br&gt;come back next cycle&lt;br&gt;but no had to get greedy&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;could have walked away a winner&lt;br&gt;instead feel like a loser&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894776&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ive been in crypto since 2015 and if i had just kept the bitcoin i originally + kept dcaing into the market, i would be at 8 figures now, easily, even after this -50% dump on bitcoin&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;But im at low 5 figures because Ive zero&amp;#x27;d out my port like 20 fucking times&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894791&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894267&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;12M (arguably less though due to liquidity)&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;current 1.3&lt;br&gt;I would unironically kill myself if I was you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894801&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894791&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I would unironically kill myself if I was you.&lt;br&gt;how much do you have?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894776&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;But im at low 5 figures because Ive zero&amp;#x27;d out my port like 20 fucking times&lt;br&gt;how?&lt;br&gt;you&amp;#x27;ve been in since 2015&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894861&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894801&lt;br&gt;Zero&amp;#x27;d out how? Perps were the main cause, and YOLO&amp;#x27;ing 6 fig buys into projects that literally went to zero&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894970&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894861&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Zero&amp;#x27;d out how? Perps were the main cause, and YOLO&amp;#x27;ing 6 fig buys into projects that literally went to zero&lt;br&gt;fuck&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;i feel you bro&lt;br&gt;whats life like now then?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895097&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;class of&lt;br&gt;2017&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;initial&lt;br&gt;20k&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;ath&lt;br&gt;~3M (arguably less though due to liquidity)&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;current&lt;br&gt;200k and rapidly dropping&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;biggest fumble&lt;br&gt;going all in memecoins and holding. genius at ath, giga retard for never taking profit&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;biggest disappointment&lt;br&gt;i have fumbled more bags than you would think is possible. sold ticker bitcoin at 20k mcap(went to 200m?) as just one example&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895117&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894970&lt;br&gt;Same as it was before, i never cashed out, besides like $80k back in 2017 as a test to see if it was all real and possible to cash out here kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895123&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anyone here moved on to trad finance?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895130&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If this entire thread isn&amp;#x27;t a shared larp (doubt), what do you all think of crypto going forward? Was 2023-2025 disappointing enough that you all are going to stay out? Is it unironically over now?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895145&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895130&lt;br&gt;10-20 year bear market imo. btc to &amp;lt;5k all alts to functionally zero.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;it was all a fugazi and we&amp;#x27;ve ran through all possible narratives that can get retards to buy and subsequently be rinsed on. prediction markets and sports betting will be the dominant forms of gambling going forwards. PMs and securities will be the preferred investments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895167&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894267&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Class of 2016 (I was 19)&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Initial: 2K&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Crypto ATH: 70K (sold in 2021)&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Current: 200K (I&amp;#x27;m 28)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I spent the last 5 years working a job and investing in stocks and metals, and ignoring Crypto.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895189&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895167&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Biggest fumble: Not going all in on Nvidia.&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t consider missing out on shitcoin pump and dumps as a fumble.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other biggest fumble: Spending too much time on crypto in the first place, and pissing away my most valuable developmental years staring at charts just to make 70K.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Biggest disappointment&lt;br&gt;I basically wasted the entire 2017 cycle on shitcoins, and vowed to get it right next time round. I was all in for the 2020-21 pump. I stacked sats for years, then when I got my pump I just took it and ran away.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895206&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894267&lt;br&gt;What kind of person gets to $12M and doesnt take $5M off the table to secure their financial future for life?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895213&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895206&lt;br&gt;Someone without financial goals and some shitcoin that mooned&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895214&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895145&lt;br&gt;Holy bottom signal post&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895313&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895130&lt;br&gt;It doesn&amp;#x27;t look good&lt;br&gt;Like the other anon said we&amp;#x27;ve run through pretty much all the alt coin narratives&lt;br&gt;How can we distill it further when we literally had coins with no utility ie meme coins.&lt;br&gt;People think we had no alt season, so the perception of the alt coin lottery comes across as no longer worth it&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Will just be flipping between Bitcoin and stables between cycles now. Alt coin game is too time consuming for the diminishing gains. At least selling tops and buying bottoms of Bitcoin only is comparatively easier.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895206&lt;br&gt;The type to run it up to 12M in the first place&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895320&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895206&lt;br&gt;some retarded NEET who drank the koolaid that his shitcoin was going to change the world (it didn&amp;#x27;t)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895358&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894267&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;class&lt;br&gt;2010&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;initial &lt;br&gt;$0&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;ath&lt;br&gt;Theoretical amount, 860k&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;current&lt;br&gt;$1200&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I spend day after day trying to get whatever I can via stock trading.&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m $1800 in the hole.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895367&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;im just glad i made it out&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895449&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894267&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; class of &lt;br&gt;2013&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; initial&lt;br&gt;5k &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; ATH&lt;br&gt;500k&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; current &lt;br&gt;100k&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;biggest disappointment&lt;br&gt;everything. Sold all my 100 BTC in 2014, went close to 300k on a shitcoin in 2018 than then immediately collapsed, got liquidated in 2022, went to 500k on another coin in 2025 but was locked in a stake for a year and when it was released, it was only worth 5k. I have fucked up again and again and gave up, i am not made for crypto or being wealthy. Could have had 10M+ if I just had kept holding btc.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895501&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here&amp;#x27;s another question, how are your fellow alumni doing? Living on a beach in Bali? Rekt waging and suicidal? Obviously there&amp;#x27;s survival bias here but I haven&amp;#x27;t kept up with anyone from my class.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As for OP&amp;#x27;s question.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;class of&lt;br&gt;2017&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;initial&lt;br&gt;20k&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;ath&lt;br&gt;1.8m&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;current&lt;br&gt;1.1m&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;biggest fumble&lt;br&gt;sold TRX at the literal unironic sat bottom kek, when it went parabolic I wanted to kms and it still stings a little but don&amp;#x27;t think about it much these days&lt;br&gt;also blew up half of my port on perps&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;biggest disappointment&lt;br&gt;The time cost mostly. Waiting a decade for a &amp;quot;measly&amp;quot; 1m which logically speaking isn&amp;#x27;t that bad but I wasted my youth and formative years looking at charts and having nothing to show for it. Any regular wagie has or will surpass me soon on top of having a more fulfilling social life network and career. I was always destined to be a sperg loser so I guess I can&amp;#x27;t be too mad.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895534&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;what causes the next bull run? What is crypto&amp;#x27;s future? &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We are past insitutional adoption, past regulation, past retail adoption (retail was burned hard by scamcoins), what causes the next run up?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m thinking we need to wait until retail forgets its past pain and we get another big stimulus check or something and they gamble it away on crypto. The only problem with this theory is that gambling has basically become legal now with gambling apps and the money might all flow into that instead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895549&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895130&lt;br&gt;No idea. I don&amp;#x27;t own shitcoins anymore outside of dust for the memes so don&amp;#x27;t care what happens to them, but at the bottom of every cycle the doomer narratives become the strongest, it always feels like it&amp;#x27;s genuinely over this time and we endure months/years of no price action, we&amp;#x27;re probably looking for even more pain once the multi-year recession for stocks comes. Recessions in stocks traditionally last 3.3 years (ath to ath, 11 months to bottom). But it&amp;#x27;s exactly that sinking feeling of despair in the pit of your stomach when even seasoned traders have lost all hope that wrecks normies and allows others to make money, why market cycles never stop occurring. But that&amp;#x27;s a tradfi thing so who knows maybe I&amp;#x27;ll baghold and kms in a decade. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The thing that bothers me the most is I am becoming old now (in my 30s) and weathering another market cycle means the prime of my life will already be pretty much over and I&amp;#x27;d have to give up on finding a wife, having kids. I never made enough money to make up for the other shortcomings in my life, and the chickens are finally coming home to roost, as they say. On the bright side I can always wage with financial security which is nice, but the dreams I had when I was young have mostly vanished.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895610&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895549&lt;br&gt;Why dont you just freeze your sperm if you’re worried about that? Being wealthy in your 40s you should have no problem finding a wife in her mid/late 20s&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>I just bought some LINK tokens. — 47 replies — 8.5/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891507</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891507?lm=1771931798</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 11:16:38 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;I just bought some LINK tokens.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891507'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 47 • Updated: 2026-02-24 11:16 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;I just bought some LINK tokens.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891546&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891507&lt;br&gt;ygmi&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891559&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891507&lt;br&gt;retard, it&amp;#x27;s going to $2&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891571&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891559&lt;br&gt;I think I&amp;#x27;m gonna be buying some each month this year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892462&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892441&lt;br&gt;Hello, I am a Linkie, can you help me?&lt;br&gt;Fud me out of my LINK tokens.&lt;br&gt;Like hit me with the hardest hitting fud you got.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892484&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892462&lt;br&gt;you actively funded hundreds of Chainlink conferences in Africa (with your money) while making Sergey a billionaire (by being a loyal baggie)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892507&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892484&lt;br&gt;As a counterpoint, I&amp;#x27;d say that any globohomo adjacent project is obliged to partake in DEI nigger shit.&lt;br&gt;I mean that&amp;#x27;s all tech stocks nowadays too.&lt;br&gt;Or does any mag 7 only hire chuds?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892549&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891559&lt;br&gt;This, it&amp;#x27;s going even lower than it did in 2022&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892576&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892072&lt;br&gt;Bad chart but it at least has a purpose that isn&amp;#x27;t just jewish fee capture. HBAR&amp;#x27;s tokenomics are brutal but it has a future in actual businesses and token use.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892582&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891606&lt;br&gt;How do you feel about the thought of pregnant sergey&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892595&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Link is &amp;gt;$1k, no one will give a fuck if they bought at $8, $10, or $4. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;But it’s not going much lower than this. When clarity passes, Link will moon the hardest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892602&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892595&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;When clarity passes, Link will moon the hardest.&lt;br&gt;Who writes these jokes?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892611&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892582&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m a Muslim man but I have to admit that pregnant Sergey really turns me on. I keep fantasizing about putting my seed inside him and watching new life grow... We get married, he gives birth, and we raise that baby under the blessings of Allah. I want to hold hands with Sergey, and looking into his eyes say &amp;#x27;I love you.&amp;#x27; I think of myself taking our son to his first day at school, watching that strong and masculine boy develop amazing computer skills like his dad.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sergey would be the ideal partner for any man wishing to start a family. His great genes give him a combination of assertiveness, strength, and intelligence. If Sergey is able to get pregnant, he has to have a uterus; if he has a uterus, he can only be a woman in the eyes of Allah. ALLAHU AKHBAR!!!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ok, I can&amp;#x27;t hide this anymore. It&amp;#x27;s coming from deep inside of me... this desire to shout...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;M A GAY MUSLIM AND I HOLD CHAINLINK! Yes, and I am not the only one. I was attracted to this community because of the feeling of brotherhood that it creates. Together we are one. We are above gender divisions and categories. Chainlink, as you know, is a gay sex position where men stick their dicks into each other&amp;#x27;s asses to form a link.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Today, I declare Chainlink to be the currency of the LGBT community.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;M GAY AND I HOLD CHAINLINK. YES! I&amp;#x27;M GAY AND I LOVE SERGEY! WOW! I&amp;#x27;M GAY AND YOU ARE TOO! TOGETHER, WE ARE GAY LINKIES AND NOTHING CAN STOP US!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;M GAY! AND I LOVE TO SAY IT! I&amp;#x27;M GAY, I&amp;#x27;M GAY, I&amp;#x27;M GAY AND I WORSHIP SERGEY! CHAINLINK! CHAINLINK! CHAINLINK!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;NO MORE CHAINS, JUST LINKS!&lt;br&gt;NO MORE CHAINS, JUST LINKS!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893058&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892595&lt;br&gt;here&amp;#x27;s some clarity for you:&lt;br&gt;YOU LOST&lt;br&gt;sell your stinks and pick up the pieces of your worthless life&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893071&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Waiting for $5&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893081&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Waiting for $81k&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893256&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891507&lt;br&gt;You know you&amp;#x27;re going to really upset them by saying that.&lt;br&gt;Based.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893401&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891507&lt;br&gt;Based. I&amp;#x27;m Funneling $6,000 a week for the next six weeks into LINK. And FudNIGGERS can tongue my anus&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894987&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893401&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m doing something like this but monthly instead of weekly&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895092&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893256&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893401&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894987&lt;br&gt;deranged cuckolds who brag about losing their entire networth&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895106&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895092&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;He thinks all my assets are Link.&lt;br&gt;Holy fucking retard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895113&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895092&lt;br&gt;I know I am buying low when I read posts like yours hehe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895114&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891507&lt;br&gt;no way&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895116&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895113&lt;br&gt;cuckolds like you said the same shit in 2022 when it was trading at $8&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895118&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895116&lt;br&gt;I also bought during 2022 and 2023 hehe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895126&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895118&lt;br&gt;I bet you made a ton of money with Chainlink during this bullrun :)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895137&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895126&lt;br&gt;I buy during bear markets and then it goes up yes&lt;br&gt;Now we are in a bear again so I buy again&lt;br&gt;Simple as&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895143&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895137&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;2021&lt;br&gt;$53&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;2026&lt;br&gt;$8&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;okay cuckold&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895153&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895143&lt;br&gt;You can&amp;#x27;t read saar?&lt;br&gt;Was 2021 a bear?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895212&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895153&lt;br&gt;It was a bear for LINK, saar&lt;br&gt;LINK has been in a bear nonstop since August of 2020, saaar&lt;br&gt;you&amp;#x27;ve been bleeding dry for 5 years and six months, saaaars&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895222&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891507&lt;br&gt;do you think you will find someone who will buy those tokens from you ?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895228&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895153&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;t. brown cuckold&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895286&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895222&lt;br&gt;Checked and yes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895300&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891559&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892075&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892549&lt;br&gt;What is it that makes you all so sure?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>How far will BTC crash when MSTR closes its doors and liquidates its holdings? — 8 replies — 7.8/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61895670</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61895670?lm=1771947983</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:46:23 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;How far will BTC crash when MSTR closes its doors and liquidates its holdings?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61895670'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 8 • Updated: 2026-02-24 15:46 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;How far will BTC crash when MSTR closes its doors and liquidates its holdings?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895790&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;there is nothing compelling them to &amp;#x27;liquidate&amp;#x27; their holdings&lt;br&gt;this is just a fantasy of yours and not a real eventuality&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895835&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895790&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;there is nothing compelling them to &amp;#x27;liquidate&amp;#x27; their holdings&lt;br&gt;MSTR shareholders may beg to differ.&lt;br&gt;There is equally nothing compelling them to ride Saylors elevator all the way to zero. And it&amp;#x27;s the shareholders who&amp;#x27;ll force MSTR to liquidate first.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895872&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895835&lt;br&gt;Back in 2020 when mstr started this accumulation, Saylor announced it and offered a buy out with a premium to anyone who didn&amp;#x27;t approve of the strategy. Anyone &amp;quot;who begs to differ&amp;quot; doesn&amp;#x27;t have enough skin in the game to make a case to liquidate. All they can do is sell their own shares. I don&amp;#x27;t own any mstr but I don&amp;#x27;t bet against it either.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895889&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895670&lt;br&gt;Just imagine, this guy will be responsible for the two biggest tech bubbles in history bursting once this is over.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895928&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895670&lt;br&gt;12k, sweep the previous bear market lows and make everyone think its going to 0.&lt;br&gt;makes perfect sense to me for this limp bull market to drop so low to then initiate a stronger bull market like previous bull markets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896044&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895835&lt;br&gt;Youre clueless and you dont know shit about anything.&lt;br&gt;No one can force him to sell even if bitcoin stays at sub 10k for many years.&lt;br&gt;Cope harder no coiner tard&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896093&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61896044&lt;br&gt;No, &amp;#x27;clueless&amp;#x27; is the commodity Saylor is running out of. Rapidly. Shame, he&amp;#x27;ll have to face reality soon, isn&amp;#x27;t it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896115&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895670&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;liquidate&amp;quot; the holdings&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;look inside&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;the bank just takes all of the BTC&lt;br&gt;literally nothing happens&lt;br&gt;this fag barely even moves the market because he buys OTC from other whales anyway&lt;br&gt;complete nothingburger&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>The War with Iran — 6 replies — 5.7/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61895849</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61895849?lm=1771947872</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:44:32 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;The War with Iran&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61895849'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 6 • Updated: 2026-02-24 15:44 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;A geopolitical risk premium is priced-in to all parts of this market right now.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We see a 3 different potential scenarios:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. US makes deal with Iran: Stocks rise, commodities fall&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. US does &amp;quot;one-time&amp;quot; strike with Iran: Brief volatility which ends with stocks rising, commodities falling&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. US enters prolonged war with Iran: Stocks fall, commodities rise&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our positions win in 2 of the 3 scenarios outlined above, which we believe are more likely than #3.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If the US truly is setting up for a long war with Iran, then this would be highly bearish for equities, bullish for crude and gold.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why don&amp;#x27;t we think this is the case?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump wants $2/gallon gas and wants to be the &amp;quot;Peace President.&amp;quot; None of these objectives are obtained in a prolonged war with Iran, particularly with mid-term elections on the horizon.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;That is our current mindset on how we are approaching this market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895853&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I also have a club for those interested in the stock market, where I publish all paid premium content, as shown in the attached photo. I will save you time and hundreds of dollars on subscriptions, which you will get practically for free.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895951&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;bump&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895972&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895853&lt;br&gt;Please feel free to ask any questions you may have ;)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895984&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895849&lt;br&gt;Yea there’s almost no chance Trump invades Iran. It’s less popular than operation Iraqi freedom or Afghanistan. There’s also already a mutiny happening with the troops, the US economy is already in recession and even normies are wising up to Israeli influence over the government. An invasion would completely destabilize the country domestically even worse than the Epstein files&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896103&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895849&lt;br&gt;Totally normal volume spike&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61896104&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61895849&lt;br&gt;I see three possibilities happening in the future&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I win the lottery&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I have to split the lottery&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I do not win the lottery&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;our positions win in 2 of 3 of the scenarios outlined above, which we believe are more likely than #3 (only 33.3333% of the options)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>