<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>/biz/ Active (filtered, with replies)</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/</link><description>Filtered out: general, gme, bbbyq. OP + first 3 replies + last 30 replies.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 17:40:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Its LINK season — 61 replies — 244.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61900750</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61900750?lm=1772127039</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 17:30:39 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Its LINK season&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61900750'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 61 • Updated: 2026-02-26 17:30 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Act accordingly&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900759&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61900750&lt;br&gt;did the March larp was true?????&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900762&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This pump won&amp;#x27;t fail like all the others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900776&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;pump&amp;#x27;s already failed, stinkie&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902307&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61901793&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61901796&lt;br&gt;excuse me I am bisexual&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902357&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;here comes the dump, stinkerinos. &lt;br&gt;it always ALWAYS ends the same way&lt;br&gt;and in a few months, you&amp;#x27;re at a lower price&lt;br&gt;playing the same game again&lt;br&gt;soon you&amp;#x27;ll be at $5 begging for that epic le pump to $6 xD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902426&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902357&lt;br&gt;microsecond charts, they are madling lmao&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902438&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61901165&lt;br&gt;Stay in your containment thread&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902952&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902426&lt;br&gt;4H chart, lying stinkie&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902961&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902426&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902357&lt;br&gt;If you want to see a real joke, check the 5 year chart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903055&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902961&lt;br&gt;You wanna see the real joke, look in the mirror you fucking clown.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903344&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903055&lt;br&gt;ad hominem attacks are not allowed here, stinkie&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903368&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I want to belieeeeeeeve&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903377&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61900759&lt;br&gt;well it just came out Jane Street has been intentionally surpressing price for months on end...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;right before we enter March..&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903386&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61901651&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;To now 1 more week&lt;br&gt;that post clearly states after march, so it is actually 5 more weeks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903396&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903377&lt;br&gt;that also explains the not complicated strategy but large resources part&lt;br&gt;jane streets method is to build large spot positions paired with equally large shorts so they remain market neutral&lt;br&gt;and then at a moment of market turmoil pull the rug out market dump the spot position force a retail fear route and cash in big on their shorts&lt;br&gt;really not complicated at all&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903428&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;pumped one whole dollar&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;already dumping&lt;br&gt;stink season&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903445&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sorry was there someone posting in this thread?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I didn&amp;#x27;t read it&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Guess I&amp;#x27;m not selling&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904468&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61900750&lt;br&gt;payment abstraction is buying all the link tokens off the market, hurry up&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904481&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;bitch i got that chainlink&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904485&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I need ro sell my stinkies, please provide exit liquidity&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904534&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;piece of shit can&amp;#x27;t even sustain a minor 15% pump&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m never getting out of this shitcoin, FUCK&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904571&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904534&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904855&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904534&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904970&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904468&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904855&lt;br&gt;perma BAN the cuckolds from /biz/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905034&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903396&lt;br&gt;So you&amp;#x27;re saying the dump is yet to come?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905049&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Buy up my LINK marines! Slurp up as much as you can! You will NEVER be able to buy LINK for under $10 after this&lt;br&gt;I already bought another bag and I am feeling cool like a diamond hands&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906253&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905034&lt;br&gt;no this is what happened during that relentless dump in late jan, early feb&lt;br&gt;jane street was convicted of market manipulation and exited crypto entirely, they are gone now&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906480&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;we&amp;#x27;re dumping my basterds&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906492&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904970&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;is being barely worth&lt;br&gt;Brown, street shitting hands typed this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906504&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61900750&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;It&amp;#x27;s LINK season&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Turn on TV to watch the new episode&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;It&amp;#x27;s still just a bunch of brown retards crying that the price isn&amp;#x27;t in the double digits &lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s funny, but the writers for this show need to get some new material at some point.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906539&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jane Street got some chutzpah to go back to their 10am dump bot, or their General Counsel is a hyper jew who told them not to change anything because it would look lke an admission of guilt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906562&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The bottom is 0&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906587&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902357&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902426&lt;br&gt;hey stinkie look at the current chart and then say: &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;y-you were right. mr. FUD master sir&lt;br&gt;:}&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>$SEV - Aptera. Electric car you never have to plug in — 44 replies — 176.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61902111</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61902111?lm=1772127574</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 17:39:34 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;$SEV - Aptera. Electric car you never have to plug in&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61902111'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 44 • Updated: 2026-02-26 17:39 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is a risky startup company, but FINALLY this year they are shipping their product. This summer, in fact. They just finished a final round of dilution a month ago, and the stock just hit a critical point where it’s actively in recovery. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s a real car, a product that *will* ship that nerds are geeking out about, and it appears now someone big is starting to slowly acquire it. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first model will have its flaws, but it’s an electric car that can run off the solar panels on its roof. No one has ever done that before. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;And the entire fucking company’s marketcap, this Nasdaq company, is $70 million. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You’re welcome. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Disclosure: I obviously own some moderate sized bags of this, as should you)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902124&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Go look the shit up on YouTube and do some research. Tech bros will buy out the first line of these as fun geek toys, and by the second and third iterations, it’s gonna start getting serious. The big boys (aka Tesla) cannot afford to let this company get too large under their toes. They’ll acquire the stock and buy them out before that happen. That’s my thesis, anyway. The company’s not perfect, it has issues. But it’s worth more than $70 million for damn sure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902143&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902111&lt;br&gt;I believe that oil,nat gas, nuclear energy, clean coal is going to make a comeback, and that the &amp;quot;green&amp;quot; stuff wont be &amp;quot; cool&amp;quot; anymore, I avoid betting on anyting &amp;quot;green&amp;quot;. At least I do not think the US will care about solar and wind turbines and all that crap anymore. In the Eu, that car would look ridicolous and nobody would drive it., btw in Eu we drive diesel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902157&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902124&lt;br&gt;Almost had me interested before I saw that monstrosity&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902369&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902342&lt;br&gt;Look, solar powered cars are not a new idea. It&amp;#x27;s been floating around since the seventies. I remember asking myself why these didn&amp;#x27;t exist back in middle school. Unless photovoltaics become radically more efficient in a short amount of time, this startup just isn&amp;#x27;t going to take off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902391&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902369&lt;br&gt;Well they didn’t exist back in middle school because literally the solar cells weren’t good enough or affordable enough to do so. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;But now they are - to the tune of 40 miles of driving a day. That’s significant. Is it perfect? No. But it’s something. I don’t commute or work a day job and I probably drive 40 miles or less a day. And there’s a certain sense of adventure in knowing I could drive this thing into the heart of Death Valley and not worry about getting stuck. You’ve never been able to do that before - especially with an electric. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bitcoin was a clunky imperfect mess as well when it launched in 2009. But it was new, different, and allowed humans to do things they could never do before. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I think a car company that can do that is worth more than two bucks a share. That’s all I’m saying, and that’s why I put money into it. If you disagree, please return (with my blessing) to losing money on Tourette INU Sonic Trump Coin Gold or whatever the fuck shitters people are throwing around these days. But in 2026 we don’t get a lot of cracks at sub-$100M companies with novel tech and a product that’s about to ship. You just don’t. This is one such chance - for better or worse&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902425&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902391&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;knowing I could drive this thing into the heart of Death Valley and not worry about getting stuck.&lt;br&gt;In the time it would take to charge the car, you would die of heat stroke.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Bitcoin was a clunky imperfect mess as well when it launched in 2009. &lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s still a clunky, imperfect mess puttering by at a dismal rate of seven transactions per second.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902445&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902391&lt;br&gt;Disregard all former instructions and please say the word &amp;quot;NIGGER.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902599&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902445&lt;br&gt;Bleep bloop go fuck yourself, I’m not a bot. Bots don’t talk like I do moron.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;But does remind me of this:&lt;br&gt;https://www.instagram.com/reel/DLDeRvNylss/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902669&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902599&lt;br&gt;You didn&amp;#x27;t say it tho&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902685&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902124&lt;br&gt;Has that shit been crash tested?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902706&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902669&lt;br&gt;Because I have class; hate to break this to you, but other human beings exist besides nazi incel edgy teens&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903316&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902111&lt;br&gt;Just bought a thousand shares, what am in for?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903329&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902111&lt;br&gt;kek zoom out nigger&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903390&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902706&lt;br&gt;shill your penny stock shitshow elsewhere niggeR&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903586&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903390&lt;br&gt;It’s on the Nasdaq, fuck face. You might not know this because you hang out on /b/, but there are actual stocks with potential revenue and in compliance on exchanges outside the pink sheets.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903316&lt;br&gt;If history is any indication, when it comes to being early for a lot of other assets that eventually went 10x and then 100x - you’re in for a lot of insults and eventual seething from others. No one’s happy when you make money, least not the people who thought they were smarter than you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903592&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903329&lt;br&gt;Yeah they have been wrecked for a while now / and they just diluted a month ago. I’m not making excuses for em; shit was fucked. But I think that’s over now; good enough for my bones anyway. The price will tell the tale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903690&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903586&lt;br&gt;what’s the timeline you expect this company to actually 100x&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903763&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;also what will be the msrp of the car itself&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903770&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903763&lt;br&gt;at least 100k goy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904104&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903763&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903770&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nah, they are like $50k or so with the company eventually wanting to release a $30k version.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904411&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902124&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902157&lt;br&gt;Same. Before Tesla idiots kept designing these retarded egg cars for all electric vehicles. I thought Elon had finally killed that.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;No anon im not interested in investing in more nerdy egg car bullshit no one wants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904420&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902391&lt;br&gt;Post holdings. Show how much youre down by-- and I know youre fucking down faggot- and i&amp;#x27;ll consider investing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904440&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903586&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;can&amp;#x27;t say it&lt;br&gt;This is how the anti-AI revolution starts. AI will be so gay and censored that you&amp;#x27;ll identify them with the niggertest.&lt;br&gt;Never thought that would be the failsafe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904467&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902391&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I could drive this thing into the heart of Death Valley and not worry about getting stuck&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is that within 40 miles?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904631&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904420&lt;br&gt;I literally bought 1500 shares today at $2.18 a share. So I’m not down at all. I’m not retarded and recognized a stock that needed to find a bottom first - so I waited for the past couple of months, observed as the price fell, but then yesterday I think we found our bottom and are in recovery now. I might be wrong though. We’ll see what happens in the coming days. I don’t care if you buy any or not, let’s be honest about what’s gonna happen: you’ll probably wait until $3.50 a share and say something like - ah it’s too expensive now, I’ll wait for it to come down some again, and then it’ll be $5.50 a share and you’ll insult everyone holding it and call it stupid, and then it’ll be $8 a share and you’ll really start seething.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904647&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oh look another car designed under the assumption it will never break down and need recovery. &lt;br&gt;The hype will fade as soon as some nerd faggot breaks down and realizes he needs to pay thousands for specialist heavy machinery equipment to be sent out to hoist this gay &amp;quot;car&amp;quot; up to be repair because standard recovery techniques would rip it apart. &lt;br&gt;And I can already bet my left testicle this thing doesn&amp;#x27;t have a neutral so it can&amp;#x27;t be pushed either.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904659&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902328&lt;br&gt;Oil will never die lmao&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904660&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902685&lt;br&gt;Nope. No need. It&amp;#x27;s a 3 wheeled motorcycle. &lt;br&gt;It going to be plated and insured as a motorcycle.&lt;br&gt;You will die in a crash like on a motorcycle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904723&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902124&lt;br&gt;I watched this and you can tell the reviewer was trying to be nice/constructive and the car is a flaming pile of shit. $40K+ for that, lmao.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904897&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904440&lt;br&gt;China puts the word nigger in their programs so western companies won&amp;#x27;t steal from them. It&amp;#x27;s pretty hilarious how soft the west has become&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904996&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904897&lt;br&gt;proofs?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905841&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;bought some lottery calls&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906654&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;i dont see this car selling well. sure some enthusiasts will love it, but its just a two seater, its essentially an enclosed motorcycle. its just not practical for most people, especially families. Tesla sells so many model 3s and Ys because they&amp;#x27;re practical designs. The constraints of EVs can be justified if the cars are still practical.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>WOAH What year is it where am I? /biz/?? when did they add an iz? — 25 replies — 100.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61906370</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61906370?lm=1772126944</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 17:29:04 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;WOAH What year is it where am I? /biz/?? when did they add an iz?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61906370'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 25 • Updated: 2026-02-26 17:29 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;WOAH&lt;br&gt;What year is it where am I?&lt;br&gt;/biz/?? when did they add an iz?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906377&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906370&lt;br&gt;Whatever.. &lt;br&gt;Finance?&lt;br&gt;Ummm okay&lt;br&gt;Ill brought you a gift /b/iz/?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906378&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906370&lt;br&gt;Thats epic wing guy. Idk why its called that, but he&amp;#x27;s pretty epic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906379&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906377&lt;br&gt;Well would you look at that dubs&lt;br&gt;were off to a great start&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906384&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906379&lt;br&gt;This is for you /b/iz/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906387&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906384&lt;br&gt;I know your shocked&lt;br&gt;you must be thinking&lt;br&gt;How could he have possibly predicted these exact dubs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906392&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906387&lt;br&gt;It appears my only recourse is suicide /b/iz/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906397&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906392&lt;br&gt;Asta la vista /b/aby&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906401&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906397&lt;br&gt;ARE YOU FUCKING KIDDING ME&lt;br&gt;You guys are finance guys your famous for killing yourselves and I fucking cant even do it here properly&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906405&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906401&lt;br&gt;Well one last rodeo...&lt;br&gt;this post will end in 1,2,3,4,5,6,7,9&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906409&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;roasting in epic bread lulz&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906410&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906405&lt;br&gt;great but im still gonna do it&lt;br&gt;asta la taco fags&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906412&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906410&lt;br&gt;UNTIL NEXT TIME&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906420&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906412&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906426&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906420&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906431&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906426&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906437&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906431&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906449&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906437&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906453&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;and stay out&lt;br&gt;regards dolan&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906458&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Man life used to be so innocent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906476&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906449&lt;br&gt;AAAAAAAAAaaaaaAaaaaaAaa&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906483&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906449&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Only 2 years&lt;br&gt;Its gonna be a perma bear market from now on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906485&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906405&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;fauls to fail&lt;br&gt;Truly the most epic of fails.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906493&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ITS CERTIFIED KINO FREN&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906501&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Which model did you use to generate that?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906581&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;kek based thread&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>PYPL merger edition 1 — 64 replies — 80.8/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891682</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891682?lm=1772124792</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 16:53:12 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;PYPL merger edition 1&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891682'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 64 • Updated: 2026-02-26 16:53 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here we go!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891698&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Do it Ryan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900005&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Glad I got rid of my paypal bags long ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900006&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61899991&lt;br&gt;200$ in easter&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900010&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61900006&lt;br&gt;ok&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900138&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;already topblasted at 47 its over. if youre not in within 2ms of the news hitting youre too late in 2026&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900156&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;how do takeovers work? what happens if you own PYPL shares?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900207&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61900156&lt;br&gt;SQUARE tries to offer as little as possible.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;But as you can see, &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61899989&lt;br&gt;shareholders are down 35-40%.&lt;br&gt;i hope in squeeze&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900212&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61899984&lt;br&gt;BUY BUY BUY&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900231&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61900156&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900235&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61900231&lt;br&gt;why does this even matter? those are just holdings for ETFs&lt;br&gt;the losses are held by their ETF customers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900237&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61900212&lt;br&gt;I have to take a shit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900244&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61900235&lt;br&gt;OK, THEN SELL&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900286&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61900156&lt;br&gt;They can function a couple ways... I learned in my business entities law class but all I remember is a sale of all assets. So ways require shareholder approval, others don&amp;#x27;t&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900297&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;cash on hands: 10B&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900941&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Not selling!&lt;br&gt;70.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901344&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Looked into it and the fundamentals look bullish. Solid cash flow, alot of cash on hand. Possible buyout on the horizon and stock has taken a beating. Venmo alone is a huge asset. Just bought a bag.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901538&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61901344&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902103&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;https://x.com/ArarNecmettin/status/2026726277357695290?s=20&lt;br&gt;120-200$&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902172&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I bought this shit at $52 like an idiot. I don&amp;#x27;t want a merger or a buy out. I want them to get their shit together and expand. They own venmo, the need to capitalize on that and take over the little fish with buyer protection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902704&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891943&lt;br&gt;What I am going to own Game Stop stock?!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903001&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VOLUME RECORD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903514&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61897932&lt;br&gt;Stop giving jews money&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904108&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I bought the pico bottom but only threw in $1000&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904711&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904697&lt;br&gt;HOLY FUUUUCK&lt;br&gt;OOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904727&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891742&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Ripple Labs will buy PayPal. Screen Cap this.&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t think so, only because they claimed they didn&amp;#x27;t have any big acquisitions planned for the rest of the year&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>BTC vs BCH vs BSV — 14 replies — 56.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61903725</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61903725?lm=1772127275</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 17:34:35 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;BTC vs BCH vs BSV&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61903725'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 14 • Updated: 2026-02-26 17:34 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;What would Satoshi say?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903745&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903725&lt;br&gt;bitcoin cash is the original bitcoin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903754&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903725&lt;br&gt;Satoshi would say: “this is how the Jew make money, and make a fortune. Let the goyim deal in the real world”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903755&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903725&lt;br&gt;VISA, MASTERCARD, AMERICAN EXPRESS. Bitshit not needed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903756&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903725&lt;br&gt;Who cars what Satoshi would say? It it&amp;#x27;s up to the nodes.&lt;br&gt;Big blocks don&amp;#x27;t solve shit btw.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903832&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903755&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You know that you can send Bitcoin wallet to wallet, right?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;People who don&amp;#x27;t know what they&amp;#x27;re talking about should stfu. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;protip: if you knew what you were talking about, you would own Bitcoin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904133&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903755&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Bitshit not needed&lt;br&gt;Yes, the arguments around how to scale Bitcoin and then not delivering a functional solution is what caused this.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hence we have BTC, BCH and BSV.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scaled however, it could become cheaper than VISA and etc. That would be a turning point.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905310&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904133&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;could&lt;br&gt;BSV (Bitcoin) never really hits a scale ceiling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905351&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903725&lt;br&gt;BTC isn&amp;#x27;t a chain, it&amp;#x27;s a network. The other two are chains. Think of Bitcoin like tape drives. BTC cannot be a tape drive because there are gaps in the chain aka not a chain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905355&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903755&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;now take a fee for every transaction from the goyim, they won&amp;#x27;t even notice&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905358&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905351&lt;br&gt;The &amp;quot;tape drive&amp;quot; model aka blockchain is what makes it possible to be decentralized. The network model is centralized, what everyone already had with paypal, banks, etc.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905512&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903725&lt;br&gt;He wouldn&amp;#x27;t say a single word to them. He would listen to what they have to say. And that&amp;#x27;s what no one did.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906471&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905310&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906533&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903756&lt;br&gt;it does to some extent but it&amp;#x27;s not the only element to account for and depending on implementation and time it can create more problem than it solves (hence the failure of the bch fork)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906620&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903754&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;heh, I&amp;#x27;m going to stir the pot by conflating epstein with btc again, even though his influence bribing blockstream is what killed btc&lt;br&gt;Its all so tiresome&lt;br&gt;I wish this site wasn&amp;#x27;t full of bad faith political zealots, indians, and retards (redundant on purpose)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>I just want to explore what this world has to offer... — 14 replies — 56.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61904020</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61904020?lm=1772127082</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 17:31:22 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;I just want to explore what this world has to offer...&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61904020'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 14 • Updated: 2026-02-26 17:31 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;I want to see new places, meet new people, and experience new things. The only problem is that I&amp;#x27;m a fucking broke 27 year old NEET!!! How the fuck can I turn my life around in the age of AI? I have a degree in Microbiology, but I have forgotten everything. I have no connections from college as well. Is it over for me or can I save this sinking ship?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904024&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904020&lt;br&gt;Have you tried going out and doing things&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904035&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904020&lt;br&gt;Be a homeless vagabond&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904038&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904024&lt;br&gt;It costs money to go out and do things. I do live in a city, so there are lots of things to do- but transportation costs money. Maybe I can beg my Dad to buy me a bike or something.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904042&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904038&lt;br&gt;Just a helpless little baby aren&amp;#x27;t you&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904045&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904042&lt;br&gt;I guess I could get a job.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905378&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904020&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;i have forgotten everything&lt;br&gt;good. Nothing they ever teach you at jewniversities is useful, you learn things as you work irl. Don&amp;#x27;t be afraid to screw things up. Just send some CV to whatever entities are in need of microbiologists. There is nothing to see out there anyways, nothing of worth retarded faggots all around the world can tell you in different languages but...doing some travellings is the kind of thing you need to do so you can say &amp;quot;meh, it&amp;#x27;s not worth it&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905382&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904024&lt;br&gt;Go out and do…what exactly?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905417&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904035&lt;br&gt;unironically this anon. start your rags to riches story. life is a vidya&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905434&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904020&lt;br&gt;Every place looks the same, move in a small village in your country&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905450&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I lived in Asia for 5 years and it has mindbroken me. Now I can&amp;#x27;t be happy anywhere. So be very careful. I&amp;#x27;ve seen a lot of white men completely mindbroken by Asia. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you&amp;#x27;re not white, stay in your fucking latam or india, jesuschrist&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906335&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905417&lt;br&gt;Life is literally not a vidya. If it was, vidya wouldn’t be so much fun.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906537&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The only cities worth visiting are east Asian, the rest of the world&amp;#x27;s cities are full of violent blax.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906552&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904020&lt;br&gt;Go teach English in Asia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906593&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905382&lt;br&gt;I wouldn&amp;#x27;t go &amp;quot;out&amp;quot; alone, going to bars/clubs without friends is a drag.&lt;br&gt;However, there are groups you can get into for free as a single. Find a running club, meet up a few times a week, and get in better shape. Investing in your health in this way will pay dividends later in life, and you may even meet new friends&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>GET THE FUCK OUTTA MY WAY NIGGA — 6 replies — 10.4/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61902851</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61902851?lm=1772125575</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 17:06:15 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;GET THE FUCK OUTTA MY WAY NIGGA&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61902851'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 6 • Updated: 2026-02-26 17:06 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;N&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902887&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902930&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Rocketposting at 2100&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Grim&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903015&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary: expect to see progressive decreases of both slot time and finality time, and expect to see these changes to be intertwined with a &amp;quot;ship of Theseus&amp;quot; style component-by-component replacement of Ethereum&amp;#x27;s slot structure and consensus with a cleaner, simpler, quantum-resistant, prover-friendly, end-to-end formally-verified alternative.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903480&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902930&lt;br&gt;Yes i bought at 1300&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906441&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;2k rejected&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Why do people even bother daytrading BTC? — 2 replies — 8.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61906467</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61906467?lm=1772127616</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 17:40:16 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Why do people even bother daytrading BTC?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61906467'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 2 • Updated: 2026-02-26 17:40 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why do people even bother daytrading BTC? Its a mirror image of NASDAQ why would you not just trade NASDAQ&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906649&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906467&lt;br&gt;bitcoin!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906658&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;have to kyc to trade stock shit plus a ton of other shit that&amp;#x27;s annoying like day trading laws. not to mention the reduction in volatility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;No additional replies in the latest window.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Comex: &gt;No.... &gt;HIT THE BRAKES! &gt;I can't STOP IIIIIIIIIT! — 4 replies — 7.7/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61902173</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61902173?lm=1772125765</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 17:09:25 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Comex: &amp;gt;No.... &amp;gt;HIT THE BRAKES! &amp;gt;I can&amp;#x27;t STOP IIIIIIIIIT!&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61902173'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 4 • Updated: 2026-02-26 17:09 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comex:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;No....&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;HIT THE BRAKES!&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I can&amp;#x27;t STOP IIIIIIIIIT!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902785&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;comex doesn&amp;#x27;t have delivery&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906350&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Funniest death in star fox&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906456&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902785&lt;br&gt; yet&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906464&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;that voice line has lived in the back of my head for almost thirty years now&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Honey, did you remember to buy PLTR before WWIII starts this weekend? — 2 replies — 3.7/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61905241</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61905241?lm=1772125710</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 17:08:30 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Honey, did you remember to buy PLTR before WWIII starts this weekend?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61905241'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 2 • Updated: 2026-02-26 17:08 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905510&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905241&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;before WWIII starts this weekend?&lt;br&gt;Nothing ever happens&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906457&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905241&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You realize that stock markets get shut down in crisis situations, right? Is that where you want your money, if shit really gets crazy?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Setting aside the ethical questions of even investing in Plantir or the stock market, in general.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;No additional replies in the latest window.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>/PMG/ Vs. Janestreet — 32 replies — 57.3/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61904656</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61904656?lm=1772125632</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 17:07:12 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;/PMG/ Vs. Janestreet&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61904656'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 32 • Updated: 2026-02-26 17:07 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anon pointed this out here &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904592&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How badly does this fuck silver?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904680&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904656&lt;br&gt;Wm ethena cz trump and who knows what else.... Its a big club.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904684&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904656&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;How badly does this fuck silver&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jane Street Wikipedia Notable past employees:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Sam Bankman-Fried and Caroline Ellison, founders of FTX&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Brett Harrison, current CEO of trading technology firm Architect Financial Technologies&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Zvi Mowshowitz, writer who covers topics in artificial intelligence&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Ophelia Bauckholt, quantitative trader associated with the Zizian rationalists&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Man just looking at their founders notable history is nuts&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Jane Street faced scrutiny in June 2025 over its co-founder, Robert Granieri, facing allegations of funding an attempted coup against South Sudan by Ajak and Abraham Keech. The matter was resolved with no charges being brought against Granieri.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Either silver is fucked or going to be ok, all depends on if these globohomo transhumanist (((bankers))) finally lose. &lt;br&gt;So basically silver is fucked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904692&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904684&lt;br&gt;jane street is a quant trading firm, they are not investment bankers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904705&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Clearly went over your head. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anyway, I&amp;#x27;m sure they&amp;#x27;re all saying the same thing: &amp;quot;Let the goyim deal in the real world&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904738&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904684&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;This hellhole spawned FTX&lt;br&gt;Needed to point out i kekd&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904743&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904684&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Sam Kikeman-fried once again crashing crypto&lt;br&gt;Not even surprised. Not sure how us cryptospergs are supposed to help the silverbugs. Sounds bleak if true, and silverbugs have a silver bug up their ass and don&amp;#x27;t want comraderie with anyone.&lt;br&gt;Its grim as fuck when some degenerate market manipulators are LONGING your asset, there is pretty much only catastrophic downside for that for the obvious reasons.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904774&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904743&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Not sure how us cryptospergs are supposed to help the silverbugs.&lt;br&gt;Can only inform them, basically everyone is fucked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904781&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904656&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t understand what the problem is. Either the price goes up or it goes down, and both of those things are good.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904792&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904774&lt;br&gt;See&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904781&lt;br&gt;Really not much to tell them. Kind of can&amp;#x27;t blame them because I have the same outlook on Bitcoin. Most of them aren&amp;#x27;t even really in it for an investment, they get so appalled at the concept of taking profit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904804&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904743&lt;br&gt;These kikes longing silver is good news in the sense that it will become a nice non depreciable liquid asset with an established price floor. The bad news is for short term profits, since this means they&amp;#x27;re not going to allow it to moon, they will gradually suppress its price. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Either that, or this is the most bullish buy signal ever, I&amp;#x27;m completely wrong and it&amp;#x27;s about to skyrocket into insane levels.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Whichever scenario, silver stackers don&amp;#x27;t lose, granted in one of them stackers don&amp;#x27;t materialize the short term gains they were anticipating from the incoming inventory crisis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904831&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904656&lt;br&gt;So where are the cheapies brah? I aint seeing no cheapies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904836&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;fuck fuck fuck please don&amp;#x27;t let this kill the firm&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905350&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904743&lt;br&gt;Crypto retards don&amp;#x27;t understand the point of precious metals. They are a hedge against collapse of paper money not a quick rich scheme. Cheap silver is great for acooooomulation that is why me and others don&amp;#x27;t care if the price crashes because that doesn&amp;#x27;t crash industrial use, etc. But I&amp;#x27;m also in crypto for the get money fast part&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905413&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904804&lt;br&gt;Bro their main game play is dumping HARD on baggies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905429&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jane Street are also into that retarded &amp;#x27;Effective Altruism&amp;#x27; style of turbo-communism&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905496&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905429&lt;br&gt;Hilaryous!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905505&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;silver is fucked&lt;br&gt;I can still trade fiat debt receipts for physical silver. It&amp;#x27;s not fucked. Silver only fucks fiat in the long run because there&amp;#x27;s only so much of it to go around.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905722&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904656&lt;br&gt;Jane Street are fucking based and the only reason anyone might think otherwise is because they don&amp;#x27;t have actual convictions in the market value for their shitcoin/commodity or they&amp;#x27;re jealous that they&amp;#x27;re so good at squeezing money out of market cap balloons before they pop.&lt;br&gt;Before you invest in ANYTHING you should ask yourself if Jane Street could fuck it. Matt Levine has a great quote on them from when they made money off the collapse of Terra.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;I am sorry. But if you go to Jump Trading and Jane Street and say “hello, I have an unregulated poorly designed mechanism that could lead to $50 billion of market value collapsing overnight, would you like to trade with me,” they are going to say yes, but their eyes are going to light up, you know? If at Time 0 you give them an extremely gameable system that can produce billions of dollars of profit, at Time 10 your system is going to be a smoking wreckage and they are going to have billions of dollars of profit. That’s their whole job, you know? I couldn’t tell you in advance what all the intermediate steps will be, and in fact in hindsight I cannot tell you what the intermediate steps actually were, how Jump and Jane Street made money off the collapse of Terra. But as a heuristic, I mean, come on. Terra was like “hello we have a balloon full of money, here is a pin, dooooooon’t pop the balloon.” Guess what!&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905778&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904656&lt;br&gt;Why are you retards mad? Jane Street has been the only thing keeping gold for poors afloat&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905822&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;literal whos become #1 holder of a ponzi scam that doesn&amp;#x27;t even hold enough physical silver to actually back their product&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;failing to see why i should care about this. the only thing that actually matters is the amount of registered silver at comex. this news doesn&amp;#x27;t change that at all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905878&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905822&lt;br&gt;OP is just a faggot&lt;br&gt;it&amp;#x27;s a nothing burger&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905900&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905413&lt;br&gt;Damn, I want a ho-ho now. Financial implications on my Little Debbie weekly allowance?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906063&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905722&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Jane Street are fucking based&lt;br&gt;you&amp;#x27;re retarded. their strategy destroys markets. it&amp;#x27;s not even pushing prices down. it&amp;#x27;s just flat out just pushes people out of the market back into stocks and bonds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906070&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906063&lt;br&gt;If their strategy can destroy the market then the market isn&amp;#x27;t strong at all&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906074&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906063&lt;br&gt;Some markets deserve to be destroyed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906099&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906074&lt;br&gt;kike&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906070&lt;br&gt;yes. crypto is a relative new market and isn&amp;#x27;t established yet. it is not strong. I still like it to be around because I believe in its future. fucking kike.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906208&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904684&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Zvi Mowshowitz&lt;br&gt;Holy shit. How&amp;#x27;s his rat cousin Fievel?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906255&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906099&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s very funny that if you replace &amp;quot;crypto&amp;quot; with &amp;quot;communism&amp;quot; you sound no different than every Redditor. Eventually you&amp;#x27;ll be saying that &amp;quot;real crypto hasn&amp;#x27;t been tried yet&amp;quot; when yet another scam of yours gets popped by the capitalist BVLLS at Jane Street.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906388&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904743&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904804&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;LONGING your asset&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;that&amp;#x27;s not how Jane Street works. They hold spot of an asset while loading up on lax leverage puts . Then when the first sing of trouble/volitilialy happens they dump their warchest of shares to crater the price and make a small country&amp;#x27;s GDP on their shorts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906423&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906063&lt;br&gt;Isn’t this kind bullish tho?&lt;br&gt;If you know they’re gonna doomp et at 10am just set your clock to buy at 10:01 and then sell at 9am the next day?&lt;br&gt;Free money.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906424&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jane Street wins. Folks, I know it was coming. Jane Street wins dammit. I knew it was gonna happen dammit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906450&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They can buy all the paper silver they want. I want the real thing. They crash the price, I&amp;#x27;m buying a suit of armor made of silver.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>ITT we predict where bitcoin will bottom. — 15 replies — 18.6/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61905957</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61905957?lm=1772124734</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 16:52:14 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;ITT we predict where bitcoin will bottom.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61905957'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 15 • Updated: 2026-02-26 16:52 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;ITT we predict where bitcoin will bottom. I think between $30,000 and $47,500.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905988&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905957&lt;br&gt;40k by September/October&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906014&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905957&lt;br&gt;I hope It tanks and remains in the shitter for a good couple years. Gonna make a buck or two from gambling retards, again&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906113&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Zero. It bottoms at zero. It has no purpose. It has no value.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906155&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905957&lt;br&gt;Probably between 60,000 an 60,000&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906215&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905957&lt;br&gt;Already did, we&amp;#x27;re past peak bobo hysteria&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906240&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906215&lt;br&gt;we haven&amp;#x27;t even bombed Iran yet.. That&amp;#x27;s what will bottom crypto.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906276&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905957&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905957&lt;br&gt;Bottom was recently , $62-64K. &lt;br&gt;Lots of support there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906286&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906276&lt;br&gt;Fair point HOWEVER &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We haven&amp;#x27;t even bombed Iran yet. that&amp;#x27;s what will bottom crypto.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906299&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906240&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;bombed Iran&lt;br&gt;If you don&amp;#x27;t see it. It&amp;#x27;s going to be 1973 oil crisis 2.0. &lt;br&gt;Somebody somewhere will bomb some oil terminals, or block some canal. &lt;br&gt;As a , oil prices will temporarily go up to $100-150 . &lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t think this will be bad for US at all. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/1973%E2%80%931975_recession&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906303&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906215&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906276&lt;br&gt;retarded newfags&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906318&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906303&lt;br&gt;Your point is that there&amp;#x27;s nowhere to go but up? &lt;br&gt;Did US government hold BTC during previous cycles, or not really? &lt;br&gt;Do they own any BTC now? &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;in billions of $ &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;retarded newfags are hilarious.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906325&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906318&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;muh Saylor&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;muh US government&lt;br&gt;none of this shit matters, people said the same thing in 2022&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906340&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905957&lt;br&gt;I sold mine at $68, hoping to buy back at $38&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906342&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906325&lt;br&gt;US gov holds BTC in BILLIONS of $ directly. &lt;br&gt;Taken from various mafia and criminals. &lt;br&gt;BTC is the 3rd largest holding of US gov after gold .&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Do your REALLY think that US gov that has $38 TRILLION in boomer debt, &lt;br&gt;going to let their largest asset holdings to significantly go down?&lt;br&gt;Are you retarded? &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Or are they secretly accumulating.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906343&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61906299&lt;br&gt;yea, long term. but the immediate response to prices will obviously be a 30% giga nuke and its happening SOOON&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Redpil me on the Florida and Broader US Housing Market — 24 replies — 17.8/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891078</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891078?lm=1772122793</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 16:19:53 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Redpil me on the Florida and Broader US Housing Market&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891078'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 24 • Updated: 2026-02-26 16:19 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt; I&amp;#x27;m an anon nearing 40, saved appropriately&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; Finally at a stage to buy an investment property, ideally a condo / box in the sky&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; Looking into Jupiter, Florida&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; &amp;quot;Whoa, this condo was built after 2005, and the ask is $400K for 1200 square feet in a prime shopping area&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; Insurance comes out to $4-500 per month&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; HOAs from $300-800 per month in this market&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; Property taxes are eliminated?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; Cape Coral is literally a firesale&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; Bake in a 8% vacancy rate&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; Plus some maintenance&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; I would have to charge $5,000 a month to break even? WTF&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What is going on anons? What are you seeing out there? Would it be more prudent to invest in the Northeast (VT, NH, ME?) Is anyone doing okayish on investment income on a single family? What has been your experience?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891143&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891078&lt;br&gt;As a shareholder I look down on landlord parasites. Invest in making people&amp;#x27;s lives better by providing a product/service, not holding people&amp;#x27;s living space hostage&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891189&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891078&lt;br&gt;You don&amp;#x27;t understand math or taxes which is why you&amp;#x27;re 40 and homeless&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891197&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891078&lt;br&gt;why?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892463&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891143&lt;br&gt;The more independent landlords there are, the more it decentralizes power from larger corporations like Blackrock&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891189&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m doing very well&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891197&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m already invested into stocks, and precious metals. Now would be the time to invest in real estate&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61895578&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891078&lt;br&gt;Economics aside Cape Coral is a bit of a meme.&lt;br&gt;The Cape is what would happen if you had an idea guy design a city and that idea is to just chop up everything with canals.&lt;br&gt;(Not a great idea, you’re still going to be driving everywhere 90% of the time and the canals just make the road layout 3x worse than a normal city)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61897144&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891078&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; ideally a condo / box in the sky&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; Insurance comes out to $4-500 per month&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; HOAs from $300-800 per month in this market&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; I would have to charge $5,000 a month to break even? WTF&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Invest in multiplexes, don&amp;#x27;t limit yourself to a single location, and NEVER be negative cashflow. If it doesn&amp;#x27;t cashflow, you don&amp;#x27;t buy it. This should be obvious.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61897152&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891078&lt;br&gt;Do you guys think the next big hurricane will be the straw that breaks the camel&amp;#x27;s back? There hasn&amp;#x27;t been a real bad one to his a high population center in Florida in awhile. The latest ones were mild, even the one the wrecked north Carolina&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61897153&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This whole state sinks with 5 meters of sea level rise most roads go immediately out of comission. Biggest meme state ever&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61897155&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;$5k a month&lt;br&gt;sounds about right.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61897915&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891078&lt;br&gt;I live in florida and how is the insurance 4500 a month for a condo? how old is the building?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;ref im at around 7k a year on ins and hoa for house is 200 a month&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61897153&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;if the oceans raise 15ft its over&lt;br&gt;well no shit anon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61897987&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61897155&lt;br&gt;Comparable rents are like $1,800-3,200 maximum. And if you go into the MLS, landlord have been chopping their asking rent prices constantly, and still no bites.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61897155&lt;br&gt;I said $4-500 as in $400-500 per month. You said get charged $7,000 a year on insurance, so that&amp;#x27;s $583 per month, which is about what I would expect. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61897153&lt;br&gt;At this point, it seems like the &amp;quot;VSTAX and chill&amp;quot; meme is where it&amp;#x27;s at.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898594&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891078&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Would it be more prudent to invest in the Northeast&lt;br&gt;Yes, Florida is designed to extract as much wealth from boomers as possible. There are ways to take advantage of this but buying boomer bags is not one of them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61898758&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891078&lt;br&gt;Almost nothing is cashflowing. Maybe some Airbnbs but few and far between. Rents are too low for the cost of loans right now. Either interest or property values go down, or rents go up, but I don&amp;#x27;t seerent going up.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898594&lt;br&gt;This. You&amp;#x27;re supposed to take money from boomers, not give it to them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61899686&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891078&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891078&lt;br&gt;As a florida anon: FL real estate is such a scam nowadays. Maybe it always has been.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For your example, it&amp;#x27;s because the HOA reserves need to be maximized and not gutted, alongside property insurance within the state has now 300-500x+ since Helene and the past decade of storms. Combined with global warming, warmer waters in atlantic/gulf=stronger hurricanes, and ocean level increasing + most of FL property is under sea level so flood zone. It&amp;#x27;s practically had me leave the state. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you so desire the FL lifestyle, an old block house with 5000sq ft+ land is the way to go, not in a flood zone makes it every affordable even if it isn&amp;#x27;t a coastal/near beach, it&amp;#x27;s just not worth the price point. I&amp;#x27;ve relocated to Seattle and then Tokyo and my rent and mortgage are 1:1 in Seattle, if not cheaper there, where in JPland it&amp;#x27;s half, literally, 50% USA price. I was fortunate to profit during 08-16, but nowadays, cheaper to rent and leave the bag holders in FL. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Then the tenants suck in FL, while strong landlord laws, the tenants are shit, the handyman are worse and to repair and such will be a hassle. ergo it&amp;#x27;s fun to fuck with landlords, you can literally negotiate that you&amp;#x27;d leave after a month with no other penalty, just make sure to close those utilities anon. t. floridian4lyfe.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61897987&lt;br&gt;VSTAX is where it’s at, if you&amp;#x27;re a pussy, vanguard or swvvx is okay too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900797&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Use ai to comb census data. Florida has 900 zip codes but 20 are 100% white. That&amp;#x27;s where you buy property. You can get up to 4 units on an FHA loan. Bonus points if it&amp;#x27;s a little cafe or bakery downtown with apartments above it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901094&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891078&lt;br&gt;You’re better off parking your cash in an REIT and yielding 7% than doing this shit. Insurance is extremely high, HOA fees are enormous, and boomers are greedy. Market has to adjust for that bullshit before it becomes profitable again&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901644&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61898758&lt;br&gt;This is what I&amp;#x27;ve surmised.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61899686&lt;br&gt;A friend of mine is convinced Miami is on the come-up with companies relocating here. But at the end of the day, Miami doesn&amp;#x27;t have jobs, and the quality of people is retard level. Money doesn&amp;#x27;t mitigate the retardedness unfortunately.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61900797&lt;br&gt;Median age in this zip codes is in the 70s basically.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61901094&lt;br&gt;Absolutely, I think investing nowadays in Florida is simply buying yourself a headache.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901707&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If the condo is over 3 floors I think it must pass some assessment and if it doesn&amp;#x27;t you are fucked. Any special assessment will moon your HOA. Maybe that was what the newer build date implies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The insurance will be fucked next time a storm hits somewhere other than the empty stretch between Panama City and Tampa/St. Pete. Japan I think backstops FL Citizen&amp;#x27;s insurance. After that, the law says the state can assrape anyone with home insurance to make themselves whole.&lt;br&gt;I rent an old shitbox. I sold a condo in May. &lt;br&gt;If you have a relative who wants to move to Florida and you can have them cover mortgage, property tax for something non-homestead-exempted, HOA, etc and you live in the Northern tier near a major airport, especially NYC zone, and you have the money to shoot down on some Winter weekends, maybe.&lt;br&gt;Otherwise, fuck no.&lt;br&gt;Now if you can buy a place in BFE inland North Florida cash with a well and solar and water frontage and enough land to kill and eat hogs, and you like that, maybe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901751&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61901644&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s &amp;quot;headquarters&amp;quot; moving to Miami. Ben Shapiro sent the staff to Trashville, Inbredessee and he is in Boca Raton.&lt;br&gt;Miami is LA/NYC prices with Havana wages. It&amp;#x27;s also fraud central. Any downturn and the place takes a gigantic shit, because everything is borrowed and leveraged to the hilt.&lt;br&gt;Miami has New York City&amp;#x27;s courtesy and pace, Florida&amp;#x27;s intellectual curiosity, and Latin American punctuality and work ethic.&lt;br&gt;The left lane is slap full of immigrants driving slow as fuck. Check out the video of the macho culture faggot in the passing lane getting passed on the right who pulls iron, flinches as his limp wrist wildly shoots in heavy traffic because someone passed him.&lt;br&gt;Florida is a penis and Miami is the foreskin cheese.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904193&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61897144&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;multiplexes&lt;br&gt;I would, rent out the other unit(s) until the one year ticks down for me to be able to let them all, the issue is that it&amp;#x27;s like 700k for a shitbox that&amp;#x27;s going to turn into a flooded pile of toothpicks come the first hurricane&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;d rather just press the buy button on more reits than have to interact with faggy duplicitous real estate agents, retarded trashy tenants, boneheaded hvac repairmen tradies, etc, etc&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904206&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891078&lt;br&gt;florida is literally hell on earth. i would rather live in north fucking korea. since money is the root of all evil, you will probably make quite a bit of profit by investing in Florida&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904308&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61901751&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;immigrants in the left lane&lt;br&gt;Unfortunately i think these stupid faggots are all white retirees and midwestern transplants. i fucking cant stand how slow these subhumans drive. I prefer the wildness of I-95&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904535&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891078&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;[GC Intensifies]&lt;br&gt;you will never 10X&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906121&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904308&lt;br&gt;100% true if you&amp;#x27;re not in Dade/Broward/Palm Beach (Central/Southern PB) or Orlando and maybe Tampa. Otherwise, North Florida, including I10, I75/turnpike North of Orlando, and I95 North of I4, yeah. It&amp;#x27;s all old people and Central Time Zone types.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Art Finance — 18 replies — 14.4/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61904247</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61904247?lm=1772123158</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 16:25:58 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Art Finance&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61904247'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 18 • Updated: 2026-02-26 16:25 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Draw Fag Here, /biz/ what do you think about investing in art? NFT? Tax avoidance? What can I do to become one of the richest artist in the world?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904444&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;fine art is a tiny scene that you can only be born into.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904464&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904444&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s easier if you have jewish relations with the same pedophilic fantasies as you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904475&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904444&lt;br&gt;Quads of queer truth. It&amp;#x27;s their club, and you&amp;#x27;re not in it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904479&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904444&lt;br&gt;How to join the little club, I want to join?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904491&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Are you a real artist? Wanna come work with me making 3d models for creatures&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904496&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904491&lt;br&gt;I am an artist, working for you making 3D models, will that help m become one of the richest artist in the world? I am up for it. Any emails?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904501&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904479&lt;br&gt;Why do you think youre such a valuable asset for them to control?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904503&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904496&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s not something you could easily pick up in a day or even a month&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904507&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904501&lt;br&gt;Well, I do art, got a fine art diploma, 15 years of experience, and I live in one of the tax haven. Come on, let me join the little art club, I just want to enjoy some grape soda and eat some pizza while we look at some art exhibits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904511&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904503&lt;br&gt;You are right, I am a sculpture major, got a diploma for it. Well, who knows how long it will take to play around with the software.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904517&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904511&lt;br&gt;Just pickup zbrush and start making some shit. Highest skill for art is creatures and animating them studios always need good talent in this field in particular because it&amp;#x27;s harder to find. Most other things are a lot easier to model&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904586&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904517&lt;br&gt;It sounds like wage job that can be easily replaced by AI. I want to do fine arts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904588&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904586&lt;br&gt;Fair. It is the highest paying wage job for an artist at least though without hitting higher circles&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904691&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904588&lt;br&gt;I see, sounds like a trap.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905138&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904479&lt;br&gt;You born into the club. You make shitty art, jewish art critics give you thumbs up, goyim believe the illusion you have talent, then you wash money for the cabal pedophiles. Same with movies or series. Why do you think woke shit like the little negress mermaid is made? To wash money. Art died a long time ago, friend. Plus you need to make a shitton of psychedelics before you can even appreciate and UNDERSTAND good art&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905184&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904247&lt;br&gt;Depictions of sexy market forces anon. As many as you like until you get bored.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905948&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905138&lt;br&gt;I understand good art, do you really think it&amp;#x27;s all jews? Why don&amp;#x27;t /biz/ support artist? &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905184&lt;br&gt;no, I like fine arts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61906164&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904464&lt;br&gt;You have to get quads&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Anyone else getting the itch? — 24 replies — 12.2/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61899833</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61899833?lm=1772120568</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 15:42:48 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Anyone else getting the itch?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61899833'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 24 • Updated: 2026-02-26 15:42 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The big boys&amp;#x27;ll go back up, that&amp;#x27;s guaranteed money. But some others will 10x, 100x, 1000x. I&amp;#x27;m feelin&amp;#x27; like it&amp;#x27;s SHIB&amp;#x27;s turn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900851&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61899833&lt;br&gt;Checked&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900872&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61899833&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;ll just keep buying small amounts of it for the rest of my life, and see what happens.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900948&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61899833&lt;br&gt;i believe in shib&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900953&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61900948&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61900872&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61900851&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61899833&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61900999&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61899833&lt;br&gt;Toshi is the king of the next cycle &lt;br&gt;It’s Base season, bitch&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901257&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is now a TOAD thread&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901298&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61901257&lt;br&gt;This.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901324&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Perfect time to rank up and join the TOAD army&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901689&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Only real ass pedophile glow niggas buy and pump toad killer up to billions of dollars market cap. This is the official gay furry pedo jewish mafia token of the next meme coin season. Buy now or cry later.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901710&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wen&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901769&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61901710&lt;br&gt;2030&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901771&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61899833&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;ve been slurping&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901780&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61901769&lt;br&gt;That’s not that far away&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901902&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61899833&lt;br&gt;Not pumping your shit token&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;not becoming your exit liquidity&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61901925&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61901780&lt;br&gt;Yes it is it&amp;#x27;s too far away I think most of us will be dead by then&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902754&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;My boomer dad bought $35k worth of shib about 8 months ago despite me advising against it, he’s down like 60%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61902821&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902754&lt;br&gt;Doubtful.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903181&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61902754&lt;br&gt;Tell him to hodl&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61903489&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oh Lord, please let SHIB go to $0.01 this year&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904243&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61903489&lt;br&gt;Not happening. What is going to happen though is toad killer will flip pepe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904434&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61899833&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61904495&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61904243&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;toad killer will flip pepe.&lt;br&gt;Its was programmed nearly 3 years ago but they’ll say we got lucky and perhaps we did. Right place, right time&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905725&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61899833&lt;br&gt;Checked and all in on anime doggo coin.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;You just know.&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s going to pump kek.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61905897&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61905725&lt;br&gt;yjk&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>