<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>/biz/ Active (filtered, with replies)</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/</link><description>Filtered out: general, gme, bbbyq. OP + first 3 replies + last 30 replies.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:57:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Financial independence / retire early — 34 replies — 136.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61884958</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61884958?lm=1771847687</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:54:47 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Financial independence / retire early&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61884958'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 34 • Updated: 2026-02-23 11:54 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;How&amp;#x27;s FIRE going for you, anons?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884964&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884958&lt;br&gt;Well I&amp;#x27;m looking into LCOL countries I can retire to because waiting until I&amp;#x27;m a multi millionaire in the states is not viable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884966&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884958&lt;br&gt;Just need a 7x then I&amp;#x27;m good. Already have rope if ready if I don&amp;#x27;t reach the goal in 5 years&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884967&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884958&lt;br&gt;i have about 3m networth but haven&amp;#x27;t quit my job yet. making too much money but want to quit real bad. i took a 4 day weekend recently and got bored because i have no life and hobbies because my job dominates my life and i have no energy left over to develop my personal life after work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884974&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884968&lt;br&gt;Thailand, Vietnam, Malaysia, Albania, is what I got so far.&lt;br&gt;Maybe Japan or Italy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884976&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884958&lt;br&gt;About $30MM now, I&amp;#x27;m 38. Feels good.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884979&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884967&lt;br&gt;They&amp;#x27;ve done an excellent job of trapping you, anon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884983&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884958&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m back to ramen noodle mode.&lt;br&gt;I WILL make this savings last until I get a job again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884986&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884958&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m just living off NEETbux+savings. It doesn&amp;#x27;t completely cover rent, so once my savings are gone I&amp;#x27;m going to just KYS myself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884996&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884974&lt;br&gt;Interesting. I never thought of Japan as having a low cost of living. And I&amp;#x27;ve heard Thailand is not as cheap as it was.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884999&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884976&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884986&lt;br&gt;I listened to a Grant Cardone video on YouTube about pulling IRA retirement money into self-directed fund then you can use it to buy real estate without getting the penalty but you have to go big and do multi-dwelling unit or else IRS flags you. I&amp;#x27;m too chicken shit to try it (yet) but if you&amp;#x27;re going to an hero anyway fuck it try it&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;pull life retirement savings&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;buy 10 unit apartment building&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;give self job fixing toilets&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;collect rent from tenants &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;profit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885003&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ok maybe a 3 unit building&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885030&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884999&lt;br&gt;You literally cannot fix the toilets yourself. Under IRC §4975 you are considered a &amp;quot;disqualified&amp;quot; person. Basically you can own it but you can never touch it. Very gay way to &amp;#x27;own&amp;#x27; something.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885054&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;way ahead of schedule.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Full time job income (104K + 11K in retirement)&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Cost of living 32K&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Fully owned apartment(450K)&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;308K in liquidish assets&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;90K in retirement&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;2K coming in every month from passive revenue from a side business (vidya gaems)&lt;br&gt;In 7-8 years i will probably reach full FIRE. But i&amp;#x27;m releasing new products this year. If i can have similar success i will probably just Barista FIRE living the gamedev dream.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885059&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884967&lt;br&gt;Dude, just quit. You&amp;#x27;ll probably decompress after a month or two, then you can re-evaluate. If you decide you need to work, then you can just go apply to some jobs. Maybe you&amp;#x27;ll decide you want to work in a library or something stupid like that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885062&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885030&lt;br&gt;that fucking sucks what is Cardone talking about then?&lt;br&gt;retirement money is just going to the bank then when I starve to death. maybe that was their plan all along. &lt;br&gt;take the 10% penalty + taxes ? now it&amp;#x27;s a duplex maybe in a cold flyover state&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885102&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just had my 2nd kid.&lt;br&gt;Already gave up and accepted that I&amp;#x27;ll be waging til I die.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885131&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884958&lt;br&gt;Pretty good despite the recent market drawdown. I stopped working 9 months ago and moved to a luxury condo in Thailand. Expenses are relatively low but I&amp;#x27;m still paying my mortgage and car note in America. I get a little bit of income from trading options and renting out my house to my younger sister. I&amp;#x27;m financially set for the rest of my life but I&amp;#x27;m still figuring out what I want to do as far as family, kids, etc.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885135&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885062&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885030&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884986&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;ok I found this. instead of self directed IRA to have to roll it into a business startup&lt;br&gt;so don&amp;#x27;t an hero yet &lt;br&gt;or put me down as your beneficiary first&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;https://www.bankrate.com/loans/small-business/what-are-robs/#:~:text=Key%20takeaways,penalties%20are%20associated%20with%20ROBS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885141&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884967&lt;br&gt;Nigger. Based on the 4% rule you can draw about 120k yearly off investments and statistically never run out of money. Wife and I retired early w/ Lite Fire. No debt. Last year our gross income was $55,000. We bought and sold a RV, Saw the Grand Canyon, Zion, Bryce Canyon, Rushmore. Took a 21 day cruise from west coast through Panama Canal, Cruised out of Florida for 3 weeks and hung out in Fort Lauderdale for 2. Did 2 more week in the Caribbean. Have a 20 day transatlantic cruise from NYC to Sicily booked with stops in 9 ports in April. Tons of midweek short trips seeing cool shit. Leaving work is an adjustment definitely but I have never been happier. See the world, meet people, always with an eye to relocation. Picrel is heading into Cartagena Columbia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885152&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884967&lt;br&gt;I was just like you before I decided to walk away. I call it &amp;quot;golden handcuffs&amp;quot; when a job pays so well that it makes you feel obligated to keep going even though you don&amp;#x27;t need the money. Your job feels like your identity but I promise you&amp;#x27;ll forget about it after you quit and find new hobbies and a gf.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887260&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884974&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884996&lt;br&gt;Japan is not a lcol area. Its cheaper compared to the west but not Thailand/Vietnam cheap. My plan is to live 90 days visa free there a year and live frugally elsewhere for the rest of the year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887270&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884958&lt;br&gt;Closing in on luxury fat FIRE thanks to gold/silver/oil/uranium. Fuck crypto.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887292&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t want to retire early, cuz id probably just be doing the same thing without getting paid for it, but i have enough money to be comfortable for now&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887302&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I am starting to realize the whole game plan of FIRE is just giving me reason to wake up in the morning, something to look forward to. I dont think I will really be that much happier once I achieve my dream of semi financial freedom.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887313&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887292&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;id probably just be doing the same thing without getting paid for it&lt;br&gt;Your job is your hobby? Congrats. What do you do?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887338&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s not really going.&lt;br&gt;Would take me getting my inheritance and buying the bottom of the next global market crash and riding the recovery wave with everything I can throw in during it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887601&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;uhh im 38. been retired since 32. probably unretiring soon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887625&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887313&lt;br&gt;gay prostitute&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890044&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887302&lt;br&gt;frugality is like a game, to see how little i can spend each month&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890071&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885054&lt;br&gt;what&amp;#x27;s your side business anon? reseller?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890085&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;is 1.5M too little to retire?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I round tripped 8 figs being greedy&lt;br&gt;its all i have left&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890089&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890085&lt;br&gt;depends where you live&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890151&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885102&lt;br&gt;My #2 is 4 months old now. Thanks to the fire-induced frugality I was able to reduce my hours for half a year by 10 hours a week which was priceless in itself. Will probably also wage forever but probably only 20 hours or so per week.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884958&lt;br&gt;We managed to pay off the house @32. other than that I only have 15k cash and 50k in the MSCI. &lt;br&gt;The plan was to retire @40 but unrealistic unless I win the lottery ( and I don&amp;#x27;t even play)&lt;br&gt;So yes full fire is impossible right now, but on the plus side: we need less than 2k/ month for a very comfortable life. &lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m converting a part of the house to a rental flat atm which should bring another 600 per month and allow for tax deductions.&lt;br&gt;After installing solar this year my electricity bill should drop from 110 to 40 per month. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;So all in all we can have a cozy lifestyle for an acceptable trade off in lifetime. &lt;br&gt;Wife would like to work 20 hours/week in 10 years or so, I should be able to fully switch to do freelance consultant work in my niche ( or not. Her meager wage combined with the surplus of the next 10 years should easily pay for everything and give the kids a nice tailwind) &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m putting 180 bucks/month per kind into an ETF which should become a nice 150k downpayment (infl.adj.) when they turn 27&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>insider here, again. — 30 replies — 120.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61879263</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61879263?lm=1771847294</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:48:14 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;insider here, again.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61879263'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 30 • Updated: 2026-02-23 11:48 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;i hope you bought BBBY-WT BBBY-WARRANTS&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879648&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I have a few thousand of these along with shares what am I in for&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879767&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879648&lt;br&gt;getting dumped on by OP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879836&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879767&lt;br&gt;Due to my current occupation, I am prohibited from holding stocks, options, or similar investments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879895&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This you?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879921&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879767&lt;br&gt;idk I mean bed bath was once a huge American retail darling...the historic overstock chart is super schizo/presently quite low...these warrants are trading like a shitcoin which is funny...I also don&amp;#x27;t dislike lemonis. He&amp;#x27;s a media player and if you actually listened to some of his shit there does seem to be an interesting intersection between blockchain capabilities and homeownership etc...not financial advice of course just a variety of things I was peeking at when researching&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879944&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879263&lt;br&gt;no&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879999&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879836&lt;br&gt;What is your current occupation anon? Nothing revealing but in general etc...the exercise price of the warrants is $15...trading currently at less than a dollar it seems like a confusing deal...at this point if one likes the company wouldn&amp;#x27;t shares be the move? I did some modeling around warrant prices if the shares price goes to xyz and that is very interesting...also speaking of interesting what&amp;#x27;s the deal with the alleged cusip similarity to the old bbbyq shares?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880091&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879999&lt;br&gt;Financial system. I am not asking you to hold those warrants until they are exercised. I am asking you to hold them and sell the warrants when we can realize a substantial profit. Nice quads.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881477&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880091&lt;br&gt;Interesting. Wouldn&amp;#x27;t trading the warrants implicitly come with a short term capital gains tax insofar as its impossible to hold them over a year at this point? Would have to be some pretty fair gains to offset that 40% hit...anyways doesn&amp;#x27;t the warrants increasing in price also imply that the shares have gone up in price as well? I ran some informal modeling estimates using black scholes with iv, roughly .65 years to expiry and this is what I came up with: 15.5 bbby share price = 4.50ish warrant price...25 share price/12ish warrant price...60 share price/45ish warrant price...100 share price/85ish warrant price...200 share price 185ish warrant price...I make no claim as to the veracity of these numbers, just for fun. Anyways what do you see happening to the bbby stock price for these warrants to be worthwhile? Am I thinking on the right track in general?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881670&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879263&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881753&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879999&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881477&lt;br&gt;note the digis&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881916&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879263&lt;br&gt;Buy these if you want, but remember, these warrants are not related to the canceled BBBYQ/DK-Butterfly, reguardless of what the BBBYQ schizos say.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881980&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881916&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;nobody tell him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882152&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879263&lt;br&gt;I hold a few&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882389&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;why are americans starting to invest more into VT?&lt;br&gt;isn&amp;#x27;t america the greatest country on earth?&lt;br&gt;for me it has always been VOO&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882429&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;look at NPC holder distribution&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;there&amp;#x27;s no big dumps&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;base still present&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;conviction quietly intact&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884950&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880091&lt;br&gt;So you&amp;#x27;re allowed to buy warrants, won&amp;#x27;t your employer know you bought them?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885366&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get ready everyone. I don&amp;#x27;t think they will be able to kick the can after this sneeze. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885357&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886042&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;what about BBBYQ? i lost all my money. the little i&amp;#x27;ve earned since then i&amp;#x27;ve spent on equipment that will make me a self-made millionaire thanks to my own intellect and blood sweat and tears and not thanks to ryan cohen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886054&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61886042&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886916&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BUY&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887055&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61886042&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;he doesn&amp;#x27;t know what % of powerwash/lawncare businesses fail in their first two years.&lt;br&gt;I appreciate your entrepreneurial spirit, but this isn&amp;#x27;t the flex you think it is.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887380&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887055&lt;br&gt;i&amp;#x27;m not trying to flex i&amp;#x27;m saying the BBBYQ should pay off without having to double down on BBBYW as well. it&amp;#x27;s fucking ridiculous how you can do everything right and run into complete disasters in investing and in other things and getting trolled by random assholes like you as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887389&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ryan cohen and larry cheng are behaving like autistic wankers after making thousands of people lose their life savings and pulte is a clown if he was just grifting BBBYQ investors&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887406&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;and trump is apparently a rapist pedophile murderer who rigged the 2024 election with elon musk and mostly everyone on wall street is getting away with psychopathic scammers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887414&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887380&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;BBBYQ should pay of&lt;br&gt;There will be no payoff for BBBYQ, ever.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887426&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887414&lt;br&gt;then RC should be held accountable for grifting BBBYQ investors, it&amp;#x27;s insulting to everyone&amp;#x27;s intelligence to claimi he did nothing to take advantage of people who looked up to him. though GME maxis are insufferable so they kinda deserve to get scammed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887888&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887380&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m not trolling you, brother. You&amp;#x27;re right, sometimes you do everything right and shit sucks anyways. That&amp;#x27;s what the book of Job is about. You still need to keep the faith, like he did.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889098&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887380&lt;br&gt;BBBYW is more like a lifeboat for people who missed BBBYQ. If you held a fat stack (10,000 plus) of BBBYQ into cancellation then you are good.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890133&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889098&lt;br&gt;2,000 sh @ 038&lt;br&gt;I dont care&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>TICK TOCK WAGIE — 26 replies — 85.8/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61884227</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61884227?lm=1771846776</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:39:36 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;TICK TOCK WAGIE&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61884227'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 26 • Updated: 2026-02-23 11:39 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;MONDAY WILL BE HERE BEFORE YOU KNOW IT!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884234&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;bezos will laugh at me for 30 years until I retire and am too old to enjoy it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884271&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;ve not worked in two years now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884444&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884227&lt;br&gt;total wagie death. &lt;br&gt;retired at 28.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884609&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NOW THE PARTY DON&amp;#x27;T START TILL I WALK IN&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885590&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Don&amp;#x27;t forget to set you alarm and back up alarms tonight, wagie. cannot have you being late for the 06:00 standup&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885594&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884227&lt;br&gt;foh nigga you keep offering VTO&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885608&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885590&lt;br&gt;Winter storm, no one will be in the office, faggot!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885622&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884227&lt;br&gt;that&amp;#x27;s ok Jeff, i have become desensitized to waging&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885626&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885608&lt;br&gt;Acts of god will be docked from your pay&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885888&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884227&lt;br&gt;Joke&amp;#x27;s on you Archon, cause I got fired. Can&amp;#x27;t own my soul if I starve myself to death on purpose now can you? Who can take my Monday mornings from me when I can&amp;#x27;t even afford a calender? Jeff Bozos.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885921&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Monday is my day off though, Jeff.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886102&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884227&lt;br&gt;your 48-hour trial of living is nearly over, wagie. the weekly humiliation ritual about to kick off once again&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886324&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884227&lt;br&gt;Wagies, don&amp;#x27;t forget to pack your little plastic lunch container and bring a snack&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886327&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stay strong, wagies. That 2% annual raise is definitely coming this time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888158&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;grow up wagie&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888163&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888158&lt;br&gt;i already have a routine&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888177&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884227&lt;br&gt;Only soft millenials complain about work. Real men do what needs to be done to make enough to solidify yourself in life and make your mark. Living in mommy&amp;#x27;s basement and trading bitcoin doesn&amp;#x27;t make you cool or edgy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888219&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61886102&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;those chicken legs&lt;br&gt;Stop skipping legs day you nigger&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888304&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884227&lt;br&gt;uh ohh wagie&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889294&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888158&lt;br&gt;He&amp;#x27;s just like me&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889305&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884227&lt;br&gt;Hey Jeff, one of your little faggot drivers didnt follow my instructions to put the box of quaker instant oat meal(maple flavor packets) on my porch. Instead they left them at my gate..in the rain..in a cardboard box...cardboard jeff..&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889850&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;four to go&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889963&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889305&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890034&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884227&lt;br&gt;wagies are you ready for MechaBezos to whip your ass so you work faster today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890092&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!!!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890116&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888163&lt;br&gt;So proud of this young man, probably still gets ID&amp;#x27;d&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Link vs XRP — 10 replies — 39.2/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889600</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889600?lm=1771846948</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:42:28 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Link vs XRP&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889600'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 10 • Updated: 2026-02-23 11:42 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;When will the gap close? Link came within a hair of flipping xrp in January ‘21. We all know that Link is everything Xrp fraudulently claims to be so it makes sense that this chart should flip soon enough. Will it be gradual or violent? Will it flip because xrp crashes or because Link moons? &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most importantly where are some places you can use Link as collateral to borrow Xrp to take full advantage of the trade of the century?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889606&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m so tired.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889622&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889600&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889606&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889620&lt;br&gt;Link is scam&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Buy XRP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889634&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889606&lt;br&gt;Xrp is like chainlink if all the nightmares came true: no use case, no revenue, an ipo that formally cuts token holders out of the picture etc.. and we need over a 10x to reach their market cap. This fact always gives me energy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889799&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889634&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889823&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889600&lt;br&gt;It won&amp;#x27;t. Even RLUSD will pass link&amp;#x27;s marketcap in a matter of a few months.You invested poorly in a project with the only purpose of jewishly injecting fees for literally no reason and assuming people will allow you to entrench in core services. It is a bad financial and moral investment&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889827&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889634&lt;br&gt;XRP had no ICO. Link sells to retail at every pump and drains operator rewards it claimed it wouldn&amp;#x27;t. Link has literally zero use case outside arbitrary jewish rent seeking crypto toll boothing. It solves no problem and has no use outside ADDING frictions. XRP from Ripple alone has: &lt;br&gt;https://ripple.com/insights/institutional-defi-on-xrpl-scaling-real-world-finance-with-xrp-at-the-core/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889841&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889600&lt;br&gt;not gonna happen, jews will reward retard boomers once again, they are the golden generation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890083&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889600&lt;br&gt;strongly believe 2026-2027, hopefully you&amp;#x27;re ready. won&amp;#x27;t be instant, but still swift. cant believe there are anons who actually think like this &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889827, i hope they dont disappear and comment a little longer so we can have fun with them. chainlink wont be the only crypto that will flip xrp either&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890125&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;xrp&lt;br&gt;BOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOM&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Buy Gold ASAP and stay away from Silver. — 7 replies — 28.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890123</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890123?lm=1771847831</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:57:11 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Buy Gold ASAP and stay away from Silver.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890123'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 7 • Updated: 2026-02-23 11:57 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gold will skyrocket when Trump bombs Iran.&lt;br&gt;Kikes and Glowies advertising the silver scam.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890127&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890123&lt;br&gt;Begone jew&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890130&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890123&lt;br&gt;You must be a zogbot trying to keep the goyim away from holding silver which is an essential component of milspec electronics, batteries, radars, primary explosives and so on. There&amp;#x27;s approximately 500 ounces of silver in every tomahawk cruise missile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890139&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890123&lt;br&gt;There are 90 tonnes of silver in a blackhawk tank you filthy jew!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890143&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890127&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890130&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Silver has no real value because it can be corroded.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;There&amp;#x27;s no central bank around the world who buys silver. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KKKXVTZAk9s&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890147&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890127&lt;br&gt;Love this execution tool that killed the criminal Jew. Christianity is a Jewish psyop&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890156&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890147&lt;br&gt;Another jew&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890159&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890147&lt;br&gt;Its the real world™, everything is a jewish psyop.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Day 516 Of Bobo Rekt in Anus Posting Until BTC is at 180K — 7 replies — 28.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61887585</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61887585?lm=1771847717</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:55:17 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Day 516 Of Bobo Rekt in Anus Posting Until BTC is at 180K&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61887585'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 7 • Updated: 2026-02-23 11:55 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887641&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;there goes my hero&lt;br&gt;watch him as he goes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887748&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887585&lt;br&gt;oh noooo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887752&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;its happening&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888339&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887585&lt;br&gt;As Bobo lay there with cum oozing out of ass, Bobina is getting helped by Mumu Johnson&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888380&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GOING DEEP AND HARD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888483&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887752&lt;br&gt;you have my curiousity, is the green line monetary supply?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890154&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887585&lt;br&gt;sorry for your loss brown man&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;but pls continue to astound us with your guidance&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>theyre STILL buying this — 14 replies — 24.3/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889884</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889884?lm=1771845796</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:23:16 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;theyre STILL buying this&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889884'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 14 • Updated: 2026-02-23 11:23 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;theyre STILL buying this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889888&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;un &lt;br&gt;fucking &lt;br&gt;believable&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889891&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;this is the biggest crime and scam EVER HOW THE FUCK IS IT AT 240 HOW DO THEY KEEP DOING THIS&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 1MIN CANDLE ON SPOT IS 400K$ VOLUME AND ON PERPS ITS FUCKING 10M$&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889892&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;how CAN IT BE PROFITABLE who the FUCK BUYS THIS???????????????&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889894&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;first it goes from FUCKING 180 TO FUCKING 320 and it STILL WONT DIE!!!!!!!!!!!!!!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I CANNOT BELIEVE THIS PIECE OF MOSSAD SHIT&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889895&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889892&lt;br&gt;Israel spambots&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889899&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889895&lt;br&gt;its FUCKING UNBELIEVABLE how the fuck can this work. the only way is by controlling the CEX its binance and mossad together&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889904&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HOW THE FUCK IS THIS PIECE OF SHIT THE SAME PRICE AS FUKCKING YESTERIAIYDIYDYAIDYADYAI I FUCKING HATE YOU MOOSSAD NIGGERSIFJSOIHFJSOGJISGAEPJIRG UFUICCKOYU&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889906&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AND IM THE ONLY NIGGER ON THE INTERNET WHO NOTICES IT BECAUSE EVERYTHING IS SO FAKE AND GAY NOW THAT LITERALLY NOBODY REALIZES THE CRIMETHEFT GOING ON ON THIS FUCKING PIECE OF SHIT&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;FOR 4 &lt;br&gt;FUCKING&lt;br&gt;MONTHS&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;FOUR!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889910&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;un FUCKING BELIEVABLE theyre gonna FUCKIG PUMP IT 20% AGAIN AAAAAAAGOAEGOAUGOAUGOAEGJOAIJGOAJIGOAI&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889919&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;fucking unbelivable&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;who has infinite funds? HOW can this be profitable? HOW?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;they instalong with $10M then they start selling it for 2 days&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;SOMEHOW NOBODY sells&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;NOBODY sells it down&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;WHO THE FUCK KEEPS BUYING IT?????????????&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;biggest fucking crypto crime happening before every nigger&amp;#x27;s eyes. literally un fucking believable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889927&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UN FUCKING BELIEVABLEFUAOGFIAEGAGEATJAET4JWPY4JEWPRJEPRHJERHEK&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890004&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889899&lt;br&gt;u think so?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890005&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889919&lt;br&gt;the jews did 10/10&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890079&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890004&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890005&lt;br&gt;yeah fucking jews. still shorting it to 0&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Is the meteoric rise of gold a sign of the upcoming death of the american empire? — 3 replies — 11.3/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890018</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890018?lm=1771846909</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:41:49 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Is the meteoric rise of gold a sign of the upcoming death of the american empire?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890018'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 3 • Updated: 2026-02-23 11:41 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Is this the time where Europe takes control of the world once again?&lt;br&gt;Is this why European stocks are massively outperforming US equities?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890023&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890018&lt;br&gt;only in a commodity so incredibly lame would a 2x over a couple years be considered a meteoric rise&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;But yes, it would be bad for the US if it had NOT also risen in every other currency in the world. Right? If it just went up in dollars that would be a bad sign. But it went up in every currency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890097&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890018&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Is this the time where Europe takes control of the world again?&lt;br&gt;You cunts are the most cucked defeated obedient people on the entire planet, and yet you come out of nowhere with this totally disjointed and tone deaf Jingoism.&lt;br&gt;How about you start actually rebelling in your own countries. Last I checked you&amp;#x27;ve all been letting muzzies rape your women unchecked, decapitate you, your governments do whatever the fuck they want, including send gibs to israel, you fags tax unrealized capital gains, tax 50-60% of income, your birth rates are amongst the lowest in the entire damn world, some of you are giving drugs to cows to stop them from farting and killing them in the process, you barely even have functioning militaries, let alone any guns or armaments amongst your populace. I could go on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890121&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t take women or Europeans seriously.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;No additional replies in the latest window.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>how do you guys cope with the fact that OF egirls are making tens of millions a year? — 37 replies — 24.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889270</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889270?lm=1771842326</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 10:25:26 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;how do you guys cope with the fact that OF egirls are making tens of millions a year?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889270'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 37 • Updated: 2026-02-23 10:25 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;how do you guys cope with the fact that OF egirls are making tens of millions a year? this shit is really unbelievable man i am seething so hard holy fuck&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889273&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I literally just don&amp;#x27;t care. Nobody will ever love them and I can also make 10 million without displaying my butthole for the world to see&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889278&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s only like top1% creators making millions&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889279&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889273&lt;br&gt;i didnt care too for so long but now im starting to care fml its just so unfair.. Not only are they extremely hot they also get to make 20MM a year for years scamming with bikini pics on OF&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;its just so unfair i feel like crying&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889292&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;Theres literally only been one titty streamer that turned that 5 minute success into owning multiple gas stations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889298&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889292&lt;br&gt;Car washes are where the money is at&lt;br&gt; Once you get your bag idk why people keep doing it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889301&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889283&lt;br&gt;okay this makes me feel better thanks man&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889304&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bro, these bitches don’t “make” money they just receive donations. There’s just as many if not more girls just receiving money from sugar daddies without an OF. These bitches would be getting money from sugar daddies regardless, instead of 1 or 2 sugar daddies giving them tons and tons of money they have thousands of sugar daddies giving them a little bit of money. If anything they are getting a worse deal from OF. Freedom and independence will never make a woman happy so they have no clue what to do with their lives anyways. It’s just one of the perks of being a woman, you get all your shit paid for. Just like women have access to secretary positions where all it takes is a retard to answer a phone and take messages and reply to emails just because they’re attractive and the bosses want them around. There’s a price on beauty and it’s a very short window to capitalize on. All they have to do is take a few pictures and videos, it could be all in the same day, and those pictures can be rolled out for years so they literally don’t have to do any work and can just let an agency handle everything. Almost all these bitches use an agency so they are giving up almost 50% of the profits to men. So there is an easy way for you to capitalize on these bitches profits you just aren’t doing it. This shit has been going on for centuries. It’s nothing new it’s just online.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889315&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are thousands of whores that lose their dignity on OF without making any money at all&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889322&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;You know there are criminals, corrupt politicians, and mindless corporate drones making more than that, right? Perhaps you imagine an economy in which people are compensated for the value they provide to society. That&amp;#x27;s only an ideal, not the economy that exists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889335&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;I am still a virgin at 35 and over my entire life I have wasted only 2.40 CHF on women. I&amp;#x27;m proud of myself that I&amp;#x27;m not a cuck.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889339&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;a girl I knew from school started an onlyfans. everyone she grew up with saw her getting fucked. she made like $200 and deleted it a couple months later. I feel like this is probably pretty common&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889347&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889339&lt;br&gt;Is she hot? You gonna share with the class?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889349&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889335&lt;br&gt;Was that 2.40 CHF for a cup of coffee? Bus fare?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889354&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889339&lt;br&gt;Girl I knew in the office years ago had hers leaked by one of the bitchy HR ladies. Like 14 people paid 5 bucks to sub to it and watched her rail herself with a 7 inch hog.&lt;br&gt;Eventually it got to her and started impacting her work and she was put on a PIP.&lt;br&gt;She quit like a month later. Think about that. At best she made the equivalent of a few burgs at Wendy&amp;#x27;s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889368&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889354&lt;br&gt;You made that up in your head. Why would HR have her porn videos&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889372&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889347&lt;br&gt;yea she was hot. she was also one of my good friends sisters. i didnt save any of the videos though&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889354&lt;br&gt;yep&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889378&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889368&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s not really difficult to understand if you understand how women work. Her being HR just happened to be where she worked. Office gossip is unfortunately how office wagies fill their day. Men aren&amp;#x27;t much different desu. We just talk about we railed so and so on the weekend. &lt;br&gt;Office women are vile and will say the most endearing things to your face before finding ways to tell your wife at the Christmas party how she heard you got blown by your manager&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889392&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;Are they?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;rented cars&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;leased jets&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;AirBNBs in Dubai for two days&lt;br&gt;All the illusion of being rich. Even if they did make a few shekels, they are definitely beholden to the pimp that is laundering money through them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889405&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;grow boobs then if you don&amp;#x27;t like it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889409&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;Barely any of them do, pretty much just the hottest ones that are willing to get their brains fucked out on camera. If you aren&amp;#x27;t one of the hottest guys willing to have your dingle out for the world to see it really isn&amp;#x27;t comparable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889429&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889409&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s an enormous amount of work too when you get big enough to make decent cash but not enough to sustain yourself. Answering 48 messages in the morning yourself because you can&amp;#x27;t afford to pay a guy to do it for and you can&amp;#x27;t not answer because these guys are shelling out 70 percent of your revenue. Then you return. Film more. Do it again and scrape by for maybe 900 bucks a month.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s almost more worth it to end up being worth a few cheeseburgers so you know you aren&amp;#x27;t worth it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889624&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you really cared you would be pimping OF models by now. You think women do anything in their own? They all have pimps.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889631&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s not glamorous but you can go on craigslist whenever you want and make a quick couple hundred getting your dick sucked by lonely old queers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889644&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889631&lt;br&gt;How is that even worth $200? Enjoy your money pox&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889769&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889273&lt;br&gt;Holy cope. Obviously most men will love them because men are horny dogs. Its 2026, prime time to realize men are the more pathetic gender. This aint the 50s champ.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889773&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889273&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Nobody will ever love them&lt;br&gt;These bitches get BFs all the time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889775&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;how do you guys cope with the fact that OF egirls are making tens of millions a year?&lt;br&gt;Only the top 1% do, the rest make around few hundred USD or few 20-40USD a month.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889273&lt;br&gt;Lot of them have BFs and lot of them don&amp;#x27;t do porn with other men just sell their nudes but most aren&amp;#x27;t making enough to retire on not by a longshot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889777&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;1. They don&amp;#x27;t receive all that money, they are hired under an umbrella corporation, they are just models for hire.&lt;br&gt;2. They are women, they don&amp;#x27;t know how to invest their money (see amouranth, it was her husband who put her in front of the camera, managed her socials and invested her money)&lt;br&gt;3. I can&amp;#x27;t see what you would do with that much money, unless you are hyper-dependent on people doing things for you...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889804&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;They aren&amp;#x27;t. The vast majority have sold their souls for triple digit profits&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889830&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Comparing yourself to women is one of the first steps on the tranny pipeline lmao&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889840&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;Go sell your asshole to strangers and lookmax then you lazy cunt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889979&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;Nothings stopping you from doing gya shit on onlyfans&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889986&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;Doesn&amp;#x27;t bother me in the least.&lt;br&gt;Firstly, it causes tons of women to throw their lives away being whores. So is hardly a victory for women.&lt;br&gt;Secondly, what does that money do other than ruin their lives? Women crave a man higher on the totem pole than they are, now they can&amp;#x27;t find one for two reasons.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Fake and Gay Economy — 94 replies — 13.7/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61871520</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61871520?lm=1771823171</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:06:11 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Fake and Gay Economy&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61871520'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 94 • Updated: 2026-02-23 05:06 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;When will this gay as economy finally collapse and how can i profit from it?&lt;br&gt;Its ridiculous the woman at our workplace contribute nothing to the company and make more money than i do&lt;br&gt;Its infuriating we just had a bunch of lay offs and we lost some of oir best workers but somehow a bunch of HR shits who do nothing all day still work here&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871530&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HR is a necessary function, chud&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871569&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871530&lt;br&gt;For what?&lt;br&gt;Genuinely why do we need it to this extent?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871755&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871569&lt;br&gt;Protect the corp from lawsuits&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883066&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879023&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;If they didn&amp;#x27;t provide value they wouldn&amp;#x27;t be there.&lt;br&gt;75% or more of white collar work literally does nothing, roasties or not.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883243&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;Did they fire itty bitty titties &amp;amp; a bob?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883399&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;When there is an alternative for the money and people to pour over into.&lt;br&gt;Fagmerica&amp;#x27;s slow decline relies on everywhere else being shittier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883616&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;HR while i&amp;#x27;m anxious, waiting for them to communicate their decision about hiring me, being unemployed and thinking about suicide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883644&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882495&lt;br&gt;you know, society almost always makes you think you desire gen z boss and a mini, but fuck that, i&amp;#x27;m gonna say it, loud and proud: i&amp;#x27;m more akin to have a relationship with secret product and a trench, i dont know if its about my selfsteem, i would like to be enough for gen z boss and a mini. Maybe what i need is 5&amp;#x27;3 and an attitude.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883760&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883243&lt;br&gt;They got promoted to Chief Diversity, Equity &amp;amp; Inclusion Officer&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883781&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883644&lt;br&gt;You meant to say inclined. You are more inclined. Akin means &amp;quot;similar to&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883784&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882869&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;incel&lt;br&gt;Im so confused as to what that term means, involuntarily celibate? But its not being celibate if your literally having sex. Such a weird term clearly carrying different meaning. What is the point of using a term that literally has no definition to its meaning, you might aswell speak in baby noises at this point.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884146&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;guys, ALL we have to do is called women like this ugly chopped shit to their face as much as possible and they will lose all motivation to live&lt;br&gt;they are SO fragile in that regard.&lt;br&gt;next time you are walking down the street and see some bitch like this just start yelling “YOURE UGLY”&lt;br&gt;they will spend the next week and a half minimum making reddit posts about it and getting their SSRI prescription upped.&lt;br&gt;don’t ever engage with any ideas or thoughts they have. just pick apart their appearance. you look like a fridge and a stick insect at the same time. your fake dyed hair sucks. you have clown makeup on, you must have learned how to do makeup at the circus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884272&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883066&lt;br&gt;So you&amp;#x27;re saying ceo&amp;#x27;s willingly burn 75% of their money for fun?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884291&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884272&lt;br&gt;he&amp;#x27;s saying the ceo is a fucking retard&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884297&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;I want to shove my cock deep into the first one from behind. Just lift the skirt and blast the pussy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884717&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883784&lt;br&gt;Yes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884737&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871569&lt;br&gt;Without HR you could complete the work, banter and build a genuine camaraderie with your common co-worker, but we cant have unions, and its better if you&amp;#x27;re all divided and conquered, here&amp;#x27;s a harpy to make your life hell&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884742&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873193&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872087&lt;br&gt;These niggers actually get it. All problems flow downstream from jews controlling the issuance of your (since 1913) fake and gay fiat debt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885902&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873611&lt;br&gt;You must be over 18 to use this site&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886326&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882442&lt;br&gt;Yeah this kind of mega über schizos who believe in fe and no nuke use this phrase holy shit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886329&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882442&lt;br&gt;And yes the idea of space is falsifiable you absolute schizo. Satellites wouldn&amp;#x27;t even work without it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886359&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883784&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Such a weird term clearly carrying different meaning. What is the point of using a term that literally has no definition to its meaning&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s just people overusing words or ideas to oblivion, where they lose all context. It&amp;#x27;s like the worst insult was being called gay way back, then it was subverted (actually gay is cool), then it became retarded, then it got subverted (actually retarded is cool because you&amp;#x27;re not trying), then it become autistic, then it became subverted (actually it&amp;#x27;s interesting to be autistic), now it&amp;#x27;s random baby talk by gen alpha (mog, cortisol spike, chopped, unc, lil bro, frame, aura farming, 67, incel, cuk). Now it&amp;#x27;s being subverted by people overusing the terms even if they don&amp;#x27;t apply to anyone or anything in the context at all. Someone not having sex for a week = incel. Someone having a slightly embarrassing moment (cortisol spike), someone better looking walking past (mogged), doing something that&amp;#x27;s barely good (aura farming), having a strong presence even if it&amp;#x27;s completely autistic and retarded (frame). Or like when old people started wearing skateboard shirts having no clue what it was, or everyone and their dog wearing an off white shirt. People make shit gay eventually, it&amp;#x27;s a universal law.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886363&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;work office job (engineer) with way too many women and diversity hire niggers and Indians who do nothing all day&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;get new (white) South African Vice President&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;calls us all together&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;in his funny accent tells us he’s an engineer and knows the business and there will be changes&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;tells us he will cut 20% of the workforce soon&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;everyone is shit scared and the normie femoids start climbing over each other trying to save their useless asses&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;office girlies start spreading rumours about everyone and everything in desperate attempt to make themselves look better&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;don’t give a fuck, I’m a technician and actually make money for the company unlike them&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Vice President just observes the shit show and never comments on anything while he feels out the office&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;come in one Monday&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;literally all blacks are gone&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;all except the actual useful Indians are gone&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;he culled every single female that we all knew had jewish make believe adult daycare jobs&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;only kept the old hag secretaries that actually do a great job&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kek, based white nigger. Turns out all it takes is some third world coloniser to clean this woke shit up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886555&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872076&lt;br&gt;We are not capitalist.&lt;br&gt;We have been Trotskyist since the end of WW2.&lt;br&gt;Having a central bank is plank #5 of the commie manifesto.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886576&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884742&lt;br&gt;It was a bit delayed until after 1913.&lt;br&gt;They couldn’t go full fakeconomy immediately, or they would have been shut down.&lt;br&gt;They had to wait and boil the frog slowly, using the occasional crisis as a speed boost.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886586&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t ever interact with HR once I&amp;#x27;m hired until I&amp;#x27;m inevitably fired. From where comes the HR hate? Are they the ones who actually make the decisions to fire us?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886684&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;this board is dead as shit holy fuck&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886687&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61886684&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s the weekend. It picks up when the market is open.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886692&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;d fuck all of them. At the same time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887220&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61886363&lt;br&gt;Sounds illegal and fake. This is such an obvious thing to do, there must be a reason it doesn&amp;#x27;t actually happen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889346&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s not going to collapse... bill gates will grow some cheap bug burgers and psyop all the women to think it&amp;#x27;s healthy and great for the environment... so we can continue feeding billions of women to do nothing but work in an office.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889382&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61886363&lt;br&gt;How was he able to be able to gauge who&amp;#x27;s useful and who&amp;#x27;s not in such a short period of time?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889387&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889346&lt;br&gt;Also, paying women to do nothing is one of the best birth controls there is. They are incapable of dating down. Sorry, just the messenger. bullshit jobs, especially for women, will never end until picrel collapses.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unfortunately, the jews also don&amp;#x27;t want picrel to collapse because then their banks would go broke. So we&amp;#x27;re stuck in hell.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Why not Start an Online Casino? — 8 replies — 12.1/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889846</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889846?lm=1771845493</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:18:13 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Why not Start an Online Casino?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889846'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 8 • Updated: 2026-02-23 11:18 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;What exactly is stopping me?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;buy a license for $15k in XYZ island&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;only take crypto to avoid KYC on burgerbros&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;run some clean poker games&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;collect money&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889851&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889846&lt;br&gt;Basad, be the cz killer!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889853&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Owning a casino is one way that putting all your profits back into it can go wrong.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889866&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How big is the crypto gambling audience even?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889869&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889846&lt;br&gt;I like your idea. But I find it hard to believe you just pay for your license and you’re free to do whatever you please. Prob too much red tape/ rules/regulations to. Can’t let the goyim get a step up at all. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You think you can get away with non KYC? I’m interested in hearing how&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889883&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889869&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;you think you can get away with non-kyc?&lt;br&gt;There are already sites that are doing this operating in the US today. Ignition, ACR. and Coinpoker notably on the crypto side and WPT gold on the sweepstakes side. only coinpoker and WPT shill via ecelebs and in general US noncompliance sites seem like an underserved area of the market. I don’t get why there aren’t more players.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889886&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889866&lt;br&gt;Considering GGPoker takes direct crypto deposits, it’s presumably massive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889896&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Because the Australian government only allows poker machines. No poker or games outside of casinos, polymarket is banned. Online poker banned. Two up (coin flip game) is unbanned one day a year but banned for the rest of the year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890069&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889846&lt;br&gt;nothing, just need a few millions to start, and go through all the regulation hell&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>2026 is THE year of the Link token. You'll see. Check 'em. — 46 replies — 11.7/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61882840</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61882840?lm=1771833738</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 08:02:18 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;2026 is THE year of the Link token. You&amp;#x27;ll see. Check &amp;#x27;em.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61882840'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 46 • Updated: 2026-02-23 08:02 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;2026 is THE year of the Link token. &lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;ll see. Check &amp;#x27;em.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882854&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882840&lt;br&gt;Great year for Sergey. Horrible year for baggies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882857&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882840&lt;br&gt;you have nothing to check, not even dubs, you will fail&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882865&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Uh, I&amp;#x27;ma put my cat on the keyboard. Meow meow meow, meow, meow meow. Meow meow. Meow meow? Meow. (Financially speaking)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884132&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;digits and link is $100 eoyt 2026&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884172&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884132&lt;br&gt;You are low energy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884202&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882840&lt;br&gt;linkies are THE cuckolds of crypto xD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884230&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882840&lt;br&gt;Zero digits in this thread. SAD!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884400&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884230&lt;br&gt;How is that even possible?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884841&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883854&lt;br&gt;how embarrassing&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884942&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;$500 EOY CHECKEM&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885073&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;$10,000 EOY. Check em niggers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885105&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;$20 in April, digits confirm&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885130&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882840&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;whitnessed&lt;br&gt;$120 eoq&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885795&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is known&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885804&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885795&lt;br&gt;I hate these niggers so much. Every financial opinion piece they spew out is complete dog shit on crypto. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;...And for that reason goy, BUY BITCOIN! Just because!&amp;quot; &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;And PLEASE pay for a subscription to our stock picks!&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;Everytime. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;They made retards generational baggies the last run.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886478&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882895&lt;br&gt;It hasnt even begun yet&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886491&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882857&lt;br&gt;check the chart&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886642&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882840&lt;br&gt;Depends on how badly the US starts to tank because crypto is designed to step in once the dollar begins to collapse.&lt;br&gt;The alternative is the complete collapse of the global economy and a new dark age for humanity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886644&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882865&lt;br&gt;kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888654&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;pool remains closed&lt;br&gt;stack remains unsold&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888690&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;$120 eoy &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;clarity starts the next bull run, check em&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888705&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Linky remains stinky, check ‘em&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888709&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Poo poo pee pee caca doo doo wee wee, check em&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888754&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Okay hear me out&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The potential for 81K is possible though ironically. When you account for staking locking up 95% or even more of the circulating supply(350 Mil, the rest are spoken for on nodes already). I suspect by 2026 BTC will only have around 35-40% dominance as well, projects with specific applications will begin to take hold. Oracles, various layer 1&amp;#x27;s that enable Smart contracts, DEFI, decentralized cloud computing, decentralized cloud storage, and probably other things that haven&amp;#x27;t even been conceptualized yet.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We are supposed to see at least 8 Trillion MCAP by 2025 of all crypto according to the experts. Klaus Schwab mentions this in his book.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I think we will see 4-5 Trillion at the peak of the next bullrun easy. That will probably be early to mid 2022. Next peak bull run will probably mid to late 2026 which could easily run 16-20 Trillion MCAP of all crypto. In the scheme of things that is only around 18-25% of the global GDP. Its honestly not that much.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now lets say LINK network protocol captures 4 Trillion by 2026 peak bull run. At even 80% staking saturation (70 Million circulating supply) the price is close to 60,000 per LINK, around 57,000. At 15% circulating supply, its 52.5 Million LINK with a 4 Trillion MCAP is 76,000 per LINK.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;These numbers sound ridiculous at first or to the uniniated but again when you understand what LINK is/does its honestly not. We are buying a share of the fat protocol that will monetize Web 3.0. I mean think if HTTPS would have been monetized. The Internet itself is worth around 19 Trillion and when you add in data accumulated from the &amp;quot;Internet of Things&amp;quot;, it adds a 5-10x multiplier roughly.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Internet is more or less 25 years old for the masses as a whole. If there were 350 Million shares circulating, they would be worth just under 54,000 each at its current estimated value.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pic related is fun and entertaining but ironically achievable in the time frame suggested&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Discuss&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888841&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888754&lt;br&gt;Sounds good I hope it’s true&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888850&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888754&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;now let&amp;#x27;s say that [impossible thing] could happen&lt;br&gt;nice ass though&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888854&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;$1000 EOY&lt;br&gt;It has always been and always will be&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889104&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884400&lt;br&gt;kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889172&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888754&lt;br&gt;mental illness :/ if only we had a place to put you people that did not have internet access&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889312&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Something something it’s like a mental asylum or something and there is a locker or something and you have like the locker code or something but not really and the locker will open in a few years and there’s like heaps of money or something? Anyway, that’s how holding LINK feels like, or something&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;just hold for another decade bruv&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889341&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The First Reptilian Bank of Canada just aped 300 GLNK and you&amp;#x27;re bearish???&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889715&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889341&lt;br&gt;based reppies finna save us no cap. trust&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889793&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884942&lt;br&gt;Triple and link will hit $502&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>I sold. 4600 Stinkies, 14.8 ETH. thanks for nothing — 14 replies — 10.6/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889893</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889893?lm=1771843101</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 10:38:21 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;I sold. 4600 Stinkies, 14.8 ETH. thanks for nothing&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889893'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 14 • Updated: 2026-02-23 10:38 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;I sold. 4600 Stinkies, 14.8 ETH. thanks for nothing&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889901&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You are a traitor&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889903&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889893&lt;br&gt;ee sold?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889911&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889893&lt;br&gt;kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889912&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889893&lt;br&gt;Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889925&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889903&lt;br&gt;Literally this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889930&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889925&lt;br&gt;refinance where OP?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889939&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OP set us free&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889961&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889939&lt;br&gt;kek this guy :D &lt;br&gt;reallife wojak&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889983&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I CANT FEEEEEEEEL&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;THE WAY I DID BEFORE&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;TIME WONT HEAAAALL&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;THIS DAMAGE ANYMORE&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889985&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889983&lt;br&gt;You were the only real trader left. We all were waiting for you to sell and now we pump it unitl you fomo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889988&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889983&lt;br&gt;nigger big jew banks predicting 10k btc in tumor weeks™ and u selled?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889994&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889983&lt;br&gt;didnt see those jewtube spams here in the past 4 days about how fucking over for beetkoin and it will never go back up ever again? maybe even negative values in dollars? :D&lt;br&gt;always buy the retard 10iq nigger fud, dont capitulate it!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890002&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889985&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889988&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889994&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I lied. I sold my highest cost basis ETH buys (4.3 ETH total). I have a nice 10k realized loss hole for 2026, but I still think ETH and link make me whole by end of year. I’m expecting a false flag or full scale war with strike on Iran, millions of deaths. So I wanted to pull some out, contemplating selling some more but maybe we get a little fakeout pump. Im hoping to slurp some more if we get one less capitulation, if It runs and I miss out, I still got an ok bag. Also stay frosty for a grid down scenario. Best of luck anons&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890009&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890002&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Why do people on this board whine piss and moan about having six-figs? — 58 replies — 8.7/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61883830</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61883830?lm=1771823889</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:18:09 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Why do people on this board whine piss and moan about having six-figs?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61883830'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 58 • Updated: 2026-02-23 05:18 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Do any of you realize how unbelievably lucky you are compared against most in even 1st-world countries? Your average person is tens of thousands in credit card debt and struggling to pay off their klarna these days. Even worse, they&amp;#x27;re a few months behind on their mortgage and about to lose their house.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meanwhile, your lot go &amp;quot;WAAAAAA WOE IS ME I&amp;#x27;M ONLY WORTH $475K AT 23 YEARS OLD I&amp;#x27;LL NEVER BE RICH!!!!!&amp;quot; Even if you&amp;#x27;re larping, I mean fuck you don&amp;#x27;t&amp;#x27; realize how spoiled rotten and ridiculous you sound, you&amp;#x27;re not even funny nor cute when you whine like that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883852&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883830&lt;br&gt;yea but crypto went down&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883873&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883830&lt;br&gt;because im still a wageslave you retarded cockgargling faggot&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883874&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883830&lt;br&gt;There are no 1st world countries anymore. It goes:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Switzerland, Northern Italy, Poland, and everybody else&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884765&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884755&lt;br&gt;You are kinda free if you are in the top 10% ig. They are the group still spending in usa.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884780&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883830&lt;br&gt;Another day another poorfag trying to drag me into his crab bucket.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;FUCK OFF YOU PIECE OF SHIT LOSER STOP TRYING TO MAKE EVERYONE SUFFER WITH YOU&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884789&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884780&lt;br&gt;He isn’t wrong. American median household income is 60k.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885028&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883830&lt;br&gt;Six figs isnt enough to retire. Anyways Im at very low 6 figs one slight dump in stocks and Im back to 5 figure hell.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I want out of the wagecage and its not luck when the average person in the US probably buys fast food 10 times a week, goes out to a restuarant once a week at $200 per visit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885045&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;it called being tongue-and-cheek you stupid fucking retarded fucking nigger&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885049&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885045&lt;br&gt;oops meet to say tongue in cheek but whatever&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885051&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884789&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;median household income&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;household&lt;br&gt;Kek they try so hard to giving a realistic number. Show me median individual income, emphasis on median. Don&amp;#x27;t feed me &amp;quot;average&amp;quot; which is easily skewed upwards.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;you live in a nation of 100 people&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;1 person makes $1b&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;99 people make $10k&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;average houshold size is 10 people&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;median individual income $10k&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;median household income $100k&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;average individual income ~$10m&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;average household income ~$100m&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885310&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885051&lt;br&gt;by your own math median is just as misleading as mean&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885331&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883830&lt;br&gt;500k is nothing. If you have this, congrats. You can spend your entire net worth and buy a decent house. Now what? &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;There has to be more than this, op. People who are &amp;quot;doing well&amp;quot; should be able to actually make a change in this world, yet they can barely afford to buy a house. The system is broken&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885340&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885331&lt;br&gt;Back in muh day we just gathered sticks of wood and nailed cardboard&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885350&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883830&lt;br&gt;The majority of people in first world countries are boomers, they own multiple houses, have had multiple wives, multiple kids, multiple cars, multiple pension plans. I literally have nothing in comparison.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885360&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885350&lt;br&gt;Dont go there just stay where you are. When they send their drones china will just hack them and make them crash. And thats how the white cookie crumbles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885501&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885310&lt;br&gt;But far more accurate to reality than the supposed reality they try to paint. In both median individual and household income the amounts are more accurate than average while median individual income bears the most accuracy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885512&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m about to enter 6 figure hell next week, what am i in for?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885530&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883830&lt;br&gt;My 300k is literally nothing&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885562&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885512&lt;br&gt;5 figure hell after trump&amp;#x27;s tariff tirade&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885855&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883830&lt;br&gt;Lucky? I&amp;#x27;m a fucking wage slave. Having 600k usd means fuck all when houses cost 2 million AUD in Sydney and I&amp;#x27;m 30 years old. I don&amp;#x27;t want to work the rest of my life (I won&amp;#x27;t anyway as AI is about to take me out)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885862&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885512&lt;br&gt;Depends on your age and savings rate&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885873&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883830&lt;br&gt;Nope. Not good enough.&lt;br&gt;Sense of accomplishment is relative. We want to go up in life, not down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885878&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883830&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s good that I was born when and where I was. It is a good thing. I greatly appreciate being born on a scaffold.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885983&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885051&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;what is law of large numbers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885987&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885331&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;muh house&lt;br&gt;Kys retard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886585&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885512&lt;br&gt;Obsessively watching your portfolio everyday, and realizing you’re still broke. I eased off the gas and just started spending a little and enjoying life more when I hit 100k. If it’s gonna be another 30 years to retire, I might as well the ride.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886699&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885350&lt;br&gt;Wait 50 years and you&amp;#x27;ll be even richer than boomers unless you fuck it up&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886704&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885855&lt;br&gt;You can always rope&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886984&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;over 500k at 32&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;165k safe public sector income&lt;br&gt;Never gonna make it ;_;&lt;br&gt;Forever angry at myself for buying the chainlink ICO and then selling before it mooned.&lt;br&gt;Shill me your shitcoins and meme stocks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889254&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61886984&lt;br&gt;$500k at 32 is a lot. If you simply invest in an index fund you could get 10% per yeat. Doubling every 7 years. You will have $2 million cash by age 46, which is good. Purely through passive investment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889285&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889254&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s 7% per year normally, but we are likely entering a decade of stagnation in stocks now after the 2 decade megabull we&amp;#x27;ve had&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889380&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884630&lt;br&gt;Meh, I sold 12 BTC for $40 each&lt;br&gt;Now I&amp;#x27;m broke, but debt free and 300 link&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889424&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61886984&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;meme stocks&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For 165k income? SCHD.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Quick! I need to take a payment of $4000 worth of BTC Should I take t now at ~66.4k or do I wait till tomorrow hoping th… — 5 replies — 7.8/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890028</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890028?lm=1771845558</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:19:18 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Quick! I need to take a payment of $4000 worth of BTC Should I take t now at ~66.4k or do I wait till tomorrow hoping th…&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890028'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 5 • Updated: 2026-02-23 11:19 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Quick!&lt;br&gt;I need to take a payment of $4000 worth of BTC&lt;br&gt;Should I take t now at ~66.4k or do I wait till tomorrow hoping the market crashes to sub-60k&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890032&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I get the sense this thread makes the goy gold holders seethe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890033&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890028&lt;br&gt;There’s no shot it drops below 60 tomorrow. We’ll probably see a slight uptick in price and crabbing for a few days. Just like the last “crash”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890039&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890032&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;ve been holding gold since October, I&amp;#x27;m pretty happy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890065&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890028&lt;br&gt;$4000 worth of bitcoin at 66k and $4000 worth of bitcoin at 60k is still $4000. Are u fucking stupid&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890075&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890028&lt;br&gt;im afraid to buy bitcoin anymore cause it will dump the same second i buy&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;strategy for using bitcoin:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;buy it&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;instantly sell it for the thing you want to buy 1 minute later&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;shits like hot potato&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>