<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>/biz/ Ticker Threads</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/</link><description>Threads mentioning tickers</description><item><title>[NOT] Welcome to /biz/ - Business &amp; Finance — 1 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/60278989</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/60278989</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 20:47:07 +0000</pubDate><description>Open article for full content</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;[NOT] Welcome to /biz/ - Business &amp;amp; Finance&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/60278989'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 1&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;This board is for the discussion of topics related to business, economics, financial markets, securities, currencies (including cryptocurrencies), commodities, etc -- as well as topics relating to starting and running a business.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Discussions of government policy must be strictly limited to economic policies (fiscal and monetary). Discussions of a political nature should be posted on &amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;/pol/. Global Rule 3 is also obviously in effect.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Note: /biz/ is NOT a place for ADVERTISING or SOLICITING. Do NOT use it to promote your business, ventures, or anything you may have an interest in. Anything that looks remotely like advertising or soliciting will be removed. Begging/asking (including tipping) for cryptocurrencies or asking for money/capital is also strictly forbidden.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;60278993&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Check the catalog before posting a new thread!Reply to existing threads about a topic instead of starting a new one. Mods will delete obvious duplicate threads and spam without notice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded><enclosure url="https://i.4cdn.org/biz/1745614027988142s.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0" /></item><item><title>[BTC BUY CLI GUI TX] /XMR/ Monero General — 246 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61810651</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61810651</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:36:07 +0000</pubDate><description>Open article for full content</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;[BTC BUY CLI GUI TX] /XMR/ Monero General&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61810651'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 246&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Welcome to /XMR/ Monero General, dedicated to the discussion of the world&amp;#x27;s most widely adopted privacy coin.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;XMR payments are anonymous, low-fee, and fully fungible. Users can send and receive XMR globally without having to worry about tainted coins. Battle-tested privacy tech (Ring Signatures, Stealth Addresses and RingCT) ensures that critical TX data cannot be gleaned from the Monero blockchain; the TX history of all XMR users is kept hidden, with TXs being optionally transparent via the aid of a view key.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;XMR ensures low TX fees by employing a dynamic block size that can &amp;quot;stretch&amp;quot; to easily accommodate sudden TX spikes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;XMR&amp;#x27;s mining algorithm, RandomX, is optimized for devices using general-purpose CPUs e.g. desktops, laptops, smartphones, tablets, keeping the barrier to entry low and ASICs out of the equation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;XMR&amp;#x27;s tail emission - 0.6 XMR per block forever - incentivizes for-profit miners to keep mining, helping boost long-term network security. This constant linear inflation trends to zero and is offset by coin loss.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;XMR has proven to be the only altcoin capable of overcoming BTC&amp;#x27;s network effect by driving it out of the darknet economy BTC dominated for over 10 years. XMR is also starting to overtake BTC in clearnet commerce as well.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you still have questions, feel free to ask. A MoneroChad will be with you shortly.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;XMR Redpill: https://youtube.com/watch?v=wq6w03E2DS4&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;BUY XMR: https://monero.eco/exchanges/&lt;br&gt;Crypto ATMs: https://coinatmradar.com/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;XMR Resources: https://monero.observer/resources/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;XMR Stats: https://moneroj.net&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;USE XMR: https://cryptwerk.com/pay-with/xmr/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;OFFICIAL WEBSITE: https://getmonero.org&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;MINING: &lt;br&gt;https://www.getmonero.org/get-started/mining/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;WALLETS:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Desktop&lt;br&gt;Official GUI/CLI wallet&lt;br&gt;Featherwallet&lt;br&gt;Stack Wallet&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Mobile&lt;br&gt;Cake Wallet&lt;br&gt;Monero.com&lt;br&gt;Stack Wallet&lt;br&gt;Unstoppable &lt;br&gt;Monerujo (Android)&lt;br&gt;Monfluo (Android)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Infodumps&lt;br&gt;https://rentry.org/monero-explained&lt;br&gt;https://moneroinfodump.neocities.org &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Previous: &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61761870&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856863&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856711&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;Monero General&amp;quot; thread&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;CTRL + F &amp;quot;nerva&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;140 results&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your unmaintained shitcoin will NEVER be relevant you poojeet retards. Everyone with more than 2 braincells can tell that you&amp;#x27;ve been shitting up the board trying to advertise. Please do the needful and make your own general. Except you can&amp;#x27;t do that right? Because NO ONE cares about it and it dies immediately unless you coordinate to keep it alive in your gay little discord server.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856711&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854237&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854655&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Jewish media bashing monero&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Just like they did with Trump&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Sub Artic IQs dont notice theyre promoting it on purpose&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Paid promoters ITT walk around the fact that concern was brought up by actual users and went unanswered or were outright removed posts/threads, then claim the view key fud was started by the very mossad theyre unironically supporting&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Glowner, promoted by Glews.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855579&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855558&lt;br&gt;I never bought crypto with PayPal but if you can buy LTC, do it. Once you swap to Monero and have it in your personal wallet you become invisible and cannot be deanonymized.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855567&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855558&lt;br&gt;Once it gets to your wallet it disappears.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855558&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855365&lt;br&gt;Ok, installed the cake wallet program, made the wallet, both monero and litecoin. Now I need to actually buy the crypto so I can transfer it to the wallet I just made. I think I still have an old paypal account which apparently allows you to buy crypto now. Is that ok for me to buy litecoin, transfer it to the cake wallet and exchange it for monero or will I be de-anonymized for using paypal just this once?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855365&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855123&lt;br&gt;Yeah, follow the chat here: &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61817263&lt;br&gt;If you have any issue or problem at a specific step ask here and we&amp;#x27;ll help.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Enjoy the &amp;quot;beer&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855123&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I need to send someone 5$ for a beer while anonymous. Thing is I have no fucking clue how any of this cryptocurrency works. Can someone explain to me same way you would to a retard?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855033&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61696670&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;suggest wallet that can store XRP,XMR,USDT and Zcash is there any&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Turns out this actually does exist. Hope this anon is still lurking &lt;br&gt;https://edge.app&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854655&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854237&lt;br&gt;They really seemed to think the view key fud would be more effective if they now need to publish paid articles&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854237&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61810651&lt;br&gt;Bloomberg published an article on Monero this morning. It’s behind a paywall but here is the article thanks to some Twitter anon.&lt;br&gt;https://pastebin.com/6aqniwe1&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;As digital assets go mainstream and law enforcement agencies get more adept at seizing illicit crypto, “privacy coins” like Monero hark back to the industry’s foundational idea: the creation of a decentralized electronic cash system running outside the purview of governments and central banks. That’s given them a cult following among libertarian-leaning crypto users — while providing a handy tool for criminals.&lt;br&gt;The rest of the article is just (((Bloomberg))) seething about how it can’t be tracked and a mention of the upcoming hard fork.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853405&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851879&lt;br&gt;Get any other coin and swap for Monero on Trocador.&lt;br&gt;Have the monero sent to your cake wallet.&lt;br&gt;Go on Dread to find what&amp;#x27;s the current best darknet market.&lt;br&gt;Go on the DNM and buy your product with Monero.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;All the steps take a bit of time but it&amp;#x27;s not complicated. Once you know how everything works it&amp;#x27;s no more complex than an Amazon order.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61852911&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851879&lt;br&gt;What this guy said&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61852742&lt;br&gt;Then visit Dread dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad onion&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61852742&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851879&lt;br&gt;Send any major crypto to Trocador. Swap to XMR.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851879&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I’ve been out of it for a while, how do I buy some and use it to acquire ketamine? Last time I was doing this, we used bitcoin and it was $220.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851533&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851129&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Youll never answer the questions regarding the upcoming fork and always link their github page because YOU dont understand it.&lt;br&gt;I link the github because I like having a source to back up my claims, and I actually want you to stop being a faggot and refute them&lt;br&gt;No, accusations of being a fedfreemasonbot out to get you are not refutations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;For some reason, Monero thinks its better to implement something that is unnecessary rather than something that should be implemented.&lt;br&gt;Who exactly are you to decide whether or not a feature is unnecessary and shouldn&amp;#x27;t be implemented?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Maybe its because you all brought up the &amp;quot;doomer fantasy&amp;quot;? He never mentioned it.&lt;br&gt;Given how he was asking about them&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61838139&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;so when someone says kyc will ask for this and then the feds will use it for surveillance, theyre correct? then it&amp;#x27;s not FUD&lt;br&gt;I hit the fast forward button on his line of thought since he clearly believes that view keys present some sort of threat, and I didn&amp;#x27;t feel like waiting 10 posts for him to go &amp;quot;WELL IF THEY GET ENOUGH TO VIEW KEYS IT&amp;#x27;LL BE THE END OF PRIVACY!&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;If this was wrong of me, then my bad.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Your wins are not the wins you think they are.&lt;br&gt;Who said I was trying to win anything? Why are you perpetuating this weird fantasy? You&amp;#x27;re weird bro. Not a good look at all, man.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851379&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851332&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Ive posted twice&lt;br&gt;Correct, I was speaking about rVCB8pdb, I assume you were doing that too or do you speak about yourself in the third person? &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;and none of it was about nerva.&lt;br&gt;Good job not having and reading comprehension and forgetting you posted: &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;they cant even BTFO nerva jeets lmfao (&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849231)&lt;br&gt;and: &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I was banned recently for criticizing it. Look at the nerva faggots. (&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851129)&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851332&lt;br&gt;You combined any criticism against XMR with nerva. So by your own logic most of the criticism here comes from the nervajeets.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Never did,&lt;br&gt;If you don&amp;#x27;t have any questions, then why do you keep pestering me about needing to answer them? &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Never mentioned it.&lt;br&gt;All three of your posts mentioned nerva in a positive light.&lt;br&gt;Feel free to answer any of my questions (see &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851255 for the easiest ones) or give me any of the question which you apparently don&amp;#x27;t have but are lamenting as being unanswered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851332&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851235&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;No, you retards get banned for shilling for nerva. Also it&amp;#x27;s weird to assume he got banned after his 14th post over 3 days meanwhile you&amp;#x27;ve also posted fud over the days and still are present. &lt;br&gt;Ive posted twice you jeetbot, (3 times now) and none of it was about nerva. Ill disregard the rest of this botpost.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851245&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Your questions? You don&amp;#x27;t seem to have any.&lt;br&gt;Never did, go back and reread my posts.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851255&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;xmrbotpost about nerva. &lt;br&gt;Never mentioned it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Glownero&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851255&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851129&lt;br&gt;In return I&amp;#x27;d like to ask you a few questions: &lt;br&gt;1. How do you ensure unmaintained software keeps up with the security demands it has?&lt;br&gt;2. How do you ensure that no one attacks nerva by locally clustering CPUs? &lt;br&gt;3. Why do your devs believe Discord to be a development platform despite being on github? &lt;br&gt;4. How do you ensure the safety of your devs in case of an attack by glowies if they all use the ID-requiring discord and 40% of them (50% of your lead devs) having doxxed themselves publicly?&lt;br&gt;5. What other questions do you have for me?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851245&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851129&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;always link their github page because&lt;br&gt;Me? No I didn&amp;#x27;t. I know github is something that challenges the nerva jeet heavily so instead I break it down in very simple terms. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;because YOU dont understand it.&lt;br&gt;Your questions? You don&amp;#x27;t seem to have any.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;the reason the reddit comments dont get answered is because NO ONE understands it.&lt;br&gt;I already answered all of the questions I saw. If you have more let me know. The assumption that no one understand cryptography or psychology is absurd considering the existence of that field. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The reason the even more damning questions get deleted is because theyre asking the right questions.&lt;br&gt;Like what? So far each question I saw I answered on here. I don&amp;#x27;t use reddit but feel free to keep me updated on orange site. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;For some reason, Monero thinks its better to implement something that is unnecessary&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;ve already been told that view keys will have some benefits. I recall hardware wallet and merchant software support being named in this thread. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;rather than something that should be implemented.&lt;br&gt;Devs, due to being part of a community and mostly unpaid, decide what they wish to implement. If it&amp;#x27;s fcmp++ they&amp;#x27;ll work on fcmp++, if it&amp;#x27;s carrot, they&amp;#x27;ll work on carrot. You can&amp;#x27;t force strangers that donate their time to do only what you want them to do especially if it&amp;#x27;s a feature you can easily avoid. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Take a good hard look at that statement youre defending&lt;br&gt;That literally nothing will worsen with carrot? Seems like a fine statement to me. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Since youll never post an answer to the questions,&lt;br&gt;I can&amp;#x27;t speak for anon but I already answered every question you have. If you have any other questions let me know.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851235&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851129&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;For some reason, criticizing your shitcoin (Monero) is against jannie law.&lt;br&gt;No, you retards get banned for shilling for nerva. Also it&amp;#x27;s weird to assume he got banned after his 14th post over 3 days meanwhile you&amp;#x27;ve also posted fud over the days and still are present. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;They keep being banned as well.&lt;br&gt;Who knows, maybe it&amp;#x27;s the constant shilling and the spam they don&amp;#x27;t just post here but on the board itself through a variety of threads. Btw when you don&amp;#x27;t get banned your generals just hit page 10 and die. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;What doesnt puzzle anyone is how your general stays up for days without deletion,&lt;br&gt;That&amp;#x27;s because the XMR general is fairly active and removing established generals would just lead to more shitposting. I hope you don&amp;#x27;t want the 10 millionth LINK thread this year.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;yet the only organic traction your threads have are from posters who get banned criticizing you.&lt;br&gt;Did you forget the moonfags that tried to take over this general, the qubic fud, the view key fud and the zioncash shills? All of those happened less than 6 months ago. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;and have this site backdoored.&lt;br&gt;No need for a backdoor when the mods are jews and feds. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;If competition shows up, the thread gets shadow banned and falls off the catalog.&lt;br&gt;Really? What happened to &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61841738 &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61827591 &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61822264 and &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61809799? Those are just some of the ones you had and that died because your community consists entirely of a few jeets and baggies. Graciously I sometimes enter your threads and ask you simple questions which you can&amp;#x27;t answer despite their simplicity. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Youll never answer the questions regarding the upcoming fork&lt;br&gt;I did a few hours ago and now I&amp;#x27;m waiting for more questions. Let me know if you have some.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851129&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849859&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850085&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850591&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I&amp;#x27;ve been waiting for a few hours now. Due to your lack of questions I assume you are agreeing with me that carrot does not pose a privacy threat&lt;br&gt;There is a good chance he&amp;#x27;s banned. For some reason, criticizing your shitcoin (Monero) is against jannie law. I was banned recently for criticizing it. Look at the nerva faggots. They keep being banned as well. What doesnt puzzle anyone is how your general stays up for days without deletion, yet the only organic traction your threads have are from posters who get banned criticizing you. Its because youre a bunch of glowniggers who work for (((the island bunch))) and have this site backdoored. If competition shows up, the thread gets shadow banned and falls off the catalog.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Youll never answer the questions regarding the upcoming fork and always link their github page because YOU dont understand it. Face the truth, the reason the reddit comments dont get answered is because NO ONE understands it. The reason the even more damning questions get deleted is because theyre asking the right questions. For some reason, Monero thinks its better to implement something that is unnecessary rather than something that should be implemented.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;In short: All proposed &amp;#x27;new&amp;#x27; attack vectors already exist&lt;br&gt;Take a good hard look at that statement youre defending&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Which sent anon into a tizzy that didn&amp;#x27;t actually refute anything I posted&lt;br&gt;Maybe its because you all brought up the &amp;quot;doomer fantasy&amp;quot;? He never mentioned it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your wins are not the wins you think they are.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;At what point will you accept this answer? Seriously, what don&amp;#x27;t you faggots get?&lt;br&gt;Since youll never post an answer to the questions, Why should they repeat themselves? Its an XMR thread, not the audience&amp;#x27;s thread. You have to provide an adequate answer and are up for scrutiny, not them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850591&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849231&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61848021&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;ve been waiting for a few hours now. Due to your lack of questions I assume you are agreeing with me that carrot does not pose a privacy threat. I&amp;#x27;m glad we could finally come to an agreement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850085&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849231&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;re clearly retarded and can&amp;#x27;t follow a conversation, so I&amp;#x27;ll highlight the points for you.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I gave the answer to the view key FUD here&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61838278&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Which sent anon into a tizzy that didn&amp;#x27;t actually refute anything I posted, here &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61838817&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;whos doomer porn fantasy? XMRfags cant even keep an eye on whos talking to who in here. I dont care about nerva.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Which I then edited to ease his butthurt here&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61839127&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The TLDR is that this particular doomer porn fantasy can&amp;#x27;t compromise anyone&amp;#x27;s privacy.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;But he wanted an official statement from the devs to ease his butthurt &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61847581&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;So I gave him that too &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61847618&lt;br&gt;Which sent anon into another tizzy, because he seems to agree with some redditor that &amp;quot;it&amp;#x27;s just toooooo hard to read the documentation! Why can&amp;#x27;t they spoonfeed me!?&amp;quot; Here &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61847794&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;why should i trust monero at all&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;picrelated from reddit thread. why cant they just tell reddit why its safe?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To which I then pounted out that he was already given the spoonfed answer that doesn&amp;#x27;t require him to read anything on github or librera &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61848809&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;And then asked the same question I&amp;#x27;ll ask you now:&lt;br&gt;At what point will you accept this answer? Seriously, what don&amp;#x27;t you faggots get?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849859&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61848827&lt;br&gt;I feel like most of the older stuff is still applicable since it&amp;#x27;s just about the basics. See picrel as an example. However I agree that the more specific guides (for example how and where to get XMR) rarely has good pictures. Do you have other bad examples so we can make a list? &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849231&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;cant even tell 4channers in a simple format&lt;br&gt;Five sentences isn&amp;#x27;t hard if you ask me. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;the taxman who says &amp;quot;gib?&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;1. You already need to be deanonymized for that. The ways you can get deanonymized will stay the same. This would also be combated by using an exchange wallet. I&amp;#x27;d probably even use an on-ramp wallet, an off-ramp wallet and a holding wallet. This way even if you were deanonymized and the IRS asks for more than what they&amp;#x27;re allowed to ask (just the income as a number, not the sources or which bank account it went to) you&amp;#x27;d still retain your privacy. &lt;br&gt;2. This is already possible by being coerced through various means. A view key won&amp;#x27;t change that. This is proven by your next sentence. &amp;gt;Normies fold faster than a wet noodle.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In short: All proposed &amp;#x27;new&amp;#x27; attack vectors already exist, require additional information that isn&amp;#x27;t easily obtained (they tried for years and still couldn&amp;#x27;t get it) and are easily mitigated. &lt;br&gt;Additionally, if someone for whatever reason was willing to inform the IRS of the relevant taxes by directly allowing access to view the wallet (which still is absurd and not how it works) it&amp;#x27;d be much easier and also less risky. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you have any other scenarios in which view keys could be exploited which are not covered already please let me know.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849231&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61847794&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61847814&lt;br&gt;They will never provide you an answer anon. Monerocucks are glowniggers, pretending to not be. Its funny watching them recoil in fear though. Just look at the past few generals, they cant even BTFO nerva jeets lmfao... look here&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61831334&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61847825&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;why cant they just tell reddit why its safe?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;doesnt and cant&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;cant even tell 4channers in a simple format&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Well *I* asked *you* that one for a reason.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Please tell me what explicit attack scenario exists in which the five dollar wrench and current KYC measurements are infeasible but having to give out your view keys is.&lt;br&gt;the taxman who says &amp;quot;gib?&amp;quot; Normies fold faster than a wet noodle.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61848809&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;You were already given the a TLDR&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;At what point will you accept this answer?&lt;br&gt;cant even get a copy and paste job on here&lt;br&gt;oh...&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;1pbtid&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You all sound like pathetic freemasons who suck jew dick.&lt;br&gt;&amp;quot;wErE nOt BaD pPl!? oH bUt YoU hAvE tO jOiN uS tO fInD OuT wHaT wE BeLiEvE iN!!!&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;kills you when you defect or tell a secret after finding out they worship the satan&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;lmao moneroniggers and their copium at their finest. Go glow on some other basket weaving forum. Is it any wonder XMR generals never get banned for advertisement? Its because 4chan is backdoored with JDIF, and JDIF &amp;amp; Monero suck each others dicks. One big blowjob circlejerk for their father satan.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;inb4 some cuck even tries to reply to me, you cant even keep up with my precision and speed. anyone who reads this knows im right. i use your shill threads to spread truth, and there is nothing you can do about it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849019&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61848053&lt;br&gt;Thanks anon. No cap fr fr Tbh I had no idea it was there before it was pointed out&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61848827&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We should look for ways to improve Monero&amp;#x27;s (official) material and appearance, not to induce any kind of pump, but to effectively convey the principles and message of why Monero, specifically out of other privacy coins, is extremely unique in the freedom it provides in contrast to all other money systems&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Right now it seems like very old material, links and screencaps keeps getting recycled. There&amp;#x27;s so many recent world events happening that tie in to Monero&amp;#x27;s use and we&amp;#x27;re missing a translation&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Monerochan (mostly AI slop) also doesn&amp;#x27;t communicate anything about Monero&lt;br&gt;There doesn&amp;#x27;t seem to be any good image macros to share from these threads&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Interested in how other people view this issue and what kind of material would get the communication standard up to the same level as its founding principles and tech&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61848809&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61847794&lt;br&gt;You were already given the a TLDR so you don&amp;#x27;t have to read through the chat logs like I and many other anons have&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61839127&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The TLDR is that this particular doomer porn fantasy can&amp;#x27;t compromise anyone&amp;#x27;s privacy.&lt;br&gt;At what point will you accept this answer?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61848342&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61848323&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;1488&lt;br&gt;based&lt;br&gt;monero is the final solution to the taxman question&lt;br&gt;and is what people think btc stands for&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m alive if that&amp;#x27;s what you&amp;#x27;re asking&lt;br&gt;and could unironically use any help if anyone could afford to&lt;br&gt;shamefully posting&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;XMR:&lt;br&gt;893qvnGketXV72jLmcDNhSWQgMQvzP4ab71HdaWMPrBrittG5PPfVrZcFKNYHv9UfXRDBkzvzNSc5bn7m7nJA6taKJ37gQW&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61848323&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61848303&lt;br&gt;1488 brother. Hope you&amp;#x27;re doing well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded><enclosure url="https://i.4cdn.org/biz/1770384967790775s.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0" /></item><item><title>[EU] The EU is going full degen — 61 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61856214</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61856214</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 07:38:08 +0000</pubDate><description>Open article for full content</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;[EU] The EU is going full degen&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61856214'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 61&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856862&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856542&lt;br&gt;Yeah no shit, dimwit. Thats why we kvetch about the EU all day that we cannot afford to heat our commieblock because of Uschi Vanderleyen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856857&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856214&lt;br&gt;guillotines&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856845&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856214&lt;br&gt;How? Infighting kills every venture the EU goes on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856826&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856363&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;If you want, I can also explain what the Savings and Investments Union would mean in practice and what concrete measures are being discussed.&lt;br&gt;go on then&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856814&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856792&lt;br&gt;thats dumb. I have even less faith in these shitty as places and like I said no one wants to move every few years, thats just straight up larp. yes you can hide your wealth but how do you explain the money once you want to convert it back into fiat. by hiding I assume mean cold wallets or pm. one of those things you cant move between countries so there is that. you cant run from the system, its global.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856800&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856418&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856774&lt;br&gt;Latvia has something called a &amp;quot;tier 3 pension pillar&amp;quot; but once your money goes in you cannot get it back no matter what until retirement and any capital gains are taxed at 25.5% when you start withdrawals.&lt;br&gt;If your employer matches your contributions from your AFTER tax wages the matching is taxed at 25.5% up front.&lt;br&gt;And you can only invest in managed funds that invest mostly in Latvian and E.U. bonds - so if the S&amp;amp;P is up 20% this year you will be up like 6%.&lt;br&gt;Americans have it good, especially with the Roth IRA.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856792&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856769&lt;br&gt;sea, south america for starters. cheap places where you can bribe your way. if not then simply become a neet, declare bankruptcy and hide your wealth, not only don&amp;#x27;t pay any taxes but ontop become a drain on the system funding you by their tax money lmao.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Or suffer, your choice. realize you play their game on their terms. personally i no longer participate they can go fuck themselve.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856776&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investment, aka giving the money to your pals&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856223&lt;br&gt;kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856774&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856418&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I really hope we get the euro equivalent of a 401k soon.&lt;br&gt;swedes have trading accounts (ISK) that are somewhat similar but their account is not necessarily for retirement and are very popular there. recently a swede was in my country (iceland) talking about this account. its something that would be nice to have. doing foreign investment here is rather bothersome. a foreign account like ibkr is needed and local banks have no online trades and 1% fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856769&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856758&lt;br&gt;move where? no country offers you 100% certainty. you almost always have to rely on the government to make rational decisions lol. no on wants to move like a bum every few years just to no get tax-raped to death because the government ran out of money.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856758&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;quite easy to understand, no? either move or become another burden&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856749&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856418&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Germany also has so many good companies you can&amp;#x27;t invest in because they are private.&lt;br&gt;Those companies are good because they&amp;#x27;re private&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856740&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856214&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;private savings&lt;br&gt;fuck fuck fuck they&amp;#x27;re going to take my money&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856725&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856214&lt;br&gt;Buddy, that is literally what US is doing tho.&lt;br&gt;When you put your savings into S&amp;amp;P500 you are investing in US economy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856714&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856418&lt;br&gt;Bankers can rob your 401k. Some companies force their employees into have them and make withdrawing any money from it a pain in the ass. If they start looting 401k&amp;#x27;s it could take days to recover yours. By then it might be too late.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856699&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856363&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;connect citizens’ savings with investments within the EU&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;looks inside EU stocks&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;shit that plummets to 0 in a couple of years&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;subsidized green energy bullshit&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;dying vehicle companies&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;penny stocks&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;banks&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;ASML is the only thing that is doing actually ok&lt;br&gt;hell no&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856692&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856393&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I want to see a modern bank run and for everyone to pull out at once&lt;br&gt;Computer says &amp;quot;no&amp;quot; and limits withdrawals&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856688&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;tfw yuropoors are more brown than americans&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856668&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A lot of scared miggers in this thread&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856606&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856214&lt;br&gt;I just read the strategy. It&amp;#x27;s basically 2 things&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;europeans are retarded and let their money rot in banks that are too incompetent to finance new innovative companies because they&amp;#x27;d rather park their assets in boomer revenue generating companies&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;American politicians became billionaires by filling the pockets of arms dealers and we kinda missed out on that so we&amp;#x27;re doing that now by putting them into EU issued pension funds and automatically enroll everyone to fund it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856598&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856214&lt;br&gt;All funny memes aside the most scary thing for my portfolio right now is not the ai bubble or any upcoming war like with iran, its straight up brussel. I see posts like that from von der Leyen or the things that the dutch do with their unrealized gains tax and I am getting really fucking scared for my future. This could fuck up my whole retirement plan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856597&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856542&lt;br&gt;Sure is. &lt;br&gt;How&amp;#x27;s it going with roubles?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856542&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856263&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856308&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856407&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;one negative mention of zelensky&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;instant (you)s&lt;br&gt;/biz/ is a board for people that have money to invest, as eastern eurpooreans you don&amp;#x27;t belong in here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856471&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856463&lt;br&gt;And here comes the boomer memes. Holy shit how old are you, nigga?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856463&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856242&lt;br&gt;You vill own nothing und be happy like a true eurocuck&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856461&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856455&lt;br&gt;Cool.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856455&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cool. Maybe ten years from now we&amp;#x27;ll be gambling on Bulgarian biotech stocks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856449&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856214&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;wdr&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;(woman, didn&amp;#x27;t read)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856442&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856431&lt;br&gt;True doe. Maybe buying lidl stonks would make them have more cashiers or invest into self checkouts, but again boomers are too retarded and fall for every vatnegro talkingpoint.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856431&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856422&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded><enclosure url="https://i.4cdn.org/biz/1771141088339567s.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0" /></item><item><title>[DD DRS DSPP DTCC FDIC] /GME/ - Settle in for Comfy (Long) Weekend Edition — 187 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61853052</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61853052</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 07:58:33 +0000</pubDate><description>Open article for full content</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;[DD DRS DSPP DTCC FDIC] /GME/ - Settle in for Comfy (Long) Weekend Edition&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61853052'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 187&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;Basic Information&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;gme.cac site redacted due to aids&lt;br&gt;https://finra-markets.morningstar.com/MarketData/EquityOptions/detail.jsp?query=14%3A0P000002CH&lt;br&gt;https://gmetimeline.com (up to 2021)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Daily reminder&lt;br&gt;s[Kek Melvies]bzilp4&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Mandatory study time&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The Everything Short&lt;br&gt;reddit.com/mgucv2&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;^watch-along&lt;br&gt;youtu.be/AaalT8rn9lc&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Naked Short Selling and Systemic Risk&lt;br&gt;youtu.be/FCiL4v7_z9E&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Failure to deliver&lt;br&gt;youtu.be/I0WXg5T3cBE&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;GameStop Investor Site&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;SEC 10-K Annual report FY24 &amp;amp; &amp;#x27;25 Proxy Statement&lt;br&gt;news.gamestop.com/annual-meeting/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;What will happen if Citadel becomes insolvent?&lt;br&gt;DTCC with 60T USD, will pay as the final boss with FDIC as the insurance&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Real-Time Trades&lt;br&gt;https://www.nasdaq.com/market-activity/stocks/GME/latest-real-time-trades&lt;br&gt;https://eresearch.fidelity.com/eresearch/gotoBL/fidelityTopOrders.jhtml&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Current Trade Halts + Short Restrictions&lt;br&gt;nasdaqtrader.com/Trader.aspx?id=TradeHalts&lt;br&gt;nyse.com/markets/nyse-arca/notices&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;All other news/DDs/etc&lt;br&gt;en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Stag_hunt&lt;br&gt;https://prospect.org/power/how-the-gamestop-hustle-worked&lt;br&gt;https://computershared.net/?bot=drsbot&lt;br&gt;DRS Guide:&lt;br&gt;reddit.com/ptvaka&lt;br&gt;Avoid DSPP (more information under legacy links):&lt;br&gt;sec.gov/about/reports-publications/investor-publications/holding-your-securities-get-the-facts&lt;br&gt;HF/broker class action lawsuit evidence:&lt;br&gt;storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.flsd.590042/gov.uscourts.flsd.590042.416.0.pdf&lt;br&gt;SEC GME/meme stocks report:&lt;br&gt;sec.gov/files/staff-report-equity-options-market-struction-conditions-early-2021.pdf&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;DD Compilation:&lt;br&gt;reddit.com/mnss65&lt;br&gt;Quarterly Movements, Equity Total Return Swaps, DOOMPs, ITM CALLs, Short Interest, and Futures Roll Periods:&lt;br&gt;reddit.com/pb22oj&lt;br&gt;Cellar Boxing:&lt;br&gt;reddit.com/pmj9yk&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Temporary alliance with reddit and Jaws to take down other sharks, we can go back to hating each other later&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;reddit DDs don&amp;#x27;t take them for fact use your brain&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Check your broker and clearing house to ensure you&amp;#x27;re not rugpulled&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last time on /GME/: &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61847072&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As always:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;sneed hedgies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856861&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855015&lt;br&gt;That&amp;#x27;s why shill get upset when they are mocked and called jeets that eat cow poop. They have to read it. They try to use shaming tactics when they are insulted. The reality is that using slurs against them does make you blend in, because they can&amp;#x27;t reply in kind. Calling them jeets and Jews in the fastest way to make them I&amp;#x27;d jump.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856693&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hi like Ichimoku, I think it is neat. too bad it is useless&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856434&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856331&lt;br&gt;Isn&amp;#x27;t it crazy the implication of systemic stock suppression, is that you&amp;#x27;re gambling all non-suppressed stocks against the suppressed ones? Pretty wacky scenario.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856346&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855460&lt;br&gt;Hope some got laughs at my expense yesterday, not native english. Spent past summer in Amsterdam and having girls that directly available was .. new (and wah the weed). 5 red light visits and 3 of them 10/10 experience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856331&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;55 trillion market cap&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856300&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856282&lt;br&gt;Right at that point I&amp;#x27;d be cutting just-below-threshold deals for securities backed loans and then just not paying them back. Tax free windfall, plowed straight into assets of my choice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856282&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855670&lt;br&gt;I feel like they&amp;#x27;d make an emergency exception of some kind. The worst thing they could possibly do is forcibly diamond hand everyone for a month straight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856112&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Burry is reposting his sneeze summary.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;https://x.com/michaeljburry/status/2022915353601290650&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856100&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855670&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Is it really in our prophecy that moass happens because anons can&amp;#x27;t fucking sell?&lt;br&gt;Technically volatility halts could keep the markets in this autonomous glacier where it becomes very hard to clear/confirm trades: https://www.luldplan.com/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here&amp;#x27;s the NYSE halts that get updated during regular hours: https://www.nyse.com/trade/trading-information&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856072&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jannies are retroactively deleting comments inside threads that are already archived on 4chan.org&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;this comment exists on warosu:&lt;br&gt;https://warosu.org/biz/thread/61791741#p61792435&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;but that same comment was removed from the thread AFTER it was already archived.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61791741&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855930&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I wonder why DFV bought all those chewy shares?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855879&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Any Dutch bros here? Is the bill pretty much guaranteed to pass senate?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855852&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854610&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;just deep value investing in a company experiencing a historic turnaround&lt;br&gt;this sentence is to shills what the garlic is to vampires.&lt;br&gt;it&amp;#x27;s 100% obvious that gamestop is NOT a &amp;quot;memestock&amp;quot; (made up fake label anyways) but a normal stock traded on the stock market and all indicators and fundamentals point towards a bullish outlook. that&amp;#x27;s factual.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855824&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;QED&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855792&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855783&lt;br&gt;Not to mention that in a situation where GME&amp;#x27;s share count is fully reconciled, the options chain will not be a safe haven. Force majeure cash settlement inbound for the optionfags while DRS chads rest easy as gazillionaires.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Sorry goy, an Act of God happened! Here&amp;#x27;s some cash! Sorry about your GME options contract!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855783&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855769&lt;br&gt;I would sooner buy long dated puts on spy than options on gme. Just buying shares and warrants seems smarter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855774&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855769&lt;br&gt;AvailableWarewolf/ftwbiz will be killed post moass&lt;br&gt;lol&lt;br&gt;lmao&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855769&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855529&lt;br&gt;It would explain why everyone who mentions buying LEAPS gets dogpiled by screeching retards even though DFV&amp;#x27;s whole strategy was LEAPS+shares.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855745&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854860&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854674&lt;br&gt;kek we&amp;#x27;re close&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855670&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854868&lt;br&gt;At that price even selling half my shares I qualify for that 30 day &amp;quot;please let me sell&amp;quot; bullshit that anon was talking about. Is it really in our prophecy that moass happens because anons can&amp;#x27;t fucking sell?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855653&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;*all shares in broker = $250k.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855647&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855615&lt;br&gt;I would also argue&lt;br&gt;1 warrant = 1 wagmi - $32&lt;br&gt;1 share in broker = $250k&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855615&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855141&lt;br&gt;1 share in CS:GO = 1 wagmi&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;x+1 share in CS:GO = 1 wagmi &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The bigger x is, the faster 1 wagmi happens&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855166&lt;br&gt;I would like to test being rich now. That would help.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855545&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ken Griffin is having a bad week. Let us take a moment of silence for ken Griffin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855534&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854591&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Is there really a doubt that a “meme stock” has been deemed a new type of security with different rules and exceptions?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;post a link to this new regulatory framework. They can delay as long as the derivatives market allows hiding short interest (bill hwang did this) and hiding positions inside swaps and other bespoke instruments. BBBY owns tzero, nothing happens without M&amp;amp;A activity, guess which companies will be involved?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855529&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;https://www.reddit.com/r/Superstonk/comments/1r4t2a0/the_strike_price_symphony_1/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t know what to make of this. The post and all of OP&amp;#x27;s comments are clearly written by AI. But it seems compelling. But this isn&amp;#x27;t the first time clearly AI DD promised a groundbreaking insight that ended up not meaning anything.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855492&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855427&lt;br&gt;Youre in that 4chan monger telegram group arent you&lt;br&gt;you sick sick man&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855472&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855323&lt;br&gt;i will turn all my dollars into other memecoin like € so i will be fine&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855460&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855427&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;im gonna go from having banged 20 escorts this year&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s only February.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855427&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ill trade some drs for metals, can hold 200+ drs forever and wagmi with rest of position or loan against it. this is my final stand investment and taken too much shit from this gay ass planet that spite alone carried me these past 5 years with ease. but yalla rain cone wasting my prime years here and def dont wanna larpfag in some faggot office the next 40 years.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;im gonna go from having banged 20 escorts this year into 2000 the next 10 years, should stars align :)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded><enclosure url="https://i.4cdn.org/biz/1771055913680926s.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0" /></item><item><title>[DE EU UK US WOEVY] /pmg/ - Precious Metals General — 271 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61855017</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61855017</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 21:37:29 +0000</pubDate><description>Open article for full content</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;[DE EU UK US WOEVY] /pmg/ - Precious Metals General&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61855017'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 271&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;Why precious metals?&lt;br&gt;https://youtu.be/i3S4rl6ehiI &lt;br&gt;https://youtu.be/gksenA5Al_A &lt;br&gt;https://youtu.be/FI7NnOg2rxo &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Huge deficits in minerals such as silver by 2050 inevitable&lt;br&gt;https://youtu.be/iibsrDXdEos [Embed]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Bullion dealers&lt;br&gt;https://libertycoin.com/ (US)&lt;br&gt;https://www.chards.co.uk/ (EU/UK)&lt;br&gt;https://www.silburycoins.co.uk/ (Ancient)&lt;br&gt;https://www.luciteria.com/ (Other rare metals)&lt;br&gt;https://www.ma-shops.com/ (Numismatics)&lt;br&gt;https://www.goldeneaglecoin.com/ (US)&lt;br&gt;https://stoutgold.co/ (US)&lt;br&gt;https://www.aydincoins.com/ (US)&lt;br&gt;https://prospectorsgoldandgems.com/ (US)&lt;br&gt;more at:https://pastebin.com/gZfZHtNE&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Numismatic search&lt;br&gt;https://en.numista.com/catalogue&lt;br&gt;https://www.ngccoin.com/price-guide/world&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;News and graphs&lt;br&gt;https://numismag.com/en/home-en&lt;br&gt;https://silverseek.com&lt;br&gt;https://www.silverdoctors.com&lt;br&gt;https://www.mining.com&lt;br&gt;https://silverbacksnakes.io/finance/silver&lt;br&gt;https://www.gold.org/goldhub/data/gold-reserves-by-country&lt;br&gt;https://wtfhappenedin1971.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Compare&lt;br&gt;https://findbullionprices.com (US)&lt;br&gt;https://eu.compare.pm (EU)&lt;br&gt;https://www.gold.de/aufgeldtabelle (DE/EU)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Resources&lt;br&gt;https://www.jmbullion.com/ultimate-guide-to-90-silver-coins&lt;br&gt;https://kevinsworkbench.com/junksilverguide&lt;br&gt;https://www.coinflation.com&lt;br&gt;http://coinapps.com&lt;br&gt;https://erikasgrig.com/calculators/rpi-calculator-inflation&lt;br&gt;https://learn.apmex.com/buying-guide/buying-in-the-usa&lt;br&gt;https://pastebin.com/5aLmWUUK&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Prospecting&lt;br&gt;https://youtu.be/ZCL6FKQZyoM &lt;br&gt;https://www.usgs.gov/programs/mineral-resources-program/science&lt;br&gt;https://www.mndm.gov.on.ca/en/news/mines-and-minerals&lt;br&gt;https://www.amazon.ca/Gold-Creeks-Ghostowns-British-Columbia/dp/088839988X&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Nitric acid, magnets, and ping test&lt;br&gt;https://youtu.be/3mg9YcAShTo &lt;br&gt;https://youtu.be/NgSXg-WOEVY &lt;br&gt;https://youtu.be/2ymGAyKAg-k &lt;br&gt;https://www.fakebullion.com/index.php/resources/fake-bullion-database&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Silver Hallmarks Encyclopedia&lt;br&gt;https://www.925-1000.com/&lt;br&gt;https://www.silvercollection.it/hallmarks.html&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Previous thread: &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61852374&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856859&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856852&lt;br&gt;i do 1oz gold : 100oz silver for my stack&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856856&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856852&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;all in on silver&lt;br&gt;i don&amp;#x27;t think we can go wrong with this strategy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856852&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;thought about buying gold. but still going all in on silver&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856848&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856820&lt;br&gt;Andy Schechtman talked about some of this in a recent interview with Maneco64.&lt;br&gt;Apparently, the GENIUS act is part f the US Govt and the Fed Reserve plan to save the US form absolute collapse.&lt;br&gt;Somehow it a way to eventually be able to bring back manufacturing in the long term.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alot of it is still beyond my understanding much if it is unfamiliar to me but its starting to make sense, Andy describes it as &amp;quot;diabolically&amp;quot; clever, maybe evil. but its an option that prevents outright default of US debt.&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t know but it seems like it boils down to devaluing the dollar so much that by the time they have to payout on things like treasury bills, the USD/gold value is such that it is &amp;quot;cheap&amp;quot; to pay off those t-bill debnts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856842&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856819&lt;br&gt;fine, I&amp;#x27;ll grab one or a handful. It&amp;#x27;ll average £85-86 / Britannia. I hope this does moon because I want my father in law to appreciate that I&amp;#x27;m trying more and more to save for his daughter and our kids in future&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856836&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856552&lt;br&gt;Good rant and based.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856820&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856778&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;How the US government or Federal Reserve &amp;quot;values&amp;quot; gold on its books obviously has no effect on the market price of gold at the moment. Disagree?&lt;br&gt;Correct, simply &amp;quot;revaluing&amp;quot; gold on their books is just an accounting trick and does nothing.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m suggesting that the government will effectively devalue the dollar. They&amp;#x27;ve already devalued it from $2000 to $5000. What&amp;#x27;s two more doublings?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It reduces the cost of servicing their debt by 80% and will happen one way or another as Trump wants yield curve control (lowered interest rates) because they can&amp;#x27;t allow the US Treasury long rates to go above 5% of it starts a cascade of a debt spiral.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is NO money in the social security &amp;quot;trust fund&amp;quot; so all the new boomer entitlements need to be covered by money printing.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Much of the government revenue comes from taxes collected from rising equity prices, hence the &amp;quot;Dow 50000&amp;quot; comment. A recession that market corrects, and results in job losses, cuts government revenues while increasing expenditures for supports and stimulus.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We are sailing into a perfect storm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856819&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856816&lt;br&gt;Just pay the tax, silver is going to $500 in 2 weeks according to the coin merchants&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856816&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m going to buy my first coin this week, hopefully today. I just can&amp;#x27;t shake the VAT addition on the coin(s) I want. Would you recommend I go for gold sovereigns instead or should I start on ebay and vinted for some deals on silver here in Britlandistan&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856810&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Good to be here in /pmg/ where we have some chance of sharing and learning important lessons on the history and current state of the system.&lt;br&gt;it gives us a chance to do what we can, in as much as it is in our power to do so, to protect ourselves from the infernal machinations of the robber-baron abomination that continues to rape and pillage in their constant vampire ball.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856787&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856660&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856717&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856721&lt;br&gt;thanks frens&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856786&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856773&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;StoneX Bullion&lt;br&gt;This website is broken right now, still showing silver at 80$ for many days and wrong prices.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856778&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855952&lt;br&gt;How the US government or Federal Reserve &amp;quot;values&amp;quot; gold on its books obviously has no effect on the market price of gold at the moment. Disagree? Try buying gold for $42 an ounce. So what difference would it make if the US government suddenly said &amp;quot;gold is now worth $20,000&amp;quot;? It makes no difference at all UNLESS the US government starts buying gold for that amount. Otherwise it can say gold is worth a gazillion dollars an ounce and nothing changes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856773&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856764&lt;br&gt;Oh nuts that&amp;#x27;s a lot yeah.&lt;br&gt;I like StoneX Bullion, goldsilbershop.de and a few others.&lt;br&gt;Those 2 have low premium options and 20 shipping within the eu.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856764&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856754&lt;br&gt;yes, now it is just 500euro - but shipping costs are ridiculous: 80 euro outside the netherlands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856754&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856738&lt;br&gt;Silver mountain now has a minimum order amount if 2500. Nice to know Hollandgold doesn&amp;#x27;t yet.&lt;br&gt;I hope they let you combine the order.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856753&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856734&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;it&amp;#x27;s been a bi-partisan permissiveness and complicity that has allowed the casino-banking, finance and investment environment that brings us to these situations&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856746&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856534&lt;br&gt;fuck it, I&amp;#x27;ll pay the egregious VAT from the mint and buy silver ounces for £80+. I believe in this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856738&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I made a mistake and made two small orders. The shipping will obligerate my ratio. I hope they are open to combine orders at hollandgold. Otherwise i am screwed. I am retarded&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856737&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855722&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855725&lt;br&gt;steve bannon probably&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856734&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856713&lt;br&gt;yeah, they will each spin it for their own narrative as much as they can. &lt;br&gt;but to hell with Ds and to hell with Rs, it&amp;#x27;s been a bi-partisan permissiveness and complicity that has allowed the casino-banking, finance and investment environment that brings us to these situations&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856730&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855568&lt;br&gt;Waiting for next week, I&amp;#x27;m thinking these kikes are desperate enough to try to smash this down to 60s. Also I&amp;#x27;m still waiting on a shipment from nearly a week and a half ago. They&amp;#x27;re deliberately taking their sweet ass time to process these orders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856721&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856646&lt;br&gt;Cool seeing these coins. Share more anytime.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856717&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856617&lt;br&gt;Cool items:)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856713&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856706&lt;br&gt;Just in time for the mid-terms. Ds are rubbing their hands. Most voters are too dumb to realize that recessions are baked in years before and all the attempts to delay them result in an even worse crash.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Like putting out every little forest fire, dead undergrowth builds up and eventually, there is a much larger, much more destructive fire than would have otherwise happened.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This happened in Yellowstone years ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856706&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855017&lt;br&gt;The collapse is still coming. &lt;br&gt;things that were done leading up to the 2008 crash are happening again.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Urgent Warning From Prof. David Cay Johnston - This Is How It Began Last Time&lt;br&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xL9ZF2fV5do&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856672&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The jew fears Silver&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856660&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856637&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856646&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856640&lt;br&gt;Nice &lt;br&gt;I like bronze&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856657&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;2 more days of stacktards cope and seethe until the next week of cope and seethe .... Lmao&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856646&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856640&lt;br&gt;backside.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I stop now with the spam, i have one last medal from 3.Reich i can post but only if theres a demand for it. Enjoy sunday /pmg/!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded><enclosure url="https://i.4cdn.org/biz/1771105049951580s.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0" /></item><item><title>[AGAIN THE WHAT] Thread 61856830 — 4 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61856830</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61856830</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 13:49:28 +0000</pubDate><description>Open article for full content</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;[AGAIN THE WHAT] Thread 61856830&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61856830'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 4&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;rejected AGAIN&lt;br&gt;WHAT THE FUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUCK&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856851&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;these Asians with hundreds of millions of dollars won&amp;#x27;t stop dumping lol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856841&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856830&lt;br&gt;DO THE BARTMAN&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856839&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856830&lt;br&gt;i tried to tell you retards but you didnt listen&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856834&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856830&lt;br&gt;Eth isnt allowed to pump, sorry!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded><enclosure url="https://i.4cdn.org/biz/1771163368676934s.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0" /></item><item><title>[TV] /smg/ - stock market general — 196 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61853891</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61853891</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 15:28:14 +0000</pubDate><description>Open article for full content</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;[TV] /smg/ - stock market general&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61853891'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 196&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;waifu edition&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Some helpful links to numb the pain&lt;br&gt;https://findahelpline.com/&lt;br&gt;https://www.nvidia.com/refunds/&lt;br&gt;https://www.whitehouse.gov/refunds&lt;br&gt;https://jlingz.com/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Educational sites:&lt;br&gt;https://www.investopedia.com&lt;br&gt;https://www.khanacademy.org/economics-finance-domain&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Financial TV Streams:&lt;br&gt;https://www.newslive.com/american/cnbc.html&lt;br&gt;https://www.livestreamy.net/bloomberg/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Charts:&lt;br&gt;https://www.tradingview.com&lt;br&gt;https://www.finscreener.com&lt;br&gt;https://www.portfoliovisualizer.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Screeners: so you feel like in the movies&lt;br&gt;https://finviz.com/&lt;br&gt;https://etfdb.com/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Gambling:&lt;br&gt;https://www.optionsplaybook.com/options-introduction/&lt;br&gt;https://www.optionsprofitcalculator.com&lt;br&gt;https://optionstrat.com/&lt;br&gt;https://www.optionistics.com/quotes/option-prices&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Pre-Market and Live data:&lt;br&gt;https://www.investing.com/indices/indices-futures&lt;br&gt;https://finance.yahoo.com/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Calendars&lt;br&gt;https://www.marketwatch.com/economy-politics/calendar&lt;br&gt;https://www.earningswhispers.com/calendar&lt;br&gt;https://www.cmegroup.com/trading/interest-rates/countdown-to-fomc.html&lt;br&gt;https://www.mortgagenewsdaily.com/data/building-permits&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Boomer Investing 101: so zoomers with meme stocks can outperform you&lt;br&gt;https://www.bogleheads.org/wiki/Getting_started&lt;br&gt;https://www.sec.gov/search-filings&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Misc smg:&lt;br&gt;https://www.financialjuice.com/home&lt;br&gt;https://finance.yahoo.com/trending-tickers&lt;br&gt;https://market24hclock.com/&lt;br&gt;https://www.dividendchannel.com/drip-returns-calculator&lt;br&gt;https://brokerchooser.com/&lt;br&gt;https://www.chathamfinancial.com/technology/us-market-rates&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Previously on /smg/: &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850998&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856849&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856099&lt;br&gt;DeFi stands for definanced because you lose all your money&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856812&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856782&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m Getting New Income!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856801&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856796&lt;br&gt;Nothing ever happens&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856796&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856564&lt;br&gt;trump is in the files, dumbass.&lt;br&gt;QUICK, SEND OVER ANOTHER NEGOTIATING AIRCRAFT CARRIER!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856783&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;god that is some jewish shit. guaranteed glickman or one of the other usual suspects has some backdoor kike shit going on. this is still incredible theft. easily worth well north of $50. i&amp;#x27;m still getting paid but i almost have half a mind to roll a portion of profit out into december $35 strike calls on the chance institutional ownership swats this shit down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856782&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You Didn&amp;#x27;t Think Neetbux Trader Would Fail Right!??&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856763&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856525&lt;br&gt;THAT&amp;#x27;S IT??!?!?!&lt;br&gt;VOTE IT DOWN&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856703&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856629&lt;br&gt;I am the GAMB &amp;amp; GRRR anon lol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856636&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856630&lt;br&gt;*sniffs you* markit closed silly!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856630&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Let&amp;#x27;s Go Guys Trade Stocks!!!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856629&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856514&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856620&lt;br&gt;what is depressing you guys so much maybe I can help?&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m a nice internet UNC who likes the smell of newfrens&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856625&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856594&lt;br&gt;and they closed their gay loophole for people who have extreme returns&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856623&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856594&lt;br&gt;also when I look closer at this it seems its the same in the nl you can just move it into a company and then pay 25% without the unrealizted gains thing. So I think nl is actually just competing with germany because of the weed legal thing boss&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856620&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sometimes I feel sad about my portfolio, all the while a great bullrun carries me - Ancient Bizraeli saying.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856610&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856594&lt;br&gt;because eternally nothing ever happens&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856609&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856594&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;If this happens to your country, what&amp;#x27;s your out?&lt;br&gt;in my country there would probably be some way arround it kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856594&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s fucked.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Netherlands scenario (B) of 36% tax on unrealized gains is actually equivalent to -50% on annualized returns over a lifetime due to volatility resulting in -75% wealth confiscation over a 40 year period.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If this happens to your country, what&amp;#x27;s your out?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856589&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856573&lt;br&gt;reminder to buy when there is blood in the streets&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;https://youtu.be/Jn-Yrp1PVdw?si=Fxcz_J95VD9wXQXh&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856573&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US stock market is very dead for the next couple weeks (plus).&lt;br&gt;Come Monday I will eject almost the last vestiges after already getting rid of MU, meaning my stupid Take Two, SOFI and MSFT plays (bought the dip -- now realize while they will eventually pay off, it&amp;#x27;s dead capital).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Getting really gooky and nippy in my &amp;#x27;folio.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856564&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856525&lt;br&gt;Israel wins again&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;HE CAN&amp;#x27;T KEEP GETTING AWAY WITH IT&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Also lads, Iran deal is on and Bitcoin computer is mooning I think we&amp;#x27;re all gonna be ok on Taco Tuesday!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856563&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856556&lt;br&gt;they&amp;#x27;re waiting for monday to tank the market&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856556&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;long weekend&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;no big geopolitical event has happened yet&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What the fuck is going on???&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856525&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Congrats ZIM bros, buyout at $29-30 now confirmed apparently.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I bought last summer at $16 waiting for this buyout. I did not hold because I got impatient.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I know some of you have been holding.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856514&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;wow /smg/ is depressing on the weekends&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856500&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856495&lt;br&gt;if only FSLY was public&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856499&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856495&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;think about the deep value of a company full of women&lt;br&gt;Shorting it ON MARGIN&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856497&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;So Let&amp;#x27;s Catch The Robinhood Stack!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856495&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856490&lt;br&gt;it is priced as if it going bankrupt&lt;br&gt;think about the deep value of a company full of women&lt;br&gt;they can just upload pictures of themselves and there you go the company is profitable again&lt;br&gt;checkmate&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;https://youtu.be/uU-XtwUa4No?si=5DvJbbU35WIiCeCV&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856494&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855204&lt;br&gt;The 20k allowance resets every year in April. So you&amp;#x27;ve got like 2 months to fill another 15k. Then your allowance is reset and you can put in another 20k for the new tax year. Repeat over a few years, plus growth from the investments, and you can be sitting on a pretty big pile that is all tax free.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856490&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856489&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;they are the company with the most women working there&lt;br&gt;brb full port shorting it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded><enclosure url="https://i.4cdn.org/biz/1771082894968487s.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0" /></item><item><title>[AI] Thread 61856385 — 3 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61856385</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61856385</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 09:14:15 +0000</pubDate><description>Open article for full content</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;[AI] Thread 61856385&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61856385'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 3&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;/biz/ bros how is AI going to effect the logging industry?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856823&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856385&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;effect&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856559&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;did someone say log?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856475&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856385&lt;br&gt;Humanoids replace humans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded><enclosure url="https://i.4cdn.org/biz/1771146855189243s.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0" /></item><item><title>[BTC CIA NSA] Professor Jian says Bitcoin is CIA — 13 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61856632</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61856632</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 12:10:28 +0000</pubDate><description>Open article for full content</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;[BTC CIA NSA] Professor Jian says Bitcoin is CIA&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61856632'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 13&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Been listening to this asian nigga for a while, he&amp;#x27;s now saying that BTC is CIA or NSA project.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The anonymity and &amp;quot;store of value&amp;quot; would benefit them greatly while permitting them to spy economies like North Korea&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856821&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856632&lt;br&gt;Its not just bitcoin, &amp;quot;every crypto&amp;quot; is back door&amp;#x27;d by the spooks.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8QdCvssobis&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856818&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856632&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;BTC is CIA or NSA project.&lt;br&gt;Yeah no shit&lt;br&gt;Are you willing to bet against the american empire thought? I think it still has a couple of centuries in it, so I&amp;#x27;m investing in it&amp;#x27;s scams.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856813&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856757&lt;br&gt;he has some good thoughts im ngl, i assume he teaches at a chinese private school. to give him the benefit of the doubt..&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;germany was the most advanced civilization the world has ever known.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;teh lectures on the divine comedy&lt;br&gt;learned some new stuff from those i thought it was good...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856809&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856632&lt;br&gt;This was well known on /biz/ 10 years ago&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What has this board become&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856775&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856659&lt;br&gt;Definitely. Answer yourself this: what could a government&amp;#x27;s incentive be to ban 1 cryptocurrency (monero) over the other?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856757&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856728&lt;br&gt;He clearly spent too much time on the chinese version of /x/. How he got a job teaching children i dont know. Still entertaining to watch though.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856728&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;this retard has so many fucking inaccuracies and fails to qualify his claims. hes a chinaman who was raised in canada, who went to yale. its like he is the mouth peace for kosher critical thinking.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;race was invented by europeans during colonialism&lt;br&gt;dna disproves this&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;all of roman history is fictitious and propaganda&lt;br&gt;same could be said for any ancient source especially china&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;the jews are hated because haters gonna hate, nobles need someone to blame etc&lt;br&gt;milk toast intellectual who thinks he reads between the lines, yet has a very surface layer understanding of the social underpinnings of power movement and how they work.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;also, crypto isn&amp;#x27;t something you should be investing in, this has been well known for a while. trade futures&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856675&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;who gives a fuck as long as it makes money&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856671&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856632&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The entire financial system of the planet is a Hebrew project on goys. We already know this dumbass. No need to split hairs with BTC etc.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856659&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is Monero the way? I don&amp;#x27;t even know where to put my hard earned vbucks anymore&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856651&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856632&lt;br&gt;so, much like the Internet?&lt;br&gt;Cool, Thank you, CIA (or NSA)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856649&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856632&lt;br&gt;Wait until you learn about how the internet was invented, FUDboy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856648&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Epstein had a role in making it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded><enclosure url="https://i.4cdn.org/biz/1771157428316382s.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0" /></item><item><title>[NFT] Thread 61855938 — 8 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61855938</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61855938</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 04:48:37 +0000</pubDate><description>Open article for full content</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;[NFT] Thread 61855938&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61855938'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 8&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Non-/biz/ here, forgive the potentially retarded question. When NFTs were being hyped up as being this revolutionary advancement in...something, there were often claims that owning an NFT of a particular kind or value would enable the holder to access benefits from it essentially in perpetuity. Obviously no one gives three-fifths of a fuck about NFTs these days, but even during their heyday was anything like that claim realized?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;vaguely /biz/ placeholder pic&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856808&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855938&lt;br&gt;in short - yes. either from a check built into a smart contract, a merkle tree compiled from NFT owners at a certain blockheight, or simply a signature from a wallet holding the NFT.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856244&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855938&lt;br&gt;I come from professional digital art. NFTs were puzzling from the start. We had been selling digital rights via contract for years for free, so the idea of paying for a NFT.. a jpg with no space for PSD data. Seemed absolutely retarded. Only desperate talentless hacks and grifters fell for it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856238&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855958&lt;br&gt;Pretty sure BAYC had exclusive events and gifts sent for holders. Somehow I doubt getting to wear an &amp;quot;exclusive&amp;quot; ape hoodie at a club with your fellow nftfags was worth the investment&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855965&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855938&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t understand what her text means. Did he use her underwear to wipe his ass and then dropped it off at her dorm or was it always at her dorm&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855959&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855938&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;my&lt;br&gt;why did she shit herself&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855958&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855938&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;owning an NFT of a particular kind or value would enable the holder to access benefits from it essentially in perpetuity.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Benefits like what?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855943&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855938&lt;br&gt;No, it was the most obvious scam ever and anyone who bought an nft is a retard&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded><enclosure url="https://i.4cdn.org/biz/1771130917252363s.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0" /></item><item><title>[NEW SET TCG] TCG General - NEW SET — 22 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61851061</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61851061</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:07:07 +0000</pubDate><description>Open article for full content</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;[NEW SET TCG] TCG General - NEW SET&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61851061'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 22&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;day 352 of growing my charizard collection till it hits $1mil&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;would do you think of Ascended Heroes, flop or gigainvestible?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856806&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856736&lt;br&gt;If semen isn’t your thing there are other variants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856736&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855394&lt;br&gt;what is there to love about this card it looks like a semen kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855394&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853401&lt;br&gt;Just do a competitive classic at least rare in value that people will always remember fondly. Liliana, tarmogoyf, titan, Thalia. People also love lands. Classic dual lands are almost always going to retain value. Personally, if it was me, I would collect Narcomoeba even though it’s uncommon because I love that card and I love dredge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855364&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854870&lt;br&gt;congrats, yeah trade it for some pokemon booster boxes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855029&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851929&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;ve only bought/opened 1 booster box in my life and I got the best card. &lt;br&gt;When I looked at the massive stack of bulk off to the side the sense of waste was unreal and that was the last time I ever did that even though I won.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854870&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854259&lt;br&gt;Yup, both natty pulls&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854259&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854111&lt;br&gt;nice did you pull them both?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854152&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854113&lt;br&gt;Amazing mtg went from this to your pic in less than 30 years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854125&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854113&lt;br&gt;I showed this card to a huge LotR fan friend of mine and he thought it was a meme and looked ready to blow his brains out when I told him it was real&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854113&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853401&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854111&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Think I&amp;#x27;m going to sell these for a quick buck&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853544&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853401&lt;br&gt;good plan anon i dont play MTG but wish you well on your hoarding journey&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853510&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853421&lt;br&gt;I would like to evade Universes Beyond garbage, because i hate it with every fiber of my body.&lt;br&gt;PREFERABLY i would like to dig in some older sets, when MTG was good, find some 25 cent rare and invest couple hundreds in buying it.&lt;br&gt;Surely someone on /biz? actually plays MTG constructed or EDH and can share his wisdom about what card is terribly under priced in his opinion&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853421&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853401&lt;br&gt;one of the sonic or spiderman cards as they also have autistic fanbases&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853401&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I want to do some degen gambling and by hundreds (thousands preferably) of a single Magic the gathering card.&lt;br&gt;What cards would you guys suggest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853355&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853087&lt;br&gt;prismatic booster bundles &amp;amp; etbs, also surging sparks booster boxes (as think they reprinted recently right so price is low?)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853087&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thinking about going all in on Prismatic sealed&lt;br&gt;Maybe some destined rivals, surging sparks, and paldea evolved&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gonna research one piece aswell&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What do you guys think is the most sure/safe investment to get a 2X over the next year or 2?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851929&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;why am i such a retard why do i rip sealed product why am i such an idiot gambler i&amp;#x27;m down $3500 this month just fucking give me good cards pleaseeeeeee&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851697&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851653&lt;br&gt;3000 zards so far, $50k probs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851653&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851061&lt;br&gt;How many zards do you have and what is your total price paid?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851119&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851085&lt;br&gt;sold my only 151 upc for $400 six months ago rip&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851085&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some joker is listing a single 151 UPC for $450 plus $200 shipping. With that being said my price target is where Celebrations UPC’s are now ($1000 a box)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded><enclosure url="https://i.4cdn.org/biz/1771016827761692s.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0" /></item><item><title>[BCH] Thread 61855284 — 3 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61855284</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61855284</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 23:17:34 +0000</pubDate><description>Open article for full content</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;[BCH] Thread 61855284&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61855284'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 3&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cardanofags Keke&amp;#x27;d by BCH. Finally this shitcoin got outed of the top10.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856803&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BCH is nice. Cheap to transfer, nice privacy features (though not even remotely close to XMR), smart contracts on chain for hedging and leverage trading it, accepted almost everywhere BTC is accepted.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It used to have a much better community of devs at some point but the stability it has now also has its merits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855345&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855284&lt;br&gt;it was at 12 for few weeks and has been out of 10 for over a month.&lt;br&gt;you slow or something?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855331&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;both these trash dead projects should be out of the top 200&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded><enclosure url="https://i.4cdn.org/biz/1771111054273158s.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0" /></item></channel></rss>