<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>/biz/ Active (filtered, with replies)</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/</link><description>Filtered out: general, gme, bbbyq. OP + first 3 replies + last 30 replies.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 15:17:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>IMF calls on China to cut industrial subsidies in half — 124 replies — 496.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61872964</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61872964?lm=1771686646</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 15:10:46 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;IMF calls on China to cut industrial subsidies in half&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61872964'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 124 • Updated: 2026-02-21 15:10 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872971&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872964&lt;br&gt;This is a strategic move by the Chinese to kill off the competition in other countries so the Chinese companies can dominate the sectors and then raise the prices&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872974&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;i&amp;#x27;m sure china will get right on that&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872978&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;jews mad&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872971&lt;br&gt;they can do it forever without raising the prices&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878126&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878121&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;/pol/tard word salad gibberish complete with the &amp;quot;hyperinflation&amp;quot; meme word&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878133&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878126&lt;br&gt;Wumao&lt;br&gt;China is dead and has been for the better part of 13 years. All the corruption and attempts to paint over the political and economic failures are now coming home all at the same time. There won&amp;#x27;t be a &amp;quot;people&amp;quot; &amp;#x27;republic&amp;#x27; of China by 2030&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878137&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878133&lt;br&gt;I think you&amp;#x27;re Indian.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878138&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878133&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;more /pol/tard word salad gibberish complete with foreign language pejorative meme word&lt;br&gt;if i had to guess: IQ ~80, GED or &amp;#x27;cyber high school&amp;#x27;, has never read a book in his life, career in manual labor for a wage between $18/hour and $22/hour.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878148&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878137&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878138&lt;br&gt;Wumaos &lt;br&gt;When the checks stop coming you gone. The rest of the country is going to slaughter you&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878155&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878148&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;When the checks stop coming you gone&lt;br&gt;Confirmed Indian&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878160&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878155&lt;br&gt;Wumao, who do you think is first going to be rationalized away? You or chair man chang? You gonna die chink&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878162&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878109&lt;br&gt;They made a bet that reaching out infrastructure to the hundreds of millions of people of low-productivity regions could improve domestic demand to the extent that their subsidies start to be consumed internally. The problem is that the low-productivity areas are, of course, low income and the only two options which exist to them are:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Direct UBI for low-income areas&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Creating even more highly subsidized factories to employ low-income people and give them a better wage&lt;br&gt;Honestly for them the UBI route is likely more cost-effective, to avoid further deflating the value of the plants they already have. The 3rd (much) more challenging and expensive option would be to migrate the sweat-shops and low-skill factories out to the countryside from bigger city centers and reassign the existing factories to high-tech, high-skill plants such as chip foundries and advanced component manufacturing. To a certain extent they&amp;#x27;re being forced into this already due to sanctions etc on high-end chips, but if it&amp;#x27;s their primary gameplan then it&amp;#x27;s progressing way too slowly. Modernizing a billion people (bugs) is a hell of a project&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878168&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878160&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;re stinking up the thread.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878171&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878162&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;UBI&lt;br&gt;That&amp;#x27;s the funny part, the polity as the bureaucracy as the socialist &amp;quot;billionaire&amp;quot; bastards that rely on the continuation of the sovereign bond ponzis are going to hang on the same gallows&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878316&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878171&lt;br&gt;Are you ESL? I feel like I got schizophrenia just from reading your post&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880069&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874731&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;17% of the US population who are hooked on SSRIs get their supplies cut off, along with the active ingredients we buy from them for everything else. We lost the bio-warfare game before it even began.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880124&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875629&lt;br&gt;Everything done by a government can be construed as being a subsidy&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Good infrastructure is a subsidy&lt;br&gt;Skilled workforce is a subsidy&lt;br&gt;Low crime rate is a subsidy&lt;br&gt;Friendly regulatory environment is a subsidy&lt;br&gt;Low cost of living for employees is a subsidy&lt;br&gt;Ease of worker relocation and efficient job matching is a subsidy&lt;br&gt;Low taxes due to government thrift is a subsidy&lt;br&gt;Etc&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880265&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873120&lt;br&gt;On the world though? Also where would China be without Amazon and Walmart like worse than Thailand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880291&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875302&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;If a basket of various goods in the US goes for 100 dollars and that same basket of goods in Vietnam goes for 10 dollars (ALL ELSE BEING EQUAL), then a fair exchange rate would be 10 dong for one dollar&lt;br&gt;That is a made up rule. There is no fundamental reason for why 1 dong should have the same purchasing power as 1 dollar. Currency units are just made up. Vietnam could introduce a new currency superunit called the bong, say 1 bong is equal to 25,970 dong and also that 1 bong is equal to 1 dollar. That would satisfy your rule while also de facto maintaining the current exchange rate.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is a natural reason for why the basket is cheaper in dollar terms in Vietnam, which is the Balassa-Samuelson effect&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;There’s a reason why economists or even someone casually interested in the economy and trade policy use these terms.&lt;br&gt;Yes, because they are shills trying to find arguments for why China should make Chinese companies less competitive and/or arguments for why tariffs should be imposed against China. It&amp;#x27;s really all just to protect the profits of domestic companies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880312&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880291&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;say 1 bong is equal to 25,970 dong and also that 1 bong is equal to 1 dollar.&lt;br&gt;*say 1 bong is equal to 2,597 dong and also that 10 bong are equal to 1 dollar&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880533&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880291&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;my rule &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;it’s literally just the most basic economics&lt;br&gt;Listen, I can’t explain exchange rates to you any more than I already have. Believe whatever you want. If you want to believe that exchange rates do not affect exporters or importers, go for it. It’s of no consequence to me if you sound retarded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880545&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880069&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;leftists kill themselves en masse after their meds run out leading to a 100 year Republican dynasty&lt;br&gt;Still not seeing the downside&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880558&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880545&lt;br&gt;The downside is that the mentally sound people are not going to just off themselves. They are going to take it out on everyone around them like they normally do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880563&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880558&lt;br&gt;mentally ill*&lt;br&gt;Ultimately its going to be an improvement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880603&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880533&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s not &amp;quot;basic economics&amp;quot;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fiat currency units are arbitrary. Fiat currencies have no inherent or fair value because they aren&amp;#x27;t tied to anything real.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;If you want to believe that exchange rates do not affect exporters or importers&lt;br&gt;That&amp;#x27;s not what I was saying&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880653&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880603&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875302&lt;br&gt;Again, a currency does not have to have an underlying physical asset in order to have value in relation to something else. I’m not sure why you think it does. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is not my pet theory. It’s just basic economics. Just look into Purchasing Power Parity, and if you don’t get it, that’s fine. Again, you can believe whatever you want. I’ve done my due diligence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880707&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Give it to me straight: Has China already won? It seems to be doing better than the west.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880739&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880653&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m not saying a fiat currency can&amp;#x27;t have value relative to something else. I&amp;#x27;m saying it does not have an inherent or fair value, and therefore it cannot be undervalued or overvalued. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;When I said a fiat currency is not tied to anything real, I meant that it&amp;#x27;s not backed by anything real fixed at any specific predetermined ratio. I did not mean that it cannot be exchanged for anything real.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m familiar with PPP, and there is no reason why it should be the exchange rate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880750&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873505&lt;br&gt;currency you nigger, currency, not money.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880812&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880739&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; I&amp;#x27;m saying it does not have an inherent or fair value, and therefore it cannot be undervalued or overvalued.&lt;br&gt;It can be in relation to something else. &lt;br&gt;If one dong can buy a bicycle in Vietnam, and a dollar can buy a bicycle in the US, and this 1:1 ratio roughly carries across a multitude of good, and Vietnam’s nominal exchange rate for USD is 100:1, the currency is undervalued. It is worth much more than the nominal exchange rate suggests. Its real value *in relation to the US dollar* is higher than its nominal value. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; there is no reason why it should be the exchange rate.&lt;br&gt;It is not the exchange rate. It is a factor in the exchange rate. The reason makes sense. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is important to understand that we are talking about managed exchange rates here, and it’s much more obvious in these examples. Many economists also think that currencies can be undervalued/overvalued even if both currencies float freely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880827&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872964&lt;br&gt;As if China will give a shit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880935&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880707&lt;br&gt;Yes, considering where all the gold and silver is going.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882682&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872964&lt;br&gt;Jews have no power in China&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883413&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What is even supposed to be illegal about a government subsidizing a critical infrastructure industry and innovation?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;government spends trillion dollars on nigger welfare with negative ROI&lt;br&gt;or&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;government spends trillion on energy, housing, vehicles with long term national benefits&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;who the fuck decides what a country can spend their tax income from?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Fake and Gay Economy — 67 replies — 268.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61871520</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61871520?lm=1771686535</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 15:08:55 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Fake and Gay Economy&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61871520'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 67 • Updated: 2026-02-21 15:08 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;When will this gay as economy finally collapse and how can i profit from it?&lt;br&gt;Its ridiculous the woman at our workplace contribute nothing to the company and make more money than i do&lt;br&gt;Its infuriating we just had a bunch of lay offs and we lost some of oir best workers but somehow a bunch of HR shits who do nothing all day still work here&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871530&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HR is a necessary function, chud&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871569&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871530&lt;br&gt;For what?&lt;br&gt;Genuinely why do we need it to this extent?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871755&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871569&lt;br&gt;Protect the corp from lawsuits&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873324&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873293&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Almost all women working provide value&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873510&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871569&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;re either trolling or never worked a day in your life,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873611&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871931&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873193&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Fake and Gay&lt;br&gt;Why is are Schizos always using that phrase? I instantly know there is a schizo take coming when i read this. Some schizo takes are interesting, some are even good, some are good to think through and some are just funny to read. But they stzill are schizo takes and mostly bullshit influeces too much by wish bias. So how and where did this phrase pick up with schizos. When i know, its around 2021/2022 when the schizo&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;economy will collapse and people will starve due to lockdowns&lt;br&gt;did not materialize. Then they started with this phrase to somehow save their prediction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873806&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872076&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;no less than three seething replies about muh real capitalism&lt;br&gt;If you abolished the state it would be reinvented by the wealthy overnight&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873944&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873611&lt;br&gt;Fake and gay was in use when I 1st started using this site in 2011.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873988&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;Hopefully never because I have a fake overpaid job, just not in HR&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876439&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872064&lt;br&gt;And prevent White women from breeding&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877263&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;everyone wants to be rich without doing jack shit, jews are just more succesful at the game and more honest about what the game is, maybe because they invented it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;there are less and less people talking about &amp;#x27;&amp;#x27;value&amp;#x27;&amp;#x27; in a real way, no one believes in it, no one believes that value is real or there is merit to providing it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;everything is about winning or losing, and brother let me tell you, I&amp;#x27;m not gonna be one of the cucks who focuses on helping society or building when I can make my money sitting in my computer and playing the money game, the money game is more fun and rewarding than going to medical or engineering school.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877287&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;go in to interview for a technical role&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;see vidrel being filmed in the hallway on your way in&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;the job pays well&lt;br&gt;wat do?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877298&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872085&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872087&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872233&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872278&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;REAL capitalism has never been tried&lt;br&gt;This is real capitalism, and it&amp;#x27;s retarded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878294&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871569&lt;br&gt;Because human beings(the goyim) is just another resources that the &amp;#x27;choosen ones&amp;#x27; can exploid.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878310&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877287&lt;br&gt;call them a bunch of FAG KIKE TRANNIES and instead get a based n&amp;#x27; trad job shoveling horse shit for $14.35/hour with no health insurance&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878355&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878294&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;human beings&lt;br&gt;its the best asset you can own, they work, (produce free goods) they pay taxes(fake money holds value), they eat poison food and get sick, then forced to consume overpriced drugs(more profits), there is no stock that can make better return over lifetime and asset(the goy) is free.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878449&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873611&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Why is are Schizos always using that phrase?&lt;br&gt;In zoomer lingo, it&amp;#x27;s copium. They are losers who can&amp;#x27;t cut it. Naturally, they are not the problem and anyone who does great in the current system is cheating (hence fake and gay).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;These types would be losers under any system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878715&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871931&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;They don’t actually do nothing &lt;br&gt;These retarded whores are of no value to society work force.&lt;br&gt;They can not weld , machine, approve engineering drawings or balance the company finances or protect them f taxes.&lt;br&gt;All they do is prevent men from building modern day Rome.&lt;br&gt;Go back to plebbit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878722&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;Are they dancing because nobody replied to their emails and they have nothing to do or are they bragging about not replying to emails?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879023&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878715&lt;br&gt;If they didn&amp;#x27;t provide value they wouldn&amp;#x27;t be there. The reality is that HR prevents the company from getting sued out of existence. If you want to hate HR, that is valid but just know that hate should be reflected to the legal system that allows for the company to be sued. Yes they prevent men from being men and are only there to protect women&amp;#x27;s feelings but guess what women&amp;#x27;s feelings are what the legal system is currently based on with shit like abortion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882397&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873944&lt;br&gt;Really? Hm ok&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878449&lt;br&gt;I dont quite get how you see this? You say not cheating is loser tier?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882408&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;know a fat art hoe with an Art History degree&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;before she began selling pics of her huge tits online and streaming herself playing videogames, she was working remotely in Operations (HR) at an office&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I got a liberal arts degree in pre-law, aiming to be a lawyer&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;constantly see dopey bitches get accepted to their law schools of choice, I was not and no one would hire me to paralegal or legal assistant roles either despite demonstrating superior knowledge of the law, only roasties&lt;br&gt;I wouldn&amp;#x27;t mind the fake and gay, if it wasn&amp;#x27;t explicitly directed towards fucking over as many men as possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882442&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873611&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;fake&lt;br&gt;rooted in make-believe&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;gay&lt;br&gt;You are a faggot if you believe it, or even want to believe it&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For example, space is fake and gay. It&amp;#x27;s fake because it&amp;#x27;s built around unfalsifiable, circular reasoning &amp;quot;science&amp;quot; with no anchor to the real world. It&amp;#x27;s gay because you are a spiritual homosexual if you think Star Trek is something to aspire to. Thus, space is fake and gay.&lt;br&gt;Nukes are fake and gay because the bombs do not exist and cannot exist (fake), and gay because thinking you live in a world where you are scared a jew can push a button and wipe out a city is inherently pathetic and homosexual. &lt;br&gt;The modern workplace is fake and gay, because the work isn&amp;#x27;t actual work it&amp;#x27;s role-play daycare for adults. And it&amp;#x27;s gay because it&amp;#x27;s a system that empowers women above all, turning all males into low T cucks instead of productive men who build real shit with their hands and have real accomplishments. They make you pretend to work then pay you with fake money conjured out of thin air by jews running the banks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882487&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871569&lt;br&gt;because the line need to go UP even if you burn half of the World for it, that&amp;#x27;s modern capitalism&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882495&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871931&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882506&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873181&lt;br&gt;underrated&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882519&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871937&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;HR is a reflection of fake and gay legal system.&lt;br&gt;I run my own business and thats why i&amp;#x27;d never want to hire anyone.&lt;br&gt;I can&amp;#x27;t wait until AI and robots become advanced enough that i can just have robots as my employees that help me with my tasks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882601&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882495&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t get it. It doesn&amp;#x27;t make me mad but I don&amp;#x27;t understand what are they saying and why. It&amp;#x27;s just some retards flailing.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In fact this type of dance could be performed by Chris Chan and it would not look out of place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882608&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882495&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882869&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871530&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871569&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871755&lt;br&gt;Our HR manager is the local cum dumpster. Even I&amp;#x27;ve dumped my nerdy incel load in her pussy a few times.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883066&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879023&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;If they didn&amp;#x27;t provide value they wouldn&amp;#x27;t be there.&lt;br&gt;75% or more of white collar work literally does nothing, roasties or not.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883243&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;Did they fire itty bitty titties &amp;amp; a bob?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883399&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;When there is an alternative for the money and people to pour over into.&lt;br&gt;Fagmerica&amp;#x27;s slow decline relies on everywhere else being shittier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>the US is in recession — 58 replies — 232.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61869320</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61869320?lm=1771686926</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 15:15:26 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;the US is in recession&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61869320'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 58 • Updated: 2026-02-21 15:15 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;the US is in recession&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869343&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869320&lt;br&gt;doomed fag nation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869350&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Adjust by population&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869389&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bump&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874552&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I am one of those assholes. But then again, I pull like 290k. Make that paper bitch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876139&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869320&lt;br&gt;Has nothing to do with making ends meet and everything to do with shitty spending habits&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876213&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869507&lt;br&gt;Don&amp;#x27;t forget the people that sign up for two WFH positions and fake their way through both.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876310&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61876213&lt;br&gt;Stop talking about me. I made a small fortune in the past 5 years doing this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876386&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869320&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;this is insane&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;less than 1% of the population is working more than one full-time position&lt;br&gt;Okay. Personally I&amp;#x27;m interviewing for a second job just because I want more money.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876391&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870855&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870872&lt;br&gt;Yeah we should be like Obama and just accept that jobs will never return. It takes time to improve things so don&amp;#x27;t ever try, silly goy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876412&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;the cope itt is crazy. it hurts to watch a once-great nation falling apart in denial.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876435&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China will take over as world superpower&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876558&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870808&lt;br&gt;this is like those 5&amp;#x27;11&amp;quot; vs 6&amp;#x27; memes &lt;br&gt;holy shit, they cannot be serious&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876562&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870808&lt;br&gt;How bad is it if this is the good news damn&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876847&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869320&lt;br&gt;I have talked to retarded job hogs proud of being exploited. Seriously you can&amp;#x27;t ask for a raise and give me one of your jobs? Then you mock me for failing to get a job? You are hogging 2 jobs. If you didn&amp;#x27;t work 2 jobs there would be room for unemployed people to have jobs too. Boomer X fuckers still don&amp;#x27;t get it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877134&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870808&lt;br&gt;I hope you’re trolling&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877277&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869343&lt;br&gt;as long as wagies keep waging, it aint doomed nigga&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877309&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869320&lt;br&gt;People are working two or more jobs and you call this recession? Fucking hilarious&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877311&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61876310&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61876213&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;SING UP FOR&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;like places are just a great volunteer association and not a rigorous shittest from hr.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877894&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869507&lt;br&gt;There are 7 days a week anon. If you consider a 40 hour week a full time job, then an 80 hour week is two full time jobs. That&amp;#x27;s under 12 hours a day, every day. Plus commutes to the two jobs, you are out of home 13 to 14 hours. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61876213&lt;br&gt;99% larpers, 1% get caught after on-boarding period&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61876139&lt;br&gt;Other than fast food, I doubt people who work 80 hour weeks even have time to spend their money on bullshit. They probably just shower and collapse to bed at the end of the day. My bet is that they are paying a mortgage or have an incapacitated spouse or parent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877899&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;if the US is in recession, why did Doordash just have it&amp;#x27;s biggest ever jump in orders?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878363&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869517&lt;br&gt;I cant imagine working more than 50 hours a week, tf is wrong with americans? Working 70 hours a week to buy an oilguzzler to commute to work? Living in the sterile suburbs? Tossing a coin everytime a negro passes you on the street? What is even the point of all that?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878371&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872563&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880061&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877899&lt;br&gt;People can&amp;#x27;t afford cars, and there&amp;#x27;s a decline in driver&amp;#x27;s license applications. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;And Increased senior population demand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880092&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878363&lt;br&gt;to enrich uncle sam at the small cost of every waking minute of your life&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880116&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878363&lt;br&gt;I work 100+ hours plus just to not get evicted by my corporate landlord. My rent is $4,000 a month. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boomers here opose affordable housing because it&amp;#x27;s gonna hurt their home values. But fuck me I guess.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880131&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878363&lt;br&gt;Forgot screenshot&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880323&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869320&lt;br&gt;What a perfect moment for the Democrats to rule against receiving free money from the rest of the world because we are all pinky friends and we all love each other&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880329&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870808&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Pro Trump post in a fag infested board&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anon...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880446&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880323&lt;br&gt;Explain?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882513&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880131&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;d just kill myself. I don&amp;#x27;t see you wagies as human.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883379&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869320&lt;br&gt;All this effort to pay off loans from jews.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883410&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878363&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I cant imagine working more than 0 hours a week&lt;br&gt;ftfy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883424&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870808&lt;br&gt;A lot of business is booming better than this. There&amp;#x27;s been a 300% increase of day cares in Minnesota. Golden age baby&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>CRYPTO IS DEAD — 15 replies — 60.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61880718</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61880718?lm=1771686518</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 15:08:38 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;CRYPTO IS DEAD&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61880718'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 15 • Updated: 2026-02-21 15:08 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Crypto is dead. So I&amp;#x27;m looking into buying again, maybe lump sum maybe DCA. What do you think, anons? Some think that the bear market is just starting so maybe it&amp;#x27;s better to wait... but idk, the sentiment seems rather depressed already. Anyone else also accumulating rn or ar you waiting for october? Alts or BTC?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880730&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;rn&lt;br&gt;Tiktok negrobabble gets your thread filtered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880848&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880730&lt;br&gt;You answered tho?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881053&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880718&lt;br&gt;all other macro bottoms took several months of crabbing before the markets went up again, we havent done that yet&lt;br&gt;probably better to wait it out and only deploy capital when its clear the trend has shifted&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;like last macro bottom in late 2022, if you waited till conformation you bought at 18k instead of 16k, a marginal difference&lt;br&gt;i&amp;#x27;ll assume that nobody actually nabbed the 60k bottom here for how short it was&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881059&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881053&lt;br&gt;My fear is that the bull run was kinda front runned so what if the bear is also like that, leading to a shorer bear market&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881187&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881059&lt;br&gt;very reasonable assumption but again wait for the turn&lt;br&gt;unless you believe the snap back up will be violent, which is hard to do with sentiment this bad&lt;br&gt;even on the fakest V-est of v-dips during corona you had a good while to buy at 4k&lt;br&gt;and like i said you already missed the 60k window&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881266&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880718&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;ve been DCAing for that past two months. My instinct tells me this year is going to be really bad for crypto. Lots of crashing, crabbing, doom and gloom. So I&amp;#x27;ll slurp up as much bloody water as I can and hope that in the next few years we either finish collapsing or I&amp;#x27;m incredibly wealthy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881505&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880718&lt;br&gt;I voted for this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883131&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881187&lt;br&gt;That&amp;#x27;s not true, pic related is the covid dip. You had a total of 5 days at 5k, then it started a pretty steep recovery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883135&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881266&lt;br&gt;Pretty much this, except things will probably turn suddenly when CLARITY passes in a month or 2&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883290&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880718&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883374&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883135&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Polity is going to make my bag go line up&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;BUY MY BAG NOW&lt;br&gt;no&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883380&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;btc behaves like a more volatile leveraged spy. I thought the whole idea is crypto being a hedge against fiat and being decentralized. now american companies like mstr and blackrock own huge chunks and the whole crypto movement depends on american regulations. I dont own crypto and I never will. Everyone still being heavily into crypto at this moment must be desperate as fuck otherwise I dont get it. Last 5 years btc couldnt even outperform the s&amp;amp;p lol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883384&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883380&lt;br&gt;Everyone being into ponzi asset, including every single ponzi paper in the spx is desperate &lt;br&gt;You can&amp;#x27;t print yourself out of a demographic deflation. Your advertising is futile&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883390&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880718&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Polkadot crypto&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;https://www.figment.io/insights/polkadots-dynamic-allocation-pool-dap-an-evolution-in-issuance-and-staking/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883398&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883390&lt;br&gt;Go advertise somewhere else freak jeet/chink&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Nerva — 3 replies — 12.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61883377</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61883377?lm=1771686605</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 15:10:05 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Nerva&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61883377'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 3 • Updated: 2026-02-21 15:10 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;CPU-only privacy coin from 2018 that refuses to die.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;No GPUs, ASICs or Pools&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Truly decentralized&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Network hashrate steadily growing 400-500KH/s&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Relisted on Nonkyc and CEXSwap&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;New GUI wallet update coming soon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883381&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fuck off ad bot&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883400&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883381&lt;br&gt;that&amp;#x27;s a no from me dawg&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883409&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883377&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;tripple dubs&lt;br&gt;Nerva is here to stay&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;No additional replies in the latest window.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Bro just give me 50 stocks to shotgun I will literally build a balanced portfolio of all your posts ITT. — 64 replies — 28.4/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61874540</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61874540?lm=1771678921</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 13:02:01 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Bro just give me 50 stocks to shotgun I will literally build a balanced portfolio of all your posts ITT.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61874540'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 64 • Updated: 2026-02-21 13:02 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bro just give me 50 stocks to shotgun I will literally build a balanced portfolio of all your posts ITT. Dont repost tickers. Trips I&amp;#x27;ll buy 5x the amount. This is a financial experiment, not a shill thread. /biz/ should outperform the market. No cryptos. Go&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874568&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I dont own many individual stocks here are the ones i have:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;GLEN SHELL MDT DHR ISRG RHM BRK.B RR. FCX IYAA NOV GOOG YAR IFX ROK LGEN boeing VOW SNPS TSLA AMBA SNPS SYM RKLB AVAV OUST CRCL&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874578&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874540&lt;br&gt;uhm, Accenture&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874612&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874578&lt;br&gt;looks good!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881271&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This would have been a good thread so I can&amp;#x27;t believe faggot OP abandoned it.&lt;br&gt;Someone copy paste the thread into an AI tool and tell it to spit back the first 50 unique stock tickers and post it along with the cost to build an equal weighted ETF style portfolio out of those 50 stocks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881300&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874540&lt;br&gt;GME&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881321&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KLAR FIG JD WDAY&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881322&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Clorox&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881336&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874540&lt;br&gt;NAK&lt;br&gt;very good opportunity to buy, the EPA response is not at it seems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881768&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878135&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;sun is in front of the clouds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881844&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881768&lt;br&gt;You are right; I was too busy ogling curvy Amelia and thinking of saving the white race and sending pajeets back to notice&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881982&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881844&lt;br&gt;if only she was real&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882019&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881271&lt;br&gt;Im here, I&amp;#x27;m busy this weekend . I am 100% building the portfolio&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882026&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;we have great and balanced suggestions I just need to compile it. I will vacuum the trash value stocks. Just need to compile and weight. and like I said I didn&amp;#x27;t want to buy today because of a high possibility of weekend shenanigans&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882029&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882026&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I will vacuum the trash value stocks&lt;br&gt; I&amp;#x27;ll include falling knives I mean but with appropriate size&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882149&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874540&lt;br&gt;ARMP (Armata Pharmaceuticals)&lt;br&gt;You’re welcome&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882160&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WPM and TTWO. For the latter it now looks bad, but wait when Gta6 hits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882255&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BMXI&lt;br&gt;OMQS&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882490&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882026&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882029&lt;br&gt;AI can do this in like 8 seconds, just paste the whole thread and tell it what to do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882730&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882490&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882735&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882730&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882736&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882735&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882740&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882736&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882747&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882740&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;pick abroad index fund TO AVOID slop&lt;br&gt;Costanza&lt;br&gt;Anon can’t into getting the most out of a Jewish LLM&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882767&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882740&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882736&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882735&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882730&lt;br&gt;You are an incredibly incompetent person.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;TICKER | SHARES | TOTAL DOLLAR COST&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AEM | 6 | $901. (≈6×150.38)&lt;br&gt;AMBA | 8 | $903. (≈8×112.94)&lt;br&gt;AMZN | 4 | $840. (≈4×210.11)&lt;br&gt;AVAV | 3 | $793.89&lt;br&gt;BA | 4 | $928.12&lt;br&gt;BIPC | 23 | $950.59&lt;br&gt;CDE | 40 | $985.2&lt;br&gt;CLSK | 102 | $984.3&lt;br&gt;CODA | 73 | $982.02&lt;br&gt;COST | 1 | $985.27&lt;br&gt;CRCL | 15 | $945.3&lt;br&gt;DAVE | 5 | $882.55&lt;br&gt;DHR | 4 | $838.0&lt;br&gt;FCX | 15 | $965.1&lt;br&gt;GD | 2 | $702.84&lt;br&gt;HIMS | 63 | $985. + (~63×15.63)&lt;br&gt;HPQ | 53 | $985.03&lt;br&gt;HOOD | 12 | $913.32&lt;br&gt;IBM | 3 | $771.48&lt;br&gt;INTC | 22 | $970.42&lt;br&gt;ISRG | 1 | $504.05&lt;br&gt;JNJ | 4 | $969.96&lt;br&gt;LUCK | 8 | $903.52 (≈8×112.94) — used DUOL price as proxy (Duolingo)&lt;br&gt;MARATHON (MARA) | 123 | $980.31&lt;br&gt;MSFT | 2 | $794.46&lt;br&gt;MTD | 10 | $968.6&lt;br&gt;NOV | 48 | $978.72&lt;br&gt;OUST | 52 | $968.24&lt;br&gt;PESI | 73 | $979.66&lt;br&gt;RKLB | 20 | $962.6&lt;br&gt;ROK | 2 | $797.58&lt;br&gt;SNPS | 2 | $879.88&lt;br&gt;SYM | 18 | ~$968.31 (≈18×53.795)&lt;br&gt;TCGL | 7 | ~$984.71* — assumed ~$140.67 price (not quoted)&lt;br&gt;TTD | 39 | $978.9&lt;br&gt;TTWO | 4 | $798.88&lt;br&gt;UPST | 33 | $966.57&lt;br&gt;WMT | 8 | $983.92&lt;br&gt;WPM | 6 | $902.28&lt;br&gt;XLE | 13 | ~$988.51* — assumed ~$75.96 price (typical)&lt;br&gt;XOM | 6 | $883.68&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882771&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882767&lt;br&gt;First was ChatGPT.&lt;br&gt;Grok took way longer but here is what I ended up with using Grok.&lt;br&gt;ACN | 5 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;AEM | 4 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;AMBA | 14 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;AMZN | 5 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;ARMP | 113 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;AU | 9 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;AVAV | 4 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;BIPC | 21 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;BMXI | 39411 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;BRK.B | 2 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;CDE | 40 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;CLSK | 102 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;COST | 1 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;CRCL | 16 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;DLR | 6 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;DNN | 243 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;EPOL | 26 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;EUAD | 21 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;FCX | 15 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;FIG | 38 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;FLOT | 19 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;GD | 3 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;GOOG | 3 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;HIMS | 62 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;HOOD | 13 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;HP | 28 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;IGV | 12 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;INVZ | 1048 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;JD | 36 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;MARA | 124 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;MRVL | 12 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;NAK | 752 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;NOV | 48 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;OUST | 53 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;PESI | 73 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;RGLD | 3 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;RHM | 861 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;RR | 377 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;SHEL | 12 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;SNPS | 2 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;SYM | 18 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;TEM | 17 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;TTD | 39 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;VGSH | 17 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;WDAY | 7 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;WDEF | 28 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;WMT | 8 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;WPM | 7 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;XLU | 21 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;XYZ | 19 | 985.27&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882776&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882771&lt;br&gt;~$50k to replicate this. I could easily do it, but I won&amp;#x27;t. If $50k is less than 10% of your portfolio and you&amp;#x27;re a crazed degenerate Yolo gambler maybe give it a try. Report back results yearly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882780&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882771&lt;br&gt;EUAD and WDEF are redundant so don&amp;#x27;t buy both.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882784&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882767&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882771&lt;br&gt;COST is the highest priced stock per share.&lt;br&gt;Idiocracy was prophecy.&lt;br&gt;Gaze upon your future.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882960&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882771 (and others)&lt;br&gt;I appreciate the effort but ChatGPT and grok are dumber than midwits.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882735&lt;br&gt;I can literally tell this is gemini because of its recommendations&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;compare what i hold in my 2nd post to its baseline recommendations&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I bought some of those because gemini recommends it and I foresee normies getting their stock picks from googles ai mode&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882969&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;anyone who has extensively toyed with muh ai for finance and stock picks has come across this&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;here&amp;#x27;s why stock X is currently a &amp;quot;bottom-blasted&amp;quot; value pick: (3 bullet points, not x but y)&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;open chart&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;stock has just spent 12 weeks hitting new ATHs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882997&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;anyway it doesnt need to really pick anything, just allocate sanely&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883121&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882969&lt;br&gt;Grok is the only AI that gave me decent advice on investment s. But Gemini, chatgpt and even Claude opus were terrible. You should always do your own research with stonks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>BTC dumping? Don’t care. It’s temporary. — 73 replies — 18.5/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61869212</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61869212?lm=1771672803</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 11:20:03 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;BTC dumping? Don’t care. It’s temporary.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61869212'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 73 • Updated: 2026-02-21 11:20 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;If it drops, I buy more. If it goes sideways, I accumulate. If it pumps, I chill. I’m earning yield and stacking long term. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Short term volatility doesn’t change the plan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869234&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869212&lt;br&gt;Crypto and BTC is dead retard &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Everyone knows about it by now&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869237&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869212&lt;br&gt;The niggercattle aren&amp;#x27;t going to pump your epsteincoin bags.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869244&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869212&lt;br&gt;Pixel tranny cope.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877954&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877158&lt;br&gt;Nope. If the platform disappears, your BTC doesn’t vanish. It’s still on Bitcoin under the lock you set, and you can withdraw when the unlock conditions are met. Simple.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877961&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877152&lt;br&gt;it nukes and pumps like everything else anon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877965&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877155&lt;br&gt;You can hold both. It doesn’t have to be one or the other.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877979&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877954&lt;br&gt;You are sharing your keys with another entity. You are retarded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878072&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877979&lt;br&gt;Is it another centralized shit?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878078&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869212&lt;br&gt;Welcum bro&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878113&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872347&lt;br&gt;It’s got maybe one more bull run left in it, but $150K is never happening. Ethereum is already at the &amp;quot;no new ATHs ever again&amp;quot; stage. Crypto is dead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878176&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869234&lt;br&gt;newfag alert&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878183&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873082&lt;br&gt;you are genuinely retarded, keep making them stronger with your rocks but in the end it won&amp;#x27;t matter&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878193&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878176&lt;br&gt;Yeah and beanie babies as an asset class will come roaring back any day now. Enjoy holding your digital bags.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878207&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878193&lt;br&gt;Not exactly accurate there&amp;#x27;s a few beanie babies still fetching over a million right now anon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878212&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877711&lt;br&gt;FUD only&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878223&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878207&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;fetching&lt;br&gt;Why are they all the same price if they&amp;#x27;re an appreciating asset?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878248&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878207&lt;br&gt;Just because you ask for a price doesn&amp;#x27;t mean you&amp;#x27;ll get it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878256&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877979&lt;br&gt;No. You never share private keys. BTC is locked in a Bitcoin script where spending still requires the staker’s signature. If the platform disappears like I said, the timelock path lets you withdraw using Bitcoin only.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878321&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877722&lt;br&gt;sure anon. why? tech, users, or just hoping for a pump?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878324&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878207&lt;br&gt;Can we make money here? I&amp;#x27;m so tired of negative PNL&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878330&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878248&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s losers trade&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878331&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869212&lt;br&gt;I own a lil bit of btc and eth myself (3% of my entire portfolio) but I would unironically love to see the entire crypto market going to 0. You bitcoin maxi retards need to wake up. Your 5k stack of crypto wont magically 100x in the next 5-10 years and make you rich lol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878347&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878072&lt;br&gt;Nah. I’ve already explained it a bunch. DYOR anon. Either let BTC sleep or look into native, self custody setups and pick what fits you kek.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878349&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869514&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;the elites&lt;br&gt;There are many kinds of elites that compete against each other. Many of them want strategic reserves of BTC to trade with. BTC will never die.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878352&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878331&lt;br&gt;What&amp;#x27;s wrong with btc maxis&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878368&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877734&lt;br&gt;Damn! Taxi drivers don’t call tops and bottoms, they just repeat headlines. Stick to your plan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878374&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878078&lt;br&gt;Not my crowd. Stay poor, anon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878376&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869212&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I&amp;#x27;ve tricked myself with a berg-word for any situation!&lt;br&gt;good for you anon? what do you want me to do with this information?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878386&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869360&lt;br&gt;And yet comex+cme can evaporate 10 trillion in market cap in three days. Going to take one from the xrp schizos and say mcap doesn&amp;#x27;t mean anything. Still hold actual metals and not paper derivatives though...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879258&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878113&lt;br&gt;If crypto is dead, why is the onchain activity, stablecoins, and L2 growth still there? Price isn’t the whole story.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880618&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878349&lt;br&gt;Someone gets it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882946&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878376&lt;br&gt;It depends on you anon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882959&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869212&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is Polkadot decoupling from Bitcoin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>x50 Leverage Trading as an EU-Cuck — 11 replies — 17.8/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61882954</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61882954?lm=1771684805</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 14:40:05 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;x50 Leverage Trading as an EU-Cuck&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61882954'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 11 • Updated: 2026-02-21 14:40 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am in the EU, so Kraken only allows me x10 leverage with BTC Futures. Is there a good exchange to get x50 or x100 on a legit exchange without being frozen/funds withheld even though living in Europe? We have some cucked law that pushes most exchanges to cap at x10.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882957&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882954&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How do I 50x Polkadot&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882958&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882954&lt;br&gt;friend of mine dabbled into leveraged trading a few years ago. he told me he couldnt sleep for weeks, his heart rate was always in the 150`s and his overall quality of life was very very life. he did all that and still lost close to 20k in just a few months. he had a masters in mechanical engineering so he wasnt a complete retard. why do you say all that because I believe you are a retard and you will lose everything just like everyone else trading to do leveraged trading.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882970&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882958&lt;br&gt;I appreciate the warning, but we are all just meatslobs chasing dreams.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882980&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882970&lt;br&gt;slow and steady will work and trust me, being done with the rat race in your 30`s or 40`s wont make you magically happy. if anything you will be even more depressed because you will end up with no dreams and thats all assuming you make it somehow (which you wont).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883039&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882954&lt;br&gt;binance - the exchange with by far the most liquidity in the world and much better UI and features even int he cucked EU where I too reside&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883059&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883039&lt;br&gt;Are you able to trade more than 10x margin? They want to KYC me and the site states that their futures trading isn&amp;#x27;t available in the EU.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883068&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882954&lt;br&gt;You can use hyperliquid or aster. I prefer hyperliquid but aster allows you more degen leverage. I&amp;#x27;ve been using hyperliquid for 1 year and 0 problems. It works so well it doesn&amp;#x27;t even feel defi&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883084&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Only a fool would take on more than 10x in crapto kek. Losing your money 10x is not fast enough for you?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883093&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883068&lt;br&gt;Thank you, will check those out.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Any EU-Fags have experience with Binance (regarding KYC and leverage)?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883215&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882954&lt;br&gt;If you’re gonna leverage trade, just go for forex, gold or futures instead of crapto. Better day to day opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883332&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;please use my financial loan services &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;pllllllleaaaaase make lines go up so the uncovered collateral doesn&amp;#x27;t devalue and bankrupts me and my geriatric peers&lt;br&gt;No&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Is it even possible to make it by opening a traditional business anymore? — 11 replies — 13.1/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61881439</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61881439?lm=1771683999</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 14:26:39 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Is it even possible to make it by opening a traditional business anymore?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61881439'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 11 • Updated: 2026-02-21 14:26 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Read subject &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is it even possible? Not only do you have to jump through a million regulations and fees just to get started, you&amp;#x27;re also competing against trillion dollar mega corps who can and will undercut you because they employ ten thousand indians and illegals who work for pennies. Even traditional blue collar jobs like plumbers and HVAC are all slowly coagulating into one single corporate entity (in my area), and basically every single mom and pop store was killed during COVID. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It seems like the only way you can actually achieve anything is to basically trick angle investors into giving your bullshit tech start-up a ton of money or getting really lucky and have an app you make be bought out by a megacorp so they can rape your customers to death.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pic unrelated&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881446&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881439&lt;br&gt;Step 1: get a girlfriend&lt;br&gt;Step 2: have her start an ASMR channel on YouTube&lt;br&gt;Step 3: have her start a merchandise line on shopify&lt;br&gt;There.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881567&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881446&lt;br&gt;the pretty girl ASMR youtuber to OF is so undefeated.. Ive been watching ASMR for 8 years and the amount of hot ASMR girls that build a quick following and launch OF is high.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881609&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881446&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Step 1: get a girlfriend&lt;br&gt;Do you have anything more realistic that I can accomplish?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881624&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881609&lt;br&gt;Become a trans vtuber. Work on your feminine voice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882459&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881439&lt;br&gt;Even trillion dollar companies can&amp;#x27;t do everything. The amount of bureaucracy involved to manage such a large entity is limiting in its own ways.&lt;br&gt;You have to find a niche that isn&amp;#x27;t currently being served in your market and then create a business for that.&lt;br&gt;For example: nobody is making catgirl gfs right now, it&amp;#x27;s a completely untapped market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882478&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Corporations can now grow indefinetly due to advancement&amp;#x27;s in economic planning. It used to be theyd crash and burn after they got to a certain size.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882584&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881624&lt;br&gt;This, also after few years of HRT start OF, get cosmetic surgeries to look like a bimbo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882649&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m not sure which is a worse feeling. The frustration of losing a bunch of games for dumb reasons or the anxiety of not wanting to fuck up a good winning streak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883247&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881439&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s possible, but made very difficult by design. Can&amp;#x27;t have too many people escaping the wage cage.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Everything is over regulated, because it means only mega corps have the resources to deal with the BS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883254&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881439&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;a million regulations and fees just to get started&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;there are fees and regulations but they&amp;#x27;re not impossible to navigate, just look at how retardedness and drunkeness of the average trades small business owner.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;but you&amp;#x27;re right about consolidation and private equity ownership. there&amp;#x27;s no way around this, other than killing PE jews or the people who sell out to PE.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883298&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881446&lt;br&gt;I did a similar thing with my wife&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;have gf&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;she films herself having sex with guys in college while we were long distance&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;both of us have cuckold fetish&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;whenever she visits me we usually set aside time for threesomes with guys we meet online and sex clubs&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;eventually get married, start onlyfans where we film it all but blur the faces&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;make around $8000 a month &lt;br&gt;not a traditional business model as OP says however&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>why would anyone live here — 99 replies — 10.3/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61872797</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61872797?lm=1771652538</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:42:18 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;why would anyone live here&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61872797'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 99 • Updated: 2026-02-21 05:42 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;i recently moved to NYC to work for a &amp;quot;lucrative salary&amp;quot; (not really, because this place drains you of all your income) and after working here for 4 months i dont know why anyone would willingly live here&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;the entire city smells like rotting shit, cigarette buds and dead animals, not a faint smell, an extremely strong odor that you&amp;#x27;ll eventually just become nose blind to&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;homeless people, fucking everywhere, when i left my apartment there were homeless people sleeping in the hallways of my complex, when you go on walk there are homeless people sleeping on the sidewalk with a PILLOW and BLANKET while regular people walk over them like this is just some normal fucking occurrence (and in this shithole it is) never ever have i seen some shit like this even in the worst of cities ive lived in.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;heroin needles, weed bags, cigarette buds &amp;amp; the occasional dildo just scattered across the city sidewalks, your constantly walking over human shit, broken bottles or dime bags&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;rats and rodents EVERYWHERE. il never forget the time i bought a pizza from one of the disgusting street vendors and when i sat down at a table one of the rats were circling my feet trying to climb my leg for a bite.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;the &amp;quot;public transport&amp;quot; system is a just permanent housing for the mentally ill, every time i had to ride the subway i was scared for my life because of all the fucking looneys that inhabit the train systems&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;this is just off the top of my head, but i think the biggest mindfuck of it all is that its EXPENSIVE to live here its gonna cost you not 50k, not 100k, not 200k, to live comfortably by yourself you need 250K yearly in manhattan. 250k, to live among violent homeless people, 250k to constantly have to walk in rotting shit and roadkill. 250k to have your ears blown out by car horns &amp;amp; niggerbabble, 250k to be forced to smell the most putried scents imaginable i dont know why anyone sane would live here, this place is some sort of social experiment, some sort of anonmoly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872828&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872797&lt;br&gt;Go back to your trailer park, pussy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872853&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872797&lt;br&gt;You know the phrase &amp;quot;If you can make it in New York you can make it anywhere&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;re not making it. You&amp;#x27;re a small fish in the biggest fucking pond.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you were making it you wouldn&amp;#x27;t deal with ANY of this shit&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Oh my heck the freakin homeless have PILLOWS and BLANKETS &lt;br&gt;Literally who gives a single actual fuck&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872859&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872828&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872853&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;getting AIDS from stepping on a needle is just part of the HUSTLE AND BUSTLE&lt;br&gt;citycels are pathetic&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876859&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NYC is the only place I’ve ever seen human shit on a subway.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876874&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872797&lt;br&gt;Hi there shartycuck aren’t you like 16?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876879&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872934&lt;br&gt;Enjoy the herpes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876897&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61876842&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;now&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876915&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61876797&lt;br&gt;The point is that “low” cost of living areas are a meme.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876952&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874263&lt;br&gt;If you think Chicago smells bad wait to you smell New York on a hot summer day, retard&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877007&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874674&lt;br&gt;stop having sex with ugly women anon. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;take the risk and try to make more meaningful connections, whats the point of so many women, are you even making kids in them?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;stop drinking with low quality girls, i used to fuck 80 women in 6 months too because i didn&amp;#x27;t want commitment, very easy to do if you have a good dating profile with good pics in a city with millions of people. so its not even anything to brag about, &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;now i only date sober and fuck maybe 3 women a year. no more fucking women in the car parking lot after the first or second date, and its ok.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877430&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872797&lt;br&gt;The fun of going to new york to me is seeing the crazy people living there would be absurd&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877838&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872797&lt;br&gt;JYC is a total scam. &lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s not for the upper social layer. It&amp;#x27;s for the rich. Who are cut from the other, traveling with chauffered car. &lt;br&gt;The rent will drain all your earnings. &lt;br&gt;In 2020, they transformed Jew york hospitals into death camps (dyor on this). &lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s a city of madness. It&amp;#x27;s the madness of our world in crisis, but concentrated. &lt;br&gt;It is a successor of Babylon, Alexandria, etc... &lt;br&gt;Stay away from it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877846&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUDE i just LOVE the hustle and bustle of the big city, it’s so DYNAMIC and makes me feel like i’m in one of my favourite TV SHOWS. you should totally come on down to my studio apartment, it’s got EXPOSED RED BRICK walls and 50 square feet! we can crack open a nice hoppy ipa or three and get crazy watching some cartoons on adult swim! and dude, dude, DUDE, we have GOTTA go down to the barcade- listen here, right, it’s a BAR where us ADULTS who do ADULTING can go DRINK. BUT!!!! it’s also an ARCADE like when we were kids, so we can play awesome VIDEO GAMES, without dumb kids bothering us. speaking of which megan and i have finally decided to tie the knot- literally -we’re both getting snipped tomorrow at the hospital, that way we can save money to spent more on ourselves and our FURBABIES. i’m fuckin JACKED man, i’m gonna SLAM this craft beer and pop open another one!!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878010&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;whine&amp;quot; in ID&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;whines&lt;br&gt;Never been to NYC, never will go. Happy in my small town, simple as.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878024&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872887&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;So much propaganda and people think it&amp;#x27;s the best city in the world&lt;br&gt;If you are a jew or a degenerate perhaps.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878027&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872934&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Beautiful women outnumber eligible men.&lt;br&gt;You mean crazy roasties?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878028&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61876952&lt;br&gt;I’m never going to visit Jew York you stupid cocksucking faggot. Unless it’s to fuck your whore mother.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878030&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872950&lt;br&gt;Actually, AIDS do not exist. NOr does any viruses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878056&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61876813&lt;br&gt;kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878093&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877838&lt;br&gt;It’s not some modern Babylon, that’s my whole point. It has a relatively tame and uninspired party scene compared to some european cities, it’s women are majorly brown ect. It’s just a pretty boring third world city with big history, but doesn’t offer much in modernity besides the amazing skyscraper architechture.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878125&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872797&lt;br&gt;Why would you live in a globalist shit hole? You were desperately warned about these people. So we genuinely do not know who is stupider.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881484&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877007&lt;br&gt;I`m the anon you&amp;#x27;re answering to and I agree 100%. I realized I was wasting TIME, MONEY, and SLEEP on retard hoes that I would fuck once and never see again.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Absolute waste of time.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Money is the most important thing to secure a high quality woman you&amp;#x27;ll actually want to have children with.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881527&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872797&lt;br&gt;If you weren&amp;#x27;t part of the top 10% in 2025, you&amp;#x27;re lower class&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881538&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872797&lt;br&gt;According to people on this board, if you want to live in a nice White gated community you;re flyover White trash so yeah, living in that open air sewer means you&amp;#x27;re cultured I guess. I left that state and never looked back and that was before MS-13 was cutting people&amp;#x27;s heads off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881574&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873926&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;re delsuional if you believe that. There are no ghettos in Ohio like there are in NY and if pay was so good people wouldn&amp;#x27;t be leaving by the millions. Almost 2 million people in NYC alone have to rely on food stamps just to survive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881580&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61876831&lt;br&gt;You sound bitter and sheltered as fuck my guy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881601&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881538&lt;br&gt;I would rather live in this hell hole than a gated community in the middle of fucking no where lol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881618&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;how did you not know the reality of this BEFORE you went in?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881702&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881618&lt;br&gt;rs lol, OP is dumbass&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881790&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881538&lt;br&gt;This shithole is just a third world circlejerk + edgy reddit without downvoting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881799&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881601&lt;br&gt;You could live in nonshithole close enough to drive into the city but of course youre a shit brown welfare nigger&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881806&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872905&lt;br&gt;NYC is literally an Indian’s playground. They also have illegal Africans driving around like mad max on fucking bicycles delivering food to the legal Africans that work in bullshit government positions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882371&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881618&lt;br&gt;In the 90s/early 00’s they made multiple very popular american shows about trendy, nice and modern New York, making it look like it was as safe and had as little homeless as european cities. A lot of europeans watched them and believed the propaganda.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>SUNDAY ROAST: revolutionary tool or schizo cope? /biz/ decide — 6 replies — 10.3/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61883194</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61883194?lm=1771684927</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 14:42:07 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;SUNDAY ROAST: revolutionary tool or schizo cope? /biz/ decide&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61883194'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 6 • Updated: 2026-02-21 14:42 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;ok anons it&amp;#x27;s almost sunday. roast me.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;i spent 4 years building semn.ai and the past 3 months building the cloud infra. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;the idea: bitcoin price on a candle chart is a lossy compression of what&amp;#x27;s actually happening in the market. so i threw out the candles and built a completely different state space for BTC microstructure. a new lens that picks up regime shifts before they ever show up on your chart.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;designed for scalpers. intraday high leverage degens. the kind of moves that are over before tradingview even renders the wick.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;here&amp;#x27;s the cope part: i genuinely think this is novel. like, actually novel.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;here&amp;#x27;s the seethe part: intraday BTC degens either don&amp;#x27;t know it exists or don&amp;#x27;t give a shit.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;so /biz/, is this actually interesting or am i just another schizo who built a proprietary chart that only makes sense in my own head? &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;serious question. what would make you actually look at something like this? what would make you dismiss it immediately?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;roast the concept, roast the site, roast me. i can take it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;semn.ai&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883221&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883194&lt;br&gt;pretty ui&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883262&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I read what you wrote up until you said it was called semen AI. Then I stopped and posted this. That&amp;#x27;s about all the help you&amp;#x27;ll get out of me&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883266&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883221&lt;br&gt;thank you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883275&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883262&lt;br&gt;well actually... fair point&lt;br&gt;comes from Σεμναἲ Δεαὶ (Semnai Theai) (revered goddesses) in ancient Greek. I know the naming is controversial but for me this is the Revered Asset (btc).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883297&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883194&lt;br&gt;So you built a trading bot? Does it perform?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883336&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883297&lt;br&gt;not exactly. sure a bot could be built based on this. but the tool&amp;#x27;s intended purpose is to reduce cognitive debt whilst manually trading. it makes you money by avoiding bad trades, more than it does by getting you in trades. so discretionary. automated bot you get rekt. you can see the microstructure, know when you can leverage more, when to stay out. when it&amp;#x27;s dead. when is compression, when not to fade expansion. when there is aggressive / toxic flow. it&amp;#x27;s like weather channel for btc. you don&amp;#x27;t bet on it raining, but you know when to take your umbrella with you. does it make sense?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>LINK is over — 6 replies — 9.7/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61883208</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61883208?lm=1771684798</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 14:39:58 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;LINK is over&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61883208'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 6 • Updated: 2026-02-21 14:39 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;What will you do when LINK hits $1?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883225&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883208&lt;br&gt;It probably won’t hit $1 but actually worse in that it’ll slowwwwly draw down over the next few years to 5-ish with every pop met with a violent drawback sell off&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883228&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whenever I see AI art I’m always baffled by how boring/unfunny/literal most these guys internal world is.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883259&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883228&lt;br&gt;i quite like this piece&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;but the chainholders should be barefoot&lt;br&gt;and some should be flagellating with their chains&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883269&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883208&lt;br&gt;buy a lot and then sell when it moons to $4&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883278&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883208&lt;br&gt;Apready accepted it&amp;#x27;s over...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883330&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883208&lt;br&gt;go to the temple of time to take LINK from $7 to $16&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>By investing in the US stock markets, you are directly financing everything that you hate about the United States. — 34 replies — 7.1/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61874572</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61874572?lm=1771669905</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 10:31:45 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;By investing in the US stock markets, you are directly financing everything that you hate about the United States.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61874572'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 34 • Updated: 2026-02-21 10:31 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;By investing in the US stock markets, you are directly financing everything that you hate about the United States.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874579&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874572&lt;br&gt;I dont, stonks are gay.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874590&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874572&lt;br&gt;Until unrealized gains are taxed, kys bobo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874623&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874590&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; HR departments staffed by roasties&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; women in management&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; H1 b visas&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; Jeets taking over American industry&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; Congress members getting rich off stocks&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; Lobbyist influence on laws&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; The bankers&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; etc&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t think so, Timmy. The second that you invest, you&amp;#x27;re giving them the money for all of it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874640&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874634&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Like what?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874661&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874572&lt;br&gt;but i only invest in reddit stocks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874662&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874640&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874670&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874662&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; no living wage&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; jobs being sent over seas&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; people being replaced by machines&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; Blackrock buying up all of the homes and making home ownership unattainable&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I have some oceanfront property in Colorado, if you&amp;#x27;re interested in property.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874673&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874662&lt;br&gt;What a load of horse shit lmao&lt;br&gt;Exactly the propaganda that destroyed this place&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874678&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874670&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874673&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874679&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874678&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874701&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874679&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874713&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874572&lt;br&gt;Luckily I&amp;#x27;m not a jew lover and only invest in silver and pokemon cards&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874737&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874701&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; Americans are just lazy and not smart enough&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Okay, boomer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874763&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874737&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874774&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874763&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Have fun trading against bots, and good luck competing against the world with your best foids, trannies, jeets, and chinese spies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874778&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874572&lt;br&gt;But I love the United States&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874789&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874774&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874810&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874789&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; a free country&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Did you know the owning physical gold in the United States was illegal for 41 years?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877358&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874662&lt;br&gt;It doesn’t seem like America is more this way than any other first world country. Maybe it is slightly easier in America but that seems to be fading quickly now that the post war era is over.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877363&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t invest in the United States, bobo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877634&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877358&lt;br&gt;Looking by wealth distribution, USA isn&amp;#x27;t a first world country. It has just has a wealthy upper class and a super wealthy elite class.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877638&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;But anyways yeah bobo i know, that&amp;#x27;s why invest in european markets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877686&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874572&lt;br&gt;Not only that, I voted for it too&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877708&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874572&lt;br&gt;Only if you are investing in index funds.&lt;br&gt;You can choose to invest in what you love about this country.&lt;br&gt;I personally am investing in LMT, GD, HAL, XOM, BX, COST&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877733&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877708&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m sure that Black Rock doesn&amp;#x27;t own any of those stocks and enforcing DEI. They probably pay people enough to live off of and aren&amp;#x27;t looking to automate. Corporate culture surely hasn&amp;#x27;t infiltrated those businesses. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Can I interest you in a Rolex watch?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877891&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By investing in US stocks, I am hedging against everything I love.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877903&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877686&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;sometimes Cherri gets horny at work, dances and has sex with the men in the closests&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878643&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874572&lt;br&gt;I finance shit that literally kill people because it gives me divvies. Do you think I care in the slightest for normalfags? They are cattle to be milked dry. I hate wokeslop and yet I invested in NFLX after it dropped. To this day I never subbed to them and seed torrents of shows from there. I hate cigarettes and yet I invest in MO. I don&amp;#x27;t believe in crypto and yet I got back in BTC around 69k. I believe in socialized healthcare and yet I&amp;#x27;m a UNH baggie (avg over $300)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879220&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874623&lt;br&gt;I can profit in white Genocide? Based!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879386&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874572&lt;br&gt;I only got GME in hopes of killing off the US economy very slowly in one explosive blow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879544&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878643&lt;br&gt;You are a monster&lt;br&gt;americans have 0 moral backbone&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882835&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879544&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m not an American&lt;br&gt;Morals are a spook.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882878&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874572&lt;br&gt;i don&amp;#x27;t invest, i gamble&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Day 219 of snailposting every day until LINK is at $100 — 1 replies — 4.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61883385</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61883385?lm=1771686583</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 15:09:43 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Day 219 of snailposting every day until LINK is at $100&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61883385'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 1 • Updated: 2026-02-21 15:09 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Day 219 of snailposting every day until LINK is at $100&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883406&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yeah&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;No additional replies in the latest window.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>I have recently discovered leftwing finance youtube channels The whole things is never EVER blaming people for going int… — 58 replies — 3.8/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61872693</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61872693?lm=1771631405</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 23:50:05 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;I have recently discovered leftwing finance youtube channels The whole things is never EVER blaming people for going int…&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61872693'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 58 • Updated: 2026-02-20 23:50 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have recently discovered leftwing finance youtube channels &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The whole things is never EVER blaming people for going into debt, but blaming companies instead&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;Asking people how much debt they are in is Chud behaviour, just because they are in debt doesn&amp;#x27;t mean they can&amp;#x27;t go on a vacation, but Disneyland should be cheaper, Disney is predatory&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;The problem isn&amp;#x27;t credit card debt, that&amp;#x27;s normal, the problem is how hight the interests rates are&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;60k car loans are insane but really, why do the cars need to cost that much?&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872704&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872693&lt;br&gt;The one you used in the OP got famous for calling people retards to their faces for their debt&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872721&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872693&lt;br&gt;Caleb is just a gay zoomer Dave Ramsey. Just like with Judge Judy, it doesn&amp;#x27;t work if you&amp;#x27;re not a boomer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872722&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872704&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872721&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872693&lt;br&gt;Caleb is not the leftwing finance bro.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In fact he&amp;#x27;s fighting accusations he&amp;#x27;s far right&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876247&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872693&lt;br&gt;Despite being a fat faggot, leftists hate Caleb Hammer for making the hateful claim that you shouldn&amp;#x27;t buy junk when you have to get a 150% APY loan&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876259&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872693&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;retard takes a loan with 50% interest rate to buy some burritos at chipotle and labubus&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;completely oblivious about what loan interests means&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;ITS NOT A BAD DECISION, ITS THE FAULT OF LE EVIL CAPITALISM&lt;br&gt;lmao holy fuck&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876262&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61876259&lt;br&gt;You shouldn&amp;#x27;t even be able to take out a loan at 50% kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876287&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872693&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Wkw21YfvpBk&amp;amp;t=927s&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Literally ends with &amp;quot;ahhh cool story, stand against the wall....&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876302&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872750&lt;br&gt;There isn’t a structural issue. The issue is the majority of people are financially illiterate retards with no ability to delay gratification.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876355&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;but really, why do the cars need to cost that much?&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;Because they spent 60 years demanding massive liability payouts and more &amp;amp; more regulation...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meanwhile China today buys their electric car for 10k...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876361&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I like the show because of the click bait guests, but there&amp;#x27;s way too many commercials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876382&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61876355&lt;br&gt;Cars aren&amp;#x27;t even much more expensive if you account for inflation. &lt;br&gt;And if you consider price in gold, they are WAY cheaper.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876383&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872722&lt;br&gt;He&amp;#x27;s a homosexual so he probably is a (closeted) white supremacists&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876504&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61876245&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61876302&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Demoralization&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;NUH UH&lt;br&gt;Spoken precisely how I&amp;#x27;d imagine someone would if they knew I was right but didn&amp;#x27;t want others to catch on.&lt;br&gt;For those interested in a fix: you get together with like-minded people and pincer from the federal and local levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877446&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;the economy is rigged to make the rich richer at the expense of the poor&lt;br&gt;and&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;the poor are mostly stupid goycattle who deserve to stay poor&lt;br&gt;are both true&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878485&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61876302&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;There isn’t a structural issue. The issue is the majority of people are financially illiterate retards with no ability to delay gratification.&lt;br&gt;That and many are really greedy and selfish. The anticapitalist types are always the most greedy people.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You can&amp;#x27;t help these people btw. Might as well finance them a 7-11 churro and put their money to a better use.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878497&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877446&lt;br&gt;Elite Human Capital can utilize resources better than the poor. So it&amp;#x27;s good the system is biased in their favor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878769&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873088&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;You fix a broken system by changing the system.&lt;br&gt;How are you dumb enough to believe this?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878780&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61876504&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;We&amp;#x27;re going to fix the system, we have all the answers&lt;br&gt;If you had any of the answers, you&amp;#x27;d know how to use the system in the first place.&lt;br&gt;This like is AOC going to DC to tell us how to fix all the problems in the world and not knowing what that switch on her kitchen wall next to her sink is or why it&amp;#x27;s suddenly making noise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879278&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873088&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;by changing the system.&lt;br&gt;Communist spotted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879340&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872693&lt;br&gt;He attacks individuals though, usually calls them stupid for doing XYZ&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t like him but that&amp;#x27;s just not true anon. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872722&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61876383&lt;br&gt;He had a guest mention a bad part of town being &amp;quot;Brownsville&amp;quot; (which is the actual name of the bad part of town) and he immediately virtue signaled and brought a black guy on camera to &amp;quot;confront&amp;quot; the guest about it when it was in fact the literal town name.&lt;br&gt;Caleb is a cum guzzling faggot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879349&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872922&lt;br&gt;Conservatives are generally already better with money because they had fiscally responsible parents (notice how I said parents, as in plural)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879520&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872693&lt;br&gt;The system prices all that in and it&amp;#x27;s why we have monopoly money that gets bailed out at regular intervals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879536&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879520&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gold windows closed &lt;br&gt;Women “liberated” enter workforces&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now money is worthless&lt;br&gt;Women trapped in jobs they hate without families. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s like there’s a link between unsound money are societal degeneracy. Hmmm&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879588&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872722&lt;br&gt;Yeah except he&amp;#x27;s basically a pinko moderate besides the fact that he&amp;#x27;s come to the common sense realization that most poor people are poor because they&amp;#x27;re clearly obviously fucking retards making bad decisions. He&amp;#x27;s clearly pretty pozzed with regards to gays, &amp;quot;sex workers&amp;quot;, being unmarried with kids, thruples, etc. in the typical Reddit &amp;quot;you do you frendo&amp;quot; with his only standard being whether or not that happens to be producing outcomes the person doing them likes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;quot;Far right&amp;quot; is a faggot term for &amp;quot;conservative&amp;quot; to try to make it sound bad. You&amp;#x27;ll see very very little discussion of merely right wing in leftist media. &amp;quot;Far right&amp;quot; is &amp;quot;something I don&amp;#x27;t like&amp;quot;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;quot;Poor people are poor largely because they deserve it, they&amp;#x27;re not oppressed victims and therefore we&amp;#x27;re not terribly obligated to do much of anything just because they&amp;#x27;re irresponsible&amp;quot; is just one of the most basic conservative ideas. But it&amp;#x27;s entirely antithetical to a leftist world view that basically identifies everyone as either victims and victimizers and that rustled Jimmies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879764&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879349&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Conservatives are generally already better with money because they had fiscally responsible parents&lt;br&gt;You need to look at the latest data. Conservative core base are the people of walmart who don&amp;#x27;t marry, spend recklessly, and leech off the government. They&amp;#x27;re basically white niggers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;All the responsible Romney type republicans left.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879795&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879764&lt;br&gt;Just the same they fundamentally believe people have self-responsibility even if they hypocritically are fuckups living on gibs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879802&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879764&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;political people I don&amp;#x27;t like bad, poor, stupid&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;political people I do like good, rich, smart&lt;br&gt;Sure thing buddy. &lt;br&gt;So anyways conservatives are generally more fiscally literate people and don&amp;#x27;t rack up lots of retarded debt because they come from better homes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879815&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879795&lt;br&gt;I swear all you leftist who believe this shit come from single wide trailer parks and just hate your own upbringing and project it on everyone you disagree with.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881453&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878780&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;If you had any of the answers, you&amp;#x27;d know how to use the system in the first place.&lt;br&gt;Or, you have the moral scruples not to use the knowledge that you have.&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s not surprising to me that this doesn&amp;#x27;t occur to you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881457&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878769&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;believe&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t have to believe, I know the history. That is how it works.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881463&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879278&lt;br&gt;Oh no not namecalling&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881511&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879764&lt;br&gt;R-money is not responsible. R-money is part of a crime family, and he made all his money doing vulture capitalism and hostile takeovers and such in the 80s. He&amp;#x27;s a liberal who wants lower taxes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881532&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881457&lt;br&gt;Maintenance is required for civilization. Anything you build has to be maintained. You don&amp;#x27;t replace your entire car when your oil gets dirty.&lt;br&gt;Revolution is not. The only history you know is written by academic fuckups with no real world experience who let 3 of their 5 children starve to death rather than getting a real job, claiming to know the plight of the working class because they live in the same neighborhood, while the actual working class do this thing that&amp;#x27;s antithetical to their existence: WORK.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881453&lt;br&gt;That&amp;#x27;s not moral scruiples, that&amp;#x27;s laziness. You could do it morally but you choose not to.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>