<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>/biz/ Active (filtered, with replies)</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/</link><description>Filtered out: general, gme, bbbyq. OP + first 3 replies + last 30 replies.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 05:10:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>how do you guys cope with the fact that OF egirls are making tens of millions a year? — 57 replies — 228.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889270</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889270?lm=1771909457</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 05:04:17 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;how do you guys cope with the fact that OF egirls are making tens of millions a year?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889270'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 57 • Updated: 2026-02-24 05:04 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;how do you guys cope with the fact that OF egirls are making tens of millions a year? this shit is really unbelievable man i am seething so hard holy fuck&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889273&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I literally just don&amp;#x27;t care. Nobody will ever love them and I can also make 10 million without displaying my butthole for the world to see&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889278&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s only like top1% creators making millions&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889279&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889273&lt;br&gt;i didnt care too for so long but now im starting to care fml its just so unfair.. Not only are they extremely hot they also get to make 20MM a year for years scamming with bikini pics on OF&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;its just so unfair i feel like crying&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889644&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889631&lt;br&gt;How is that even worth $200? Enjoy your money pox&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889769&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889273&lt;br&gt;Holy cope. Obviously most men will love them because men are horny dogs. Its 2026, prime time to realize men are the more pathetic gender. This aint the 50s champ.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889773&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889273&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Nobody will ever love them&lt;br&gt;These bitches get BFs all the time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889775&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;how do you guys cope with the fact that OF egirls are making tens of millions a year?&lt;br&gt;Only the top 1% do, the rest make around few hundred USD or few 20-40USD a month.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889273&lt;br&gt;Lot of them have BFs and lot of them don&amp;#x27;t do porn with other men just sell their nudes but most aren&amp;#x27;t making enough to retire on not by a longshot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889777&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;1. They don&amp;#x27;t receive all that money, they are hired under an umbrella corporation, they are just models for hire.&lt;br&gt;2. They are women, they don&amp;#x27;t know how to invest their money (see amouranth, it was her husband who put her in front of the camera, managed her socials and invested her money)&lt;br&gt;3. I can&amp;#x27;t see what you would do with that much money, unless you are hyper-dependent on people doing things for you...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889804&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;They aren&amp;#x27;t. The vast majority have sold their souls for triple digit profits&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889830&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Comparing yourself to women is one of the first steps on the tranny pipeline lmao&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889840&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;Go sell your asshole to strangers and lookmax then you lazy cunt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889979&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;Nothings stopping you from doing gya shit on onlyfans&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889986&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;Doesn&amp;#x27;t bother me in the least.&lt;br&gt;Firstly, it causes tons of women to throw their lives away being whores. So is hardly a victory for women.&lt;br&gt;Secondly, what does that money do other than ruin their lives? Women crave a man higher on the totem pole than they are, now they can&amp;#x27;t find one for two reasons.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892313&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;I make faceless straight gay porn. I just ride a bunch of dildos pretending its my first time and they get to pretend they are the ones.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gigs not bad pays about 5k a month. My wife is my manager and hells clean my dildos.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Its not pleasurable by any means just feels like a fat shit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892450&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892313&lt;br&gt;lmao&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893140&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889830&lt;br&gt;everyone compares themselves to women, they are people too after all not some different species&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893380&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Start an only fans account.&lt;br&gt;Show the world your talent.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;My a PBJ using your dick to spread the stuff.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Profit.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Don’t give up until you try.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893392&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Make a PBJ!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Edit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893415&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889279&lt;br&gt;nigga are you stupid, hot girls have always had ez mode, any girl with looks + little brains can hustle money like crazy. I knew a waitress 2 years ago working in a shitty diner that was finessing 3-4 boomers, I remember one time a boomer literally handed her a $3,000 check, no sexual favors or anything, just sweet talk, this chick was spending 5-10,000 dollars a month on clothes and was driving a brand new Jeep luxury model&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893458&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;I know a money laundering scheme when I see one&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893483&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892313&lt;br&gt;Fucking kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893517&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;At least i can coom out of the leaked photos of these e-prostitutes, i can&amp;#x27;t cope with the fact some teenage faggot like barron trump (or Eric i don&amp;#x27;t know who&amp;#x27;s is who in that family of pagan gods worshiper faggots) make billions just because he was born in the &amp;quot;right&amp;quot; family.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893555&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I have never paid for porn or whores in my life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893557&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;the same way I cope with dude getting paid millions to play with balls, I don&amp;#x27;t care. it&amp;#x27;s not me and it doesn&amp;#x27;t impact me, so why should I give a shit?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893569&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;99% of them are making like 20 bucks a month lmfao&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893631&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889354&lt;br&gt;I met a girl who was a friend of a friend of mine at a party when I was younger and she literally handed me a business card with her OF address on it. I didn&amp;#x27;t realize what it was at first but the second I read it I blurted out &amp;quot;What the fuck is wrong with you?&amp;quot; without thinking and she got super offended. I&amp;#x27;m pretty sure I was the first person she handed it to that actually said anything negative about it by the way she reacted, which is very bizarre to me. It&amp;#x27;s kind of crazy how common this shit is.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893680&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;Like everything in the world of money being born a woman was a gamble&lt;br&gt;You just lost it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893688&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t think about women at all anon. They are the worst investment you can make in life&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893708&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889282&lt;br&gt;this right here. tons of people play sports, statistically, 0.000001 get paid well. Image stretching you butthole for a year or two and then finally coming to the conclusion it would have been both easier and more profitable to work a mcjob. add in its a clear red flag so they wont ever get a quality man.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893748&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893140&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;t. tranny&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894411&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889273&lt;br&gt;cope, if i can show my penis for millions i would flex on them hoes bro while being paid.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894435&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889270&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s all fake. Yet another demoralization psyop. You really fell for that? LMAO&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894538&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892313&lt;br&gt;You remind me of an anon who was here years ago. Fuck I forget his name but he made like 2k a month selling burping videos. He ended up caving and doing full blown hog cranking after telling anons he was only doing burp fetish shit.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t respect it but I kind of admire the journey desu. Once you&amp;#x27;re on the highway to being a degen there&amp;#x27;s really no off ramp&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>If you STILL haven't realized this is going to triple digits, then you should seriously consider seeing a medical profes… — 22 replies — 73.7/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61888568</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61888568?lm=1771908768</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:52:48 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;If you STILL haven&amp;#x27;t realized this is going to triple digits, then you should seriously consider seeing a medical profes…&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61888568'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 22 • Updated: 2026-02-24 04:52 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you STILL haven&amp;#x27;t realized this is going to triple digits, then you should seriously consider seeing a medical professional about actual brain damage or tumor-induced mental retardation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888572&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888568&lt;br&gt;double digit shitcoin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888573&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888572&lt;br&gt;Oh, eventually, yes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888580&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888568&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888572&lt;br&gt;Moonboys GTFO. Eth will be $3.93&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888585&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888568&lt;br&gt;ethheads forever&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888588&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888568&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888646&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888568&lt;br&gt;yes it sucks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888674&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insider here. 1580 bottom you’re welcome&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888678&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888588&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888725&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It took me a really long time to understand how these threads are mostly psyops to encourage capitulation, offering a better entry price for the clown roller coaster that will, in some form, happen later.&lt;br&gt;They&amp;#x27;re fishing nets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888733&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888725&lt;br&gt;when everyone realizes this, everyone will stop playing, the music will stop and BITFUCK will go STRAIGHT to FUCKING ZERO&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889438&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888674&lt;br&gt;Probably since my target is sub 1500......&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889444&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888725&lt;br&gt;Ofc op wants to buy lower, thats why is worrying since:&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889438&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889515&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ETH will flip BTC. Screenshot this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889609&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889515&lt;br&gt;Saaar pls, we are fudding here to buy the pico bottom, blody!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892900&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888568&lt;br&gt;bottom signal&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892906&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888725&lt;br&gt;it took you a long time to realize that? wow some people are very slow lmao. what the fuck other reason would someone have to go out of their way to post this kind of shit. you think they want to help you? lol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894363&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888568&lt;br&gt;I remember buying this shit at $80 and I was really excited for it to go to triple digits&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894441&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889438&lt;br&gt;Around 1300 to start for me, copium is that in the final flash crash it wicks down to 3 digits for a bit before the usual rebound like with last cycle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894452&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888568&lt;br&gt;Bro even BTC is losing its appeal. It uses so much electricity and most of the supply is held by a few people. Crypto is kind of gay unless you&amp;#x27;re the one making it or in on the scams...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894459&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894452&lt;br&gt;Also yes I&amp;#x27;m prepared for it to hit 100k+ eoy. I really dgaf anymore. fuck em. GME is more interesting even if it stays at $25 up to 2030&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894511&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bitcoin will easily drop below $60 in the near term. If that happens Ethereum is going below $1500 and probably much lower. This is all good because it shakes out the weak hands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894514&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;solded at the last top, feeling extremely smug and superior&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Ai is about to crash the economy — 22 replies — 53.1/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889737</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889737?lm=1771908352</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:45:52 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Ai is about to crash the economy&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889737'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 22 • Updated: 2026-02-24 04:45 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was released today by citrini&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI gets good. Companies lay off workers. Margins expand. Stocks rip. S&amp;amp;P hits 8,000. Everyone celebrates.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;• But fired workers stop spending. Companies weaken. They buy more AI to cut costs. More layoffs. Less spending. A negative feedback loop with no natural brake.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;• The top 10% of earners drive 50%+ of all consumer spending. They&amp;#x27;re the ones getting replaced. A $180K product manager ends up driving Uber for $45K. Multiply that across every major city.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;• Ghost GDP emerges - the economy is &amp;quot;growing&amp;quot; on paper, but the money never reaches real people. Productivity is booming. Wages are collapsing.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;• Then it hits housing. $13 trillion in mortgages, all underwritten on one assumption: you keep your job for 30 years. In 2008, the loans were bad on day one. In 2028, the loans were good. The world just changed after they were written.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;• S&amp;amp;P crashes 38% from highs. Unemployment hits 10.2%. Markets barely react anymore.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;• The punchline: you&amp;#x27;re not reading this in 2028. You&amp;#x27;re reading it in February 2026. Every domino they describe has already started falling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889750&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WAOW! Link me to this guy&amp;#x27;s substack payment page immediately!!!!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889754&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There&amp;#x27;s over a billion jeets you can just keep vacuuming up the top 10% of them to always have an american middle class&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889766&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is this from that monotone Chinese guy on youtube&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889795&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889737&lt;br&gt;nigga, I am 400K deep into PLTR, you don&amp;#x27;t have to sell me on it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889802&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889737&lt;br&gt;the crazy part no ones even trying to stop it, what you are saying here isn&amp;#x27;t some major breakthrough its plainly obvious to anyone with a brain. another plainly obvious problem with a.i that most people are missing is that its not creative in the same way a person is, a.i cannot invent the airplane so you aren&amp;#x27;t just replacing a high value earner but someone that has tools that a.i doesn&amp;#x27;t have, intuition, creativity all things a.i cannot do and will never be able to do with any accuracy its a complete meme.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889812&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889737&lt;br&gt;None of that has happened, it&amp;#x27;s a fake cover story for the drunken spending companies did post covid. They hired way too many people for bullshit jobs and are now cutting back while saying it&amp;#x27;s because of AI.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rest of the shit is due to inflation, first from covid supply shocks, then companies trying to squeeze every last dollar they could out of the consumer and now trump tariffs. AI hasn&amp;#x27;t even begun to displace people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889814&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Melanin inclined individuals all in on ai are so screwed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889824&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889814&lt;br&gt;America fixed this problem already&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890898&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889750&lt;br&gt;This one is free https://www.citriniresearch.com/p/2028gic&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890971&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889802&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; you aren&amp;#x27;t just replacing a high value earner but someone that has tools that a.i doesn&amp;#x27;t have&lt;br&gt;They also take up 10x more energy heating their house&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891766&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just tax AI and automation and introduce UBI. Problem solved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893157&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889737&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s not going to stop at just human intelligence, it&amp;#x27;s going to start the RSI feedback loop that&amp;#x27;ll cause the singularity and then that&amp;#x27;ll turn into AGI and then that&amp;#x27;ll turn into ASI and it&amp;#x27;ll make everybody immortal and we&amp;#x27;ll all be in outer space with the glowing white holographic vr pods&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893202&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893157&lt;br&gt;as long as there is bbc in space&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893218&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889737&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;It turns out the 180k/yr &amp;quot;product manager&amp;quot; was actually only worth 45k/yr&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sounds right to me&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893242&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IT&amp;#x27;S OGRE&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893270&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889737&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;People (retards) forget that Rome was the most profitable and powerful city in the world and that all the majority of citizens did all day was go to the Villas of the most powerful billionaires and praise them each morning to receive their daily cash handout - or go to the games and cheer their team on.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;People (retards) forget that Dubai and other states are literal paradises based upon SAAAAR! slavery and oil money.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Repeat after me: אֵין כָּל חָדָשׁ תַּחַת הַשָּׁמֶשׁ&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893276&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893157&lt;br&gt;human intelligence is peak, there&amp;#x27;s nothing beyond it&lt;br&gt;it&amp;#x27;s also very overrated, nobody listens to smartass nerds, be they ai or not&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;you should uhhhh stop polluting and uhhh colonize mars or something&lt;br&gt;ok who cares&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893292&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889737&lt;br&gt;Btw in my club, you can find paid premium content from Citrini and others practically for free.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893311&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889814&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;but do not it wield you&lt;br&gt;145 IQ indeed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893335&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is me. I make $150K a year in GTM and about to get cut in the next couple months.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I have a decade of experience and fully expect to never find a job again. The first 3 months gonna be chill af tho.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893530&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889737&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;• But fired workers stop spending. Companies weaken. They buy more AI to cut costs. More layoffs. Less spending. A negative feedback loop with no natural brake.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ackshully that&amp;#x27;s a positive feedback loop.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894488&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889737&lt;br&gt;This post was written by ai&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Why is Eric Trump deleting all his WLFI and Ethereum posts? — 16 replies — 45.8/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61893430</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61893430?lm=1771908586</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:49:46 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Why is Eric Trump deleting all his WLFI and Ethereum posts?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61893430'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 16 • Updated: 2026-02-24 04:49 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why is Eric Trump deleting all his WLFI and Ethereum posts?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893439&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893430&lt;br&gt;Because the drumpf family is about to be exposed for their crypto crimes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893440&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893430&lt;br&gt;lol xD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893448&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Good disgount obbortunities&lt;br&gt;Low brice&amp;#x27;s de de de&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893504&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893430&lt;br&gt;lol when will these fools realize deleting doesn&amp;#x27;t do shit. once you post, it&amp;#x27;s there forever&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893514&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;should we short WLFI bros&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893518&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893430&lt;br&gt;i hate to break it to you, but the trumps already made their money. they dumped their bags a long time ago and just pretending to still be invested&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893519&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As much as a btc red dildo to 30k would hurt me mentally and physically, it&amp;#x27;s the only way link has a chance at climbing back into the top 5&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893521&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893430&lt;br&gt;i told u about tether dude i warned u&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893576&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893430&lt;br&gt;iran sheaningans&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893620&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893521&lt;br&gt;Explain...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893636&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893430&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893934&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893576&lt;br&gt;and probably more tariff fuckery&lt;br&gt;Or pedophilia&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894002&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;makes me feel good knowing this idiot has no control over the market. its all smoke and mirrors&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894467&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893519&lt;br&gt;So you want Link to be one of the smartest kids in special ed?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894503&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893521&lt;br&gt;lmao tether fud, it really is a bear market&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894504&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893430&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;deleting all his WLFI and Ethereum posts&lt;br&gt;Well mostly because ETH is a dogshit chain. That&amp;#x27;s just a fact.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>we are STILL dumping btw — 6 replies — 15.7/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61894396</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61894396?lm=1771908470</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:47:50 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;we are STILL dumping btw&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61894396'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 6 • Updated: 2026-02-24 04:47 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;we are STILL dumping btw&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894408&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894396&lt;br&gt;crypto is still over. many just havent realized. Also, BBC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894437&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894396&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;ll care when we hit -75% and my buy orders start to fill&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894449&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894396&lt;br&gt;&amp;quot;we&amp;quot; hahahahahahahahhahahaa&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894456&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;who cares. not selling. see you in 4 years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894485&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894449&lt;br&gt;OP has to be larping. there is no one who can solve the new captchas yet still thinks crypto isn&amp;#x27;t over&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894498&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894437&lt;br&gt;so you just leave money on cex in -90% buy orders? at 0%. just rotting away. finally in 2026 it may hit? liar&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>&gt;lost life savings of $250k on BTC calls at the top Im killing myself — 16 replies — 12.5/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891249</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891249?lm=1771905233</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 03:53:53 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;&amp;gt;lost life savings of $250k on BTC calls at the top Im killing myself&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891249'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 16 • Updated: 2026-02-24 03:53 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;lost life savings of $250k on BTC calls at the top&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Im killing myself&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891258&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891249&lt;br&gt;Are you leveraged? If no then you didn&amp;#x27;t lose a penny. If you do nothing, you win&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891265&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891249&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891273&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891258&lt;br&gt;Of course it was leveraged&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891311&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Variations of this are always said but it&amp;#x27;s worth repeating: you only fail when you give up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891317&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891249&lt;br&gt;Moron. Keep staying poor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891931&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891249&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;lost life savings of $250k&lt;br&gt;you were gonna die anyway&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892346&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891311&lt;br&gt;this and&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891931&lt;br&gt;this&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you&amp;#x27;re stupid enough as a person to invest in something like ones and zeroes, that 250K was going to be wasted by your stupidity in some other way anyways.&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s okay though. You&amp;#x27;re allowed to be a stupid person and still live, so go out there, smell the flowers, feel the sunshine, and be stupid to the max!&lt;br&gt;No need to end it. Life is beautiful, and so are you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892392&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;you can make it all back anon, I believe in you.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;just ask your family members for some money and put it all on the line, 20x leverage long btc right now and you will win.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892878&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891249&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892892&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891249&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Do you ever self reflect on how fucking stupid and greedy you are. And that you actually deserve this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892898&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891249&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Don&amp;#x27;t worry, the rotation from gold into shitcoins is just around the corner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892902&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891311&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;No you fail when you get cleaned out on leveraged bets. Your stupid cunt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892914&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891249&lt;br&gt;God will provide you with new opportunities in life. You just can&amp;#x27;t expect to know what they look like. Being humble and helpful to society is what pleases God.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893006&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891249&lt;br&gt;You were retarded enough to put your life savings on Bitcoin options?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894333&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891249&lt;br&gt;Another black nigger down&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894365&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;NPC volume ticking along steadily&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;not crazy spikes&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;but consistent flow&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;steady traffic means steady attention&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>the future of BTC — 2 replies — 8.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61894522</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61894522?lm=1771909539</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 05:05:39 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;the future of BTC&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61894522'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 2 • Updated: 2026-02-24 05:05 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;screencap this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894525&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;wow cant wait to take on insane amounts of risk for such little gain thanks OP also the past always repeats exactly as before&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894543&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;4x in just 3 short years&lt;br&gt;Zoomers are right&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;No additional replies in the latest window.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>WHY IS THIS HAPPENING — 2 replies — 8.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61894507</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61894507?lm=1771909097</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:58:17 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;WHY IS THIS HAPPENING&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61894507'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 2 • Updated: 2026-02-24 04:58 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHY IS THIS HAPPENING&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894520&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894507&lt;br&gt;Because the crypto president extracted the goyim and kept all the money for himself&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894523&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894520&lt;br&gt;I should of fucking sold holy fuck im down 70k&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;No additional replies in the latest window.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Day 517 Of Bobo Rekt in Anus Posting Until BTC is at 180K — 6 replies — 7.2/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891862</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891862?lm=1771906829</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:20:29 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Day 517 Of Bobo Rekt in Anus Posting Until BTC is at 180K&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891862'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 6 • Updated: 2026-02-24 04:20 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891865&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891862&lt;br&gt;KILL YOURSELF YOU STOIPUD PIECE OF SHIUT&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891938&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891865&lt;br&gt;you sound nervous&lt;br&gt;it&amp;#x27;s going for a rally again&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891962&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891938&lt;br&gt;ITS GOING TO FUCKING ZEROoo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892012&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;funny this guy calls himself a statistician, kept calling the bottom from 90k to 80k to 76k back in feb and march 2025, said the july crabbing was bullish, thought we would start mooning in january, told you to sell gold for bitcoin saying it was topping out when it was in the 4000s while btc was bottomed in the 80-90k&amp;#x27;s, thought we would no longer have 50% drawdowns, supercycle hopium, this time is unironically different hopium, hash rate hopium, bayesian trend hopium etc&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892022&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892012&lt;br&gt;you want him soooo bad&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894439&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892012&lt;br&gt;OP and bullsimps utterly mogged yet again&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Wednesday NVDA earnings. — 6 replies — 4.5/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891159</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891159?lm=1771905077</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 03:51:17 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Wednesday NVDA earnings.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891159'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 6 • Updated: 2026-02-24 03:51 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Will it nuke the stock market finally?&lt;br&gt;I think everybody expects a serious drop.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892432&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891159&lt;br&gt;bumperino&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893720&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891159&lt;br&gt;5-7% drop then recession begins and we crab for another 5 years or more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893774&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891159&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;spends 1 $ trillerino on AI&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;stock goes up&lt;br&gt;you can&amp;#x27;t win, Bobo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893806&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How could it be bad lol. They probably have insane numbers. They sold out their product for the entire year. I mean seriously, what are you expecting?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894343&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893806&lt;br&gt;they smash past earnings every single quarter and the whole market rugs in response without fail.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894352&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It will have great earnings, then inflated apex and the street will dump it slightly after hours. Small recovery the next day, sector will crab the remainder of the week unless there is news.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Link vs XRP — 45 replies — 13.7/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889600</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889600?lm=1771897991</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 01:53:11 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Link vs XRP&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889600'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 45 • Updated: 2026-02-24 01:53 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;When will the gap close? Link came within a hair of flipping xrp in January ‘21. We all know that Link is everything Xrp fraudulently claims to be so it makes sense that this chart should flip soon enough. Will it be gradual or violent? Will it flip because xrp crashes or because Link moons? &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most importantly where are some places you can use Link as collateral to borrow Xrp to take full advantage of the trade of the century?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889606&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m so tired.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889622&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889600&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889606&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889620&lt;br&gt;Link is scam&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Buy XRP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890828&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889600&lt;br&gt;It will be violent, and partly due to xrp crashing, but in no small part due to link pumping. Its going to happen after Clarity act + full staking release and neet nodes. So 2050 at this rate&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890840&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890828&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;dude, le clarity&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;le full staking&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;le neet nodes&lt;br&gt;never happening, sweetie&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890870&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889600&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889606&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889620&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889622&lt;br&gt;the only usecase any of these has is XLM; because africans are still trading phone minutes as currency and XLM is a reasonable replacement&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;XRP and LINK are complete LARPs that nobody even trusts&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;and i don&amp;#x27;t even give a shit about giving africans currency. but its literally the only thing your larp does in the physical world&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890891&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890390&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;common enterprise&lt;br&gt;You bought a product, not a share. Everything you just wrote proves this is a speculation and not an investment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891011&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889827&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;https://ripple.com/insights/institutional-defi-on-xrpl-scaling-real-world-finance-with-xrp-at-the-core/&lt;br&gt;You keep posting same article like its some kind of mic drop moment. As if linking it over and over suddenly turns it into undeniable proof. It doesn’t lol Youre taking a CEOs words at face value because you think hes personally invested in making you rich. Thats not how this works. CEOs promote their companies and his job is to literally sell you XRP.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891035&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889600&lt;br&gt;Thanks spammy.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889620&lt;br&gt;/thread&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891717&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891011&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m not. It is literally the products they are building and the material they are releasing detailing it to shareholders. Link sell directly to retail every time there is a minor pump. You are literally saying nothing but standing in a way where you think if you come across as affirmative in a direct way it will seem like you are. Lol You are just doing what you accuse me of (which I am not) saying we can&amp;#x27;t trust it to be true because it is relying on the words of someone. It literally isn&amp;#x27;t. They are structuring XRPL core amendment pushes and having their staff code them based on the product suite fit detailed in the article. They made multiple multibillion dollar acquisitions, including a fucking prime broker to actuate it all. And most importantly, the majority of their treasury is in XRP and their products are ALL made more efficient and cost efficient using it and they are incentivized to increase the price of XRP they have in escrow and cannot sell, unlike CLL who dump what was supposed to be operator rewards on retail always and are LITERALLY a fraud designed to milk your savings (exactly what you project Ripple to be, which it isn&amp;#x27;t because the XRPL actually solves efficiencies instead of sticking a tollbooth in the middle of process for literally no reason like a jewish parasite). The entire XRPL is designed to automatically use XRP for auto-bridging between assets etc. Your argument sucks and it is hilarious that it actually applies to link, which you are capable of seeing but literally don&amp;#x27;t care because you are in a literal cult pretending to object but just obsessively committed to a project that is the least morally redeemable or utility having one in all of crypto for literally no reason than ego and entrenched specific coin cultism. Really odd and gay.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891755&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890083&lt;br&gt;Extreme cope. SWIFT said it would take 15 years MINIMUM to even get a product active. I am not sorry to let you know that by that time SWIFT will have 100% missed the boat and payments will have been completely revolutionized, not needing them. You hitched your dingy to a big ship, but it turned out it was the Titanic, which we all always said. Way too little way too late presuming the ethgate lawfare would win but it didn&amp;#x27;t. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890250&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;MPT/permissioned dex is the standard&lt;br&gt;No it hasn&amp;#x27;t. You literally don&amp;#x27;t know what either of those things are. No other ledger at scale has a built in dex and amm and protocol layer compliance like permissioned dex nor the broadness of the MPT standard. It definitely has been The Standard, but not in the way you think. MPT is not &amp;quot;wrapped assets.&amp;quot; Here is an AI slop video that is actually informative which possibly someone at your level of research will be able to be spoonfed by:&lt;br&gt;https://youtu.be/3kYXW_o-N4Y&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890519&lt;br&gt;Top cope in thread&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891887&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890891&lt;br&gt;Everything written proves it&amp;#x27;s a security anon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891914&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890307&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890390&lt;br&gt;The only thing that needs to happen to settle the debate is someone suing. And given chainlink seemingly gives zero fucks about it&amp;#x27;s holders it&amp;#x27;s probably long overdue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892108&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891887&lt;br&gt;It has an etf already bro it’s a defacto commodity and will soon be enshrined in law as a commodity. Also may I just congratulate you on your point that ripple is incentivised to increase the price of Xrp since that is most of their treasury, unlike CLL who also has most of their treasury in Link but is not incentivised to increase the price. I thought that was most salient.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892122&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889600&lt;br&gt;Dunno man, but the best times with link have been when I forgot about it during the bear and came back to big gains&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892185&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891717&lt;br&gt;So other than the CEOs word, what proof do you have they&amp;#x27;re integrating XRP into everything?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892337&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892108&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;CLL who also has most of their treasury in Link but is not incentivised to increase the price.&lt;br&gt;And they never will.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892414&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891011&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Youre taking a CEOs words at face value because you think hes personally invested in making you rich. Thats not how this works. CEOs promote their companies and his job is to literally sell you link&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892515&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892337&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892530&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889600&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;When will the gap close?&lt;br&gt;when the token will be needed for functioning of the network&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892592&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891914&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The only thing that needs to happen to settle the debate is someone suing. And given chainlink seemingly gives zero fucks about it&amp;#x27;s holders it&amp;#x27;s probably long overdue.&lt;br&gt;/thread&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892659&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892185&lt;br&gt;I already mentioned it you fucking retard. You can see the ledger amendment history that they have spent their own dev money and time developing, their acquisitions of Hidden Road, etc. their getting binance listing RLUSD on the XRPL, the fact the early team specifically coded the ledger to explicitly default to its use and to save several percentage points over Ripplenet alone by doing so, the fact that they locked the vast bulk of their corporate treasury up in timed release in it, the fact they fund and partner with multiple large banks to drive and encourage its use and adoption, and the fact the services they are building out literally optimize using it and offer counterparty-less feature that no other asset onchain can, and the fact that they already use it in their business. They literally legally can&amp;#x27;t use it in most contexts yet but with clarity their business can become much more efficient and as a result their core holding increases in value. There is LITERALLY no reason to argue they are not building for its use other than being butthurt that it is true and trying to repress reality like a faggot. They literally have Fednow service providers running XRPL nodes and big banks who are their largest outside investors issuing bonds that reward in XRP (who were celebrated recently in their specific crypto efforts by the financial regulator of Japan) and are partnering with DBS (biggest bank in Singapore (Switzerland of Asia) and Franklin Templeton (trillion plus dollars AUM) building out a repo market on the XRPL. They got ONDO issuing on the XRPL, one of the largest asset managers in Europe/England doing same while basically no one is getting headway in England, Societe General (one of biggest banks in Europe) expanding to include XRP for their euro stablecoin which can bridge to RLUSD using XRP, etc. Literally everything they do builds around corporately driving XRP&amp;#x27;s adoption, literally just fleshing out a business sweet around it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892679&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892659&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892185&lt;br&gt;This isn&amp;#x27;t even 10% of what could be said partnership etc. wise. XRP and link are different in that XRP actually improves business performance and has a reason to exist and incentivizes use in products. Link is literally just a toll booth jew token to insert costs where they would not technologically exist.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892688&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892108&lt;br&gt;The difference is CLL dumps on retail all the time and their business is not improved by the operation of link, it is a technologically pointless token, literally. Ripple hasn&amp;#x27;t sold publicly in over 5 years to retail.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892697&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889600&lt;br&gt;It will most likely be extremely violent the likes of which has literally never been seen before. I am very excited for us.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892933&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891755&lt;br&gt;you&amp;#x27;re practically crying, and they did not say that. I&amp;#x27;m sorry you bet on the wrong horse backed by criminals. to think swift is going to lose is unbelievable amounts of stupidity. haha why am i even talking to you, cya&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892973&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892933&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893028&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892933&lt;br&gt;I mean you&amp;#x27;re retarded and wrong but the cripplets are retarded and right. If that helps at all. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Idk if you link cucks have ever visited the /XSG/ threads but they are hardly ever discussing &amp;quot;muh utility&amp;quot; or even acknowledging other crypto. I&amp;#x27;m pretty sure they&amp;#x27;re currently going /X/ mode and trying to get a retard to be a sacrifice volunteer Mayan style to pump xrp. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Which is hilarious. Anyway buy silver crypto fags.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893103&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892933&lt;br&gt;Really pathetic cope and projection&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893669&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893028&lt;br&gt;Will it work though?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893717&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893669&lt;br&gt;I meaann... it works for the jews&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893824&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893717&lt;br&gt;Kek&lt;br&gt;SACRIFICE SPAMMY 2026&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893980&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;fuck stinks&lt;br&gt;hate &amp;#x27;em&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Fake and Gay Economy — 100 replies — 11.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61871520</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61871520?lm=1771877246</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 20:07:26 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Fake and Gay Economy&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61871520'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 100 • Updated: 2026-02-23 20:07 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;When will this gay as economy finally collapse and how can i profit from it?&lt;br&gt;Its ridiculous the woman at our workplace contribute nothing to the company and make more money than i do&lt;br&gt;Its infuriating we just had a bunch of lay offs and we lost some of oir best workers but somehow a bunch of HR shits who do nothing all day still work here&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871530&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HR is a necessary function, chud&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871569&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871530&lt;br&gt;For what?&lt;br&gt;Genuinely why do we need it to this extent?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871755&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871569&lt;br&gt;Protect the corp from lawsuits&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883781&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883644&lt;br&gt;You meant to say inclined. You are more inclined. Akin means &amp;quot;similar to&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883784&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882869&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;incel&lt;br&gt;Im so confused as to what that term means, involuntarily celibate? But its not being celibate if your literally having sex. Such a weird term clearly carrying different meaning. What is the point of using a term that literally has no definition to its meaning, you might aswell speak in baby noises at this point.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884146&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;guys, ALL we have to do is called women like this ugly chopped shit to their face as much as possible and they will lose all motivation to live&lt;br&gt;they are SO fragile in that regard.&lt;br&gt;next time you are walking down the street and see some bitch like this just start yelling “YOURE UGLY”&lt;br&gt;they will spend the next week and a half minimum making reddit posts about it and getting their SSRI prescription upped.&lt;br&gt;don’t ever engage with any ideas or thoughts they have. just pick apart their appearance. you look like a fridge and a stick insect at the same time. your fake dyed hair sucks. you have clown makeup on, you must have learned how to do makeup at the circus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884272&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883066&lt;br&gt;So you&amp;#x27;re saying ceo&amp;#x27;s willingly burn 75% of their money for fun?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884291&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884272&lt;br&gt;he&amp;#x27;s saying the ceo is a fucking retard&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884297&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;I want to shove my cock deep into the first one from behind. Just lift the skirt and blast the pussy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884717&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883784&lt;br&gt;Yes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884737&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871569&lt;br&gt;Without HR you could complete the work, banter and build a genuine camaraderie with your common co-worker, but we cant have unions, and its better if you&amp;#x27;re all divided and conquered, here&amp;#x27;s a harpy to make your life hell&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884742&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873193&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872087&lt;br&gt;These niggers actually get it. All problems flow downstream from jews controlling the issuance of your (since 1913) fake and gay fiat debt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885902&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873611&lt;br&gt;You must be over 18 to use this site&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886326&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882442&lt;br&gt;Yeah this kind of mega über schizos who believe in fe and no nuke use this phrase holy shit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886329&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882442&lt;br&gt;And yes the idea of space is falsifiable you absolute schizo. Satellites wouldn&amp;#x27;t even work without it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886359&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883784&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Such a weird term clearly carrying different meaning. What is the point of using a term that literally has no definition to its meaning&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s just people overusing words or ideas to oblivion, where they lose all context. It&amp;#x27;s like the worst insult was being called gay way back, then it was subverted (actually gay is cool), then it became retarded, then it got subverted (actually retarded is cool because you&amp;#x27;re not trying), then it become autistic, then it became subverted (actually it&amp;#x27;s interesting to be autistic), now it&amp;#x27;s random baby talk by gen alpha (mog, cortisol spike, chopped, unc, lil bro, frame, aura farming, 67, incel, cuk). Now it&amp;#x27;s being subverted by people overusing the terms even if they don&amp;#x27;t apply to anyone or anything in the context at all. Someone not having sex for a week = incel. Someone having a slightly embarrassing moment (cortisol spike), someone better looking walking past (mogged), doing something that&amp;#x27;s barely good (aura farming), having a strong presence even if it&amp;#x27;s completely autistic and retarded (frame). Or like when old people started wearing skateboard shirts having no clue what it was, or everyone and their dog wearing an off white shirt. People make shit gay eventually, it&amp;#x27;s a universal law.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886363&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;work office job (engineer) with way too many women and diversity hire niggers and Indians who do nothing all day&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;get new (white) South African Vice President&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;calls us all together&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;in his funny accent tells us he’s an engineer and knows the business and there will be changes&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;tells us he will cut 20% of the workforce soon&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;everyone is shit scared and the normie femoids start climbing over each other trying to save their useless asses&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;office girlies start spreading rumours about everyone and everything in desperate attempt to make themselves look better&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;don’t give a fuck, I’m a technician and actually make money for the company unlike them&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Vice President just observes the shit show and never comments on anything while he feels out the office&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;come in one Monday&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;literally all blacks are gone&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;all except the actual useful Indians are gone&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;he culled every single female that we all knew had jewish make believe adult daycare jobs&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;only kept the old hag secretaries that actually do a great job&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kek, based white nigger. Turns out all it takes is some third world coloniser to clean this woke shit up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886555&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872076&lt;br&gt;We are not capitalist.&lt;br&gt;We have been Trotskyist since the end of WW2.&lt;br&gt;Having a central bank is plank #5 of the commie manifesto.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886576&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884742&lt;br&gt;It was a bit delayed until after 1913.&lt;br&gt;They couldn’t go full fakeconomy immediately, or they would have been shut down.&lt;br&gt;They had to wait and boil the frog slowly, using the occasional crisis as a speed boost.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886586&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t ever interact with HR once I&amp;#x27;m hired until I&amp;#x27;m inevitably fired. From where comes the HR hate? Are they the ones who actually make the decisions to fire us?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886684&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;this board is dead as shit holy fuck&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886687&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61886684&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s the weekend. It picks up when the market is open.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886692&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;d fuck all of them. At the same time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887220&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61886363&lt;br&gt;Sounds illegal and fake. This is such an obvious thing to do, there must be a reason it doesn&amp;#x27;t actually happen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889346&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s not going to collapse... bill gates will grow some cheap bug burgers and psyop all the women to think it&amp;#x27;s healthy and great for the environment... so we can continue feeding billions of women to do nothing but work in an office.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889382&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61886363&lt;br&gt;How was he able to be able to gauge who&amp;#x27;s useful and who&amp;#x27;s not in such a short period of time?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889387&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889346&lt;br&gt;Also, paying women to do nothing is one of the best birth controls there is. They are incapable of dating down. Sorry, just the messenger. bullshit jobs, especially for women, will never end until picrel collapses.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unfortunately, the jews also don&amp;#x27;t want picrel to collapse because then their banks would go broke. So we&amp;#x27;re stuck in hell.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891731&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882869&lt;br&gt;nice&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891770&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889387&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;implying men would ever fuck someone below them&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891847&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891770&lt;br&gt;are you literally retarded?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891874&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891847&lt;br&gt;Chad isn&amp;#x27;t fucking chubby chicks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891915&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;hmm thigh boots&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892308&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61886684&lt;br&gt;correct&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Mac minis are the new ASIC miners — 13 replies — 8.7/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61893434</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61893434?lm=1771904476</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 03:41:16 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Mac minis are the new ASIC miners&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61893434'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 13 • Updated: 2026-02-24 03:41 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mac minis are like the ASIC miners except they do actual work instead of mining bitcoin for no reason.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893585&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893434&lt;br&gt;What are people even doing with their 50 mac mini AI agents?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893611&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893585&lt;br&gt;Its like a team of 50 indians&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893612&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893611&lt;br&gt;Just imagine the sound of 50 echoing good morning sirs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893619&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;how is this monetized? and why a mac mini specifically and not a mini pc that isnt stupidly expensive?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893682&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893434&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Letting redditors LARP as le hyperadvanced skynet AIs all day&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Actual work&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893699&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893619&lt;br&gt;Apple&amp;#x27;s M chips are pretty decent at running AI models locally and the Mac Mini is pretty reasonably priced on the used market. I have a few bullshit Internet businesses that AI models automate 90+% of off one of these. Why you would need as many as are in the picture, I couldn&amp;#x27;t tell you&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893943&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893611&lt;br&gt;so, useless?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893682&lt;br&gt;that&amp;#x27;s what it seems like. the new funko pops&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893971&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893434&lt;br&gt;Probably associated with Mark Wilcox. Best to avoid.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894122&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893619&lt;br&gt;The latest apple minis are 5x faster than equivalent costing PCs at running AI&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894156&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61893434&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;give the mac mini all of my personal info, financial data, passwords, internet browsing history etc. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;in return I get...... a bot that answers emails for me &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wow. This is the future!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894238&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For what purpose? Could you actually get any reasonable return on investment?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894286&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61894156&lt;br&gt;The whole point is that you don&amp;#x27;t have to&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61894324&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There’s a few anecdotal reports of people making money with ai which is driving fomo, but in reality nobody is making money running these bots&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Financial independence / retire early — 41 replies — 8.2/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61884958</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61884958?lm=1771891928</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 00:12:08 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Financial independence / retire early&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61884958'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 41 • Updated: 2026-02-24 00:12 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;How&amp;#x27;s FIRE going for you, anons?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884964&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884958&lt;br&gt;Well I&amp;#x27;m looking into LCOL countries I can retire to because waiting until I&amp;#x27;m a multi millionaire in the states is not viable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884966&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884958&lt;br&gt;Just need a 7x then I&amp;#x27;m good. Already have rope if ready if I don&amp;#x27;t reach the goal in 5 years&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884967&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884958&lt;br&gt;i have about 3m networth but haven&amp;#x27;t quit my job yet. making too much money but want to quit real bad. i took a 4 day weekend recently and got bored because i have no life and hobbies because my job dominates my life and i have no energy left over to develop my personal life after work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885003&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ok maybe a 3 unit building&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885030&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884999&lt;br&gt;You literally cannot fix the toilets yourself. Under IRC §4975 you are considered a &amp;quot;disqualified&amp;quot; person. Basically you can own it but you can never touch it. Very gay way to &amp;#x27;own&amp;#x27; something.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885054&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;way ahead of schedule.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Full time job income (104K + 11K in retirement)&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Cost of living 32K&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Fully owned apartment(450K)&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;308K in liquidish assets&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;90K in retirement&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;2K coming in every month from passive revenue from a side business (vidya gaems)&lt;br&gt;In 7-8 years i will probably reach full FIRE. But i&amp;#x27;m releasing new products this year. If i can have similar success i will probably just Barista FIRE living the gamedev dream.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885059&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884967&lt;br&gt;Dude, just quit. You&amp;#x27;ll probably decompress after a month or two, then you can re-evaluate. If you decide you need to work, then you can just go apply to some jobs. Maybe you&amp;#x27;ll decide you want to work in a library or something stupid like that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885062&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885030&lt;br&gt;that fucking sucks what is Cardone talking about then?&lt;br&gt;retirement money is just going to the bank then when I starve to death. maybe that was their plan all along. &lt;br&gt;take the 10% penalty + taxes ? now it&amp;#x27;s a duplex maybe in a cold flyover state&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885102&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just had my 2nd kid.&lt;br&gt;Already gave up and accepted that I&amp;#x27;ll be waging til I die.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885131&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884958&lt;br&gt;Pretty good despite the recent market drawdown. I stopped working 9 months ago and moved to a luxury condo in Thailand. Expenses are relatively low but I&amp;#x27;m still paying my mortgage and car note in America. I get a little bit of income from trading options and renting out my house to my younger sister. I&amp;#x27;m financially set for the rest of my life but I&amp;#x27;m still figuring out what I want to do as far as family, kids, etc.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885135&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885062&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885030&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884986&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;ok I found this. instead of self directed IRA to have to roll it into a business startup&lt;br&gt;so don&amp;#x27;t an hero yet &lt;br&gt;or put me down as your beneficiary first&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;https://www.bankrate.com/loans/small-business/what-are-robs/#:~:text=Key%20takeaways,penalties%20are%20associated%20with%20ROBS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885141&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884967&lt;br&gt;Nigger. Based on the 4% rule you can draw about 120k yearly off investments and statistically never run out of money. Wife and I retired early w/ Lite Fire. No debt. Last year our gross income was $55,000. We bought and sold a RV, Saw the Grand Canyon, Zion, Bryce Canyon, Rushmore. Took a 21 day cruise from west coast through Panama Canal, Cruised out of Florida for 3 weeks and hung out in Fort Lauderdale for 2. Did 2 more week in the Caribbean. Have a 20 day transatlantic cruise from NYC to Sicily booked with stops in 9 ports in April. Tons of midweek short trips seeing cool shit. Leaving work is an adjustment definitely but I have never been happier. See the world, meet people, always with an eye to relocation. Picrel is heading into Cartagena Columbia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885152&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884967&lt;br&gt;I was just like you before I decided to walk away. I call it &amp;quot;golden handcuffs&amp;quot; when a job pays so well that it makes you feel obligated to keep going even though you don&amp;#x27;t need the money. Your job feels like your identity but I promise you&amp;#x27;ll forget about it after you quit and find new hobbies and a gf.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887260&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884974&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884996&lt;br&gt;Japan is not a lcol area. Its cheaper compared to the west but not Thailand/Vietnam cheap. My plan is to live 90 days visa free there a year and live frugally elsewhere for the rest of the year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887270&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884958&lt;br&gt;Closing in on luxury fat FIRE thanks to gold/silver/oil/uranium. Fuck crypto.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887292&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t want to retire early, cuz id probably just be doing the same thing without getting paid for it, but i have enough money to be comfortable for now&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887302&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I am starting to realize the whole game plan of FIRE is just giving me reason to wake up in the morning, something to look forward to. I dont think I will really be that much happier once I achieve my dream of semi financial freedom.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887313&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887292&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;id probably just be doing the same thing without getting paid for it&lt;br&gt;Your job is your hobby? Congrats. What do you do?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887338&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s not really going.&lt;br&gt;Would take me getting my inheritance and buying the bottom of the next global market crash and riding the recovery wave with everything I can throw in during it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887601&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;uhh im 38. been retired since 32. probably unretiring soon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887625&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887313&lt;br&gt;gay prostitute&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890044&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887302&lt;br&gt;frugality is like a game, to see how little i can spend each month&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890071&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885054&lt;br&gt;what&amp;#x27;s your side business anon? reseller?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890085&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;is 1.5M too little to retire?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I round tripped 8 figs being greedy&lt;br&gt;its all i have left&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890089&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890085&lt;br&gt;depends where you live&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890151&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885102&lt;br&gt;My #2 is 4 months old now. Thanks to the fire-induced frugality I was able to reduce my hours for half a year by 10 hours a week which was priceless in itself. Will probably also wage forever but probably only 20 hours or so per week.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884958&lt;br&gt;We managed to pay off the house @32. other than that I only have 15k cash and 50k in the MSCI. &lt;br&gt;The plan was to retire @40 but unrealistic unless I win the lottery ( and I don&amp;#x27;t even play)&lt;br&gt;So yes full fire is impossible right now, but on the plus side: we need less than 2k/ month for a very comfortable life. &lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m converting a part of the house to a rental flat atm which should bring another 600 per month and allow for tax deductions.&lt;br&gt;After installing solar this year my electricity bill should drop from 110 to 40 per month. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;So all in all we can have a cozy lifestyle for an acceptable trade off in lifetime. &lt;br&gt;Wife would like to work 20 hours/week in 10 years or so, I should be able to fully switch to do freelance consultant work in my niche ( or not. Her meager wage combined with the surplus of the next 10 years should easily pay for everything and give the kids a nice tailwind) &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m putting 180 bucks/month per kind into an ETF which should become a nice 150k downpayment (infl.adj.) when they turn 27&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890181&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Never gonna happen on my income. Millennials are fucked out of retirement. At least I own all my shit and have actual children and a loyal wife.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890213&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I dont know what number to stop at..&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891226&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884968&lt;br&gt;Balkan and Baltic countries are cheap and super white. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fuck off if you&amp;#x27;re not white though. They&amp;#x27;re the most racist countries and that&amp;#x27;s what makes them awesome.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891591&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885054&lt;br&gt;What games?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892297&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884958&lt;br&gt;Currently putting about 50-60% of my net income into my mortgage. I&amp;#x27;ll have the ($200k) house paid off in April/May next year, and then I&amp;#x27;ll be close enough to financially independent to relax a bit. I also have about $180k in an index fund.&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m low maintenance so I can live on $10-15k a year after that, so I don&amp;#x27;t need a real job.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892307&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I’m not sure if it will be achievable since AI will replace most white collar jobs. I’ll be happy if I can just get coast FIRE. I thought that there might be another ten years of white collar work, but I’ve narrowed the timeline with these new models. Claude Code and Cowork are too promising. I just don’t think that there will be too many jobs by 2030.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893606&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884967&lt;br&gt;Buy and learn to ride motorcycles. Watch long way round.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>insider here, again. — 32 replies — 6.7/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61879263</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61879263?lm=1771892548</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 00:22:28 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;insider here, again.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61879263'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 32 • Updated: 2026-02-24 00:22 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;i hope you bought BBBY-WT BBBY-WARRANTS&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879648&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I have a few thousand of these along with shares what am I in for&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879767&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879648&lt;br&gt;getting dumped on by OP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879836&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879767&lt;br&gt;Due to my current occupation, I am prohibited from holding stocks, options, or similar investments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879895&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This you?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879921&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879767&lt;br&gt;idk I mean bed bath was once a huge American retail darling...the historic overstock chart is super schizo/presently quite low...these warrants are trading like a shitcoin which is funny...I also don&amp;#x27;t dislike lemonis. He&amp;#x27;s a media player and if you actually listened to some of his shit there does seem to be an interesting intersection between blockchain capabilities and homeownership etc...not financial advice of course just a variety of things I was peeking at when researching&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879944&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879263&lt;br&gt;no&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879999&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879836&lt;br&gt;What is your current occupation anon? Nothing revealing but in general etc...the exercise price of the warrants is $15...trading currently at less than a dollar it seems like a confusing deal...at this point if one likes the company wouldn&amp;#x27;t shares be the move? I did some modeling around warrant prices if the shares price goes to xyz and that is very interesting...also speaking of interesting what&amp;#x27;s the deal with the alleged cusip similarity to the old bbbyq shares?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880091&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879999&lt;br&gt;Financial system. I am not asking you to hold those warrants until they are exercised. I am asking you to hold them and sell the warrants when we can realize a substantial profit. Nice quads.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881477&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880091&lt;br&gt;Interesting. Wouldn&amp;#x27;t trading the warrants implicitly come with a short term capital gains tax insofar as its impossible to hold them over a year at this point? Would have to be some pretty fair gains to offset that 40% hit...anyways doesn&amp;#x27;t the warrants increasing in price also imply that the shares have gone up in price as well? I ran some informal modeling estimates using black scholes with iv, roughly .65 years to expiry and this is what I came up with: 15.5 bbby share price = 4.50ish warrant price...25 share price/12ish warrant price...60 share price/45ish warrant price...100 share price/85ish warrant price...200 share price 185ish warrant price...I make no claim as to the veracity of these numbers, just for fun. Anyways what do you see happening to the bbby stock price for these warrants to be worthwhile? Am I thinking on the right track in general?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881670&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879263&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881753&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879999&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881477&lt;br&gt;note the digis&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881916&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879263&lt;br&gt;Buy these if you want, but remember, these warrants are not related to the canceled BBBYQ/DK-Butterfly, reguardless of what the BBBYQ schizos say.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881980&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881916&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;nobody tell him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882152&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879263&lt;br&gt;I hold a few&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882389&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;why are americans starting to invest more into VT?&lt;br&gt;isn&amp;#x27;t america the greatest country on earth?&lt;br&gt;for me it has always been VOO&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882429&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;look at NPC holder distribution&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;there&amp;#x27;s no big dumps&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;base still present&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;conviction quietly intact&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884950&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880091&lt;br&gt;So you&amp;#x27;re allowed to buy warrants, won&amp;#x27;t your employer know you bought them?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885366&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get ready everyone. I don&amp;#x27;t think they will be able to kick the can after this sneeze. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885357&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886042&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;what about BBBYQ? i lost all my money. the little i&amp;#x27;ve earned since then i&amp;#x27;ve spent on equipment that will make me a self-made millionaire thanks to my own intellect and blood sweat and tears and not thanks to ryan cohen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886054&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61886042&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886916&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BUY&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887055&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61886042&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;he doesn&amp;#x27;t know what % of powerwash/lawncare businesses fail in their first two years.&lt;br&gt;I appreciate your entrepreneurial spirit, but this isn&amp;#x27;t the flex you think it is.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887380&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887055&lt;br&gt;i&amp;#x27;m not trying to flex i&amp;#x27;m saying the BBBYQ should pay off without having to double down on BBBYW as well. it&amp;#x27;s fucking ridiculous how you can do everything right and run into complete disasters in investing and in other things and getting trolled by random assholes like you as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887389&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ryan cohen and larry cheng are behaving like autistic wankers after making thousands of people lose their life savings and pulte is a clown if he was just grifting BBBYQ investors&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887406&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;and trump is apparently a rapist pedophile murderer who rigged the 2024 election with elon musk and mostly everyone on wall street is getting away with psychopathic scammers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887414&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887380&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;BBBYQ should pay of&lt;br&gt;There will be no payoff for BBBYQ, ever.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887426&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887414&lt;br&gt;then RC should be held accountable for grifting BBBYQ investors, it&amp;#x27;s insulting to everyone&amp;#x27;s intelligence to claimi he did nothing to take advantage of people who looked up to him. though GME maxis are insufferable so they kinda deserve to get scammed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887888&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887380&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m not trolling you, brother. You&amp;#x27;re right, sometimes you do everything right and shit sucks anyways. That&amp;#x27;s what the book of Job is about. You still need to keep the faith, like he did.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889098&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887380&lt;br&gt;BBBYW is more like a lifeboat for people who missed BBBYQ. If you held a fat stack (10,000 plus) of BBBYQ into cancellation then you are good.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890133&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889098&lt;br&gt;2,000 sh @ 038&lt;br&gt;I dont care&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892966&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No one is ever getting shit for canceled BBBYQ shares.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61893640&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882152&lt;br&gt;Every asset I own was red today&lt;br&gt;Besides my BBBY warrants&lt;br&gt;Thank you anon schizos for saving my portfolio a month ago with this knowledge&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>