<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>/biz/ Active (filtered, with replies)</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/</link><description>Filtered out: general, gme, bbbyq. OP + first 3 replies + last 30 replies.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 19:49:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>IMF says China needs stronger social protection — 7 replies — 26.5/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61877385</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61877385?lm=1771615989</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 19:33:09 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;IMF says China needs stronger social protection&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61877385'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 7 • Updated: 2026-02-20 19:33 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why doesn&amp;#x27;t China care about the elderly? This is ageist.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877393&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;china, please be gooder goys&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;t. IMF&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877397&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;translation&lt;br&gt;please stop inventing and manufacturing shit your going to be a world power; instead be a [[[consumer]]] based economy where jews get printed money from your fed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877419&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877385&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Social protection expenditure includes health expenditure.&lt;br&gt;They can just make their health care more expensive on paper and then IMF is wrong. I need to make it bros, the amount of stupidity in the world is too great for me to remain poor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880207&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877385&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;We NEED you to CONSUME, we need you in more DEBT.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880246&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877385&lt;br&gt;OECD countries are not a good role model&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Household savings are a good thing, China just needs to ensure the savings are channeled more into productive investments rather than real estate speculation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880279&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877385&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;excessive households savings&lt;br&gt;I can practically feel the hand rubbing from here&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880328&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bros it&amp;#x27;s getting ugly for the West. The IMF is having to beg for China to stop winning so much.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>TARIFFS BTFO — 9 replies — 21.3/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61878997</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61878997?lm=1771615417</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 19:23:37 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;TARIFFS BTFO&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61878997'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 9 • Updated: 2026-02-20 19:23 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;tariffs BTFO&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;america up&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;europe up&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;asia down (LMAO)&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;crypto up&lt;br&gt;Post animal spirits of the bullish kind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879108&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I lost all my Mumu memes in a boating accident&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879131&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878997&lt;br&gt;I only have bobina memes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879165&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879133&lt;br&gt;dats nuts nigga&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879572&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879131&lt;br&gt;same she mogs mumu and mumus are retarded, well i have the crab too she&amp;#x27;s slutty&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880217&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878997&lt;br&gt; Trump will reapply the tariffs utilizing Section 232 and 301. All existing tariffs will continue. Literal nothingburger that media wants you to salivate over. It will however block future admins from using emergency powers to enact domestic taxes. Based outcome in every way except Lutnick.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880242&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880217&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Trump will reapply the tariffs utilizing Section 232 and 301. All existing tariffs will continue&lt;br&gt;yeah no. now cope&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880253&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879133&lt;br&gt;dats nuts nigga&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880262&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878997&lt;br&gt;bullis hxrp&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>OOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO — 3 replies — 12.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61880331</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61880331?lm=1771616373</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 19:39:33 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;OOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61880331'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 3 • Updated: 2026-02-20 19:39 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;OOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880347&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TODAYS NEWS WAS NOT BULLISH&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880353&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ARE YOU NOT ENTERTAINED?!?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880360&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;not gonna pass 70&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;No additional replies in the latest window.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>I can't believe I'm saying this but — 3 replies — 12.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61880231</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61880231?lm=1771616066</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 19:34:26 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;I can&amp;#x27;t believe I&amp;#x27;m saying this but&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61880231'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 3 • Updated: 2026-02-20 19:34 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chainlink (Ticker: LINK) is actually floating my portfolio today&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880248&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;it&amp;#x27;s floating in a swamp to your grave, stinkie&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880303&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880231&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;2017 ICO ETH scam token floats my entire portfolio&lt;br&gt;what a fucking retard lmao&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880332&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880231&lt;br&gt;Oh neat lets look. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;1 day chart&lt;br&gt;+2%&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;He&amp;#x27;s euphoric again&lt;br&gt;Let&amp;#x27;s check the 5yr&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Oh... oh my.... -73%&lt;br&gt;-73%&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;-73%&lt;br&gt;-73%&lt;br&gt;Anon... Link has no ROI... &lt;br&gt;Rotate at the next exit pump.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;No additional replies in the latest window.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>&gt;has a near infinite amount of acts that all have to be individually defeated in court So you DIDNT buy during the false… — 3 replies — 9.8/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61880276</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61880276?lm=1771615834</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 19:30:34 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;&amp;gt;has a near infinite amount of acts that all have to be individually defeated in court So you DIDNT buy during the false…&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61880276'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 3 • Updated: 2026-02-20 19:30 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;has a near infinite amount of acts that all have to be individually defeated in court&lt;br&gt;So you DIDNT buy during the false push right? Your not retarded enough to think it was going to end right? You&amp;#x27;re not one of those coping /biz/tards are you?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880286&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;wonder if the supreme court will brand him as a vexatious litigant kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880290&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He&amp;#x27;s honestly really funny&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880314&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880286&lt;br&gt;Can&amp;#x27;t be able to do that because they need to rule on all the individual acts, also they have been like 90% ruling in favor of him. Tariffs will stay on for his entire presidency but will just change act justification&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;No additional replies in the latest window.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>IMF calls on China to cut industrial subsidies in half — 110 replies — 352.3/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61872964</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61872964?lm=1771615815</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 19:30:15 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;IMF calls on China to cut industrial subsidies in half&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61872964'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 110 • Updated: 2026-02-20 19:30 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872971&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872964&lt;br&gt;This is a strategic move by the Chinese to kill off the competition in other countries so the Chinese companies can dominate the sectors and then raise the prices&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872974&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;i&amp;#x27;m sure china will get right on that&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872978&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;jews mad&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872971&lt;br&gt;they can do it forever without raising the prices&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877115&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875572&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875564&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874440&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I sincerely hope you&amp;#x27;re just too young or pol-brained to know any better, but just in case you aren&amp;#x27;t:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Chinese state does not give out money (or make sure other financiers are available to give out money) in order to create productive, competitive industry. They do it for 2 reasons:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;It lets them massively overproduce a good (solar panels, EVs, E-bikes, ect...) at a loss in order to crush foreign manufacturing bases and corner the production&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;It helps ensure employment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Half the reason for the boondoggle that has been OBOR is that it meant the Chinese could use central Asia as a dumping ground for all of the dogshit concrete and steel they were churning out at a loss for years. There wasn&amp;#x27;t an appetite for that much material when they were making it, and they knew it. Export profits were not the point. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 2nd point is the bigger deal. Basically, for a long time, the deal in China was that so long as the average guy could get a job if he wanted one, and didn&amp;#x27;t make too much noise, things would get better. The CCP revolution that conquered the country was built on jobless, angry people, and the guys running the CCP did not want to be on the other end of that deal. Therefore, the CCP is willing to subsidize terrible business that are guaranteed to lose money, so long as they can promise jobs. The problem these days is that youth unemployment is high and climbing and the increasingly small share of the Chinese population that is young is more and more dissatisfied with living in a PvE server as the E.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;61876817&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;best at everything that matters&lt;br&gt;What a funny way to say, &amp;quot;polluted their soil, water, and air so thoroughly that not even their party members are able to avoid bone marrow cancer anymore.&amp;quot; You would think that they would just incinerate the waste solvents from all the REE processing like Victorian industrialists, but I guess it was 0.000003 RMB cheaper per ton to just dump it into the nearest waterway.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877159&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877115&lt;br&gt;Ameri fat Kool aid&lt;br&gt;USAID mental gymnastics&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877162&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877115&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;OBOR boondoggle&lt;br&gt;opinion discarded. Remain uninformed and get fucked. &lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t know why low info retards like you are so confident and unaware to the point of spending time typing out that trash.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877164&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877115&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;What a funny way to say, &amp;quot;polluted their soil, water, and air so thoroughly that not even their party members are able to avoid bone marrow cancer anymore.&amp;quot; You would think that they would just incinerate the waste solvents from all the REE processing like Victorian industrialists, but I guess it was 0.000003 RMB cheaper per ton to just dump it into the nearest waterway.&lt;br&gt;lol&lt;br&gt;what a funny way to cope with living in a country that can&amp;#x27;t make hdmi cables&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877170&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;just pollute the water bros!!&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;we will break chinese REE monopoly in no time!!!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877198&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873794&lt;br&gt;esl subhumans once again on an american website.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877206&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Uh-oh l didn&amp;#x27;t realize we were all just supposed to go along with the &amp;#x27;china wise like 1000 year old fish&amp;#x27; retardation. Fucking spare me. We&amp;#x27;re talking about a place that has regular catastrophic flooding on a river its people have continually inhabited and farmed for over 3000 years.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;They will scream, they will cry, they will seethe&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;but they will never talk about ROI on that rail road/highway combo that was supposed to cross the most economically desolate strip of earth possible to connect &amp;quot;where?&amp;quot; with &amp;quot;who cares?&amp;quot;.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;A country that still cannot manage to make etchants more complicated than RCA cleans is gonna totally dominate semiconductors &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The really fun environmental whoopsie they did recently was related to cadmium and arsenic uptake. Cotton was being grown in fields contaminated with heavy metals, which is relatively fine since the fibers won&amp;#x27;t get consumed. Then the order came down to convert cotton fields to grain. The only reason that anyone noticed a problem is that cadmium poisoning causes rapid onset joint pain.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;But none of that can top the hilarity of deleting literally millions of infants between 1980 and 2015, then turning around and being utterly shocked at running out of young people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877210&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877206&lt;br&gt;we&amp;#x27;re talking about the only place that can make hdmi cables&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877217&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;cotton fields&lt;br&gt;are all in Xinjiang, which btw produces the absolute best cotton in the world. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;growing grains in Xinjiang&lt;br&gt;ror&lt;br&gt;rmao even&lt;br&gt;do you even read what you wrote and see how retarded you sound?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877223&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;environmental protection&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;in 2026&lt;br&gt;Are we really going to pretend that this matters at all anymore? Look at who&amp;#x27;s the fucking president. Look at what he&amp;#x27;s doing to the EPA.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;And if Europe wants to have competitive manufacturing again, they&amp;#x27;ll likely lax regulations too.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t like it either, a lot of people are going to get fucked. However competitive manufacturing means slashing prices, which means ignoring everything that doesn&amp;#x27;t show up on a quarterly report.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877619&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872964&lt;br&gt;Instead of wasting money on niggers, China subsidizes real businesses that make things?&lt;br&gt;IMF Jews are seething.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877897&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61876817&lt;br&gt;I am not arguing that China doesn’t produce essential goods. I am trying to explain how these conditions happened. While there are tons of reasons that Chinese manufacturing rose to prominence—huge cheap labor force that was previously kept away from foreign investment, America putting China on the MFN list—a consistently cheap currency is one of them, hence why they have been accused of currency manipulation for literal decades. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Currency can ligma balls or be infinitely expensive compared to other currencies, it does not matter. It may seem that it does, but it does not.&lt;br&gt;This is just patently untrue. Obviously, if China’s currency were infinitely expensive, which would be the equivalent to having a self-imposed trade embargo, nobody would buy their products. What you would see is the rapid expansion of the industries that China has a monopoly on; a part of the reason that these industries do not pop up elsewhere is that potential manufacturers know that it’s difficult to compete with how cheap Chinese goods are, so why bother. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You seem to genuinely believe that exchange rates do not ultimately matter in trade, which simply ignores how international trade functions. I’ll give you another example. After WWII, the US set Japan’s exchange rate intentionally low as a part of the Dodge Plan because they wanted a democratic stronghold in Asia, and they knew giving them a cheaper currency would help their export market. This worked TOO WELL. Over the course of the next forty years, Japan became so dominant in the export market that other countries began to panic and they “renegotiated” the exchange rate again at the plaza accords (this would have disastrous effects). If we were in the 80’s, you would point to Japan and say that “look at all the great products they make. It doesn’t matter what their exchange rate is,” and that would ignore the conditions that gave rise to their export dominance in the first place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878109&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872971&lt;br&gt;Doesn&amp;#x27;t help them a bit. The chink economy is still in a deflationary death spiral and there is no way in hell its ever going to get out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878121&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61876956&lt;br&gt;Lmfao. You can produce whatever you want, when demand dies as it has for the last 6 years you are going to sit on overproduction. Add a corrupt communist bureaucratic political party tyranny that plays same asset re-leveraged ponzi to increase its monetary base you get economic deflation and monetary hyperinflation - that&amp;#x27;s the perfect breeding ground for insurgency &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ccp and Chinese bureaucrats and polity is going to be slaughtered in the streets&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878126&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878121&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;/pol/tard word salad gibberish complete with the &amp;quot;hyperinflation&amp;quot; meme word&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878133&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878126&lt;br&gt;Wumao&lt;br&gt;China is dead and has been for the better part of 13 years. All the corruption and attempts to paint over the political and economic failures are now coming home all at the same time. There won&amp;#x27;t be a &amp;quot;people&amp;quot; &amp;#x27;republic&amp;#x27; of China by 2030&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878137&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878133&lt;br&gt;I think you&amp;#x27;re Indian.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878138&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878133&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;more /pol/tard word salad gibberish complete with foreign language pejorative meme word&lt;br&gt;if i had to guess: IQ ~80, GED or &amp;#x27;cyber high school&amp;#x27;, has never read a book in his life, career in manual labor for a wage between $18/hour and $22/hour.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878148&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878137&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878138&lt;br&gt;Wumaos &lt;br&gt;When the checks stop coming you gone. The rest of the country is going to slaughter you&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878155&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878148&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;When the checks stop coming you gone&lt;br&gt;Confirmed Indian&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878160&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878155&lt;br&gt;Wumao, who do you think is first going to be rationalized away? You or chair man chang? You gonna die chink&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878162&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878109&lt;br&gt;They made a bet that reaching out infrastructure to the hundreds of millions of people of low-productivity regions could improve domestic demand to the extent that their subsidies start to be consumed internally. The problem is that the low-productivity areas are, of course, low income and the only two options which exist to them are:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Direct UBI for low-income areas&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Creating even more highly subsidized factories to employ low-income people and give them a better wage&lt;br&gt;Honestly for them the UBI route is likely more cost-effective, to avoid further deflating the value of the plants they already have. The 3rd (much) more challenging and expensive option would be to migrate the sweat-shops and low-skill factories out to the countryside from bigger city centers and reassign the existing factories to high-tech, high-skill plants such as chip foundries and advanced component manufacturing. To a certain extent they&amp;#x27;re being forced into this already due to sanctions etc on high-end chips, but if it&amp;#x27;s their primary gameplan then it&amp;#x27;s progressing way too slowly. Modernizing a billion people (bugs) is a hell of a project&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878168&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878160&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;re stinking up the thread.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878171&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878162&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;UBI&lt;br&gt;That&amp;#x27;s the funny part, the polity as the bureaucracy as the socialist &amp;quot;billionaire&amp;quot; bastards that rely on the continuation of the sovereign bond ponzis are going to hang on the same gallows&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878316&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878171&lt;br&gt;Are you ESL? I feel like I got schizophrenia just from reading your post&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880069&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874731&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;17% of the US population who are hooked on SSRIs get their supplies cut off, along with the active ingredients we buy from them for everything else. We lost the bio-warfare game before it even began.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880124&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875629&lt;br&gt;Everything done by a government can be construed as being a subsidy&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Good infrastructure is a subsidy&lt;br&gt;Skilled workforce is a subsidy&lt;br&gt;Low crime rate is a subsidy&lt;br&gt;Friendly regulatory environment is a subsidy&lt;br&gt;Low cost of living for employees is a subsidy&lt;br&gt;Ease of worker relocation and efficient job matching is a subsidy&lt;br&gt;Low taxes due to government thrift is a subsidy&lt;br&gt;Etc&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880265&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873120&lt;br&gt;On the world though? Also where would China be without Amazon and Walmart like worse than Thailand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880291&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875302&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;If a basket of various goods in the US goes for 100 dollars and that same basket of goods in Vietnam goes for 10 dollars (ALL ELSE BEING EQUAL), then a fair exchange rate would be 10 dong for one dollar&lt;br&gt;That is a made up rule. There is no fundamental reason for why 1 dong should have the same purchasing power as 1 dollar. Currency units are just made up. Vietnam could introduce a new currency superunit called the bong, say 1 bong is equal to 25,970 dong and also that 1 bong is equal to 1 dollar. That would satisfy your rule while also de facto maintaining the current exchange rate.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is a natural reason for why the basket is cheaper in dollar terms in Vietnam, which is the Balassa-Samuelson effect&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;There’s a reason why economists or even someone casually interested in the economy and trade policy use these terms.&lt;br&gt;Yes, because they are shills trying to find arguments for why China should make Chinese companies less competitive and/or arguments for why tariffs should be imposed against China. It&amp;#x27;s really all just to protect the profits of domestic companies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880312&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880291&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;say 1 bong is equal to 25,970 dong and also that 1 bong is equal to 1 dollar.&lt;br&gt;*say 1 bong is equal to 2,597 dong and also that 10 bong are equal to 1 dollar&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>the US is in recession — 53 replies — 201.5/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61869320</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61869320?lm=1771615992</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 19:33:12 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;the US is in recession&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61869320'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 53 • Updated: 2026-02-20 19:33 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;the US is in recession&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869343&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869320&lt;br&gt;doomed fag nation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869350&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Adjust by population&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869389&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bump&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872563&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869517&lt;br&gt;3 days a week is not a full time job.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872729&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870872&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;think&lt;br&gt;*know&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872903&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870845&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;defining a recession by the fucking dictionary&lt;br&gt;stupid nigger&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872909&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;it&amp;#x27;s been in recession since two thousand fucking eight &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;they just can&amp;#x27;t hide it anymore&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872927&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872563&lt;br&gt;36+ hours is a full time job, retard&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874552&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I am one of those assholes. But then again, I pull like 290k. Make that paper bitch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876139&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869320&lt;br&gt;Has nothing to do with making ends meet and everything to do with shitty spending habits&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876213&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869507&lt;br&gt;Don&amp;#x27;t forget the people that sign up for two WFH positions and fake their way through both.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876310&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61876213&lt;br&gt;Stop talking about me. I made a small fortune in the past 5 years doing this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876386&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869320&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;this is insane&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;less than 1% of the population is working more than one full-time position&lt;br&gt;Okay. Personally I&amp;#x27;m interviewing for a second job just because I want more money.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876391&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870855&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870872&lt;br&gt;Yeah we should be like Obama and just accept that jobs will never return. It takes time to improve things so don&amp;#x27;t ever try, silly goy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876412&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;the cope itt is crazy. it hurts to watch a once-great nation falling apart in denial.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876435&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China will take over as world superpower&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876558&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870808&lt;br&gt;this is like those 5&amp;#x27;11&amp;quot; vs 6&amp;#x27; memes &lt;br&gt;holy shit, they cannot be serious&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876562&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870808&lt;br&gt;How bad is it if this is the good news damn&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876847&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869320&lt;br&gt;I have talked to retarded job hogs proud of being exploited. Seriously you can&amp;#x27;t ask for a raise and give me one of your jobs? Then you mock me for failing to get a job? You are hogging 2 jobs. If you didn&amp;#x27;t work 2 jobs there would be room for unemployed people to have jobs too. Boomer X fuckers still don&amp;#x27;t get it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877134&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870808&lt;br&gt;I hope you’re trolling&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877277&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869343&lt;br&gt;as long as wagies keep waging, it aint doomed nigga&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877309&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869320&lt;br&gt;People are working two or more jobs and you call this recession? Fucking hilarious&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877311&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61876310&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61876213&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;SING UP FOR&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;like places are just a great volunteer association and not a rigorous shittest from hr.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877894&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869507&lt;br&gt;There are 7 days a week anon. If you consider a 40 hour week a full time job, then an 80 hour week is two full time jobs. That&amp;#x27;s under 12 hours a day, every day. Plus commutes to the two jobs, you are out of home 13 to 14 hours. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61876213&lt;br&gt;99% larpers, 1% get caught after on-boarding period&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61876139&lt;br&gt;Other than fast food, I doubt people who work 80 hour weeks even have time to spend their money on bullshit. They probably just shower and collapse to bed at the end of the day. My bet is that they are paying a mortgage or have an incapacitated spouse or parent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877899&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;if the US is in recession, why did Doordash just have it&amp;#x27;s biggest ever jump in orders?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878363&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869517&lt;br&gt;I cant imagine working more than 50 hours a week, tf is wrong with americans? Working 70 hours a week to buy an oilguzzler to commute to work? Living in the sterile suburbs? Tossing a coin everytime a negro passes you on the street? What is even the point of all that?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878371&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872563&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880061&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877899&lt;br&gt;People can&amp;#x27;t afford cars, and there&amp;#x27;s a decline in driver&amp;#x27;s license applications. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;And Increased senior population demand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880092&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878363&lt;br&gt;to enrich uncle sam at the small cost of every waking minute of your life&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880116&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878363&lt;br&gt;I work 100+ hours plus just to not get evicted by my corporate landlord. My rent is $4,000 a month. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boomers here opose affordable housing because it&amp;#x27;s gonna hurt their home values. But fuck me I guess.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880131&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878363&lt;br&gt;Forgot screenshot&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880323&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869320&lt;br&gt;What a perfect moment for the Democrats to rule against receiving free money from the rest of the world because we are all pinky friends and we all love each other&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880329&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870808&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Pro Trump post in a fag infested board&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anon...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>I have recently discovered leftwing finance youtube channels The whole things is never EVER blaming people for going int… — 53 replies — 41.7/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61872693</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61872693?lm=1771612361</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:32:41 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;I have recently discovered leftwing finance youtube channels The whole things is never EVER blaming people for going int…&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61872693'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 53 • Updated: 2026-02-20 18:32 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have recently discovered leftwing finance youtube channels &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The whole things is never EVER blaming people for going into debt, but blaming companies instead&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;Asking people how much debt they are in is Chud behaviour, just because they are in debt doesn&amp;#x27;t mean they can&amp;#x27;t go on a vacation, but Disneyland should be cheaper, Disney is predatory&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;The problem isn&amp;#x27;t credit card debt, that&amp;#x27;s normal, the problem is how hight the interests rates are&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;60k car loans are insane but really, why do the cars need to cost that much?&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872704&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872693&lt;br&gt;The one you used in the OP got famous for calling people retards to their faces for their debt&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872721&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872693&lt;br&gt;Caleb is just a gay zoomer Dave Ramsey. Just like with Judge Judy, it doesn&amp;#x27;t work if you&amp;#x27;re not a boomer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872722&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872704&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872721&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872693&lt;br&gt;Caleb is not the leftwing finance bro.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In fact he&amp;#x27;s fighting accusations he&amp;#x27;s far right&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876211&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873117&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;This is nigger logic and it almost never works out.&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s the only thing that works.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873133&lt;br&gt;How&amp;#x27;s Tel Aviv?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876215&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873914&lt;br&gt;We&amp;#x27;re saying the same thing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876222&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Notice how individuals are considered the irresponsible ones, and not the governments that devalue the currency so that it&amp;#x27;s fucking worthless? Why doesn&amp;#x27;t (((Caleb))) talk about that?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876223&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61876222&lt;br&gt;Or the institutions that charge usury-level interest, that&amp;#x27;s another point I should add&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876245&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873088&lt;br&gt;You, as an individual, will never, ever fix the system and the chances of a revolution sweeping along to do so, which by the way will just have some other bullshit attached, is slim to none and slim just left town. That leaves you alone, in the system, to &amp;quot;cope&amp;quot;. How will you do that? By reading the rules and bending them enough to make you prosperous within its confines. Everything else is a fuckkng pipe dream and you will just waste years toiling in it when you could have been making it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thats what faggots who blame the system do. They give up. They dont have the fortitude. They dont put in &amp;quot;the hard work&amp;quot; to bend the rules and make them selves prosperous. They just drag everyone else down into thier level of misery out of envy. Dont be that fucking loser. Be the guy who makes it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876247&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872693&lt;br&gt;Despite being a fat faggot, leftists hate Caleb Hammer for making the hateful claim that you shouldn&amp;#x27;t buy junk when you have to get a 150% APY loan&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876259&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872693&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;retard takes a loan with 50% interest rate to buy some burritos at chipotle and labubus&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;completely oblivious about what loan interests means&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;ITS NOT A BAD DECISION, ITS THE FAULT OF LE EVIL CAPITALISM&lt;br&gt;lmao holy fuck&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876262&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61876259&lt;br&gt;You shouldn&amp;#x27;t even be able to take out a loan at 50% kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876287&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872693&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Wkw21YfvpBk&amp;amp;t=927s&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Literally ends with &amp;quot;ahhh cool story, stand against the wall....&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876302&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872750&lt;br&gt;There isn’t a structural issue. The issue is the majority of people are financially illiterate retards with no ability to delay gratification.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876355&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;but really, why do the cars need to cost that much?&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;Because they spent 60 years demanding massive liability payouts and more &amp;amp; more regulation...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meanwhile China today buys their electric car for 10k...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876361&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I like the show because of the click bait guests, but there&amp;#x27;s way too many commercials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876382&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61876355&lt;br&gt;Cars aren&amp;#x27;t even much more expensive if you account for inflation. &lt;br&gt;And if you consider price in gold, they are WAY cheaper.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876383&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872722&lt;br&gt;He&amp;#x27;s a homosexual so he probably is a (closeted) white supremacists&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876504&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61876245&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61876302&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Demoralization&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;NUH UH&lt;br&gt;Spoken precisely how I&amp;#x27;d imagine someone would if they knew I was right but didn&amp;#x27;t want others to catch on.&lt;br&gt;For those interested in a fix: you get together with like-minded people and pincer from the federal and local levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877446&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;the economy is rigged to make the rich richer at the expense of the poor&lt;br&gt;and&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;the poor are mostly stupid goycattle who deserve to stay poor&lt;br&gt;are both true&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878485&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61876302&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;There isn’t a structural issue. The issue is the majority of people are financially illiterate retards with no ability to delay gratification.&lt;br&gt;That and many are really greedy and selfish. The anticapitalist types are always the most greedy people.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You can&amp;#x27;t help these people btw. Might as well finance them a 7-11 churro and put their money to a better use.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878497&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877446&lt;br&gt;Elite Human Capital can utilize resources better than the poor. So it&amp;#x27;s good the system is biased in their favor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878769&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873088&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;You fix a broken system by changing the system.&lt;br&gt;How are you dumb enough to believe this?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878780&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61876504&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;We&amp;#x27;re going to fix the system, we have all the answers&lt;br&gt;If you had any of the answers, you&amp;#x27;d know how to use the system in the first place.&lt;br&gt;This like is AOC going to DC to tell us how to fix all the problems in the world and not knowing what that switch on her kitchen wall next to her sink is or why it&amp;#x27;s suddenly making noise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879278&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873088&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;by changing the system.&lt;br&gt;Communist spotted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879340&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872693&lt;br&gt;He attacks individuals though, usually calls them stupid for doing XYZ&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t like him but that&amp;#x27;s just not true anon. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872722&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61876383&lt;br&gt;He had a guest mention a bad part of town being &amp;quot;Brownsville&amp;quot; (which is the actual name of the bad part of town) and he immediately virtue signaled and brought a black guy on camera to &amp;quot;confront&amp;quot; the guest about it when it was in fact the literal town name.&lt;br&gt;Caleb is a cum guzzling faggot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879349&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872922&lt;br&gt;Conservatives are generally already better with money because they had fiscally responsible parents (notice how I said parents, as in plural)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879520&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872693&lt;br&gt;The system prices all that in and it&amp;#x27;s why we have monopoly money that gets bailed out at regular intervals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879536&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879520&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gold windows closed &lt;br&gt;Women “liberated” enter workforces&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now money is worthless&lt;br&gt;Women trapped in jobs they hate without families. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s like there’s a link between unsound money are societal degeneracy. Hmmm&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879588&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872722&lt;br&gt;Yeah except he&amp;#x27;s basically a pinko moderate besides the fact that he&amp;#x27;s come to the common sense realization that most poor people are poor because they&amp;#x27;re clearly obviously fucking retards making bad decisions. He&amp;#x27;s clearly pretty pozzed with regards to gays, &amp;quot;sex workers&amp;quot;, being unmarried with kids, thruples, etc. in the typical Reddit &amp;quot;you do you frendo&amp;quot; with his only standard being whether or not that happens to be producing outcomes the person doing them likes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;quot;Far right&amp;quot; is a faggot term for &amp;quot;conservative&amp;quot; to try to make it sound bad. You&amp;#x27;ll see very very little discussion of merely right wing in leftist media. &amp;quot;Far right&amp;quot; is &amp;quot;something I don&amp;#x27;t like&amp;quot;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;quot;Poor people are poor largely because they deserve it, they&amp;#x27;re not oppressed victims and therefore we&amp;#x27;re not terribly obligated to do much of anything just because they&amp;#x27;re irresponsible&amp;quot; is just one of the most basic conservative ideas. But it&amp;#x27;s entirely antithetical to a leftist world view that basically identifies everyone as either victims and victimizers and that rustled Jimmies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879764&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879349&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Conservatives are generally already better with money because they had fiscally responsible parents&lt;br&gt;You need to look at the latest data. Conservative core base are the people of walmart who don&amp;#x27;t marry, spend recklessly, and leech off the government. They&amp;#x27;re basically white niggers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;All the responsible Romney type republicans left.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879795&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879764&lt;br&gt;Just the same they fundamentally believe people have self-responsibility even if they hypocritically are fuckups living on gibs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879802&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879764&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;political people I don&amp;#x27;t like bad, poor, stupid&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;political people I do like good, rich, smart&lt;br&gt;Sure thing buddy. &lt;br&gt;So anyways conservatives are generally more fiscally literate people and don&amp;#x27;t rack up lots of retarded debt because they come from better homes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879815&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879795&lt;br&gt;I swear all you leftist who believe this shit come from single wide trailer parks and just hate your own upbringing and project it on everyone you disagree with.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>He is right — 39 replies — 37.1/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61877610</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61877610?lm=1771613154</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:45:54 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;He is right&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61877610'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 39 • Updated: 2026-02-20 18:45 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The anon who has been telling us to get out of US stocks might be on to something&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877621&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;america is dying&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;put your money into europe (dead continent)&lt;br&gt;investors are retarded&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877631&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877621&lt;br&gt;Poor lil igor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877668&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877659&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_countries_by_total_fertility_rate&lt;br&gt;List the 2025 fertility rates in ascending order. China is one of the worst in the whole world. And people are saying even these numbers are manipulated up by the Chinese gov.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877688&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877668&lt;br&gt;Yeah. Unfortunately hoeflation and unrealistic expectations, combined with chinese men having a &amp;quot;no roasties&amp;quot; policy for women over 25 means that chicks act like bitchy little whores when they&amp;#x27;re teens, chasing millionaire chink ceo dick, then they get kicked to the curb when they wall and film videos of themselves crying that no man will even hold their hand. It&amp;#x27;s like everything shitty about the US dating scene but on &amp;quot;on the honour of my ancestors you will suffer 100fold for what you did to me&amp;quot; chinese style level.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877692&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877610&lt;br&gt;You never make alot of money following the sheeps.&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m selling all my emerging markets holdings and buying long term us treasuries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877760&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877692&lt;br&gt;thats the sheepiest possible thing&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877773&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;the world is ending&lt;br&gt;global warming will kill us all&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877819&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877621&lt;br&gt;america stonks are overvalued, emu stonks are undervalued&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877863&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877773&lt;br&gt;Kek funny american. The whitest continent on the planet becoming the global hegemony is the opposite of the world ending. It&amp;#x27;s going to be another era of enlightenment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877875&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877863&lt;br&gt;no you see the ice caps will melt and we will all drown&lt;br&gt;the point of no return is already behind us&lt;br&gt;it&amp;#x27;s over&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877884&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877863&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;how does a world Hegemon who&amp;#x27;s only known for bureaucracy rule? With what army?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877888&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877863&lt;br&gt;the &amp;quot;enlightenment&amp;quot; was like reddit.com but in real life, an entire historical era of that shit&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;look how brainfucked the average reddit user is and now you want to larp as an ancient, historical person who was a redditor but even dumber&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877904&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877884&lt;br&gt;EU has some of the highest tech on planet, and are in the process of building the EU army.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877888&lt;br&gt;We have the enlightenment to thank for most of our human rights and science. Reddit just inherited the culture of the enlightenment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877909&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877904&lt;br&gt;they created a fake history during the enlightenment to brainfuck goyim beyond repair&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;they&amp;#x27;re all in on it too, there are just levels that are more exclusive than others&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;look up Jakob Bernays (Freud&amp;#x27;s Grand-uncle), Edward Bernays (Freud&amp;#x27;s Inbred uncle), Joseph Scaliger, Jean Hardouin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877911&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Look up &amp;quot;Francis Bacon&amp;quot; invented the English language&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877916&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877621&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;passportless amerifat tells you place with highest standard of living in human history is dead&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877917&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877659&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;assuming they aren&amp;#x27;t lying.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;chinks&lt;br&gt;it has never been mor Joever.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877926&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877621&lt;br&gt;Europe is the best&lt;br&gt;kys muttoid goblin&lt;br&gt;you probably live in some unwalkable shithole and have to pay an arm and a leg to see a doctor&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877927&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877610&lt;br&gt;This isn&amp;#x27;t confidence in Europe, its lack of confidence in America.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investors aren&amp;#x27;t comfortable holding cash, but that mindset will change once they realise they are holding all of it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investors overestimate how much liquidity there is in the system. It feels infinite, especially after all the QE, but there are no dollars &amp;#x27;locked up&amp;#x27; in stocks. Someone is physically holding those dollars.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Once the mindset changes, suddenly the liquidity is gone. The rug is pulled. A black hole opens up underneath asset prices.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877930&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877927&lt;br&gt;The refuge in EU assets is temporary. Once the real decline in US assets begins, people are just going to sit it out in cash. All global assets become toxic during the decline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877934&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877916&lt;br&gt;Are you even capable of parsing the basics of what he&amp;#x27;s asking, you stupid fucking pole?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877950&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877621&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;planet is dying&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;let&amp;#x27;s go to mars (dead planet)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878436&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877626&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bitcoin is infinitely better.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Educate yourself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878443&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877916&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Ukraine&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;highest standard of living in human history&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878471&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877610&lt;br&gt;spy was like 90% of my portfolio and and I sold 1/3 of it and put it into euro stoxx 600. so far it was a great decision. I have hope for the us market but I dont trust the usd.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878553&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877621&lt;br&gt;europe has a higher chance of unfucking its shit than the US&lt;br&gt;asia has more chance than either but it&amp;#x27;s very difficult to access for the average /biz/tard or $HOODnigger&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878596&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;buy high&lt;br&gt;never change biz&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878600&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877659&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;...until the US puts sanctions on China and it&amp;#x27;s illegal to invest in their companies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878612&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877621&lt;br&gt;Bad economies have good financial markets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878688&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877688&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;on the honour of my ancestors you will suffer 100fold for what you did to me&lt;br&gt;based chinks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879950&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877636&lt;br&gt;Well, according to the very white, very trad, very smart defenders of western civilization on pol, it&amp;#x27;s probably based white trad western countries like Iran, Russia and North Korea who will soon usher in economic prosperity unheard of before.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879972&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879950&lt;br&gt;Sir that sounds very based!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>BAT — 25 replies — 35.8/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61875908</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61875908?lm=1771614427</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 19:07:07 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;BAT&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61875908'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 25 • Updated: 2026-02-20 19:07 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;markets are all fucked&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;global recession &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;nobody is hiring &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;STILL holding 340k of this SHIT&lt;br&gt;The fuck am I even doing bros? Is there any hope for BAT to do literally anything?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875915&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;BAT&lt;br&gt;Holy shit. What year is it???&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875923&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875908&lt;br&gt;why didn&amp;#x27;t brave just give rewards in Ethereum or some shit&lt;br&gt;why did it have to be its own token? All they did was invent a token for the sole purpose of selling&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875927&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875923&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;he now understands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875981&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875923&lt;br&gt;Advertisers were supposed to buy it, I guess. I guess they liked how ads work already where they pay nothing to the end user and get to program them to miscegenate and eat poison.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875982&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875908&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875915&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875923&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875927&lt;br&gt;whats the usecase for this shit when everybody already uses adblockers and doesn&amp;#x27;t wanna watch ads for your 0.00001 cents worth of crypto?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;this is a smart idea on paper but fucking stupid in physical reality&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876018&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875923&lt;br&gt;Good fucking point. The ICO was fucked as well. The longer I hold the more this seems like a cash grab desu&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876025&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875908&lt;br&gt;There’s a reason why Brendan is only casually mentioned in the Epstein files and BAT is a completely and utterly useless memecoin scam. He is actually a principled man and doesn’t wanna get compromised by Jewish sexpest glowniggers. Turns out he really is the biggest brain in crypto and he won’t be doing anything with BAT until all these disgusting uncouth kikes are long gone&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876038&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61876025&lt;br&gt;Trvth Svpernova&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876042&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61876025&lt;br&gt;Wait this ain&amp;#x27;t a nvke how are you defending a guy for being in the files. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yikes that&amp;#x27;s a bad look sweetie&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876043&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875982&lt;br&gt;Jeets will watch SAR, very good customers who doing the needful, please understand sar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876047&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Remember when baggies used to pay you money to use Brave?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You can use a dogshit browser with barely-functioning adblocker and MAKE money oh boy im sure this isnt a scam&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876088&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61876042&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;how are you defending a guy for being in the files.&lt;br&gt;They couldn’t get him on the island. Go look for yourself&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876249&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;lol BAT lmao&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876295&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61876018&lt;br&gt;The ICO got slurped up in seconds kek.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875982&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;your 0.00001 cents worth of crypto&lt;br&gt;I miss the days of earning 100+ BAT monthly. The iOS rewards used to slap too u_u&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876298&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;kek op is the guy who kept bragging he had 350k for years and kept getting pissy when I told him bat was fucking dead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876301&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875908&lt;br&gt;Bancor is literally unstoppable&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876328&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61876301&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;literally unstoppable&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;down 98%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876563&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61876298&lt;br&gt;BAT isnt dead tho its just doing fuck all&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61876295&lt;br&gt;Hnnnng&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876880&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61876295&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61876328&lt;br&gt;missed these threads so much&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876917&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875908&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;re supposed to donate your BAT to your favorite eceleb, anon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877352&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61876295&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61876328&lt;br&gt;Keep the BOOBA coming&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877439&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lmao BAT you better sell this before it&amp;#x27;s removed from the browser and goes to zero I&amp;#x27;m not kidding theye phasing it out&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879857&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877439&lt;br&gt;BAT is shit but I can’t imagine it going to 0 anytime soon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879916&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875923&lt;br&gt;They originally started by giving out Bitcoin, before they figured out an ICO would be printing free money.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880145&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879916&lt;br&gt;That would’ve been so much better holy shit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>AHAHAHAHAHAHAHA AMERICAN TAXPAYERS YOU BETTER PAY UP 374 BILLION US DOLLARS AAAAAAAAAHAHAHAHAHAHAH — 22 replies — 33.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61879211</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61879211?lm=1771614540</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 19:09:00 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;AHAHAHAHAHAHAHA AMERICAN TAXPAYERS YOU BETTER PAY UP 374 BILLION US DOLLARS AAAAAAAAAHAHAHAHAHAHAH&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61879211'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 22 • Updated: 2026-02-20 19:09 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;AHAHAHAHAHAHAHA AMERICAN TAXPAYERS YOU BETTER PAY UP 374 BILLION US DOLLARS AAAAAAAAAHAHAHAHAHAHAH&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879221&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879211&lt;br&gt;Americans are the ones who are owed that money. &lt;br&gt;Do you not understand how tariffs work anon? Are you a literal retard?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879227&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879221&lt;br&gt;Redneck retards are owed that money.&lt;br&gt;Flyover hicks are owed that money.&lt;br&gt;Trailer trash are owed that money.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump doing what he does best, destroying the US state and government to benefit his hicks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879233&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brrrrrrrrrrrrrr&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879239&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879221&lt;br&gt;fuck yeah free money babyyyyyy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879274&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879221&lt;br&gt;i dont think anyone knows what that number means&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;you have to pay it back&lt;br&gt;ok well we didnt at $36 trillion, we have to at $37 trillion?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879280&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879227&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879239&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879274&lt;br&gt;companies like costco might get a refund, the average american won&amp;#x27;t get shit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879285&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;can&amp;#x27;t wait for the memecoins to snap back to ATH when the refunds start&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879291&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879280&lt;br&gt;correct. giving money to goyim is unAmerican socialist nonsense.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879328&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879221&lt;br&gt;But Trump and Besset has said over and over that the tariff costs are carried by the manufacturer and not the consumer, who is in fact doing great and bigly. Why should they then get money back?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879368&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The truth is that the tariff costs were pushed off onto other countries. All of our prices here in canada went up even though we don&amp;#x27;t have any new tariffs on shit because companies doing business in both countries just raised their prices here to offset their costs in the US.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879378&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879239&lt;br&gt;I like free money&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879432&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879211&lt;br&gt;I voted for this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879539&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879221&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879211&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Leftists under tariffs &amp;quot;Uhhhh tariffs are le bad because YOU are the one paying for them! Trump is Le bad!&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Liberals off of tariffs &amp;quot;Haha look tariffs are ILLEGAL now you get your money back. But that comes out of the revenue we got! (Which we didn&amp;#x27;t talk about as being good before) So it&amp;#x27;s le bad! Drumpf awful!!!&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879599&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879539&lt;br&gt;Prices are coming down on cheap shit whether you like it or not.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879685&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879211&lt;br&gt;Guess which tribe was buying up discounted refund claims before the ruling (including Howard Lutnick)? Trump insiders just transferred shit tons of tariff money to themselves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879727&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879280&lt;br&gt;Why should the average American get a refund when they voted for this nonsense? We should refund the tariffs to the countries we imposed them on as reparations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879763&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879221&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Americans are the ones who are owed that money.&lt;br&gt;Unless it&amp;#x27;s a small business willing to refund you or you paid the mailer yourself, all that money is being kept by the companies you bought from most likely&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879870&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You have to pay it all back miggers, every single cent&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879904&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oops! Trump just reinstated Tariffs! Too bad!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879933&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879899&lt;br&gt;To be fair, Trump himself has said there&amp;#x27;s well over 150 billion tariffs revenue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880003&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879211&lt;br&gt;usdebtclock.org is a fantasy page. The numbers on that page have a very tenuous relation to reality. Total tariff revenue in calendar year 2025 was $264B.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I guess they must be optimistically projecting future tariff revenue - which seems difficult, since tariffs would likely continue to suppress imports. Monthly tariff revenue was already in decline in late 2025.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I see they&amp;#x27;ve removed the DOGE savings counter - I guess the fantasy numbers were becoming too much of an embarassment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880158&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879211&lt;br&gt;Gonna have to wait for 5 years after paying a lawyer and going through the courts, sorry about that!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>BTC dumping? Don’t care. It’s temporary. — 70 replies — 26.5/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61869212</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61869212?lm=1771607426</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:10:26 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;BTC dumping? Don’t care. It’s temporary.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61869212'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 70 • Updated: 2026-02-20 17:10 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;If it drops, I buy more. If it goes sideways, I accumulate. If it pumps, I chill. I’m earning yield and stacking long term. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Short term volatility doesn’t change the plan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869234&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869212&lt;br&gt;Crypto and BTC is dead retard &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Everyone knows about it by now&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869237&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869212&lt;br&gt;The niggercattle aren&amp;#x27;t going to pump your epsteincoin bags.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869244&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869212&lt;br&gt;Pixel tranny cope.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877711&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869212&lt;br&gt;What about Epstein&amp;#x27;s involvement? It sucks and can&amp;#x27;t believe everything goes to him based on those evidence&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877722&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869212&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;ICP is better than Bitcoin and all other crypto. ICP buy this gem and get rich.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877734&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869234&lt;br&gt;Yep. I’ve been contacted by a couple of friends who never talk about crypto to tell me that it’s over and I was just in a taxi when the driver told me it’s finished. I’m scared to go and get my hair cut because I just don’t want to hear it from my stylist, then I’ll really know it’s over&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877954&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877158&lt;br&gt;Nope. If the platform disappears, your BTC doesn’t vanish. It’s still on Bitcoin under the lock you set, and you can withdraw when the unlock conditions are met. Simple.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877961&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877152&lt;br&gt;it nukes and pumps like everything else anon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877965&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877155&lt;br&gt;You can hold both. It doesn’t have to be one or the other.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877979&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877954&lt;br&gt;You are sharing your keys with another entity. You are retarded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878072&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877979&lt;br&gt;Is it another centralized shit?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878078&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869212&lt;br&gt;Welcum bro&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878113&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872347&lt;br&gt;It’s got maybe one more bull run left in it, but $150K is never happening. Ethereum is already at the &amp;quot;no new ATHs ever again&amp;quot; stage. Crypto is dead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878176&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869234&lt;br&gt;newfag alert&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878183&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873082&lt;br&gt;you are genuinely retarded, keep making them stronger with your rocks but in the end it won&amp;#x27;t matter&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878193&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878176&lt;br&gt;Yeah and beanie babies as an asset class will come roaring back any day now. Enjoy holding your digital bags.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878207&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878193&lt;br&gt;Not exactly accurate there&amp;#x27;s a few beanie babies still fetching over a million right now anon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878212&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877711&lt;br&gt;FUD only&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878223&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878207&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;fetching&lt;br&gt;Why are they all the same price if they&amp;#x27;re an appreciating asset?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878248&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878207&lt;br&gt;Just because you ask for a price doesn&amp;#x27;t mean you&amp;#x27;ll get it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878256&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877979&lt;br&gt;No. You never share private keys. BTC is locked in a Bitcoin script where spending still requires the staker’s signature. If the platform disappears like I said, the timelock path lets you withdraw using Bitcoin only.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878321&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877722&lt;br&gt;sure anon. why? tech, users, or just hoping for a pump?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878324&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878207&lt;br&gt;Can we make money here? I&amp;#x27;m so tired of negative PNL&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878330&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878248&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s losers trade&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878331&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869212&lt;br&gt;I own a lil bit of btc and eth myself (3% of my entire portfolio) but I would unironically love to see the entire crypto market going to 0. You bitcoin maxi retards need to wake up. Your 5k stack of crypto wont magically 100x in the next 5-10 years and make you rich lol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878347&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878072&lt;br&gt;Nah. I’ve already explained it a bunch. DYOR anon. Either let BTC sleep or look into native, self custody setups and pick what fits you kek.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878349&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869514&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;the elites&lt;br&gt;There are many kinds of elites that compete against each other. Many of them want strategic reserves of BTC to trade with. BTC will never die.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878352&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878331&lt;br&gt;What&amp;#x27;s wrong with btc maxis&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878368&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877734&lt;br&gt;Damn! Taxi drivers don’t call tops and bottoms, they just repeat headlines. Stick to your plan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878374&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878078&lt;br&gt;Not my crowd. Stay poor, anon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878376&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869212&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I&amp;#x27;ve tricked myself with a berg-word for any situation!&lt;br&gt;good for you anon? what do you want me to do with this information?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878386&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869360&lt;br&gt;And yet comex+cme can evaporate 10 trillion in market cap in three days. Going to take one from the xrp schizos and say mcap doesn&amp;#x27;t mean anything. Still hold actual metals and not paper derivatives though...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879258&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878113&lt;br&gt;If crypto is dead, why is the onchain activity, stablecoins, and L2 growth still there? Price isn’t the whole story.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>ummm this is huge for chainlink??? — 28 replies — 20.1/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61871679</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61871679?lm=1771611915</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:25:15 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;ummm this is huge for chainlink???&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61871679'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 28 • Updated: 2026-02-20 18:25 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHAT. WAS. THAT.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871713&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I farted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871744&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This has nothing to do with chainlink and everything to do with XRP, which is why garlinghouse was called to the clarity act meeting while sir gay was busy sleeping after eating 5 quarter pounders at 2am.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871896&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871679&lt;br&gt;Cuckolds will watch their shitcoin dump to $5 and masturbate their flaccid incel cock while Sergey dumps on them another 50 million tokens&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871987&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871679&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872006&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871987&lt;br&gt;Link ETF having record trade volume today (8million)&lt;br&gt;lets see if its inflows, could be the start of a big snowball.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872056&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871987&lt;br&gt;Still doesnt make any sense to me why would whales prove this to some random fag&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872065&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871987&lt;br&gt;Thesis was invalidated over a month ago, Chalm&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872229&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872065&lt;br&gt;I want to belieeeeeeeeve&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872244&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871679&lt;br&gt;The crazy part is that this is priced in and will be a sell the news event. It will just result in everything going down even more kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872339&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872056&lt;br&gt;It only makes sense if that random fag was at the right place at the right time to get an invite to a relatively small discord group that has some whale members. Whales might just be stroking their ego by bragging to him about their powers. Or maybe he smooth talked his way into gaining their respect. Stranger things have happened.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872065&lt;br&gt;Whales obviously broke the floor to convince hopeful baggies to let go&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872344&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872065&lt;br&gt;this. its over&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872450&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871679&lt;br&gt;holy shit&lt;br&gt;im fucking bullish again somehow&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872453&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872065&lt;br&gt;going to $8.50 doesn&amp;#x27;t invalidate shit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872475&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872453&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;hover between $10-$15&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;current price&lt;br&gt;Kys, sincerely, a man who has his family’s future riding on link&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872482&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872475&lt;br&gt;yes, $8.50 isn&amp;#x27;t that inaccurate, retard&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872490&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872475&lt;br&gt;based but incredibly irresponsible of you to invest money into a technology that is highly likely to appreciate in value. &lt;br&gt;bad goyim very bad &lt;br&gt;leave investment to the ones who can appreciate it&lt;br&gt;You should learn to respect your masters and fucking earn your cheddar not too much cheddar mind you through a proper exchange of time for money. &lt;br&gt;its not slavery you get just enough to fall into a social class and feel free to judge yourself against others caught in the same conditions. &lt;br&gt;HOW FUCKING DARE YOU INVEST YOUR MONEY YOU WILL NEVER BE PART OF OUR CLUB GOYIM SCUM YOU ARE OUR SLAVES BOW YOUR HEAD BEFORE US&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872495&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872475&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;tell plebs 10 is the bottom&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;move market right below that just to scare/liquidate&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s so obvious to anyone with above room-temp iq. You probably wouldn&amp;#x27;t understand, since you sacrificed your family to shitcoins&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872498&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872482&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;isn’t that inaccurate&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;retard &lt;br&gt;Friendly reminder “people” like this are abundant in society and have the same human rights as you&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872539&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872490&lt;br&gt;Calm down, just calm down&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872545&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872539&lt;br&gt;THINGS WILL NOT CALM DOWN ANON THEY WILL IN FACT CALM UP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872558&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872545&lt;br&gt;he means of course that things will escalate&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872560&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872545&lt;br&gt;kek i cooka da pizza&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872572&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871679&lt;br&gt;Just 10 more months bros. Please don&amp;#x27;t sell, okay?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875250&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871679&lt;br&gt;UPDATE: WTF IS HAPPENING WITH THIS MARKET&lt;br&gt;it dipped to 55% right after i posted this, but is now back up to 83%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877203&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871713&lt;br&gt;fpbp&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877230&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875250&lt;br&gt;how do you trade shitcoins all day and not recognize low volume on a chart&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878886&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;JUST ONE MORE YEARS MARINES!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879731&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871987&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;this larp is still being posted&lt;br&gt;Fucking kek. Linkies are truly the most mindbroken &amp;quot;community&amp;quot; in crypto.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>By investing in the US stock markets, you are directly financing everything that you hate about the United States. — 32 replies — 16.6/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61874572</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61874572?lm=1771610005</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:53:25 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;By investing in the US stock markets, you are directly financing everything that you hate about the United States.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61874572'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 32 • Updated: 2026-02-20 17:53 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;By investing in the US stock markets, you are directly financing everything that you hate about the United States.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874579&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874572&lt;br&gt;I dont, stonks are gay.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874590&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874572&lt;br&gt;Until unrealized gains are taxed, kys bobo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874623&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874590&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; HR departments staffed by roasties&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; women in management&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; H1 b visas&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; Jeets taking over American industry&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; Congress members getting rich off stocks&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; Lobbyist influence on laws&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; The bankers&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; etc&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t think so, Timmy. The second that you invest, you&amp;#x27;re giving them the money for all of it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874634&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874572&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m also directly financing everything that I love about the United States.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874640&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874634&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Like what?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874661&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874572&lt;br&gt;but i only invest in reddit stocks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874662&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874640&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874670&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874662&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; no living wage&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; jobs being sent over seas&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; people being replaced by machines&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; Blackrock buying up all of the homes and making home ownership unattainable&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I have some oceanfront property in Colorado, if you&amp;#x27;re interested in property.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874673&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874662&lt;br&gt;What a load of horse shit lmao&lt;br&gt;Exactly the propaganda that destroyed this place&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874678&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874670&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874673&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874679&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874678&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874701&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874679&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874713&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874572&lt;br&gt;Luckily I&amp;#x27;m not a jew lover and only invest in silver and pokemon cards&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874737&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874701&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; Americans are just lazy and not smart enough&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Okay, boomer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874763&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874737&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874774&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874763&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Have fun trading against bots, and good luck competing against the world with your best foids, trannies, jeets, and chinese spies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874778&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874572&lt;br&gt;But I love the United States&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874789&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874774&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874810&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874789&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; a free country&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Did you know the owning physical gold in the United States was illegal for 41 years?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877358&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874662&lt;br&gt;It doesn’t seem like America is more this way than any other first world country. Maybe it is slightly easier in America but that seems to be fading quickly now that the post war era is over.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877363&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t invest in the United States, bobo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877634&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877358&lt;br&gt;Looking by wealth distribution, USA isn&amp;#x27;t a first world country. It has just has a wealthy upper class and a super wealthy elite class.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877638&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;But anyways yeah bobo i know, that&amp;#x27;s why invest in european markets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877686&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874572&lt;br&gt;Not only that, I voted for it too&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877708&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874572&lt;br&gt;Only if you are investing in index funds.&lt;br&gt;You can choose to invest in what you love about this country.&lt;br&gt;I personally am investing in LMT, GD, HAL, XOM, BX, COST&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877733&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877708&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m sure that Black Rock doesn&amp;#x27;t own any of those stocks and enforcing DEI. They probably pay people enough to live off of and aren&amp;#x27;t looking to automate. Corporate culture surely hasn&amp;#x27;t infiltrated those businesses. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Can I interest you in a Rolex watch?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877891&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By investing in US stocks, I am hedging against everything I love.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877903&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877686&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;sometimes Cherri gets horny at work, dances and has sex with the men in the closests&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878643&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874572&lt;br&gt;I finance shit that literally kill people because it gives me divvies. Do you think I care in the slightest for normalfags? They are cattle to be milked dry. I hate wokeslop and yet I invested in NFLX after it dropped. To this day I never subbed to them and seed torrents of shows from there. I hate cigarettes and yet I invest in MO. I don&amp;#x27;t believe in crypto and yet I got back in BTC around 69k. I believe in socialized healthcare and yet I&amp;#x27;m a UNH baggie (avg over $300)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879220&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874623&lt;br&gt;I can profit in white Genocide? Based!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879386&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874572&lt;br&gt;I only got GME in hopes of killing off the US economy very slowly in one explosive blow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879544&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878643&lt;br&gt;You are a monster&lt;br&gt;americans have 0 moral backbone&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Fake and Gay Economy — 54 replies — 15.9/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61871520</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61871520?lm=1771604730</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:25:30 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Fake and Gay Economy&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61871520'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 54 • Updated: 2026-02-20 16:25 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;When will this gay as economy finally collapse and how can i profit from it?&lt;br&gt;Its ridiculous the woman at our workplace contribute nothing to the company and make more money than i do&lt;br&gt;Its infuriating we just had a bunch of lay offs and we lost some of oir best workers but somehow a bunch of HR shits who do nothing all day still work here&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871530&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HR is a necessary function, chud&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871569&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871530&lt;br&gt;For what?&lt;br&gt;Genuinely why do we need it to this extent?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871755&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871569&lt;br&gt;Protect the corp from lawsuits&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872709&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;I want to rape all of them&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872713&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Office jobs are day care for adults and factory jobs are slave labour&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;t. Office worker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872847&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;They look like they are having a dress up party where they larp as office workers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873112&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872429&lt;br&gt;i cant find fourth nigger&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873181&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873112&lt;br&gt;Yes but how would you feel if you DID find it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873193&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872076&lt;br&gt;Money is fake and gay. No surprise everything else is.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873211&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872713&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873212&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;half-chub and a hatchet&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;half-chub and a hatchet&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;half-chub and a hatchet&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873219&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;My blood is boiling while watching this webm on repeat. I hate women so much I&amp;#x27;ll turn gay.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873258&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;i wanna cut their toes off w/ my bolt cutter&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873271&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871755&lt;br&gt;Anyone who posts this ai nigger baby will be rounded up, families executed in front of them, then tortured to death slowly, skin peeled off, toenails removed, adrenaline injected to keep you conscious cartel style&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873293&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;only someone who has never had a job would think tiktok videos of girls dancing are representative of how workplaces actually operate. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Almost all women working provide value and will wash out if they aren&amp;#x27;t (or aren&amp;#x27;t sucking the manager&amp;#x27;s dick).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873312&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871755&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Epsteins Boyfriend got swagger&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873324&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873293&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Almost all women working provide value&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873510&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871569&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;re either trolling or never worked a day in your life,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873611&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871931&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873193&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Fake and Gay&lt;br&gt;Why is are Schizos always using that phrase? I instantly know there is a schizo take coming when i read this. Some schizo takes are interesting, some are even good, some are good to think through and some are just funny to read. But they stzill are schizo takes and mostly bullshit influeces too much by wish bias. So how and where did this phrase pick up with schizos. When i know, its around 2021/2022 when the schizo&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;economy will collapse and people will starve due to lockdowns&lt;br&gt;did not materialize. Then they started with this phrase to somehow save their prediction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873806&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872076&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;no less than three seething replies about muh real capitalism&lt;br&gt;If you abolished the state it would be reinvented by the wealthy overnight&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873944&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873611&lt;br&gt;Fake and gay was in use when I 1st started using this site in 2011.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873988&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;Hopefully never because I have a fake overpaid job, just not in HR&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876439&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872064&lt;br&gt;And prevent White women from breeding&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877263&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;everyone wants to be rich without doing jack shit, jews are just more succesful at the game and more honest about what the game is, maybe because they invented it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;there are less and less people talking about &amp;#x27;&amp;#x27;value&amp;#x27;&amp;#x27; in a real way, no one believes in it, no one believes that value is real or there is merit to providing it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;everything is about winning or losing, and brother let me tell you, I&amp;#x27;m not gonna be one of the cucks who focuses on helping society or building when I can make my money sitting in my computer and playing the money game, the money game is more fun and rewarding than going to medical or engineering school.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877287&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;go in to interview for a technical role&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;see vidrel being filmed in the hallway on your way in&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;the job pays well&lt;br&gt;wat do?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877298&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872085&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872087&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872233&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872278&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;REAL capitalism has never been tried&lt;br&gt;This is real capitalism, and it&amp;#x27;s retarded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878294&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871569&lt;br&gt;Because human beings(the goyim) is just another resources that the &amp;#x27;choosen ones&amp;#x27; can exploid.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878310&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877287&lt;br&gt;call them a bunch of FAG KIKE TRANNIES and instead get a based n&amp;#x27; trad job shoveling horse shit for $14.35/hour with no health insurance&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878355&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878294&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;human beings&lt;br&gt;its the best asset you can own, they work, (produce free goods) they pay taxes(fake money holds value), they eat poison food and get sick, then forced to consume overpriced drugs(more profits), there is no stock that can make better return over lifetime and asset(the goy) is free.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878449&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873611&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Why is are Schizos always using that phrase?&lt;br&gt;In zoomer lingo, it&amp;#x27;s copium. They are losers who can&amp;#x27;t cut it. Naturally, they are not the problem and anyone who does great in the current system is cheating (hence fake and gay).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;These types would be losers under any system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878715&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871931&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;They don’t actually do nothing &lt;br&gt;These retarded whores are of no value to society work force.&lt;br&gt;They can not weld , machine, approve engineering drawings or balance the company finances or protect them f taxes.&lt;br&gt;All they do is prevent men from building modern day Rome.&lt;br&gt;Go back to plebbit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878722&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;Are they dancing because nobody replied to their emails and they have nothing to do or are they bragging about not replying to emails?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879023&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878715&lt;br&gt;If they didn&amp;#x27;t provide value they wouldn&amp;#x27;t be there. The reality is that HR prevents the company from getting sued out of existence. If you want to hate HR, that is valid but just know that hate should be reflected to the legal system that allows for the company to be sued. Yes they prevent men from being men and are only there to protect women&amp;#x27;s feelings but guess what women&amp;#x27;s feelings are what the legal system is currently based on with shit like abortion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>