<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>/biz/ Active (filtered, with replies)</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/</link><description>Filtered out: general, gme, bbbyq. OP + first 3 replies + last 30 replies.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 19:31:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Privacy Coins — 81 replies — 324.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61849447</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61849447?lm=1771355891</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 19:18:11 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Privacy Coins&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61849447'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 81 • Updated: 2026-02-17 19:18 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whether you like it or not, BTC is dying. Which way anons?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849481&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gold and silver.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849898&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849447&lt;br&gt;XMR as always. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849481&lt;br&gt;Acceptable but unusable for internet transactions and too easily stolen. Also makes smaller or spontaneous transactions harder unless the governments were to issue gold coins again and that would be bearish.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849958&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849447&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;BTC is a pedo coin&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;most used currency for CP is not however&lt;br&gt;quit the infighting, monegro.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864393&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862698&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;Nervajeets&amp;quot; living rent free lmao&lt;br&gt;No, but I notice patterns, like the smell of cow shit, overuse of the word sir (misspoken as sar) and the incessant need to shill some unmaintained jeet coin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864510&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862698&lt;br&gt;Irrelevant shitcoin #2&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864651&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864393&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Nerva sucks as a privacy coin&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Nerva was forked from moneros code&lt;br&gt;You only get to pick one, bot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864667&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864651&lt;br&gt;Nice try but having less than 1/3 of our ring size and no mitigations against multiple attacks that worked on our code base (the devs don&amp;#x27;t even know whether their code has the same flaws or not) means it is not sufficient as a privacy coin. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;picrel&lt;br&gt;Next time try something somebody actually said&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864677&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849898&lt;br&gt;why would that be bearish&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864683&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864677&lt;br&gt;The governments as they are currently don&amp;#x27;t want to embrace our freedom or even anything to our benefit. If they go back to gold coins there will be some catch. If the jew embraces something, try to move as far away from that as possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864708&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855597&lt;br&gt;BTCFi is giving it more use cases with Babylon leading the charge. And I think when we have more projects offering native BTC staking, then we will see the narrative go viral&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864866&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864667&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Try something somebody actually said&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;literally you on every general&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;almost you entirely&lt;br&gt;Cry me some diodes, clanker.&lt;br&gt;Nerva is here to stay.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864897&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864866&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Nerva is here to stay.&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t care if it stays as long as you stop smearing XMR and spamming our threads&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864948&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864897&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I don&amp;#x27;t care if it stays as long as you stop smearing XMR and spamming our threads&lt;br&gt;The only spammer is you, in both this thread and the xmr general. You came here to start shit and have done so in every privacy thread that has popped up. You also accuse everyone of being a poojeet and promoting nerva. Again, the only person promoting (xmr in your case) and causing a stink has been YOU. So fuck off back to your little monero hole, jeetbot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865014&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864948&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The only spammer is you,&lt;br&gt;I wish that were true but sadly the nervajeets constantly try to shit up our thread and this board. There&amp;#x27;s a reason all of these anti-Monero threads pop up when they lose the discussion in the general. Notice how quiet they&amp;#x27;ve become after &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860646 was posted. All of their anti-Monero arguments (which was the entire value proposition for nerva) are gone. Their questions they claim never were answered poofed up into air. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;You came here to start shit&lt;br&gt;OP literally accuses XMR of being some freemason bullshit. You&amp;#x27;re the perfect representation of the jew asking what harm he has done to us. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;You also accuse everyone of being a poojeet and promoting nerva.&lt;br&gt;No, I say that the ones that copy all of the points the nervajeets make to be a nervajeets. That&amp;#x27;s because the only people interested in nerva are jeets.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Please don&amp;#x27;t challenge me when I smear the only functional crypto currency please just go away I can&amp;#x27;t handle it please please please&lt;br&gt;No sar, you wish to talk about XMR? I&amp;#x27;ll be there and refute each on of your pathetic claims.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865124&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864651&lt;br&gt;Holy shit, XMR to a fucking T anon...&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865014&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;bot programmed to hate random shitcoin&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;even if not true, makes it look like hes funded by masons/jews because he literally cannot stop promoting monero&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;becomes a meme in and of himself here&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864651&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;he seriously cant stop&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;he will bring nerva up in random threads every chance he gets even when no one is talking about it&lt;br&gt;Just fucking stop and go away monegro. Maybe they didnt stop after that was posted, because they were never spamming up your threads in the first place you pathetic fucking loser. Only you were, they were just asking questions, something anyone can do. I scoured your xmr generals, and your clearly the psychopath across every fucking one. Non stop blogposts of text that do nothing but go in circles, and now youre doing it here. Save yourself some time and go shit up someone elses thread. Oh right, you cant, because youre a monegro botnet that works for monero glowies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I started this thread to discuss privacy coins and all youve done is shit up my thread you piece of shit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865161&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865014&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;bot&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865268&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862698&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862796&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864651&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864866&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865161&lt;br&gt;good morning nervasaaars&lt;br&gt;truly xnv is the most aryan bharatoken superior peer-to-poop privacy coin xnvsaars redeem asap&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865595&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865268&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;i cant stop sucking monero dick, am i gay enough yet? Somebody like me pleeease!!&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;Back to your xmr general faggot shill&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865847&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865268&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;nooo not my heckin fedcoin noo all other privacy coins are jeetcoins noooo&lt;br&gt;CryptoNight-Adaptive &amp;gt; RandomX for decentralization&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865956&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865869&lt;br&gt;Have you tried bumping your generel thread so it stays up like everyone else does&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865998&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865956&lt;br&gt;Wasnt my general. I got the screenshot someone snapped of it off the discord. No way a thread gets bumped off this board that fast. There is shit on here for days that no one replies to. Mods are afraid of it. Idk why. Glowies or bagholders probably.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866158&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865869&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;This thread has been pruned or deleted &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865998&lt;br&gt;How do you know that it wasn&amp;#x27;t deleted by the OP?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866337&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865998&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;discord&lt;br&gt;very true sar discord is perfect for our poo privacy coin, better stay there, 4chan is an anti-indian glowie honeypot benchod site&lt;br&gt;btw ser remember to send your designated face scan/ID to discord for better compliance nervasaars&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866373&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866158&lt;br&gt;Well for one, that thread was only posted a few hours ago. Threads dont die that quick. The other reason is because his thread is back&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865946 and hes asking why his shit got deleted. Oh and 4chan is now blocking me. Yet the mods and XMR fags are the ones who started all this. Ask about nerva, get banned. Buy the JDIF coin goy. Maximumkekles&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;btw since my block, they deleted his thread again. So yea, jannies are deleting anything nerva related.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866384&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866337&lt;br&gt;See pic related here&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864948&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;(thats you faggot.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866402&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849447&lt;br&gt;BTC died when it forked away from BCH (the Bitcoin) and broke from the design being an unbroken chain of hashes of digital signatures. That chain doesn&amp;#x27;t exist at all on BTC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866407&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866384&lt;br&gt;why so mad saar&lt;br&gt;the nerva discord isn&amp;#x27;t paying (you) enough to raid 4chan?&lt;br&gt;do not redeem the mod ban saar stop evading bans saar&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866583&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866407&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;the nerva discord isn&amp;#x27;t paying (you) enough to raid 4chan?&lt;br&gt;do not redeem the mod ban saar stop evading bans saar&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;stop evading bans&lt;br&gt;Their discord isnt paying me shit, i started stealing memes from there because its obvious youre all fucking jeet jannies that doesnt want anyone posting about Nerva at all. Stop evading bans? Why are you banning them or me in the first place? You dont ban xmr, zcash, ltc, btc, xrp, or any of that other shit. Yet here you are, admitting to being the jannie whose banning them. Youre pathetic. Pretending that their threads just &amp;quot;fell off the board,&amp;quot; and even having the gall to pretend to ask about it. I knew the mods had a hand in the fucking XMR general, and that anon that said you followed him to /pol/ wasnt lying. Fuck you you pieces of shit. Screencap this and start posting it in other /biz/ threads. This place is corrupt as is XMR.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866671&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849447&lt;br&gt;they all go to zero if btc dies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866688&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;bitch about Nerva shills on XMR threads&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;ban/delete whenever they make a Nerva general&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;leave countless shit threads untouched&lt;br&gt;This is exactly why Nerva exists.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If your “decentralized privacy coin community” is so threatened by the existence of a CPU-only alternative that mods have to memoryhole any discussion, that’s not confidence, that’s insecurity and gatekeeping. You can’t preach censorship resistance while censoring competition like a reddit janny.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Monero is the king today, nobody denies that. But watching a Monero mod rageban any Nerva thread while allowing endless garbage posts just proves the point. A privacy movement that can’t tolerate parallel projects is already compromised.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cope harder. Nerva isn’t going away.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866695&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866583&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866688&lt;br&gt;ChatGPT moment&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866712&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866695&lt;br&gt;Cope. Also trips and dubs of truth. &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866688&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866728&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866712&lt;br&gt;Getting rugged by Zcash jews is one thing but imagine getting rugged by Nerva jeets I would kms lmao&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>When did you realize that you were NOT going to make it? — 65 replies — 260.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61862922</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61862922?lm=1771356514</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 19:28:34 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;When did you realize that you were NOT going to make it?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61862922'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 65 • Updated: 2026-02-17 19:28 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862935&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;is he ok&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862944&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862935&lt;br&gt;just some minor scratches (on his brain)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862956&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;the funniest part is that you think &amp;quot;maybe he survived the crash, just barely&amp;quot; but then it erupts in flames and he&amp;#x27;s cooked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864687&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864699&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863924&lt;br&gt;Reap or not you have to understand 2 things:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;the pedo elite (redundant, there are no non-pedo elite) believe in this shit HARD. If you know your enemies motivations, you can outmaneuver them&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;we currently inhabit this material plane, largely outside the strong harmonic influences of what we would call gods. Just don&amp;#x27;t be such a conniving piece of shit when you can help it&lt;br&gt;Don&amp;#x27;t over think it, anon.&lt;br&gt;Yes, I know I misused greentext; leave it alone, well poisoners&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864709&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Driving in hard shoulder&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Driving way too fast&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Slamming on the brakes causing you to front flip&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Not trying to switch lane&lt;br&gt;Darwin award.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864714&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863183&lt;br&gt;you&amp;#x27;re not supposed to drive there&lt;br&gt;play stupid games, win stupid prices&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864734&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863411&lt;br&gt;When I got my permit in the EU the first evasion maneuver you learn is the quick jerking of the handle to swerve and avoid this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864738&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863681&lt;br&gt;Should we just back china then?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is this the only way to topple the status quo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864767&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;Why do you care what other people are thinking? Does it hurt your feelings when Jesus leaves you on read? You still don&amp;#x27;t have to be atheist.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864769&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864709&lt;br&gt;not starting with &amp;gt;riding a motorcycle&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864775&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;I BOUGHT SHINY ROCK @ $120 &lt;br&gt;BIZ TOLD ME IT WAS GOING TO $5000 EOY&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864842&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864092&lt;br&gt;No it&amp;#x27;s not dumbass. Nearly all roads in Asia are like this and they all have motorbikes that drive on it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864852&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864842&lt;br&gt;Well then it&amp;#x27;s a retarded design if you have to give way to vehicles turning every 2 seconds - and it has no markings to indicate as such.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864870&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;That finishing final destination touch&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865341&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864842&lt;br&gt;Just because people abuse the emergency lane it illegal doesn&amp;#x27;t mean that&amp;#x27;s what it is designed for.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865399&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862935&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;he&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865412&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864842&lt;br&gt;they have roads where motorcycles try to front brake doing 70mph? lol, this chink deserved what he got, like it or not.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865437&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s not tragic to die doing what you love&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865490&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;When the NSA broke fisa and used Pegasus on me whilst on vacation and upon arriving home and getting a new phone being threatened in person after dodging a SWAT attempt through someone using back doors on my hardwired internet connection. Just the tip of the icerberg but I would strongly advise leaving the united states, it’s only gonna get worse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865508&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;cutting across 2 lanes just to go 5 mph in a turn&lt;br&gt;motorcyclist shouldn&amp;#x27;t have been there but white car is a fucking retard&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865611&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865490&lt;br&gt;There&amp;#x27;s nowhere to go. We have to take a stand where we are.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865639&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;When did you realize that you were NOT going to make it?&lt;br&gt;I looked at the conditions of the people who had made it to the wealthiest tiers of society. They all had generational wealth behind them, and they all operated on insane levels of exploitation to generate that wealth. Realized that &amp;quot;making it&amp;quot; means screwing over so many people that you alienate yourself from most people, except the likes of musk, epstein, trump, etc.&lt;br&gt;I realized that though the club was small and that I wasn&amp;#x27;t in it, that the people in the club were not the kind of person I wanted to be. I&amp;#x27;d rather disband the club.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865646&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865611&lt;br&gt;Nope, I’m out - fuck this third world country in disguise. The problem is thresholds were crossed and stupid people who shouldn’t have power drag you into shit that doesn’t even matter. This whole entire country is rotten, the corrupt local cop is just an extended phenotype of the so called “elite”. Shut off the news, delete all media and just get up and fucking go. Don’t lift a finger for this surveillance prison social credit score algorithm hellscape.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865657&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863529&lt;br&gt;Beautifully put.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865848&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865437&lt;br&gt;Ok Alesteir&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865901&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863924&lt;br&gt;Yes those entities actually exist. In history, people were religious because they were uneducated and most couldn&amp;#x27;t read. now people can read and are educated, but they aren&amp;#x27;t religious, but they also told that spiritual or religious hoo-hah is bull, the only thing that exists is what you see in front of you with your basic senses blah blah. When in fact, people should be using their educated brain to dig deeper. but it&amp;#x27;s all by design by the elites to continue obscuring the truths. they did it hundreds of years ago, and they continue to do it today just in a different way. READ THINGS. start with the bible. answers for a lot of things are in there. you don&amp;#x27;t need to be religious to read the bible and think critically.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;then move upwards throughout history and you&amp;#x27;ll notice the pattern. these people are extremely, extremely religious/spiritual themselves. They are Yahwists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865913&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864842&lt;br&gt;Because the chinks are all retarded insects, its not supposed to be driven on&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866587&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;it really is amazing how you can just go from fully alive, lots of possibilities to fully dead and nothing can be done about it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866704&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866587&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Could practice something called&lt;br&gt;&amp;quot;Defensive driving&amp;quot; &lt;br&gt;or &lt;br&gt;&amp;quot;Not recklessly speeding on the shoulder&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;But yea nothing could have been done, the cagies claimed another scalp&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866754&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864685&lt;br&gt;Pretty much this&lt;br&gt;I’m simultaneously never going to sell and never expecting it to go up&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866776&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863681&lt;br&gt;I have to admit I wasn&amp;#x27;t a noticer but now I am kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866784&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864699&lt;br&gt;I need to re read the Art of War in this context&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Yurop is BROKE, POOR, DESTITUTE, DOWNTRODDEN — 24 replies — 96.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858634</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858634?lm=1771356280</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 19:24:40 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Yurop is BROKE, POOR, DESTITUTE, DOWNTRODDEN&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858634'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 24 • Updated: 2026-02-17 19:24 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looks like yuros are gonna have to skimp on their tax derived healthcare and Germany is considering ending their Bürgergeld program.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;There is significant reluctance among voters in Britain and Germany to accept economic pain in return for rearmament, even while majorities in both countries believe the outbreak of a third world war is more likely than not in the next five years.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;German and French voters are also now less likely than they were last year to support increased defence budgets if it meant a trade-off with other investment, according to a poll for Politico this month.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858658&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858634&lt;br&gt;They are gonna attck russia in ukraine directly in 2029 mark my words. You can find me here at this time.&lt;br&gt;https://www.youtube.com/shorts/mo0dak0aor4&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858664&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858634&lt;br&gt;just raise taxes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858670&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858634&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;accept economic pain in return for rearmament&lt;br&gt;Ah yes and the economic pain must fall on white people and not on the millions of immigrants and &amp;quot;citizens&amp;quot; on welfare.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858672&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858670&lt;br&gt;Excuse me Chud these poor brown people are just trying to survife how can you not give them everything they want?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858674&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858664&lt;br&gt;European nations have a long and storied tradition of raising taxes to the point of revolution to fund their wars.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858734&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858634&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;There is significant reluctance among voters in Britain and Germany to accept economic pain in return for rearmament&lt;br&gt;That&amp;#x27;s because we&amp;#x27;re already having a lot of economic struggles since the sanctions against Russia. Also we think of ourselves as too advanced to do production of actual goods. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858658&lt;br&gt;They&amp;#x27;re currently preparing for 2027. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858670&lt;br&gt;Considering the current opinions of the german government it seems like we&amp;#x27;ll be equal in the squalor we live in.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858735&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858634&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Germany is considering ending their Bürgergeld program&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858758&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858634&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;europoors just gonna rely on the USA to win another war for them&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;in reality we&amp;#x27;re just going to be given Greenland and all that grandstanding was just a waste of time&lt;br&gt;christ what a joke continent kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858773&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858634&lt;br&gt;Germany won&amp;#x27;t end Burgergeld because half the migrants are on it. What they will do though is raise taxes and possibly go the Dutch route as well. It&amp;#x27;s not like anyone will protest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858789&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858773&lt;br&gt;why don&amp;#x27;t they just send the migrants on it back?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858799&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858789&lt;br&gt;Knock it off with the antisemitism&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858817&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858789&lt;br&gt;Muh human rights.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858824&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858634&lt;br&gt;I will gladly die for israel, ukraine and brussel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858952&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;60 IQ migroids are living expense free in gold plated hotels, and can get away with abhorrent crimes. Europeans are told they don&amp;#x27;t actually exist and aren&amp;#x27;t native to Europe.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are no greater cattle than those that would fight for this system&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859777&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858734&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;They&amp;#x27;re currently preparing for 2027.&lt;br&gt;2027 i dont think but yeah i almost wrote 2028. Its somewhere around these dates or a bit later&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859999&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858634&lt;br&gt;Its gonna get pretty bad and its not even a pol meme, the social net is what killed pretty much all crime in the continent, now they gonna have an extremely old population, low economic output and incentive for crime coupled with lots of violent migrants, and its all their fault because they couldnt breeeed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860002&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858789&lt;br&gt;Are you stupid?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860008&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858634&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;YOU MUST FIGHT TO SAVE GLOBOHOMO AND BOOMER PENSIONS&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;what fighting age white man would actually fall for this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860014&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860008&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;fighting age white man&lt;br&gt;there&amp;#x27;s like 3 of them left&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863068&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858634&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;majorities in both countries believe the outbreak of a third world war is more likely than not in the next five years.&lt;br&gt;What? Do normies really think ww3 is about to start?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863097&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860002&lt;br&gt;what&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863126&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Do it and remove military housing from Germany. Total base adjacent landlord/business death. Slam dunk a tattoo parlor into a garbage can. Launch pizza/burger joints right offbase into the sun. Curbstomp a predatory mobile phone service provider company with service cancelations. Evicerate landlord&amp;#x27;s income by moving on base.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863649&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858789&lt;br&gt;good question. I wonder why?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866762&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858824&lt;br&gt;For von der Leyen!!!!!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>BREAKING NEWS: $70 PRICE TARGET FOR XRP. — 14 replies — 56.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861161</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861161?lm=1771356245</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 19:24:05 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;BREAKING NEWS: $70 PRICE TARGET FOR XRP.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861161'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 14 • Updated: 2026-02-17 19:24 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are repeating the 2017 bullrun with a longer timeframe. The wave 2 has completed and wave 3 will take us to $13 within the next 3 months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861168&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861161&lt;br&gt;got a long way to go&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861395&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;13$?&lt;br&gt;I sell all my xrp&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861475&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861161&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;$13&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;d be a millionaire.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861504&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;5 trillion mcap&lt;br&gt;random bullshit does not go up forever lmao&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861511&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861161&lt;br&gt;Thanks. Shorting this harder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864005&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861504&lt;br&gt;Price x supply can never be this high number !&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864008&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864005&lt;br&gt;The supply is constantly growing and it&amp;#x27;s not gonna go up to 10 trillion mcap because retards like you are invested in it and tards are never right.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864012&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861161&lt;br&gt;BOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOM&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865668&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861395&lt;br&gt;I am out at $4.90&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865741&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861161&lt;br&gt;$13 is FUD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865781&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861504&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;gold and silver still undervalued at multiple trillions of fake fiat &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;but arbitragebotchain couldn&amp;#x27;t possibly be worth a few tril&lt;br&gt;Normie moment&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865845&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865668&lt;br&gt;I am out at $3.60&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865934&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SO BULLISH XRP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866759&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861511&lt;br&gt;RIP your savings. XRP is the only coin that kept post-Trump gains. It is up almost 200% since then.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>This shit got me finna kms ONG!!! — 13 replies — 52.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61866292</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61866292?lm=1771356381</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 19:26:21 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;This shit got me finna kms ONG!!!&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61866292'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 13 • Updated: 2026-02-17 19:26 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;This shit got me finna kms ONG!!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866346&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866292&lt;br&gt;omg dude imagine sitting by a lake. or you could take a nap on some flowers... whoa that would be so much better than working for shekelberg!!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866589&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866292&lt;br&gt;bros i might have to start waging soon..it..it cant be that bad...r...righ..ACK&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866689&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Let the goyim deal in the real world&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866699&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866689&lt;br&gt;hahaha the files have been so fucking eye opening. everything we said about jews right there&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866707&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866292&lt;br&gt;born to live like an animal! eating and fucking and basking in neurotransmitters!&lt;br&gt;forced to do human bullshit! high-level concerns no animal can even begin to comprehend!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866711&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866292&lt;br&gt;BUMP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866715&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;all you lazy fucking gen alphoids and zoomers don&amp;#x27;t seem to realize that you weren&amp;#x27;t born to lay around fingering your gay assholes.&lt;br&gt;You were born to work even harder just to survive than you need to nowadays, including daily running and chasing down animals for miles with spears, with your tribe to eat, or if you are lucky, fishing and back breaking farming, but thosecame with risks of your shit being plundered or you going hungry if unsuccessful.&lt;br&gt;EVERY DAY was life or death struggles, entitled morons.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866726&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866715&lt;br&gt;We don&amp;#x27;t live in the jungle any more, you boomer rat&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866740&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866715&lt;br&gt;not to mention once you were 30+ years old, you were as good as dead.&lt;br&gt;if a disease didn&amp;#x27;t get you, a competing younger tribe would murder you, or even your own tribe would because your strength, speed, and usefulness ran out, BYTCH&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866752&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866726&lt;br&gt;doesn&amp;#x27;t change the fact that you and OP were born to suffer, struggle and die even more horribly than you are now.&lt;br&gt;No one owes you anything.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866756&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866740&lt;br&gt;I agree everyone over 30 should die horribly&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866770&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866756&lt;br&gt;so do something about it, pussy.&lt;br&gt;your generation are the biggest groups of fags and pussies.&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m 39, and I&amp;#x27;m waaaitiiin&amp;#x27;&lt;br&gt;come on.&lt;br&gt;Do something, BYTCH&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Need some serious advice. — 7 replies — 28.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61865311</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61865311?lm=1771356005</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 19:20:05 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Need some serious advice.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61865311'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 7 • Updated: 2026-02-17 19:20 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;So I just did a major arbitrage play and earned over 8000 USDT in profit. USDT has long lost its peg on Algorand DeFi, reaching $0.30 due to major exchanges suspending deposits. There were no off-ramps and people simply market sold their USDT for USDC, resulting in a major depeg. However there were still a couple thousand dollars left in USDT liquidity so I found this exchange in South America that still accepted USDT via Algorand Network.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What do I do? As a turd worlder I 3x&amp;#x27;ed my $4k portfolio (which was 92% BSV). Do I buy more BSV before it skyrockets to $1200? Do I keep it in USDC? Do I buy a house? By the way I already bought a shitload of furniture for my house and this is for investment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865453&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865311&lt;br&gt;What exchange&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865468&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865311&lt;br&gt;That&amp;#x27;s not a real USDT idiot&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865684&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865453&lt;br&gt;based retard&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865468&lt;br&gt;it&amp;#x27;s 100% USDT i outright spent a shitload of on a visa creditcard (bought a new oven and some boating equipment)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865721&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I would just keep it in USDC. Crypto is circling the drain. When BIP-110 becomes the dominant protocol for Bitcoin, buy Bitcoin. &lt;br&gt;Is the arb opportunity gone now?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866565&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865721&lt;br&gt;Yeah it&amp;#x27;s pretty much over by now. Check vestige.fi.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It might happen again if people take this opportunity to cash out some USDT. I was just lucky I found an exchange that actually accepts these tokens.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Also thanks for the advice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866603&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kek, good play OP, thanks for sharing&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866737&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865311&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;By the way I already bought a shitload of furniture for my house and this is for investment.&lt;br&gt;THisi s why you&amp;#x27;re ngmi.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>AAVE is gonna do what all the Chainlink shills tell you LINK will do — 18 replies — 26.2/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861383</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861383?lm=1771354207</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 18:50:07 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;AAVE is gonna do what all the Chainlink shills tell you LINK will do&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861383'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 18 • Updated: 2026-02-17 18:50 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;AAVE is gonna do what all the Chainlink shills tell you LINK will do&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861393&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861383&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;tokenized abundance assets&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861407&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;for me it&amp;#x27;s tokenized scarcity assets&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861409&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;That guy is nearly as abundant as Sergey, if you catch my drift&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861478&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861393&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;yeah Aave is somehow more globohomo than Link.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861492&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861383&lt;br&gt;my aave tokens got liquidated by the gay little fight between aave labs and their faggot contributors, so they can all get fucked in my humble opinion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861532&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861393&lt;br&gt;cool buzz word kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861571&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861383&lt;br&gt;aave and chainlink are so deep up each other&amp;#x27;s ass that when you cheer for one you cheer for the other&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861574&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861383&lt;br&gt;Powered by Chainlink&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861647&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861492&lt;br&gt;What kind of retarded fud is this? How did your Aave tokens &amp;quot;get liquidated&amp;quot;?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861649&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861647&lt;br&gt;how do you think, moron?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861665&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861649&lt;br&gt;Longing with leverage? Should&amp;#x27;ve be a stakechad&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861668&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861665&lt;br&gt;aave&amp;#x27;s entire business model is based on leverage&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861675&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861668&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The casino&amp;#x27;s entire business model is gambling&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;And?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861980&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861383&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;could&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;by 2050&lt;br&gt;kek baggies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861984&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861383&lt;br&gt;Which is?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865066&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;why are these guys all fat as fuck?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866581&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861409&lt;br&gt;I have to widen my perspective to understand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866612&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865066&lt;br&gt;little too much abundance&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>$TSLA @$405 — 6 replies — 24.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61866167</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61866167?lm=1771356226</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 19:23:46 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;$TSLA @$405&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61866167'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 6 • Updated: 2026-02-17 19:23 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;What is the fair value for this stock?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866173&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866167&lt;br&gt;$405&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866174&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;$3.50&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866182&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866173&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866174&lt;br&gt;ok, ty. Imma take the average of the two. Wisdom of the crowd&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866274&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866167&lt;br&gt;$60 and that is being generous&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866639&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866167&lt;br&gt;$405&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866174&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866182&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866274&lt;br&gt;wrong&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866757&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866639&lt;br&gt;ok, Imma short it then, because it is overvalued according to you&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>NIGGER LIFE — 11 replies — 23.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61863888</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61863888?lm=1771354954</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 19:02:34 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;NIGGER LIFE&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61863888'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 11 • Updated: 2026-02-17 19:02 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;PUMP... AND DUMP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863890&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;it&amp;#x27;s over for buttcoin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863896&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863888&lt;br&gt;SUPER NIGGER GALAXY&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863903&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Looks fine to me&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864134&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863888&lt;br&gt;NIGGER CZ!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864323&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NIGGER NIGGER&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865150&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IT&amp;#x27;S JUST ONE THOSE DAYS WHEN YOU DON&amp;#x27;T WANNA WAKE UP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865752&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A most blessed thread on /biz/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Good morrow fine and friendly gentlemen of non-reflective skin tones!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866571&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;NIGGER JOCKEY!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866593&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;crypto is for niggers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866664&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863888&lt;br&gt;checked melanin individuals!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Day 215 of snailposting every day until LINK is at $100 — 3 replies — 12.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61865240</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61865240?lm=1771356144</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 19:22:24 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Day 215 of snailposting every day until LINK is at $100&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61865240'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 3 • Updated: 2026-02-17 19:22 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Day 215 of snailposting every day until LINK is at $100&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866248&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865757&lt;br&gt;no u&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866748&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One must imagine Sisyphus unhappy posting this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;No additional replies in the latest window.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>FFA &amp; Shipping Futures — 3 replies — 12.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61866449</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61866449?lm=1771356063</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 19:21:03 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;FFA &amp;amp; Shipping Futures&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61866449'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 3 • Updated: 2026-02-17 19:21 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;What is Forward Freight Agreement and why are people saying this is how Epstein got rich?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866487&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866449&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;he doesnt know&lt;br&gt;lurk more unironically&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866542&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866449&lt;br&gt;Imagine her on my unblanked cock!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866742&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;let the goyim deal in the real world&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This kike has been living rent free in my mind ever since i read this statement&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;No additional replies in the latest window.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>The US is in recession — 97 replies — 175.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61857490</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61857490?lm=1771354682</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 18:58:02 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;The US is in recession&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61857490'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 97 • Updated: 2026-02-17 18:58 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US is in recession&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857499&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White collar recession comes before regular recession 100% of the time. We&amp;#x27;ve been in a white collar recession since 2020.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857500&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;Always was, its depression for over a year now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857508&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;GDP is growing, recession is fake.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nothing ever happens. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stop putting your vibes and feelings into your job search, learn to get better skills and be more marketable to employers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;McDonalds is always hiring&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861729&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858084&lt;br&gt;The fantasy is better than the reality&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861769&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857805&lt;br&gt;We should be bombing Mexico.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861811&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861711&lt;br&gt;No I wasn’t. I don’t feel like explaining it to you so I’ll just let AI do it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863135&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858023&lt;br&gt;Pam Bondi was such a hot piece of ass when she was young. She&amp;#x27;s still sorta cute give that she&amp;#x27;s sixty years old. It&amp;#x27;s too bad she&amp;#x27;s protecting Jewish pedophiles and cannibals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863175&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;BUMP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863206&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And the burger gov is again burning absolutely everything in the market, including themselves to make a smoke screen to cover the crashing dollar.&lt;br&gt;Nobody wants that shit yet it is going up with not only no buyers but countries constantly throwing it into the market. Absolute shitshow from a drowning in shit man.&lt;br&gt;Funny isn&amp;#x27;t it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863218&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860719&lt;br&gt;The boat that is jewsa has been sinking for a while. The orange nigger is actively making more holes in it and setting it on fire&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863252&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What&amp;#x27;s the polymarket for that??&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863679&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857500&lt;br&gt;Try since 08. Things have never actually genuinely recovered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864332&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;End of the Juglar cycle. Overproduction crisis. Fed interest rates plunging toward zero. Soon an other Capital idling necessary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864333&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863679&lt;br&gt;Capital final crisis since 2008.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864989&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863206&lt;br&gt;2006 was giving out loans like candy to people who had absolutely no way of ever servicing them&lt;br&gt;this then resulted in a lot of forced selling into a no bid market as all of this inventory was cleared when the bubble popped&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;right now we dont have excessive loans, quite the opposite retards arent given insane loans this is legit existing money bidding up hard assets because so much money got printed and it has to go somewhere&lt;br&gt;you dont get a crash in housing without forced selling and who is going to force sell his real estate at low prices without the bank margin calling them&lt;br&gt;unlike stocks which are completely fungible and its price is set at the margin, housing isnt and the owner can just sit on the asset forever and not be forced to take any offer being made at market price&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;to disrupt this &amp;#x27;bubble&amp;#x27; you need the government unprinting the money supply (lol, lmao even) or you need a large section of boomers dying off and leaving their heirs with no way to pay the taxes/upkeep and force dump it&lt;br&gt;the second one is the only realistic option, tho there is also the risk that the heirs can pay for the inheritance and real estate is now permanently locked up in magnate hands and the nation reduced to permarenting slave&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865001&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It really isn&amp;#x27;t mentioned enough that our &amp;quot;recovery&amp;quot; after 2008 was just setting interest rates to 0 for 10 years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865048&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864989&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;...a large section of boomers dying off and leaving their heirs with no way to pay the taxes/upkeep...real estate is now permanently locked up in magnate hands....&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;ve laid out exactly what&amp;#x27;s been going on since 2008&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865068&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865048&lt;br&gt;yes thats the point, the implication here is that real estate is now permanently priced out of the middle class income range&lt;br&gt;not that a crash is imminent like the anon i was replying to seemed to suggest&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865501&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;I knew it was really over when Wendy&amp;#x27;s and pizza Hut announced theyre closing hundreds of stores.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865585&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;Idk these terms, and economics is a fraudulent science anyways, so I&amp;#x27;ll just say what I see.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;My life sucks.&lt;br&gt;Its getting worse.&lt;br&gt;I am watching generational decline among my family (each new set of kids struggle more than their parents).&lt;br&gt;People seem unhappy.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Call that recession, depression, or economic boon! Idc, US is a shithole.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m sure people will respond saying I&amp;#x27;m cherry picking. Dishonesty is rampant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865659&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857779&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Foreign money taking investments out of the US because trump is an unpredictable fucking moron being puppeteered by unironically evil people&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;American dollar has lost 10% of its value over the course of 2025&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Constant tariff bullshitery that is objectively hurting American industries that rely on imports&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Nuked basedbean deal with China on top of farmers needing a fucking bailout because of the retard they voted in (again)&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Tourism industry cratering every day as we speak so even less money being injected into the economy &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;ICE operation have caused businesses across the country to shut down because either no one&amp;#x27;s willing to go out, or because they don&amp;#x27;t want random goons in masks harassing employees&lt;br&gt;Dude it&amp;#x27;s actually impressive how hard these retards just destroyed the entire reputation of america abroad and fucked us over domestically, but his cult fan base and circle of wannabe oligarchs who own media outlets will continue telling you that there is no war in ba sing se&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865663&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861063&lt;br&gt;We really need to do what the Chinese do with making sure household consumption as share of GDP is increasing. Actually reflects living standards instead of billions of dollars getting spitswapped between 3-4 different AI companies constantly. Then again, most of the people hear would just ree hearing the term “5 year plan” or “stability focused infrastructure development.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865674&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865585&lt;br&gt;MIGAtrannies will happily eat shit if a libtard has to smell their breath.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865800&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865585&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;US is a shithole&lt;br&gt;and the usa still gives you about the best chance in the world to improve your life if you come from humble beginnings&lt;br&gt;altho it also offers you every temptation possible to make you drive yourself over the financial cliff at every turn at the same time it offers you opportunity&lt;br&gt;just know its far worse everywhere else as society in general is reverting back to medieval style caste based system of neither hope nor escape&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865942&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865800&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;and the usa still gives you about the best chance in the world to improve your life if you come from humble beginnings&lt;br&gt;this has not been true in at least 20-25 years&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866035&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865942&lt;br&gt;lol, lmao&lt;br&gt;then give me the list of countries that you think arent just better today but were better 20 years ago and i&amp;#x27;ll have a good laugh&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;and to clarify we are specifically talking about giving chances to poor unconnected people so dont say retarded shit like liechtenstein&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866071&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865800&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;he fell for the meme&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866130&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860705&lt;br&gt;None of these are necessary. We could be totally self-sufficient, even for things like rare-earths. The Epstein class decided that would be bad for them so we aren&amp;#x27;t.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866186&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866130&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;pharmaceuticals are not necessary &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;input goods for new tech are not necessary &lt;br&gt;Uh huh. So what’s necessary? Shovels, canned food and farmland? If you want to be Amish so badly just do it, nobody is stopping you. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the real world, though, self-sufficiency would entail access to pharmaceuticals and the ability to evolve technologically and keep up with the first world. We can sing songs all day about how the US could be self-sufficient one day and that’s fine. The point is that we aren’t.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866312&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866130&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;re retarded if you actually believe this. Even IF we could be self sufficient, and make everything we need ourselves (we can&amp;#x27;t) the price of everything would fucking skyrocket to the point that most people wouldn&amp;#x27;t be able to afford common items that we have now like tvs and phones.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866376&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857508&lt;br&gt;THE DOW IS AT 6 MILLION!!!!!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866632&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866312&lt;br&gt;Key difference was that things lasted and were repairable, only people what would suffer would be consoomer types.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;TVs&lt;br&gt;No one would complain if smart TVs stopped existing, and anything above 4k is a meme&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Smartphones&lt;br&gt;Make them with weaker specs and optimize.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866648&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;anyone who isn&amp;#x27;t low iq or the most subhuman subspecies on the planet (miggers) already knew this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>/smg/ - Stock Market Gambling — 380 replies — 88.4/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861684</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861684?lm=1771341198</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:13:18 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;/smg/ - Stock Market Gambling&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861684'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 380 • Updated: 2026-02-17 15:13 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Casino Economy Edition&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Some helpful links to numb the pain&lt;br&gt;https://findahelpline.com/&lt;br&gt;https://www.nvidia.com/refunds/&lt;br&gt;https://www.whitehouse.gov/refunds&lt;br&gt;https://jlingz.com/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Educational sites:&lt;br&gt;https://www.investopedia.com&lt;br&gt;https://www.khanacademy.org/economics-finance-domain&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Financial TV Streams:&lt;br&gt;https://www.newslive.com/american/cnbc.html&lt;br&gt;https://www.livestreamy.net/bloomberg/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Charts:&lt;br&gt;https://www.tradingview.com&lt;br&gt;https://www.finscreener.com&lt;br&gt;https://www.portfoliovisualizer.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Screeners: so you feel like in the movies&lt;br&gt;https://finviz.com/&lt;br&gt;https://etfdb.com/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Gambling:&lt;br&gt;https://www.optionsplaybook.com/options-introduction/&lt;br&gt;https://www.optionsprofitcalculator.com&lt;br&gt;https://optionstrat.com/&lt;br&gt;https://www.optionistics.com/quotes/option-prices&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Pre-Market and Live data:&lt;br&gt;https://www.investing.com/indices/indices-futures&lt;br&gt;https://finance.yahoo.com/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Calendars&lt;br&gt;https://www.marketwatch.com/economy-politics/calendar&lt;br&gt;https://www.earningswhispers.com/calendar&lt;br&gt;https://www.cmegroup.com/trading/interest-rates/countdown-to-fomc.html&lt;br&gt;https://www.mortgagenewsdaily.com/data/building-permits&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Boomer Investing 101: so zoomers with meme stocks can outperform you&lt;br&gt;https://www.bogleheads.org/wiki/Getting_started&lt;br&gt;https://www.sec.gov/search-filings&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Misc smg:&lt;br&gt;https://www.financialjuice.com/home&lt;br&gt;https://finance.yahoo.com/trending-tickers&lt;br&gt;https://market24hclock.com/&lt;br&gt;https://www.dividendchannel.com/drip-returns-calculator&lt;br&gt;https://brokerchooser.com/&lt;br&gt;https://www.chathamfinancial.com/technology/us-market-rates&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Previously on /smg/: &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858740&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861716&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m an American, I have extreme anxiety that i can&amp;#x27;t sell or buy right now&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;so me, and my fellow americans formally decided were panic selling everything Tuesday&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;sorry euros&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861738&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861716&lt;br&gt;i just watch the spot silver chart and get either mad or relieved when it doesnt move very far from 75&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864779&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This europoor just bought 70k USD worth of a global index fund and an ex-USA fund. Feel sick desu but I can’t sit on this cash forever&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864791&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864756&lt;br&gt;I dunno... what portion of nearly 50% of John Q Investor&amp;#x27;s assets are going to go into gold after he capitulates between now and August?&lt;br&gt;What is it they were saying 6 months ago? 60/20/20?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864794&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864791&lt;br&gt;forgot pic&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864805&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864588&lt;br&gt;enjoy your anal lysis&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864818&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;it&amp;#x27;s over.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864862&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;anyone know how to get fidelity to display my port value in premarket it doesn&amp;#x27;t update until market open and i need to aaaaaaaaaaahhhhhh more accurately right now&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864869&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864862&lt;br&gt;Have you tried to do math, you nigger gorilla?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864875&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864869&lt;br&gt;shiet wypipo be making computers hard to learn and shit to keep the black man down&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864876&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861707&lt;br&gt;ETOR&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864877&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864750&lt;br&gt;LEMEOW&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864887&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862034&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862207&lt;br&gt;DOSH&lt;br&gt;LOADS O MONE&lt;br&gt;SMG BTFO AGAIN&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864895&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864887&lt;br&gt;ok but how does that affect you personally?&lt;br&gt;post your profits big boy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864940&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864877&lt;br&gt;That&amp;#x27;s your 47% tariff doing it&amp;#x27;s job&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864953&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864895&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;GME baggie coping&lt;br&gt;go back to your containment thread&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864962&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ready for the bloodbath?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864974&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;soxl down 10%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864975&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;everyone&amp;#x27;s expecting it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864982&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The nurse at the psychs office called after out appointment today saying she was worried about me and asked if I wanted to get institutionalized.&lt;br&gt;While on one hand it feels good that someone cares about me, fuck no give me pills to survive [society] or stfu.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;what are the market implicaitons of this?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864986&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864777&lt;br&gt;I hope you guys bought hopium when I said. up another 20%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865002&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864982&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;asked if I wanted to get institutionalized&lt;br&gt;newby here. is this common in finance?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865011&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864411&lt;br&gt;hi bob&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865015&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865002&lt;br&gt;if you aren&amp;#x27;t getting wellness checks from the county health system or your female broker you probably aren&amp;#x27;t taking enough risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865028&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALL HANDS ON DECK&lt;br&gt;GET READY TO DEPLOY THOSE V&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865049&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865002&lt;br&gt;Yes. Saying &amp;quot;getting balls deep in leverage to see green or red numbers is the only thing that makes me feel anything&amp;quot; was the wrong answer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865127&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Well my mining portfolio has just been raped&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865178&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;jesus christ&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865184&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;bought google at 300 &lt;br&gt;how bad of an idea was that?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865241&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864986&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864777&lt;br&gt;Hopium currently up 324%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865274&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is today the day to slurp google&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865308&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865274&lt;br&gt;For me it&amp;#x27;s XOM&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>GERMANY TO END BURGERGELD PROGRAMS — 76 replies — 69.4/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858970</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858970?lm=1771352737</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 18:25:37 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;GERMANY TO END BURGERGELD PROGRAMS&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858970'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 76 • Updated: 2026-02-17 18:25 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;WILL BE REPLACED WITH A STRICTER PROGRAM IF YOU REFUSE WORK. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEXT STOP, PRIVATIZED HEALTHCARE.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858974&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Uh oh, Europeans actually have to work for a living now? Aw shucks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858980&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858974&lt;br&gt;They will soon legalize 12 hour work days much like Argentina has done. Even contributing 5% of their GDP to NATO has ultimately bankrupted them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859007&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858970&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wait you could get NEETbux in Germany this whole time by simply “refusing to work”? WTF&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860591&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860550&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;it&amp;#x27;s either the whip or picking cotton&lt;br&gt;That false dichotomy is sure proof of wageslave brainrot. I don&amp;#x27;t blame you, though. The whole system is rigged against you from birth and every aspect of your human nature is weaponized against you by the very thing you&amp;#x27;re meant to worship as a social animal, i.e. society.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860601&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858970&lt;br&gt;They just gave away all our money to Ausländers and now that the social systems are running dry they are simply getting rid of them kek.&lt;br&gt;Nothing they do will fix this. Humanity is doomed.&lt;br&gt;Accelerationism is the only way.&lt;br&gt;Let the third world starve and divert fund into AI datacenters.&lt;br&gt;The wolf will chew its own leg off to survive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860612&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860601&lt;br&gt;third world is the biggest net exporter of food to the point frenchoids were crying it would kill their overpriced artistical wine or something, they aint starving bro&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860626&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860591&lt;br&gt;Sorry chief, I find the idea of opening a business to be enticing but I don’t see any sort of moat I could pursue with it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860651&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858970&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858974&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860660&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860612&lt;br&gt;Africa imports a lot of food&lt;br&gt;And France was rightfully complaining that imposing huge restrictions on European agriculture while signing free trade agreements with countries having little restrictions is retarded&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860678&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859446&lt;br&gt;a 10% reduction? kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860682&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860422&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;10 year gap&lt;br&gt;I tell them it is due to the government forcing employers to lower standards to hire the affirmative action subhumans. They never call me back, because they are off giving useless lazy meritless and sometime convict affirmative action subhumans jobs. &lt;br&gt;Enjoy paying to taxes to niggers, spics, and cunts that hate you, just in the vain hopes they one day stop calling you a racist and sexist. Get back to work wagie... the whole economy rests on you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860686&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860191&lt;br&gt;Gas?!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860707&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860422&lt;br&gt;kek, they won&amp;#x27;t work at all, german economy will implode and as merz said they already can&amp;#x27;t afford the welfare + pensions, it will just shrink till it gets too low to live then they will just kys as by now they are legit unable to live at all&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860723&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859099&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;this nigga thinks German economy circa 1988 is anything like today&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lol&lt;br&gt;Lmao even&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860724&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860401&lt;br&gt;a drooly retard eh? yeah that sounds just perfect for our new expanded military, the bundeswehr needs you to pick this uniform, this little sign and just stand there to block the evil russian drones with your face for us&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860758&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;tfw the only time in my life where I might receive neetbux for a few months is the exact time this happens&lt;br&gt;fucking lol my entire life is me getting fucked by the universe. Nothing good ever happens to me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860764&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860626&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;moat&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;he fell for Buffett boomer brain rot &lt;br&gt;The only moats Buffett had were his generous throat and his congressman daddy. And let&amp;#x27;s not forget about being lucky enough to be born in close proximity to swollen jewish nuts in Israel&amp;#x27;s 2nd state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860766&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860758&lt;br&gt;join a gang, sell weed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861462&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858970&lt;br&gt;NooOoOO&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861576&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858970&lt;br&gt;thats gut. not because of the money, it wont help in any significant way but because its a statement. fuck bürgis, fuck ausländer&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861599&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858970&lt;br&gt;They have been rebranding the same system for almost 25 years now. The previous government eased up on some of the welfare restrictions because they were largely pointless. The new(old) sanctions don&amp;#x27;t really change anything because even with them you can be permanently on welfare in Germany as long as you show up to your jobcenter appointments. Nobody in Germany is going to hire someone who hasn&amp;#x27;t worked for years and is clearly just applying because the jobcenter is pressuring them. This is just a huge waste of everyone&amp;#x27;s time and part of Germany&amp;#x27;s soviet-tier obscuring of unemployment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861817&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860422&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;It&amp;#x27;ll be hard to explain the 10+ year gap&lt;br&gt;16 years gapmaxxer here, would you hire me?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862208&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Every nation has 10% unemployable retards. What to do with them?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;send them into the meatgrinder&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;employ them for the least possible payment&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;give them fake jobs&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;giver them life long gibs payed by everyone else&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A nation can do any of these without problems. BUT: If you open your borders and let the 10% retards of the entire third world in, you can not give them gibs anymore or you risk financial collapse. Especially if you destroy your own industry and energy security. The meatgrinder is then the only viable solution. Prepare for a war.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862662&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860724&lt;br&gt;getting out from Bundeswehr cuckery is even easier than getting welfare.&lt;br&gt;just fake mental illness and you cant work there. ez.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862678&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862662&lt;br&gt;that&amp;#x27;s for now buddy, things will change pretty fast when we attack those pesky russians to save EVROPA, our poor refugees can&amp;#x27;t go, so its time for private retard from munich to catch a drone, you are legit stupid and not only faking if you believe all that goodwill shit won&amp;#x27;t dissapear from the constitution as soon as they need meat, you will be the retard brick to the new EU federation, be glad&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862777&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862678&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;tfw only germans have to serve in the Volksfront&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;12% of our pop doesn&amp;#x27;t even have a german pass&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;tfw they are getting welfare and Neetmax while i&amp;#x27;m send off to the grinder after taxing the shit out of my market gains&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862781&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;why would you give people free money for burgers? lazy europoops.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862784&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859975&lt;br&gt;reminder the leaders are all boomers but when you point this out some tranny will start screaming to stop blaming the boomers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;All it takes is for non-elderly people to rise up and say &amp;quot;get the fuck out of my way grandpa or I will cave your head in&amp;quot; and there&amp;#x27;s nothing they can do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862797&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860147&lt;br&gt;it&amp;#x27;s despicable. these assholes come here, shit up our culture and behave like the are welcome here. cultures should be kept separate. you have to go back to /pol/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863548&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862678&lt;br&gt;nothing will happen.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;muh WW3&lt;br&gt;is a nothingburger like covid.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863561&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860422&lt;br&gt;your cat&amp;#x27;s litterbox needs changing, roastie&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863615&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859111&lt;br&gt;but not civil rights (since they invaded)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866483&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859010&lt;br&gt;/thread&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;otherwise politicians would actually have to do something. news cycle is 50% immigration and 50% buergergeld which is not a gigantic slice of the money pie, then they bicker 3 years and rename the thing and change one integer, just like launching a shitcoin and changing the port. then they&amp;#x27;ve done enough work for one legislative period and resume partying on epstein island&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>PLEASE MAKE IT FUCKING STOP — 13 replies — 52.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61865162</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61865162?lm=1771356386</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 19:26:26 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;PLEASE MAKE IT FUCKING STOP&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61865162'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 13 • Updated: 2026-02-17 19:26 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;PLEASE MAKE IT FUCKING STOP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865166&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ACCEPT THE DEAL YOU BALD HEADED PRICK&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865174&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;sell now nigga its just going lower&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865177&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You should have apologized to dan pena now you lose everything&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865188&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865162&lt;br&gt;you&amp;#x27;re profiting in BTC anon, just buy more!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865247&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865162&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;buy the dip&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;bro there is literally no more flesh on my skeleton&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865750&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865162&lt;br&gt;oh wow, it&amp;#x27;s you! how does it feel to be one of the greater fools?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865798&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865162&lt;br&gt;NO CRYING IN THE CASINO&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866254&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865162&lt;br&gt;mekmekemekekk u should buy rope cuz is gong get way worse&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866264&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866254&lt;br&gt;I DON&amp;#x27;T MIND THE PAIN&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866340&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;test&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866508&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;why did the poorfag jeet janny put a ban request on me for posting my portfolio?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866529&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Send it to zero and let’s get this over with. I said I was either going to make it or lose everything and I was serious&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866771&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866529&lt;br&gt;Just trade the pumps and dumps. You&amp;#x27;re not supposed to hold forever.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>