<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>/biz/ Active (filtered, with replies)</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/</link><description>Filtered out: general, gme, bbbyq. OP + first 3 replies + last 30 replies.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 18:29:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>IMF calls on China to cut industrial subsidies in half — 54 replies — 216.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61872964</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61872964?lm=1771525438</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 18:23:58 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;IMF calls on China to cut industrial subsidies in half&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61872964'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 54 • Updated: 2026-02-19 18:23 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872971&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872964&lt;br&gt;This is a strategic move by the Chinese to kill off the competition in other countries so the Chinese companies can dominate the sectors and then raise the prices&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872974&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;i&amp;#x27;m sure china will get right on that&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872978&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;jews mad&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872971&lt;br&gt;they can do it forever without raising the prices&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874092&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872971&lt;br&gt;Damn, that&amp;#x27;s sneaky. I wonder where they learned to do something like that?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874096&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872964&lt;br&gt;Is the IMF forgetting the Communist party in China owns everything? The CCP will allow someone to run their companies but subsidizing their companies is just robbing Peter to pay Paul. Telling them to stop subsidizing is like telling a CEO to stop paying his own employees.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874134&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874063&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Once they raise prices then other nations will become competitive though&lt;br&gt;Not if you kill off the industry in that country and they have to rebuild.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874164&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872971&lt;br&gt;China already dominates many sectors (e.g. LFP batteries, PVs) and yet prices just keep dropping&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874165&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874134&lt;br&gt;The whole point of the finance industry is to enable rapid rotations into money-making fields. Cars for example have been oversaturated for decades, can you rationalize why US automakers should be shitting out millions of taxpayer-subsidized cars? It would be more productive for that effort to be put towards profitable activities&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874338&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;the hell...? that isnt fair, only america is allowed doing that like they did with their dairy cartel (but failed as no one wants your estrogen &amp;quot;milk&amp;quot;)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874440&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;anti-industry westoid politicians think china is &amp;quot;subsidizing&amp;quot; rather than simply doing things right&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;But i&amp;#x27;m sure turning all major cities into holding zones for hostile foreigners has no negative effects...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874514&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873813&lt;br&gt;Not sure how they want this to work when they simultaneously devalue their currency artificially to get an export advantage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874542&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874514&lt;br&gt;The US is also constantly trying to devalue it&amp;#x27;s currency, the problem is that because USD is the reference point almost all other countries just match the level of devaluation, leaving the US right back where it started. China has the freedom to devalue currency relative to other countries only because it&amp;#x27;s currency doesn&amp;#x27;t have the same level of demand as the USD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874587&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874542&lt;br&gt;Exactly, we are in agreement. I don’t understand why China would want to give up their ability to easily manipulate their currency when they gain so much from that system currently, unless they want to transition out of being an export king and into being a financial king. That’s a serious shift though.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874601&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872964&lt;br&gt;Buuuuut, are you saying they should give free money to their Wall Street instead? Sorry but they don&amp;#x27;t have that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874605&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873185&lt;br&gt;They have enormous trade surpluses&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874655&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874587&lt;br&gt;Being a reserve currency gives you substantially more control than being a manufacturing giant, the US can literally print the oil price into the ground, as has been it&amp;#x27;s prerogative since the Ukraine war first started up in 2014 (speculatively to weaken the russian economy?) Anyways, if China had reserve currency then all other countries would need to stay at or exceed China&amp;#x27;s level of inflation in order to stay price-competitive and utilize the currency needed for global trade. This is assuming of course that the concept of a &amp;#x27;world reserve currency&amp;#x27; continues to exist, but desu I see less and less reason for such a thing to exist as markets continue to accelerate their interactions and improve their pricing accuracy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874731&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872971&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;we simply won&amp;#x27;t import your products to our country&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874748&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874164&lt;br&gt;The reason for this is that they aren&amp;#x27;t as good at doing it so they are printing money wildly to brute force it all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874758&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874655&lt;br&gt;Oh I agree that being the reserve currency is the most enviable global position a country can have, and I understand why China would want it. I just wonder how, logistically, this shift would happen—how a country would make a smooth transition from manufacturing export king to a financial role that in many ways conflicts with exporting efficiently. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I am asking this out of ignorance: how would exchange rates function without a reserve currency to which they are pegged? Would a given currency just have its own exchange rate with every other currency? Seems maddening.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874861&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874758&lt;br&gt;The exchange rates can still use USD as a reference point without USD being a reserve currency. Reserve currency means that if Canada ships natural gas to Vietnam, then Vietnam pays the Canadian company in USD instead of CAD or the vietnamese currency. Exchange rates would be calculated similarly to the way altcoins are measured against BTC a lot of the time, but to understand the real world value you need to reference BTC/USD. The reference point doesn&amp;#x27;t give the USD power, instead it&amp;#x27;s international trade conventions which compel most countries to buy and hold large stockpiles. That being said, if USD loses reserve status volatility would be very high compared to current day, so it may not even be a good idea to use it as a benchmark post-reserve status&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874896&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874861&lt;br&gt;Interesting, thanks for explaining. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;However, wouldn’t being the currency to which other currencies are measured still encourage it to function as a reserve currency? For example, if the yuan is still measured against the dollar, wouldn’t it still set aside dollars to manipulate its strength? It seems to me that so long as a currency is the one to which all the others are measured, it will begin to function as a reserve currency, though perhaps to a lesser degree. Some power seems to be gained from being the reference point. Again, I could be wrong about this, I’m a little out of my element.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874899&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874514&lt;br&gt;China hasn&amp;#x27;t relied on currency devaluation since the 1990s&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874905&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872964&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t get why countries can&amp;#x27;t just take what policies they want.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;China wants to subsidies industries? Fine.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA wants to tariff those Chinese industries? Fine.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Both countries should just be able to do what they see fit without everyone freaking out about it. Will some people get negatively impacted? Probably, but that is the risk that comes from doing business.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874924&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874896&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s literally just convention, you think business boomers want to spend mental energy on trading in more than two currencies? They don&amp;#x27;t give a fuck as long as the currency&amp;#x27;s worth approximately the same amount in between signing the contract and payment being issued&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874936&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874905&lt;br&gt;I do broadly agree, however if it looks like a country is going to debt-nuke the whole world you have to take some action at some point. The US is just as likely to shit the world economy as china is&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874965&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874899&lt;br&gt;Their currency is currently undervalued by roughly 16% and they actively manage its strength. How do you think they have such a ridiculous surplus? .&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874974&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874965&lt;br&gt;No they keep it tied to the dollar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875001&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874974&lt;br&gt;They have one of the most opaque central banks in the world. Nobody outside of China has any idea how they determine their exchange rate. It’s not hard to see the benefits they gain from keeping it low.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875052&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875001&lt;br&gt;Trump admin:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;NO! NO! NO! Only WE&amp;#x27;RE allowed to devalue our currency because WE need WAGESLAVES more than YOU! Y..you can&amp;#x27;t just print to build infrastructure!!! That&amp;#x27;s communist!!!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875074&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875052&lt;br&gt;I think the euros are more upset with china’s devaluation than America is. The guy in that article complaining is German. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;They’re instantiating a levy on small goods in July to combat the yuan that refuses to budge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875077&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875001&lt;br&gt;How it&amp;#x27;s done? They just keep it tied to the dollar. What are you talking about?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875121&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875077&lt;br&gt;It isn’t strictly tied to the dollar. It WAS before 2005, but now it’s a managed float system that is managed by the central bank. The dollar plays a big role, but it isn’t as if the yuan keeps strict pace with the dollar. They can (and do) manage its exchange rate. Exactly how they determine what the exchange rate should be is the opaque part. One way they manage the yuan’s value is by buying/selling dollars with their currency, and this is one reason why the keep so many dollars in reserve. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is also why, earlier in the thread, I argued that the dollar’s role as a reference point for a currency can still cause it to be accumulated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875124&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872964&lt;br&gt;Sour fucking grapes. The Jews running the west are such idiots&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>ETERNAL REMINDER 64K IS THE BOTTOM FOR BITCOIN — 21 replies — 84.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61871827</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61871827?lm=1771525583</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 18:26:23 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;ETERNAL REMINDER 64K IS THE BOTTOM FOR BITCOIN&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61871827'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 21 • Updated: 2026-02-19 18:26 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;It can&amp;#x27;t go any lower. Whoever thinks otherwise is missing the dip, then will cry later about it (they always do).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you bought it, hold. If you haven&amp;#x27;t, here is your second chance.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;but bitcoin lost two billion percent in value last year&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Zoom out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871839&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871827&lt;br&gt;Also, fuck:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;rock collectors (especially)&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;stock boomers&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;crypto memelords who make shitcoins to rug idiots and make the entire market look fake&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871846&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871827&lt;br&gt;proof??&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871852&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871846&lt;br&gt;Drew some lines in a graph&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871862&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871852&lt;br&gt;omg&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871900&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871827&lt;br&gt;$0 is the bottom for pedocoin and it&amp;#x27;s going there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871963&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871839&lt;br&gt;All of those people have made more money than you over the last two years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871965&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871839&lt;br&gt;Based&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871971&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871827&lt;br&gt;$64k is more than double the price of the actual bottom, but have fun bagholding I guess...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872021&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871971&lt;br&gt;With this negativity, you are never gonna make it. Bitcoin has intrinsic value.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872042&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871900&lt;br&gt;Checked and /thread&lt;br&gt;No one wants to be associated with Epstein tech.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872183&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;My Bitcoin strategy has served me very well&lt;br&gt;- snes was my first console and it was 16-bit, so I bought around 16k&lt;br&gt;- my next console was n64, so I bought more at 64k&lt;br&gt;- gamecube was 128-bit, and it was the last console I ever bought, literal end of the line, so I sold around 128k&lt;br&gt;I have recently got into emulation on a raspberry pie, started off with some n64 games I missed out on, but eventually plan to try out the NES, which was 8 bit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872327&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Somehow betting on Bitcoin is same as betting on SaaS, so if you think AI fear is a fad and revenue reports for SaaS are a good thing ackshually, then get all in now. The moment they&amp;#x27;ll repump same fate awaits BTC and Crypto overall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872332&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871827&lt;br&gt;you sound worried&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872337&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871827&lt;br&gt;Much lower ;-)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872341&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871827&lt;br&gt;Why would I buy bitcoin when I could just buy more of an alt coin that follows bitcoin anyways? It doesn&amp;#x27;t make sense to me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872371&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872042&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872337&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;le plebbit epstein midwit fud&lt;br&gt;blockstream != bitcoin&lt;br&gt;2014 != 2011&lt;br&gt;cope and seethe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874868&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872021&lt;br&gt;If it&amp;#x27;s so intrinsic, why does it have to be constantly explained to normies still?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875049&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wow, another seething cryptard who doesn&amp;#x27;t like PMs? How original.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875079&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871827&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;ETERNAL REMINDER 64K IS THE BOTTOM FOR BITCOIN&lt;br&gt;let me translate this for you...&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;PUMP IT BACK UP SO I CAN EXIT HIGHER!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;you need above 72k to make one bitcoin.&lt;br&gt;it takes up to 12 billion yearly for bitcoin to exist.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;it&amp;#x27;s over&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875108&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871827&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871900&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871971&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872327&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61875079&lt;br&gt;Bitcoin will be an 8 figure asset.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;time traveler&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875133&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;itt: Nobody talking about the upcoming war with Iran that will inevitably nuke all markets lmfao&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The brack swans of brack swans&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Bro just give me 50 stocks to shotgun I will literally build a balanced portfolio of all your posts ITT. — 19 replies — 76.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61874540</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61874540?lm=1771524871</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 18:14:31 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Bro just give me 50 stocks to shotgun I will literally build a balanced portfolio of all your posts ITT.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61874540'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 19 • Updated: 2026-02-19 18:14 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bro just give me 50 stocks to shotgun I will literally build a balanced portfolio of all your posts ITT. Dont repost tickers. Trips I&amp;#x27;ll buy 5x the amount. This is a financial experiment, not a shill thread. /biz/ should outperform the market. No cryptos. Go&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874568&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I dont own many individual stocks here are the ones i have:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;GLEN SHELL MDT DHR ISRG RHM BRK.B RR. FCX IYAA NOV GOOG YAR IFX ROK LGEN boeing VOW SNPS TSLA AMBA SNPS SYM RKLB AVAV OUST CRCL&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874578&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874540&lt;br&gt;uhm, Accenture&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874612&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874578&lt;br&gt;looks good!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874667&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874612&lt;br&gt;great choice&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874684&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874667&lt;br&gt;you might have called the generational pico bottom. time will tell&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874694&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TMF pussy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874706&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874540&lt;br&gt;FLOT&lt;br&gt;SHY&lt;br&gt;VGSH&lt;br&gt;XAR&lt;br&gt;EUAD&lt;br&gt;XLE&lt;br&gt;PBT&lt;br&gt;IGV&lt;br&gt;INTC&lt;br&gt;TTWO&lt;br&gt;COST&lt;br&gt;WMT&lt;br&gt;EWY&lt;br&gt;IBIT&lt;br&gt;GLDM&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874721&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BA 3 month chart&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874746&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874706&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;FLOT&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;SHY&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;VGSH&lt;br&gt; kek&lt;br&gt;I will get WMT and COST&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874749&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874721&lt;br&gt;yeah I have boing I&amp;#x27;m liking that shit. anything else?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874767&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874694&lt;br&gt;damn it looks worse than an altcoin. I will exempt myself because it is bonds&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874776&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874746&lt;br&gt;the idea here is that if/when the recession happens, rates get cut to 0 and the price of short term bonds especially goes up. at which point you sell for dry powder. in the meantime you earn a %.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874840&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874776&lt;br&gt;I see! I appreciate that. it makes a lot of sense. I will run some calculations on this insight and give it thought because it deserves a larger allocation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874846&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;thats valuable this thread is full of value already&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874852&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HP, TTD, SMR, UPST, CLSK, MARA, UBI, DJT, XYZ&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874882&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;itt WUT KAR IS GUD newfag gets baited into losing to SPY&lt;br&gt;still some good laughs to be had here&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875028&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874767&lt;br&gt;See I knew you were a pussy and wouldn&amp;#x27;t do it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875043&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874540&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;/biz/ should outperform the market.&lt;br&gt;yeah? so how do we get our share then?&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m not packing your bags for you nigger.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875088&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874540&lt;br&gt;Phos/frspf&lt;br&gt;Xom&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Microtragedy — 17 replies — 68.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61873618</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61873618?lm=1771525240</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 18:20:40 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Microtragedy&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61873618'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 17 • Updated: 2026-02-19 18:20 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Imagine DCA&amp;#x27;ing for six years for this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873641&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873618&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873651&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873618&lt;br&gt;Bitcoin is a Dyson mound of cryonetic termites and lived for millions of years on a kinetic crash course with fuck YOU.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873656&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873618&lt;br&gt;Because he can only buy when people give him money. And people only want to buy in bull markets. In a few years he will be seen as a genius though.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873658&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873656&lt;br&gt;his stock is collapsing like a shitcoin and diminishing returns will just make the next bullrun even more underwhelming&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873661&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873658&lt;br&gt;good! classic hns!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873664&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873618&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873665&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873658&lt;br&gt;Looks like it&amp;#x27;s still up a lot from 2022 and 2023&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873668&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873658&lt;br&gt;Can survive 4 years at $8,000 price levels &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Will refinance debt if he needs to&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Can&amp;#x27;t stop the cyber hornets&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873670&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873668&lt;br&gt;that&amp;#x27;s bullshit, his voice was cracking when he said that because he knows its not true.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873685&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873668&lt;br&gt;based saylor&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873789&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873668&lt;br&gt;How could BTC at $8000 not trigger a death spiral?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873792&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873618&lt;br&gt;Kek - just DCA bro! In 20 years I&amp;#x27;ll have the last laugh, you&amp;#x27;ll see!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873793&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873668&lt;br&gt;Right - but to repay debtors he has to dilute his baggie shareholders to zero. You always leave that part out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873802&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s not his money tho, right? It&amp;#x27;s his investors&amp;#x27;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873812&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873618&lt;br&gt;Let me tell you how this shit works. Mstr is a front. It&amp;#x27;s a scheme that allows elite whales to cash out at the top. Fed money goes to Blackrock who buys mstr bonds. Mstr buys Bitcoin OTC from those in &amp;#x27;the club&amp;#x27;&lt;br&gt;There wouldn&amp;#x27;t be enough liquidity otherwise. &lt;br&gt;Noone actually buys mstr it&amp;#x27;s just an Epstein type operation to move money around and the goyim are too dumb to notice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873851&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873618&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saylor is well paid to launder funds through his “Bitcoin” management&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875118&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873812&lt;br&gt;If mstr defaulted on those bonds BlackRock is going to be the biggest loser then since &amp;quot;noone actually buys mstr&amp;quot;. But I guess it won&amp;#x27;t hurt BlackRock portofolio if it really dropped to that point.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maybe ~5-10% of mstr shareholders are genuine retail traders I assume.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>My girlfriend is saying to buy ETH because the AI economy will run on it. — 12 replies — 37.7/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61874602</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61874602?lm=1771524602</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 18:10:02 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;My girlfriend is saying to buy ETH because the AI economy will run on it.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61874602'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 12 • Updated: 2026-02-19 18:10 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;My girlfriend is saying to buy ETH because the AI economy will run on it. I nodded but I didn&amp;#x27;t get what she meant. Can you guys please explain?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874613&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874602&lt;br&gt;Eth is bad coin saar, tell your beautiful sweet babe that you should buy sexy people solana!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874621&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874602&lt;br&gt;it&amp;#x27;s because ETH has been under control of AI from the beginning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874624&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;gf doesn&amp;#x27;t believe in crypto &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;wants to put everything into precious metals&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874627&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874621&lt;br&gt;This nigger has a chink puss wetting aura&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874922&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874602&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your gf is retarded; buy Bitcoin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874945&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874602&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;she&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874976&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874602&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Girl &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Knows what eth is &lt;br&gt;That&amp;#x27;s a man&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875014&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874624&lt;br&gt;She&amp;#x27;s a keeper or a dude Anon. Either way reward them by fucking their ass.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875034&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874602&lt;br&gt;Her ex and/ or side nigga said that to her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875045&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874602&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Reddit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875054&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874624&lt;br&gt;based&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875069&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874602&lt;br&gt;the AI economy will not run on ETH because it&amp;#x27;s too expensive to run especially when compared to more efficient and less cost consuming technologies out there.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;what&amp;#x27;s the most sad about all this is you&amp;#x27;re more retarded than your girlfriend for not knowing this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>How do I invest in picrelated? They seem to be popping up everywhere rapidly across the US — 13 replies — 25.4/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61871078</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61871078?lm=1771523905</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 17:58:25 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;How do I invest in picrelated? They seem to be popping up everywhere rapidly across the US&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61871078'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 13 • Updated: 2026-02-19 17:58 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;How do I invest in picrelated? They seem to be popping up everywhere rapidly across the US&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871101&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IEDs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871120&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;High powered lasers or a Ruger 22 LR&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wait, what was the question again?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871125&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871078&lt;br&gt;seen one on the highway thought it was the police, glad its probably just some yokel&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871135&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871078&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;re late. Camera surveillance has been booming business for 40 years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871259&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871078&lt;br&gt;temu&lt;br&gt;aliexpress&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871263&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871120&lt;br&gt;Laser futures already up 200% since 2024, priced in&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873331&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Buy shares in silver miners&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873471&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873331&lt;br&gt;This, those solar panels and electronics need silver&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873479&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871120&lt;br&gt;A higher velocity and/or larger diameter projectile is also acceptable. For example, .45/70 is cheeky and fun.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873492&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871078&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You get the opportunity to invest in surveillance firms only after you suck 33rd degree Freemason penis or are born as a Son of Zohar&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873544&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871078&lt;br&gt;Fun fact: each panel contains roughly 600 XRP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874287&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871078&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;ve heard that grinder cutting disk futures are really hot right now. They seem to be flying off the shelves wherever these are for some reason.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61875019&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871078&lt;br&gt;Buy silver. Solar panels need silver&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>why would anyone live here — 58 replies — 99.9/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61872797</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61872797?lm=1771523657</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 17:54:17 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;why would anyone live here&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61872797'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 58 • Updated: 2026-02-19 17:54 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;i recently moved to NYC to work for a &amp;quot;lucrative salary&amp;quot; (not really, because this place drains you of all your income) and after working here for 4 months i dont know why anyone would willingly live here&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;the entire city smells like rotting shit, cigarette buds and dead animals, not a faint smell, an extremely strong odor that you&amp;#x27;ll eventually just become nose blind to&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;homeless people, fucking everywhere, when i left my apartment there were homeless people sleeping in the hallways of my complex, when you go on walk there are homeless people sleeping on the sidewalk with a PILLOW and BLANKET while regular people walk over them like this is just some normal fucking occurrence (and in this shithole it is) never ever have i seen some shit like this even in the worst of cities ive lived in.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;heroin needles, weed bags, cigarette buds &amp;amp; the occasional dildo just scattered across the city sidewalks, your constantly walking over human shit, broken bottles or dime bags&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;rats and rodents EVERYWHERE. il never forget the time i bought a pizza from one of the disgusting street vendors and when i sat down at a table one of the rats were circling my feet trying to climb my leg for a bite.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;the &amp;quot;public transport&amp;quot; system is a just permanent housing for the mentally ill, every time i had to ride the subway i was scared for my life because of all the fucking looneys that inhabit the train systems&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;this is just off the top of my head, but i think the biggest mindfuck of it all is that its EXPENSIVE to live here its gonna cost you not 50k, not 100k, not 200k, to live comfortably by yourself you need 250K yearly in manhattan. 250k, to live among violent homeless people, 250k to constantly have to walk in rotting shit and roadkill. 250k to have your ears blown out by car horns &amp;amp; niggerbabble, 250k to be forced to smell the most putried scents imaginable i dont know why anyone sane would live here, this place is some sort of social experiment, some sort of anonmoly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872828&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872797&lt;br&gt;Go back to your trailer park, pussy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872853&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872797&lt;br&gt;You know the phrase &amp;quot;If you can make it in New York you can make it anywhere&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;re not making it. You&amp;#x27;re a small fish in the biggest fucking pond.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you were making it you wouldn&amp;#x27;t deal with ANY of this shit&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Oh my heck the freakin homeless have PILLOWS and BLANKETS &lt;br&gt;Literally who gives a single actual fuck&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872859&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872828&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872853&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;getting AIDS from stepping on a needle is just part of the HUSTLE AND BUSTLE&lt;br&gt;citycels are pathetic&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873067&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872863&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;i was paying over 150k &lt;br&gt;You mean making? &lt;br&gt;Or did you mean you were paying $12,500 per month? &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you were only making 150k then I&amp;#x27;m completely unsurprised you felt like a bitter poorfag in NYC. I make that much in a medium/low cost city in the Midwest and feel like I could use a lot more.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you moved there for a career and only made that much then yeah I think you weren&amp;#x27;t anywhere close to making an optimal move.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;All I&amp;#x27;m saying is you&amp;#x27;re a.) soft as fuck and b.) not nearly as intelligent or valuable as you think you are&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873699&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872797&lt;br&gt;so? its jew york, its there to someone to nuke it.....&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873706&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872797&lt;br&gt;OP can&amp;#x27;t handle the hustle and bustle of NYC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873716&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872797&lt;br&gt;i heard there are more dating age women than men in nyc. so might be good if you&amp;#x27;re looking to SUCKNFUCK.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873754&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873067&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;All I&amp;#x27;m saying is you&amp;#x27;re a.) soft as fuck and b.) not nearly as intelligent or valuable as you think you are&lt;br&gt;Go live there pussy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873892&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873754&lt;br&gt;fun fact &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873067 doesnt realize the inverse of &amp;quot;if you can make it in nyc you can make it anywhere&amp;quot; is the actual truth. there are people that cannot make it out of nyc. there is a huge swaths of the country where the only employer is dollar general paying $1-2/hr above minimum wage. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;any retard can come to nyc and get a six figure job, and if they dont aspire to ever own property or live in a super trendy/high end part of the city they&amp;#x27;ll be fine. meanwhile if they stayed in florida or ohio or even suburban connecticut they probably would&amp;#x27;ve been stuck working retail or at best making $60,000 a year in a place where meals still cost $14-20 and gas is still $3 a gallon and his rent is still retarded high like $1800-2400/mo because nyc/la/boston set rental pricing for the rest of the country&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873895&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;ve been to NYC and none of that happened to me howeverbeit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873906&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872797&lt;br&gt;Heh sounds exactly like my experience as an euro whi visited the city two years ago. I got assaulted by some young negress 15 minutes after i had arrived in the city, two blocks from the times square. The whole place was worse than Brasil and indeed full of homeless and untreated schizophrenics. Felt like third world to an european like me. Really showed how much USA has decayed when it’s normal for them to live in dangerous third world cities like this. Paris was literal heaven compared to it. Everything was clean, almost zero homeless, immigrants were working the shit jobs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873913&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873895&lt;br&gt;the streets are pretty disgusting after a month of frozen snow finally melting im excited for the rain tomorrow &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873906&lt;br&gt;times square is a shithole thoughever&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;its like me saying all of france is marseilles&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873926&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873892&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;or at best making $60,000 a year in a place where meals still cost $14-20 and gas is still $3 a gallon and his rent is still retarded high like $1800-2400/mo because nyc/la/boston set rental pricing for the rest of the country&lt;br&gt;Fucking trvke. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I live in Ohio making ~62k a year gross and gas prices are $2.90-$4.00 depending on the octane level you need, a meal is $25, a drink at a bar is $15, and rent in the ghetto is $1000-1200 for a studio, or $1500+ if you don&amp;#x27;t want to get shot. On top of that my health insurance is $200 a month, my car insurance is $100 a month, and there are a million other expenses that don&amp;#x27;t get cheaper because I live here.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moving to a major west or east coast city would cost me MAYBE $1500 a month in additional expenses, but I would make that all back in increased salary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873983&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873906&lt;br&gt;Oh and people we’re unironically like 75% brown. Any european big city will have by default by population alone more attractive white women. USA has truly fallen.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873913&lt;br&gt;I thought my hotel was in some shithole area until i found it was literally at the ”good part of the city” at upper west side. Didn’t matter, the whole place is full of homeless with decayed infrastructure if we don’t count the skyscrapers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874025&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873983&lt;br&gt;anywhere near nycha public housing (x houses like fredrick douglass houses which you were probably close to) or methadone clinics (8th ave between 32nd to 44th street) will be shitty.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;every euro visits midtown when really you should be visiting the lower east side and upper brooklyn, midtown manhattan is all commercial office buildings. upper manhattan is rich jews in million dollar penthouses and museums/central park getting shittier the further you go up (the old joke was white people would all get off at 96th st)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;i will give you nyc women are fucking ugly, its something in the water. i think florida unironically has better looking women by a few points. montreal has the best looking women in north america. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;marseilles was bad enough that i cannot take euros seriously when they complain about america&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874253&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872797&lt;br&gt;The trick is to cost of life max&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You want to best ratio income:cost of life&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taking into account other variables such as opportunities (i guess NY have plenty), quality of life (kek), social life, proximity to family etc&lt;br&gt;And of course taxes&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The real cheat code being to remote from a shithole with a fat 6 fig, but I personally don&amp;#x27;t feel like fucking whores in Pattaya and have my passport in a safe. But there&amp;#x27;s layers to it&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anyway please stay in NY don&amp;#x27;t come to my cuntry making real estate too expensive&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874263&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872797&lt;br&gt;Never been but I’ve been to Shitcago many times and it always smells like raw sewage it makes me sick. And the fucking people are everywhere. I start to feel mentally ill after a few hours there. I couldn’t imagine living there. Everyone who lives in a big city is absolutely 100% mentally ill.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874586&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872797&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;chud can&amp;#x27;t handle the best city in the world &lt;br&gt;Go back to whatever white trash trailer park you came from lil bro&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874607&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874586&lt;br&gt;Eh european cities beat it in party scene, chicks, safety and lack of homeless. It was maybe the best city in the world in 80s but unless you really like skyscrapers, it’s just a normal third world city.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874647&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872797&lt;br&gt;I make 36$/hr as a tradie and live in Queens. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Building my own business, because I live paycheck to paycheck. And I do not live lavishly at all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874659&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872797&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;your constantly walking over human shit, broken bottles or dime bags&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;So do the homeless just squat down and shit on the sidewalk in broad daylight? I&amp;#x27;m guessing some of it is dog shit as well.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;ve lived in Philly and didn&amp;#x27;t really see actual human feces that commonly, in my experience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874674&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872934&lt;br&gt;This is absolutely true. Since I moved here a year ago I’ve had sex with maybe 50-60 women.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874766&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873983&lt;br&gt;The subhuman brownoids everywhere is disgusting though.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hate grabbing the train and being the only White face.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874772&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872797&lt;br&gt;i like nyc&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;pink id&lt;br&gt;ngmi&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874780&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872797&lt;br&gt;then move, dumbass&lt;br&gt;get a new job and head the fuck out&lt;br&gt;tell your next employer you&amp;#x27;d take a 30% pay cut (to move to an area with half the CoL)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874781&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I went as a german student once with my class&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;saw a black women smoke crack at her porch&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;friend fought with a mix tape scammer over one dollar at time square&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;my teacher asked a person, who just snorted a gram coke at the public transit, for directions&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874850&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872797&lt;br&gt;haha you think that&amp;#x27;s bad, just wait til you get a load of the property taxes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874874&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874850&lt;br&gt;this in baltimore it&amp;#x27;s $10k/year in property taxes to live in a dilapidated rowhome from 1910. cities are a meme since 1960 or so.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874884&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872797&lt;br&gt;i don&amp;#x27;t think i would live there even if you gave me a free house. even if it wasn&amp;#x27;t a shithole, just the taxes and bullshit would cost more than rent in most places.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874586&lt;br&gt;kys nigger homo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874916&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874874&lt;br&gt;Is this real?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874971&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872853&lt;br&gt;Yeah i was wondering about how the rich people live there. Do they just stay in their small private rich people cuck zones and take the cab everywhere? Why would anyone want to live like that? Why live in a city if you can only actually inhabit small parts of it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874993&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872905&lt;br&gt;Yeah seeing kids just walking around amids the violent homeless was crazy. People in europe never have to tolerate something like that with the city of marseilles being the only exception i guess.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874996&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874586&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Roach likes to live in the infestation&lt;br&gt;Kys faggitor&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>BTC dumping? Don’t care. It’s temporary. — 24 replies — 25.1/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61869212</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61869212?lm=1771522312</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 17:31:52 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;BTC dumping? Don’t care. It’s temporary.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61869212'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 24 • Updated: 2026-02-19 17:31 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;If it drops, I buy more. If it goes sideways, I accumulate. If it pumps, I chill. I’m earning yield and stacking long term. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Short term volatility doesn’t change the plan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869234&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869212&lt;br&gt;Crypto and BTC is dead retard &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Everyone knows about it by now&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869237&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869212&lt;br&gt;The niggercattle aren&amp;#x27;t going to pump your epsteincoin bags.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869244&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869212&lt;br&gt;Pixel tranny cope.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869247&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869234&lt;br&gt;you are a pedo nigger&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869319&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869212&lt;br&gt;Btc will pump ser&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869502&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869360&lt;br&gt;Wtf&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869514&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869212&lt;br&gt;Btc is never going to pump again. The elites have cashed out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869947&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869234&lt;br&gt;Everyone knows? Are you sure bro?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872291&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869237&lt;br&gt;Blaming the market because your coin isn’t moving is peak cope.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872296&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869360&lt;br&gt;pic needs an update, it&amp;#x27;s 2T MC for shitcoins now lol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872347&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why don’t we ever talk about ETH? It is unironically more valuable than any other crypto&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873066&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869244&lt;br&gt;Bro ran out of brain cells and typed cope.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873082&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869360&lt;br&gt;And yet you&amp;#x27;ll get instantly attacked here by Israeli bots for even mentioning PMs, despite them being an objectively better investment than bitshit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873286&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873082&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;PM collectors are obsessed with Jews&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873437&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869212&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;re a fucking loser, dude.&lt;br&gt;If it goes down, you&amp;#x27;re a loser. If it goes sideways, you&amp;#x27;re a loser. If it goes up (it won&amp;#x27;t), you&amp;#x27;re a loser.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873558&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869514&lt;br&gt;BTC has ‘died’ a hundred times.&lt;br&gt;I’m stacking and putting it to work with native staking on Babylon while you doompost. See you next cycle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873610&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873558&lt;br&gt;Is it even safe?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873612&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869319&lt;br&gt;When $100k???&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873657&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869234&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869237&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869244&lt;br&gt;Bots&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873663&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873558&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;muh babylon staking&lt;br&gt;lol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873735&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873558&lt;br&gt;Anon, let other people have your coins is pretty much the only way for your Bitcoin to actually go to 0. Careful with that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874611&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873610&lt;br&gt;Ofcourse. The TVL speaks for itself.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873663&lt;br&gt;Better than letting your BTC sit there doing absolutely nothing while you pretend that’s some high IQ strategy lol.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874904&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Do you only get 0,04% yield on bitcoin if you dont have any Baby token?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>When did you realize that you were NOT going to make it? — 122 replies — 25.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61862922</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61862922?lm=1771508179</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:36:19 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;When did you realize that you were NOT going to make it?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61862922'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 122 • Updated: 2026-02-19 13:36 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862935&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;is he ok&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862944&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862935&lt;br&gt;just some minor scratches (on his brain)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862956&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;the funniest part is that you think &amp;quot;maybe he survived the crash, just barely&amp;quot; but then it erupts in flames and he&amp;#x27;s cooked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869355&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863411&lt;br&gt;He was hothead enough to ride at those speeds, but not enough to do a last second evading maneuver. &lt;br&gt;In the end he acted like a normie, which is brake when things to wrong. Which works most of the time, but in a CAR.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869395&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863410&lt;br&gt;Stop posting those image all the time fagit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869422&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;drives in the emergency lane&lt;br&gt;bikenigger got what he deserved&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869527&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863253&lt;br&gt;Fucking hate people that turn like that. Like any sense of g-forces at all is completely unacceptable to feel. FUCKING GO!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869586&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;When did you realize that you were NOT going to make it?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Define &amp;quot;Make it&amp;quot;.&lt;br&gt;Good wife, one son, over a million in my Roth IRA... did I &amp;#x27;make it&amp;#x27;?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869920&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868013&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;uhh source? What&amp;#x27;s the heckin email timestamp?&lt;br&gt;Lel&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869926&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Friendly reminder motorbikes have like 100x the fatality rate of cars, given enough time you&amp;#x27;re basically guaranteed to have a serious accident with one&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869948&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most don’t&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869998&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863529&lt;br&gt;Because they have less defining human qualities. Have you ever met an Asian with empathy or altruism? I just don’t think their brains are capable of much so we see them as something less. There’s a reason why the Asians have no soul joke seems to stick. I don’t know maybe some Asian American can explain it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870027&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;The subconscious will to die, the death drive is always present to varying degrees. It battles with the will to live. There is nothing inherently wrong with death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870172&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869948&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;doom posting with lar dee dar prose.&lt;br&gt;Just doesn&amp;#x27;t bring me happiness m8.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870204&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863182 &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922 &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;This guy was going 2x the speed limit on the shoulder. 100% deserved.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869926&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Friendly reminder&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; motorbikes have 100x the fatality rate of cars, given enough time you&amp;#x27;re basically guaranteed to have a serious accident with one&lt;br&gt;This. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;He should have realized when he bought a bike. &lt;br&gt;Then decided to go 2x speed limit on a shoulder .&lt;br&gt;This is a very common scenario, someone is turning right into a parking lot, without seeing some retard doing 2x on a shoulder lane. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Actually know a person who survived this one. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;his bike had a bigger engine , he flew OVER a car&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870288&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868079&lt;br&gt;ID probably changed because mac addr recycle, but I appreciate the effort post anon&lt;br&gt;While the bad faith posters will inevitably harvest some portion of loosh from me, as I still retain my (admittedly damaged) spirit, my comments are not necessarily for direct reply: they are also for those passive scrollers and anons who have visited this site for years and never typed a single reply or started a single thread. The silent lurkers, for which any morsel of knowledge may enlighten or ease their spiritual burden by a miniscule amount, is to whom I make these comments hidden far away from the mass of crowds who trample all over fragile truth for vulgar and banal platitudes. Godspeed, anon. We will meet again for certain, but will never know it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871361&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;He was really dry&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871366&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863411&lt;br&gt;He went around &amp;quot;up&amp;quot; and smashed into the ground&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871371&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862956&lt;br&gt;LITERALLY ME&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871626&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;After seeing the dutch new tax law&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871728&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862956&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871737&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;upon being born a goy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871780&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;agonizingly slow turn&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;no turn signal&lt;br&gt;You guys ever notice it&amp;#x27;s always big expensive SUVs that do this shit? How do the most expensive vehicles have the worst drivers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871805&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What is it about motorcycles that inspire so much seethe? Is it because 4chuds are high inhib pussy incels?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871884&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The thing is in 2014, 2017, 2021 you could take 10,000 bucks and buy basically anything and a 10x was guaranteed.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I remember taking 2021 for granted lol.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 2024 bull run saw an initial pump from alts from january to april and then htey just bled from april to september, then bled again from december to may, and from may 2025 to present the bulk of alts bled out.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I remember seeing microstrategy and I was like &amp;quot;gonna buy that when bitcoin goes back to 50k&amp;quot;. Then I saw MSTX. Hell yeah, double your money for each MSTR move, and MSTR was double bitcoin. A run to 100k from 50k would be an easy 8x. And it was. But I sold before the election and fumbled it. The fumbler. It&amp;#x27;s easy to create a perfect plan in your mind, and watch it play out exactly as you said it would, but it takes a lot of conviction to not fuck it up.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now most markets are way up. 2026, 2022, 2018, midterm years have slow market growth. The time to buy it was 2023, the time to make it was 2024, the time to swap into alts like KTA and HYPE and AVANTIS was 2025. I called everything correctly but fucked up the one thing that mattered- buying, and holding to a 10x.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871888&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871780&lt;br&gt;Boomers love driving big SUVs for some reason. Makes them &amp;quot;feel safe&amp;quot; or some shit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872189&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863529&lt;br&gt;Bug people, soulless&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872848&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863529&lt;br&gt;Because they are literally lower quality organisms. Same reason no one gives a fuck when you kill a fly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873614&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863924&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I would just like to know if all that crap about satan, moloch worship, demons, etc., it&amp;#x27;s just like a game because they simply like to eat and torture babies or do those entities really exist.&lt;br&gt;Nah but they believe in it. Very powerful people ironically fear death a lot so they somehow believe this can save them from dying.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873616&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864738&lt;br&gt;They fear China the most clearly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873938&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863529&lt;br&gt;What a dumb retard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873940&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868075&lt;br&gt;This was denied by China.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873942&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;He could have make it if he had better control of his brakes, I think he&amp;#x27;s one of these riders who only use the front brake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>NUCLEAR HAPPENING — 14 replies — 24.1/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61874535</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61874535?lm=1771523658</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 17:54:18 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;NUCLEAR HAPPENING&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61874535'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 14 • Updated: 2026-02-19 17:54 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;FED KASHKARI: CRYPTO IS UTTERLY USELESS&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874539&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No shit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874549&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874535&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;CRYPTO IS UTTERLY USELESS&lt;br&gt;We knew&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874557&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874535&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;kashkari&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Minneapolis Fed&lt;br&gt;Don’t care, didn’t ask&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874558&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874535&lt;br&gt;bring back powell!!!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874561&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;who is that&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874565&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874535&lt;br&gt;bullish&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874570&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874535&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Kashkari&lt;br&gt;crypto is useless saar bay silver sar, silver goood&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874571&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874535&lt;br&gt;Thx kaskari, just solded 100k cryptoes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874574&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;*ahem*cough*ahem*&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874773&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874574&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;saar krip toes useless pls put metal in vaults and use IOUs saaar&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874817&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874535&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;guy who famously loves the infinite money printer hates scarce assets&lt;br&gt;Waow&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874825&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874535&lt;br&gt;KASHKARI has never heard of Chainlink&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874841&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;stablecoins can&amp;#x27;t beat venmo&lt;br&gt;he&amp;#x27;s probably not aware that venmo uses stablecoins&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874997&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;that&amp;#x27;s true but listen, you just need someone to buy it off of you at a profit, so while you&amp;#x27;re a fool for buying useless shit in the first place, the other guy is a &amp;#x27;greater fool&amp;#x27;, if you will&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Me do asset management &amp; financial planning for a living AMAA — 51 replies — 16.4/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61872433</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61872433?lm=1771514525</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 15:22:05 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Me do asset management &amp;amp; financial planning for a living AMAA&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61872433'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 51 • Updated: 2026-02-19 15:22 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Me do asset management &amp;amp; financial planning for a living AMAA&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872440&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872433&lt;br&gt;Looks boring af. How haven&amp;#x27;t you kys&amp;#x27;d yourself yet?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872446&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;he doesnt trade his own money to become a player of the game like his clients&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872467&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For someone with 200k to invest, what would you do? I’m thinking of a split between SPYI, QQQI, O, and SCHD.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872716&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;interesting thread, ty anon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872888&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872526&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;US market has had a good run for about 15 years, but that doesn&amp;#x27;t mean it will continue to. Foreign stocks are beating the everloving fuck out of US stocks this year so for for example.&lt;br&gt;that&amp;#x27;s why he said global ETF&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;honestly abusing correlation seems only worth it if the assets have an equal return to stocks, all this junk has such low return even if its negatively correlated you&amp;#x27;re not going to get a free reduction in variance with it without killing your return. That&amp;#x27;s why i heard some paper showed its optimal to just go 100% stocks. Even if your a boomer, bonds aren&amp;#x27;t really worth it, you can just adjust your spending if theres a downturn and still come out ahead. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trying to finds stocks/etfs that are weakly correlated seems to be the play.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872998&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872888&lt;br&gt;There are a lot of assets that meet or beat equity markets with CAGR and are low correlation. Some are right in the data here &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872698&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gold for example has a higher average annual return, better risk adjusted return, and a 0.1 correlation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873012&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872467&lt;br&gt;All on btc shorts. Outperform those gay indexes for the next three years in one week&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873080&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872467&lt;br&gt;Why do you focus on yield so much instead of total returns?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s a lot of US large cap equity exposure with tax inefficiency if it&amp;#x27;s in a taxable account. You&amp;#x27;ll get big dividend though.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I like PTY, ASGI, etc for yield personally.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873145&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872998&lt;br&gt;no it fucking doesn&amp;#x27;t, in the last 110 years it has returned 5% while the stock market returned 10%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873184&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873145&lt;br&gt;ik this is probably bait but that&amp;#x27;s a very silly time period to look at because before we got off the gold standard it was fixed ounces/USD. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meaning 0% growth for half that period dragging the CAGR way down lol. Doesn&amp;#x27;t make sense to look at the return pre Nixon shock for that reason.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873190&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872433&lt;br&gt;if you like uncorrelated risk adjusted-returns you should look at alternative investments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873207&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873190&lt;br&gt;Returns are totally dependent on the managers imho, it&amp;#x27;s a cool class. I&amp;#x27;m not a huge fan of the illiquidity personally.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I do like some of them them, especially private farmland/timberland. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Not a huge fan of venture or growth PE, guess I&amp;#x27;m lame.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873214&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873207&lt;br&gt;have you looked into managed futures?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873220&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873080&lt;br&gt;I use my brokerage as my main savings account. Instead of getting $500/month in a high yield savings account I rather get $1400, 50-75% I could reinvest. But since you do this for a living I&amp;#x27;m going to listen and allocate more money for growth rather than yield going forward, and you&amp;#x27;re right about the taxes, I didn&amp;#x27;t think too much about that. Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873222&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873214&lt;br&gt;I cant believe I forgot about those!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I use the ETFs for simplicity. ISMF/CTA for crisis alpha. I almost went DBMF too, but I prefer the purer systematic trend heavy ones.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Do you have any strong opinions on them?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seems like extreme negative correlation, like -0.4 with 6-8% CAGR which is completely acceptable if you&amp;#x27;re rebalancing with a really aggressive equity portfolio. I considered pairing them with TQQQ or SOXL to be a total jackass at once point and pussed out,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873231&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873220&lt;br&gt;You accept more risk (volatility) for those higher returns, that&amp;#x27;s the tradeoff. If you are OK with higher risk then you could always choose one of those balanced allocation funds.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AOR for example just rebalances a 60% stock / 40% bond index portfolio.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AOA does the same thing but 80% stock (more risk)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;These really are the easy button for people that don&amp;#x27;t want to self-manage imo.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Probably a good idea to put the portion that&amp;#x27;s your emergency fund into something boring and very lowvol but decent yield. Check out JPST, that might be a good fit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873256&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873222&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873190&lt;br&gt;those are the returns for my managed futures program, im a CTA. its great uncorrelated returns but theres a lot of programs that under perform or blow up (-60%+ years). its definitely more liquid than other alternatives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873270&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873256&lt;br&gt;Damn dude you&amp;#x27;re crushing it. What&amp;#x27;s the time period on those returns?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mind if I ask what your strategy is?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Any specific managed futures ETFs you like? Are they even close to replicating the actuals?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873283&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873270&lt;br&gt;thats 20 months of performance trading 8 different futures markets. semi-systematic medium frequency trend following. im not too familiar with the ETFs that track managed futures but they usually focus on the billion dollar CTAs and those programs are lower returns lower risk just trying to be uncorrelated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873448&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873184&lt;br&gt;ok, its still not beating the stock market unlike your claim, and if you take the last 3 years out and it drops a lot. That is insane volatility that it doesn&amp;#x27;t converge after 50 years. Realistically the actual return is maybe 7% and you get very long periods of dogshit ~3%, and for all that volatility it still doesn&amp;#x27;t match the market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873450&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I’m currently halfway through finishing my CFP course&lt;br&gt;Any advice for someone trying to hit the ground running, beyond spamming LinkedIn? Or should I just accept that this job market is going to rape me until I give up hope&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873477&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872433&lt;br&gt;Cant ai just do most of that?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873686&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873477&lt;br&gt;This. Almost tooka financial advisor job. Then I realized, &amp;quot;why the fuck would anybody talk to a human about this?&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873827&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873686&lt;br&gt;Cause the AI will tell you something plausible that it thinks you want to hear, and it will partially or mostly hallucinate the data it uses to deliver that response&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873887&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872433&lt;br&gt;Do you hold any bitcoin? What are your thoughts on it and does your firm/company advise on it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874040&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872561&lt;br&gt;I am a europoor(in a very poor country) so I dont think i have access to most the stuff you are listing. I can only buy ETFs, I have most my portfolio in a Global market cap ETF some in europe ETF and a little in small cap value international and emerging markets. Also bought a sizable stack of silver sub 30 dollars but its going to be a bitch to sell. I dont invest in bonds since I think that every government will just keep on printing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874046&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873450&lt;br&gt;Connections are everything, and the exam will be easier than you think. The classes were hugely valuable, were harder and more useful than my master&amp;#x27;s degree courses. Most companies will have you try to peddle shit insurance products to friends/family at the entry level it&amp;#x27;s gross.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873477&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873686&lt;br&gt;Maybe someday, not right now. For what &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873827 said and because it just sucks at answering niche or complex questions. When I ask it things it usually feeds me flat out wrong answers that would be passable to someone that didn&amp;#x27;t do any research.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;One example is having it try to pick stocks. Gets obliterated by the index funds every time. It&amp;#x27;s a consistent loser at this because it can&amp;#x27;t make forward projections and the question is too complicated for it. Tax questions are a horror show too, you&amp;#x27;d think it would be good at those.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The main issue with AI in my eyes is that it just doesn&amp;#x27;t understand humans/human nature. Most of my job is behavioral.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873887&lt;br&gt;I do, I made a bunch of money in it 2016ish and now build and rebalance a position in my retirement accounts (5-10% allocation).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874061&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874040&lt;br&gt;Wish I knew more about EU investing, I&amp;#x27;m completely specialized for US investing so it&amp;#x27;s out of my wheelhouse. I only have a handful of expat/foreign clients.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;EU bonds have been zero or even negative for a long time. I won&amp;#x27;t touch them because they don&amp;#x27;t compensate you for loaning them money, and I can&amp;#x27;t believe people keep buying them.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apparently it has something to do with their SIPC insurance equivalent, safer park for cash than a checking account basically because of the federal coverage you get by buying a bond. I haven&amp;#x27;t looked much into it just what I heard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874087&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873887&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;does your firm/company advise on it?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Forgot to answer this part. We don&amp;#x27;t buy it in our portfolios, but we do help clients manage the risk associated with it. Some people are believers in crypto so we highlight the risks (volatility, no intrinsic value, etc) and then work with them to figure out how much of their overall investments is a prudent amount to put into that risk asset. I personally cap myself at 10% for both gold and crypto.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crypto is actually considered speculation instead of investing by most managers. Kind of like commodities/gold/NFTs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874261&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873448&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;its still not beating the stock market &lt;br&gt;It does in the 26-year backward looking period in the data array from the picture by 30bp. Instead of just pulling 7% out of your booty you could spend 10 seconds doing the present value calculation if you really wanted.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s about 9.8% annualized if you go all the way back to &amp;#x27;71 from now ($39-$5,000). That&amp;#x27;s definitely nothing to scoff at when constructing a portfolio and hedging equity markets considering the 0.1 correlation. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;That is insane volatility&lt;br&gt;Volatility is good in a portfolio of non-correlated assets that&amp;#x27;s rebalanced outside of tolerance bands.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;all that volatility it still doesn&amp;#x27;t match the market&lt;br&gt;Almost keeps up with it and doesn&amp;#x27;t move in the same direction, which is the idea. Non-correlated assets, rebalancing the volatility, and risk-return tradeoff are portfolio construction 101.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874286&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alright anon, I&amp;#x27;m out. Have a great day and I hope every one of you gets to retire early.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;PS long nursing homes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874295&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872433&lt;br&gt;Is there a gap in the asset management &amp;amp; financial planning software market? Seems you are just using an excel sheet there. Is there any way your life could be easier or more automated?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m a developer and I like money&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874345&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874295&lt;br&gt;The software is pretty comprehensive and generally way deeper than just an excel sheet, but of course there&amp;#x27;s an industry spectrum of how deep/detailed the analysis goes by firm and by program.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some is straight up basically a cash flows projection laid on top of a balance sheet (excel). The people that use this are shitty whole life insurance people.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s the auxiliary software where the money is at right now it seems. AI that reads trusts using OCR and spits out a summary to help you find issues. Tax software. Stuff like that.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our software for portfolio management (have used 3) is AWFUL though. That&amp;#x27;s a big gap for asset management imho.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Is it really that much more difficult to start a business in the eu than us? — 76 replies — 13.7/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860796</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860796?lm=1771505805</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:56:45 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Is it really that much more difficult to start a business in the eu than us?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860796'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 76 • Updated: 2026-02-19 12:56 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;You guys in the EU make less than us on paychecks, but you get to keep more of your money because you have universal healthcare and PTO while we have to pay for private insurance which chronically denies people&amp;#x27;s health situations. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Are people saying that starting a business in the EU is difficult because of the regulations? What regulations does the European union impose on its citizen&amp;#x27;s than they think it&amp;#x27;s easier to start in the United States instead?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860815&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;Depends enormously on which country are we talking about. Some are easy (Germany) some are very hard (Italy)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860817&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; you get to keep more of your money because you have universal healthcare&lt;br&gt;yeah right&lt;br&gt;good luck getting that &amp;quot;universal healthcare&amp;quot; if you&amp;#x27;re not a boomer, waiting lists are years for even a basic exam/procedure. It&amp;#x27;s either you go private (and pay out of your own pocket) or you die&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; and PTO&lt;br&gt;oh wow, 20 wagie cagie free days a year. Totally worth the 60%+ taxes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;All taxation is theft. It&amp;#x27;s just that. Taxation doesn&amp;#x27;t pay for services. It&amp;#x27;s just the way they control the economy, and here in EU they fucking LOVE to control what you can and cannot do. They print the money, they don&amp;#x27;t need to tax you. They tax you to control you (and to humiliate you)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860822&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;The healthcare thing is too much american leftie argument, it also has been very overcrowded by you guessed arabs and africans, unironically I was better treated when I broke my leg in brazil of all places then in france&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870191&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870164&lt;br&gt;did you read anything of what i said there and ignored it or are you just retarded?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Just don&amp;#x27;t collect data for commercial purposes&lt;br&gt;as a user, having to click on shit on every website for gdpr is annoying&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;It does but not allowing certain monetization strategies of the data, informing you about how, which and why what points of data are used and giving the EU a mechanism to fight against, mostly foreign, companies violating your privacy.&lt;br&gt;yeah you definitely are retarded. which part of &amp;quot;it does not protect my data&amp;quot; did you not understand?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870199&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;starting a business is very easy on both sides of the atlantic. scaling is harder in the EU because it&amp;#x27;s a fragmented market with wildly different rulesets between member states and capital markets&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870203&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870191&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;as a user, having to click on shit on every website for gdpr is annoying&lt;br&gt;Oh the horror! Let me guess, in most cases you just have to click &amp;#x27;disable all&amp;#x27; and &amp;#x27;save&amp;#x27; right? Here&amp;#x27;s a pro-tip to save you the time: Block the domain or script they use for their cookie banners&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;which part of &amp;quot;it does not protect my data&amp;quot; did you not understand?&lt;br&gt;The part where you lied.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870682&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870203&lt;br&gt;ah, i see, you are retarded. just because some laws that are lax exist doesn&amp;#x27;t mean data is protected, you fucking retarded faggot&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870744&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870065&lt;br&gt;it started long before post-WW2 tho, germs bureaucracymaxxed post-reunification during the 2nd Reich, from 1871 onward.&lt;br&gt;At first it was to keep in check all the landers trying to take the lion&amp;#x27;s share of federal credits and centralize power. And it worked gud, but then it progressively became the hellscape kafkaian machine we all know.&lt;br&gt;That&amp;#x27;s how you know the hallofcost never happened, becuz you can be sure nazis would have made endless paperworks addressing the situation, down to the very last jewish pubic hair, but we didn&amp;#x27;t find any document.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870778&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stop eating the commie propaganda. Europeans don&amp;#x27;t have savings for shit, they just have stable expenses but all their wealth is tied to inheriting homes. That&amp;#x27;s why homes are basically untaxed while stocks are treated like financial Nazism. You aren&amp;#x27;t going to spend more a healthy young person in the US, the real benefit of Europe is the private healthcare is very cheap and good &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Starting businesses in Europe sucks because of two factors. The first is low liquidity and consumer spending: unlike the US, people don&amp;#x27;t spend nearly as much, have as much to spend, or make debt. So there isn&amp;#x27;t much room for anyone to buy something new - successful businesses target liquid tourists or B2B, where they write off the huge taxes as expenses. Over regulated financial market also leads to lower liquidity and more difficulty getting loans and investors, you rely on government programs run by middle aged menopausal cunts that have never worked more than 28 hours a week &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other issue is labor laws and public perception. It&amp;#x27;s morally bankrupt to try and get more money, why aren&amp;#x27;t you happy being average, why are you trying to pull ahead. Anyone you hire can&amp;#x27;t be fired, you can&amp;#x27;t have low compensation with offset packages to get high skill labor, you need to suck some blue blooded cock to get money and not wait years for whatever permits you&amp;#x27;ll need, because they were born out of nobility and still have half the money and connections &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eurotards freak out about Epstein but every European politician and rich person rapes babies for breakfast. It&amp;#x27;s just 1) not pedo to them if they&amp;#x27;re over 14 bc muh age of consent and 2) they hide in the shadows unlike Americans, they try to be as unnoticed as possible, give a few concessions to the poor and continue ruling sucking and fucking like they&amp;#x27;ve been doing the past thousand years&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870889&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870103&lt;br&gt;What are the reforms that boomers are blocking?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870915&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869942&lt;br&gt;Yeah i feel the same. Sex, drugs and love are already the ultimate sensations and none of them are expensive. All luxuries are pretty worthless add-ons and don’t feel special. You just have a bigger bed, or a bigger car, not anything you really need.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870937&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860817&lt;br&gt;That&amp;#x27;s complete bullshit, stop making up fantasies in your mind. If there is ONE thing still somewhat running smoothly in western Europe, it&amp;#x27;s free healthcare.&lt;br&gt;Contrary to you i know what i&amp;#x27;m talking about since i was on the operation table just a month ago to fix few lower vertebrae after a bike accident. I never had to wait for anything more than few days, nor did i have to spend a single penny on pre-procedures, examinations or for the hospital stay/operation/anesthesia/post-op medication. And i don&amp;#x27;t have any health mutual.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It probably would have costed me a bazillion goybux in the jewSA.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871000&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870937&lt;br&gt;Why the fuck would it cost bajillions, even shit insurance has a max out of pocket of like 10k. If you don&amp;#x27;t have a job medicaid literally covers everything for free, the real problem is half the people that qualify are too fucking stupid to sign up for it &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Also if the accident wasn&amp;#x27;t your fault you could sue for big money, in Europe they&amp;#x27;re just like meh accidents happen enjoy the lifelong complications faggot. I will agree southern European health systems are pretty decent and their private healthcare is fantastic and cheap, but if you&amp;#x27;re German or some shit I&amp;#x27;d rather have the US system, you guys pay more in healthcare tax than any American if you have a half decent job and if you get anything where you may actually die they just say, yeah you&amp;#x27;re fucked settle your affairs or the bureaucracy will give the rest of your family a stroke, no point trying any more it&amp;#x27;s an inefficient allocation of resources&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871020&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868041&lt;br&gt;This is extremely short-sighted of them, they will end up losing the capacity to compete and fall behind slowly, they actually already are, then when they slowly go on closing business left and right from ever increasing ineficiency. What else can they even do but borrow more and more for the worst possible spending a state can do, paying bills, a budget blackhole, increasing inflation and making money useless and as those countries get poorer the services will also get far far far worse and extremely corrupt, not even talking about how such aging will make it even worse. Honestly this is reading like what happened to argentina, greece and other latam and thirdies socialist govts did, it will work fine as long as the economy can keep it, when it starts to shrink it will be poverty hell. I will agree that america treats us workers pretty bad, but this welfare paradise of the EU won&amp;#x27;t work for long either, they will end up forced to cut things and get closer to us if they want to survive a world with China, India, US and former colonies being no longer mudhutts but mildly developed enough to make raw resources more expensive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871023&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;Lots of retards ITT.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Setting up a business is child&amp;#x27;s play in places like Denmark, Sweden, Estonia. Setting up, doing tax returns and all interactions with gov is handled through online ID and takes seconds.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Places like Bulgaria, Romania, Slovenia are selling themselves as business friendly. Very low taxes. Some places like Bulgaria have extremely low dividend taxes so you pay yourself with dividends. Romania has a corporate setup where you pay a tiny percentage on the turnover. Ideal for freelancers or small business with high margins or just extreme low expense. In all of these places, corporate setups and accountants cost next to nothing.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Then you have some almost offshore jurisdictions still in the EU with insanely beneficial rules for some niches and very low taxes. Like Cyprus and Malta.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now regulations, what regulations? Anything (except guns, booze, some gambling, cigarettes I guess) is traded freely between the states under the same legislation. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Also: we get sued way less over here. Do the math on that one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871050&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; wife started selling her paintings&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; she declared herself first, this was needed to attend some events&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; French government instantly asks her for €800, before she has made her first sale&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; this is what they estimate she&amp;#x27;d owe them at the end of the year based on their estimates of how much she will earn, so they ask for it upfront&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; you can contest it but it&amp;#x27;s actually faster to wait for the year to end so they are proven wrong&lt;br&gt;I hate them so much...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871051&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860860&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;taxes&lt;br&gt;depends where, some places will legit rape your revenue&lt;br&gt;Combined with some insane regulations and you legit can&amp;#x27;t start a company&lt;br&gt;Best example is France, fucked up taxes, and if you want to get into tech, or anything that involves personal data, you need cough up 6 to 7 figures so that your cyber security is in the norm&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871089&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860815&lt;br&gt;This&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871111&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871020&lt;br&gt;I will die long before I see some high tech company or even mid tier industry appear in latam, africa or even india, they will always be turning up cheap raw resources because they are simply brown subhumans with low iq, not even talking about russia post-war. Its an unfounded fearmongering that we will ever have to compete with them lol, you forget europe will never fall to thirdie level of mismanagement simple because we are better educated and white. At the very worst unlikely scenario we will always make money from tourism anyway, but honestly this is all american envy for no reason, we are not stopping you from doing the same.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871116&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871023&lt;br&gt;So you&amp;#x27;re admitting you can only live off arbitrage? Who the fuck are you selling to in Romania or Bulgaria, Romania is actually marginally based because it&amp;#x27;s spread its asshole to US companies for cheap EU labor, those Nordic countries you listed have a smaller economy than Pennsylvania so yeah if you want to sell troon support stickers you&amp;#x27;re good but you&amp;#x27;re not going to make shit otherwise &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Portugal is also kind of based but it fully relies on US and other European investments, as well as inexistent enforcement of labor laws and pathetic salaries. I don&amp;#x27;t get how you&amp;#x27;d start up there without the first 100k being gifted though, or the family having land, or working abroad first &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As I said, Europe is only viable for tourism or B2B, you will never become a millionaire opening a bakery or car wash or hamster fentanyl university of arts like the US, there&amp;#x27;s no consumer spending to eat&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871180&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871116&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Europe is only viable for tourism or B2B, you will never become a millionaire&lt;br&gt;Lmao, just look at economic charts, most european economies have high tech industry as the main economic activity, american bullshit as usual, nobody needs to be a millionaire in europe, we already live better than one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871183&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871116&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Who the fuck are you selling to in Romania or Bulgaria,&lt;br&gt;As I said, you are a fucking retard. Your company is in Bulgaria, but you sell to fucking anyone in EU the same way while paying insanely low corporate tax and next to no admin fees. You ship from anywhere you want in the EU, or have staff in bloody Manila if you wish. What the fuck does that have to do with arbitrage? You incorporate wherever you want since it is your legal right.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I doubt you are entrepreneurial material though, so do not bother grokking the potential here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871191&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871000&lt;br&gt;The suing thing is the biggest AIDS of USA. People are already well compensated enough in europe for their troubles. The ”if you make a honest mistake, someone will see their opportinity and sue you and financially destroy your life” mentality just creates even more stress to an already high stress environment of USA. It just makes people act even more legally defensive at every turn and creates useless bureucracy and slows things down. Getting raped when everything didn’t go 100% nicely is not something to be proud of.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871214&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871020&lt;br&gt;This is the most midwit take and the reason why USA is failing now (it has become a nation of midwits due to poor public education). People have been saying this for decades but right now europe is in a bullrun while USA has been becoming an oligarchic brasil since the 80s. Clearly socialism doesn&amp;#x27;t just lead to inefficiency but instead to more efficiency for all instead of just few hoarding the wealth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871353&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871183&lt;br&gt;Learn to read Fritz, you are saying what I&amp;#x27;m saying while sounding like a mong. You&amp;#x27;re setting up in poor countries to sell to richer countries&amp;#x27; businesses while using the common market, it&amp;#x27;s geographic arbitrage you sausage guzzling troon, and you&amp;#x27;re selling to businesses. All that free education and you&amp;#x27;re still poorer than a fucking car salesman in Pensacola&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871500&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871214&lt;br&gt;What? Excluding Pooland all major eu economies have stopped growing or deacelerated fast, people were saying it for decades with reason, if it wasnt for a miraculous fall of the ussr and a flood of cheap raw resources and energy with negligible transport costs from russia it would&amp;#x27;ve happened earlier as it did post-2008 when europe started to lag more and more behind the US and China.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871533&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867554&lt;br&gt;Nigger&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;give us taxes goy&lt;br&gt;ok, well, how much&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;We don&amp;#x27;t know uwu&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;you tell us&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;but if you&amp;#x27;re wrong we get to take even more of your money lol&lt;br&gt;you just said you don&amp;#x27;t know what I owe&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;thats right &lt;br&gt;so how do you know if I pay wrong?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Don&amp;#x27;t get cheeky with us you little shit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871570&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871500&lt;br&gt;That guy is fucking retarded why even argue. The average European is still a moron, printing useless degrees doesn&amp;#x27;t make people smarter. They still cuck themselves daily. He&amp;#x27;s happy to never own anything so his blue blooded friends can hoard the land and wealth like they&amp;#x27;ve always done &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Muh healthcare muh taxes &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Half of every country is too fucking poor to pay tax, and the top 10% isn&amp;#x27;t stupid enough to pay tax, so the middle class just pays 50% of their income while being happy they can rent a shit hole for life and that they&amp;#x27;re better off unemployed than working in terms of life quality &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I will definitely return to Europe once my nest egg is built, I&amp;#x27;ll just live in 2 different countries 179 days a year and live off US divvies therefore paying no retard tax and just paying private healthcare out of pocket, or if I really make it just pay the flat 100k Italian tax and get private insurance for 300 a month that will pay for top quality coverage while I sip Italian wines and hire high end eastern european hookers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871624&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871570&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;can’t get women otherwise so has to pay for hookers&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thanks for revealing that you’re some dysfunctional weirdo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871681&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871624&lt;br&gt;Thanks for showing why you&amp;#x27;re weak, religious morals won&amp;#x27;t get you anywhere. Also very europilled, way more Europeans use hookers than Americans outside the lower class - but you pretend like it&amp;#x27;s somehow weird while you haven&amp;#x27;t even been to church since your communion &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For now I bang for free, outside working and life only about one chick a week, but you bet your ass I&amp;#x27;ll buy some dimes when I can live off passive income, at least they&amp;#x27;re safe and making good money unlike the daughters you gave away to arabs to be beaten and bred to show how woke you are&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871776&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many countries are gatekept by language.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871778&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;People are doing a lot of grifting and lobby work for deregulation. Starting a business isn&amp;#x27;t really difficult.&lt;br&gt;There are some bad things, in Germany for example financing rounds require a notary to read out the whole contract in person to you. But a lot of these things you and 90% of small business owners won&amp;#x27;t encounter in practice&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860837&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;tax system is so incredibly fucking complex you have to hire people just to calculate how much you own&lt;br&gt;You legitimately think accountants only exist in Europe?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873866&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868110&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s not bullshit. Europeans are smart. The European rich just refused to pay programmers so any good programmer went to America over the past 35 fucking years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>By investing in the US stock markets, you are directly financing everything that you hate about the United States. — 19 replies — 13.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61874572</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61874572?lm=1771520491</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 17:01:31 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;By investing in the US stock markets, you are directly financing everything that you hate about the United States.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61874572'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 19 • Updated: 2026-02-19 17:01 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;By investing in the US stock markets, you are directly financing everything that you hate about the United States.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874579&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874572&lt;br&gt;I dont, stonks are gay.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874590&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874572&lt;br&gt;Until unrealized gains are taxed, kys bobo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874623&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874590&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; HR departments staffed by roasties&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; women in management&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; H1 b visas&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; Jeets taking over American industry&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; Congress members getting rich off stocks&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; Lobbyist influence on laws&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; The bankers&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; etc&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t think so, Timmy. The second that you invest, you&amp;#x27;re giving them the money for all of it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874634&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874572&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m also directly financing everything that I love about the United States.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874640&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874634&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Like what?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874661&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874572&lt;br&gt;but i only invest in reddit stocks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874662&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874640&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874670&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874662&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; no living wage&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; jobs being sent over seas&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; people being replaced by machines&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; Blackrock buying up all of the homes and making home ownership unattainable&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I have some oceanfront property in Colorado, if you&amp;#x27;re interested in property.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874673&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874662&lt;br&gt;What a load of horse shit lmao&lt;br&gt;Exactly the propaganda that destroyed this place&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874678&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874670&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874673&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874679&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874678&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874701&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874679&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874713&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874572&lt;br&gt;Luckily I&amp;#x27;m not a jew lover and only invest in silver and pokemon cards&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874737&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874701&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; Americans are just lazy and not smart enough&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Okay, boomer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874763&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874737&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874774&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874763&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Have fun trading against bots, and good luck competing against the world with your best foids, trannies, jeets, and chinese spies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874778&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874572&lt;br&gt;But I love the United States&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874789&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874774&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874810&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874789&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; a free country&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Did you know the owning physical gold in the United States was illegal for 41 years?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>the US is in recession — 29 replies — 12.5/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61869320</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61869320?lm=1771517366</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:09:26 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;the US is in recession&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61869320'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 29 • Updated: 2026-02-19 16:09 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;the US is in recession&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869343&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869320&lt;br&gt;doomed fag nation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869350&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Adjust by population&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869389&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bump&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869494&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869320&lt;br&gt;The US is in a bad shape but posting absolute numbers instead of relative is not very helpful&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869507&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869320&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;two full time jobs&lt;br&gt;yeah sure.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;7 AM they wake up &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;8 AM they&amp;#x27;re in JOB LOCATION 1 and start working&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;5 PM they stop working and teleport to JOB LOCATION 2&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;2 AM of the next day they go back their home&lt;br&gt;it&amp;#x27;s impossible to do two full time jobs and there&amp;#x27;s no way you can convince me otherwise.&lt;br&gt;People that do two jobs are usually two part times or at most a full time and part time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869517&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869507&lt;br&gt;The way I did it was one factory job was 3 12 hour shifts Friday, Saturday, Sunday with full time bonus and then the second factory job was 4 10 hour shifts Mon-Thursday. Shit sucked, but it&amp;#x27;s not as bad as working on a fishing boat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869528&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;that&amp;#x27;s a drop in the bucket compared to what over 200 million&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869545&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869343&lt;br&gt;fpbp&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870419&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869320&lt;br&gt;Best economy ever goy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870436&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Those people are probably in debt or drive around in cars they cannot afford&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870446&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870419&lt;br&gt;Nah. It&amp;#x27;s over&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870529&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Not my problem&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870572&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869320&lt;br&gt;So? If we all starve then so will trannies, which is a win in my book&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870623&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869320&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;There are so many job positions available people can get 2 of them&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Recession&lt;br&gt;If anything business-is-a-boomin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870808&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869320&lt;br&gt;The economy has never been better. Trump literally doubled steel production in one year. Go back to plebbit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870844&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870808&lt;br&gt;We should all build steel furnances in our backyard for glorious leader trump&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870845&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869320&lt;br&gt;Too bad Biden got the definition of recession changed by websters and wikipedia the day we entered one back in 2022. Now a recession means whatever we want it to mean, aka there will never be another recession again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870850&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869320&lt;br&gt;I voted for this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870855&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870808&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;2% increase in steel production &lt;br&gt;We’re back!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870872&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870808&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;1%&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;They really think you mutts are retarded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870899&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870872&lt;br&gt;I was being generous kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871327&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869343&lt;br&gt;It won&amp;#x27;t be doomed if the poor wagies keep working like that&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872300&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869507&lt;br&gt;I worked 2 full time jobs more then once&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;morning shift at restaurant&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;7am -2pm&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Deliver Pizza&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;4pm--10pm, midnight on Friday&lt;br&gt;Morning shift was Monday- Friday&lt;br&gt;pizza shift was Thursday-Sunday&lt;br&gt;so only 2 days of the week actually sucked ass. Delivering Pizzas though was working with friends and we would smoke pot and drink beers, didn&amp;#x27;t feel like work really.&lt;br&gt;This was in the aftermath of 2008, during 2009/10 I did that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872563&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869517&lt;br&gt;3 days a week is not a full time job.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872729&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870872&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;think&lt;br&gt;*know&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872903&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870845&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;defining a recession by the fucking dictionary&lt;br&gt;stupid nigger&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872909&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;it&amp;#x27;s been in recession since two thousand fucking eight &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;they just can&amp;#x27;t hide it anymore&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872927&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872563&lt;br&gt;36+ hours is a full time job, retard&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874552&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I am one of those assholes. But then again, I pull like 290k. Make that paper bitch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Fake and Gay Economy — 43 replies — 9.4/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61871520</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61871520?lm=1771509338</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:55:38 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Fake and Gay Economy&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61871520'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 43 • Updated: 2026-02-19 13:55 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;When will this gay as economy finally collapse and how can i profit from it?&lt;br&gt;Its ridiculous the woman at our workplace contribute nothing to the company and make more money than i do&lt;br&gt;Its infuriating we just had a bunch of lay offs and we lost some of oir best workers but somehow a bunch of HR shits who do nothing all day still work here&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871530&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HR is a necessary function, chud&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871569&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871530&lt;br&gt;For what?&lt;br&gt;Genuinely why do we need it to this extent?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871755&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871569&lt;br&gt;Protect the corp from lawsuits&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872085&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872076&lt;br&gt;We dont live in capitalist system&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Its been state capitalism for long time&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872087&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872076&lt;br&gt;This is a fiat problem, not a capitalism problem.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872170&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871569&lt;br&gt;The purpose of HR is to protect the company. Putting a retarded and narcisstic Stacy in and having her railroad, gaslight, and demoralize employees, is her primary objective. Think of it as internal forced arbitration&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872188&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872072&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;ai will replace the hr roastie&lt;br&gt;yes&lt;br&gt;but then she will just be hired to do something even more worthless&lt;br&gt;that will pay even more&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872195&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s because they decide whom to fire. Make the lists, at least, which then get approved without looking. Do you think they&amp;#x27;d put themselves on it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872202&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;For once, all of picrelated feet don&amp;#x27;t look like they smell so good. God I hate HR&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872233&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872076&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;capitalist&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;where the corporations control the government&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;and steal all the the money via bail outs and money printing&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;thats not capitalism&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872278&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872233&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Government prints money to give it corporations so they can just give it to each other in a circle to make number go up&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Corporations just use that imaginary money to buy back their own stocks to artificially make number go up&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;80 billion dollars given to Israel so all Israeli citizens are guaranteed healthcare and higher education and six figure stipends while you are denied this in your own country&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;Capitalism&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872395&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872072&lt;br&gt;You couldn&amp;#x27;t be more wrong. HR stands for HUMAN relations. People aren&amp;#x27;t going to an ai to feel INCLUDED alongside their fellow HUMANS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872429&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872395&lt;br&gt;it stands for human resources, all they do is make sure all your tax paperwork is filed, and onboard you correctly. thats it. how old are you? what do you do? give me your life experience with the various firms youve been with, make your case anon. no one likes hr, especially not the partners/ board members.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872476&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;theres a human glut right now we need the roasties to manage the bust in order to put the company in a better position for the boom&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872709&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;I want to rape all of them&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872713&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Office jobs are day care for adults and factory jobs are slave labour&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;t. Office worker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872847&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;They look like they are having a dress up party where they larp as office workers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873112&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872429&lt;br&gt;i cant find fourth nigger&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873181&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873112&lt;br&gt;Yes but how would you feel if you DID find it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873193&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872076&lt;br&gt;Money is fake and gay. No surprise everything else is.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873211&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872713&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873212&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;half-chub and a hatchet&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;half-chub and a hatchet&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;half-chub and a hatchet&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873219&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;My blood is boiling while watching this webm on repeat. I hate women so much I&amp;#x27;ll turn gay.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873258&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;i wanna cut their toes off w/ my bolt cutter&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873271&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871755&lt;br&gt;Anyone who posts this ai nigger baby will be rounded up, families executed in front of them, then tortured to death slowly, skin peeled off, toenails removed, adrenaline injected to keep you conscious cartel style&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873293&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;only someone who has never had a job would think tiktok videos of girls dancing are representative of how workplaces actually operate. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Almost all women working provide value and will wash out if they aren&amp;#x27;t (or aren&amp;#x27;t sucking the manager&amp;#x27;s dick).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873312&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871755&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Epsteins Boyfriend got swagger&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873324&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873293&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Almost all women working provide value&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873510&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871569&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;re either trolling or never worked a day in your life,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873611&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871931&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873193&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Fake and Gay&lt;br&gt;Why is are Schizos always using that phrase? I instantly know there is a schizo take coming when i read this. Some schizo takes are interesting, some are even good, some are good to think through and some are just funny to read. But they stzill are schizo takes and mostly bullshit influeces too much by wish bias. So how and where did this phrase pick up with schizos. When i know, its around 2021/2022 when the schizo&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;economy will collapse and people will starve due to lockdowns&lt;br&gt;did not materialize. Then they started with this phrase to somehow save their prediction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873806&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872076&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;no less than three seething replies about muh real capitalism&lt;br&gt;If you abolished the state it would be reinvented by the wealthy overnight&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873944&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873611&lt;br&gt;Fake and gay was in use when I 1st started using this site in 2011.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873988&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;Hopefully never because I have a fake overpaid job, just not in HR&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>