<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>/biz/ Active (filtered, with replies)</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/</link><description>Filtered out: general, gme, bbbyq. OP + first 3 replies + last 30 replies.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 19:31:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Fake and Gay Economy — 99 replies — 147.4/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61871520</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61871520?lm=1771872665</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 18:51:05 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Fake and Gay Economy&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61871520'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 99 • Updated: 2026-02-23 18:51 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;When will this gay as economy finally collapse and how can i profit from it?&lt;br&gt;Its ridiculous the woman at our workplace contribute nothing to the company and make more money than i do&lt;br&gt;Its infuriating we just had a bunch of lay offs and we lost some of oir best workers but somehow a bunch of HR shits who do nothing all day still work here&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871530&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HR is a necessary function, chud&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871569&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871530&lt;br&gt;For what?&lt;br&gt;Genuinely why do we need it to this extent?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871755&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871569&lt;br&gt;Protect the corp from lawsuits&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883760&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883243&lt;br&gt;They got promoted to Chief Diversity, Equity &amp;amp; Inclusion Officer&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883781&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883644&lt;br&gt;You meant to say inclined. You are more inclined. Akin means &amp;quot;similar to&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883784&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882869&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;incel&lt;br&gt;Im so confused as to what that term means, involuntarily celibate? But its not being celibate if your literally having sex. Such a weird term clearly carrying different meaning. What is the point of using a term that literally has no definition to its meaning, you might aswell speak in baby noises at this point.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884146&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;guys, ALL we have to do is called women like this ugly chopped shit to their face as much as possible and they will lose all motivation to live&lt;br&gt;they are SO fragile in that regard.&lt;br&gt;next time you are walking down the street and see some bitch like this just start yelling “YOURE UGLY”&lt;br&gt;they will spend the next week and a half minimum making reddit posts about it and getting their SSRI prescription upped.&lt;br&gt;don’t ever engage with any ideas or thoughts they have. just pick apart their appearance. you look like a fridge and a stick insect at the same time. your fake dyed hair sucks. you have clown makeup on, you must have learned how to do makeup at the circus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884272&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883066&lt;br&gt;So you&amp;#x27;re saying ceo&amp;#x27;s willingly burn 75% of their money for fun?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884291&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884272&lt;br&gt;he&amp;#x27;s saying the ceo is a fucking retard&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884297&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;I want to shove my cock deep into the first one from behind. Just lift the skirt and blast the pussy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884717&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883784&lt;br&gt;Yes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884737&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871569&lt;br&gt;Without HR you could complete the work, banter and build a genuine camaraderie with your common co-worker, but we cant have unions, and its better if you&amp;#x27;re all divided and conquered, here&amp;#x27;s a harpy to make your life hell&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884742&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873193&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872087&lt;br&gt;These niggers actually get it. All problems flow downstream from jews controlling the issuance of your (since 1913) fake and gay fiat debt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885902&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873611&lt;br&gt;You must be over 18 to use this site&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886326&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882442&lt;br&gt;Yeah this kind of mega über schizos who believe in fe and no nuke use this phrase holy shit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886329&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882442&lt;br&gt;And yes the idea of space is falsifiable you absolute schizo. Satellites wouldn&amp;#x27;t even work without it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886359&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883784&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Such a weird term clearly carrying different meaning. What is the point of using a term that literally has no definition to its meaning&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s just people overusing words or ideas to oblivion, where they lose all context. It&amp;#x27;s like the worst insult was being called gay way back, then it was subverted (actually gay is cool), then it became retarded, then it got subverted (actually retarded is cool because you&amp;#x27;re not trying), then it become autistic, then it became subverted (actually it&amp;#x27;s interesting to be autistic), now it&amp;#x27;s random baby talk by gen alpha (mog, cortisol spike, chopped, unc, lil bro, frame, aura farming, 67, incel, cuk). Now it&amp;#x27;s being subverted by people overusing the terms even if they don&amp;#x27;t apply to anyone or anything in the context at all. Someone not having sex for a week = incel. Someone having a slightly embarrassing moment (cortisol spike), someone better looking walking past (mogged), doing something that&amp;#x27;s barely good (aura farming), having a strong presence even if it&amp;#x27;s completely autistic and retarded (frame). Or like when old people started wearing skateboard shirts having no clue what it was, or everyone and their dog wearing an off white shirt. People make shit gay eventually, it&amp;#x27;s a universal law.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886363&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;work office job (engineer) with way too many women and diversity hire niggers and Indians who do nothing all day&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;get new (white) South African Vice President&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;calls us all together&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;in his funny accent tells us he’s an engineer and knows the business and there will be changes&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;tells us he will cut 20% of the workforce soon&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;everyone is shit scared and the normie femoids start climbing over each other trying to save their useless asses&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;office girlies start spreading rumours about everyone and everything in desperate attempt to make themselves look better&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;don’t give a fuck, I’m a technician and actually make money for the company unlike them&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Vice President just observes the shit show and never comments on anything while he feels out the office&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;come in one Monday&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;literally all blacks are gone&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;all except the actual useful Indians are gone&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;he culled every single female that we all knew had jewish make believe adult daycare jobs&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;only kept the old hag secretaries that actually do a great job&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kek, based white nigger. Turns out all it takes is some third world coloniser to clean this woke shit up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886555&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872076&lt;br&gt;We are not capitalist.&lt;br&gt;We have been Trotskyist since the end of WW2.&lt;br&gt;Having a central bank is plank #5 of the commie manifesto.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886576&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884742&lt;br&gt;It was a bit delayed until after 1913.&lt;br&gt;They couldn’t go full fakeconomy immediately, or they would have been shut down.&lt;br&gt;They had to wait and boil the frog slowly, using the occasional crisis as a speed boost.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886586&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t ever interact with HR once I&amp;#x27;m hired until I&amp;#x27;m inevitably fired. From where comes the HR hate? Are they the ones who actually make the decisions to fire us?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886684&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;this board is dead as shit holy fuck&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886687&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61886684&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s the weekend. It picks up when the market is open.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886692&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;d fuck all of them. At the same time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887220&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61886363&lt;br&gt;Sounds illegal and fake. This is such an obvious thing to do, there must be a reason it doesn&amp;#x27;t actually happen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889346&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s not going to collapse... bill gates will grow some cheap bug burgers and psyop all the women to think it&amp;#x27;s healthy and great for the environment... so we can continue feeding billions of women to do nothing but work in an office.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889382&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61886363&lt;br&gt;How was he able to be able to gauge who&amp;#x27;s useful and who&amp;#x27;s not in such a short period of time?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889387&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889346&lt;br&gt;Also, paying women to do nothing is one of the best birth controls there is. They are incapable of dating down. Sorry, just the messenger. bullshit jobs, especially for women, will never end until picrel collapses.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unfortunately, the jews also don&amp;#x27;t want picrel to collapse because then their banks would go broke. So we&amp;#x27;re stuck in hell.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891731&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882869&lt;br&gt;nice&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891770&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889387&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;implying men would ever fuck someone below them&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891847&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891770&lt;br&gt;are you literally retarded?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891874&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891847&lt;br&gt;Chad isn&amp;#x27;t fucking chubby chicks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891915&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;hmm thigh boots&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Link vs XRP — 27 replies — 108.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889600</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889600?lm=1771874784</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 19:26:24 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Link vs XRP&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889600'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 27 • Updated: 2026-02-23 19:26 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;When will the gap close? Link came within a hair of flipping xrp in January ‘21. We all know that Link is everything Xrp fraudulently claims to be so it makes sense that this chart should flip soon enough. Will it be gradual or violent? Will it flip because xrp crashes or because Link moons? &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most importantly where are some places you can use Link as collateral to borrow Xrp to take full advantage of the trade of the century?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889606&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m so tired.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889622&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889600&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889606&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889620&lt;br&gt;Link is scam&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Buy XRP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889634&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889606&lt;br&gt;Xrp is like chainlink if all the nightmares came true: no use case, no revenue, an ipo that formally cuts token holders out of the picture etc.. and we need over a 10x to reach their market cap. This fact always gives me energy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889799&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889634&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889823&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889600&lt;br&gt;It won&amp;#x27;t. Even RLUSD will pass link&amp;#x27;s marketcap in a matter of a few months.You invested poorly in a project with the only purpose of jewishly injecting fees for literally no reason and assuming people will allow you to entrench in core services. It is a bad financial and moral investment&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889827&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889634&lt;br&gt;XRP had no ICO. Link sells to retail at every pump and drains operator rewards it claimed it wouldn&amp;#x27;t. Link has literally zero use case outside arbitrary jewish rent seeking crypto toll boothing. It solves no problem and has no use outside ADDING frictions. XRP from Ripple alone has: &lt;br&gt;https://ripple.com/insights/institutional-defi-on-xrpl-scaling-real-world-finance-with-xrp-at-the-core/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889841&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889600&lt;br&gt;not gonna happen, jews will reward retard boomers once again, they are the golden generation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890083&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889600&lt;br&gt;strongly believe 2026-2027, hopefully you&amp;#x27;re ready. won&amp;#x27;t be instant, but still swift. cant believe there are anons who actually think like this &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889827, i hope they dont disappear and comment a little longer so we can have fun with them. chainlink wont be the only crypto that will flip xrp either&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890125&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;xrp&lt;br&gt;BOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOM&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890250&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889827&lt;br&gt;always funny to see them gloating with their &amp;quot;MPT&amp;quot; and permissioned dex when literally all of that has been absolute standard and normal for the rest of crypto&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;XRP retards are even saying wrapped assets on their chain is something novel like lmao&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890307&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889600&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;We all know that Link is everything Xrp fraudulently claims to be&lt;br&gt;Since when did sergoy claim link was a bridge currency? &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The bigger issue you&amp;#x27;ll have saying it&amp;#x27;s &amp;quot;everything&amp;quot; XRP claims to be&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Is it a security or not? &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Which honestly give me an idea, which maybe will settle things in the USA. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Holding this piece of shit token + writing the previous statement out made me realize, we can probably class action chainlink and find out legally. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Is security or not? &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Has it or has it not been advertised as one?&lt;br&gt;Might be able to recover these -50% bags and get the SEC involved to settle things. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;No more waiting on the pool to open. No more cope on clarity act. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anyone willing to get this started?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890390&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;What AI thinks&lt;br&gt;Argument That LINK Is a Security&lt;br&gt;Under the Howey test (SEC v. W.J. Howey Co.), an asset is a security if there is:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;An investment of money&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;In a common enterprise&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;With a reasonable expectation of profit&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Derived from the efforts of others&lt;br&gt;LINK can arguably meet all four elements:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Investment of money: &lt;br&gt;People buy LINK with capital.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Common enterprise: &lt;br&gt;The value of LINK rises and falls with the success of the Chainlink ecosystem.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Expectation of profit: &lt;br&gt;Many buyers hold LINK expecting price appreciation, not immediate utility use.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Efforts of others: &lt;br&gt;The value of LINK depends significantly on the continued development, partnerships, and ecosystem growth driven by Chainlink Labs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additionally, the original token distribution helped fund development, which resembles capital formation typical of securities offerings.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thoughts anons? Is this class actionable?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890519&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889823&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889827&lt;br&gt;Oh hey I remember this deranged plebbit shitbag peddling cripple marketing material unironically&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;if you make fun of me or my fat jew goblin xrp shitcoin youre a LITERAL &amp;quot;pharisee&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;youre LITERALLY &amp;quot;abstracting&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;mirroring&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;xrp is LITERALLY a force of objective good guys, for real&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;xrp is gonna LITERALLY save the banks FROM usury &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I LITERALLY have no idea how swift fees work on a basic level and all of my hopium relies on my failure to comprehend this&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;muh LITERAL saudi prince&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890539&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biepum is in this very thread, seething at the standard.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;All and every progress regarding the &amp;#x27;&amp;#x27;flippening&amp;#x27;&amp;#x27; that they have been praying for can be found here&lt;br&gt;https://link-flip.alwaysbeshipp.ing/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;RLUSD will sooner overtake chainlinks mcap than chainlink xrp&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890828&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889600&lt;br&gt;It will be violent, and partly due to xrp crashing, but in no small part due to link pumping. Its going to happen after Clarity act + full staking release and neet nodes. So 2050 at this rate&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890840&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890828&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;dude, le clarity&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;le full staking&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;le neet nodes&lt;br&gt;never happening, sweetie&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890870&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889600&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889606&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889620&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889622&lt;br&gt;the only usecase any of these has is XLM; because africans are still trading phone minutes as currency and XLM is a reasonable replacement&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;XRP and LINK are complete LARPs that nobody even trusts&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;and i don&amp;#x27;t even give a shit about giving africans currency. but its literally the only thing your larp does in the physical world&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890891&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890390&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;common enterprise&lt;br&gt;You bought a product, not a share. Everything you just wrote proves this is a speculation and not an investment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891011&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889827&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;https://ripple.com/insights/institutional-defi-on-xrpl-scaling-real-world-finance-with-xrp-at-the-core/&lt;br&gt;You keep posting same article like its some kind of mic drop moment. As if linking it over and over suddenly turns it into undeniable proof. It doesn’t lol Youre taking a CEOs words at face value because you think hes personally invested in making you rich. Thats not how this works. CEOs promote their companies and his job is to literally sell you XRP.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891035&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889600&lt;br&gt;Thanks spammy.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889620&lt;br&gt;/thread&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891717&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891011&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m not. It is literally the products they are building and the material they are releasing detailing it to shareholders. Link sell directly to retail every time there is a minor pump. You are literally saying nothing but standing in a way where you think if you come across as affirmative in a direct way it will seem like you are. Lol You are just doing what you accuse me of (which I am not) saying we can&amp;#x27;t trust it to be true because it is relying on the words of someone. It literally isn&amp;#x27;t. They are structuring XRPL core amendment pushes and having their staff code them based on the product suite fit detailed in the article. They made multiple multibillion dollar acquisitions, including a fucking prime broker to actuate it all. And most importantly, the majority of their treasury is in XRP and their products are ALL made more efficient and cost efficient using it and they are incentivized to increase the price of XRP they have in escrow and cannot sell, unlike CLL who dump what was supposed to be operator rewards on retail always and are LITERALLY a fraud designed to milk your savings (exactly what you project Ripple to be, which it isn&amp;#x27;t because the XRPL actually solves efficiencies instead of sticking a tollbooth in the middle of process for literally no reason like a jewish parasite). The entire XRPL is designed to automatically use XRP for auto-bridging between assets etc. Your argument sucks and it is hilarious that it actually applies to link, which you are capable of seeing but literally don&amp;#x27;t care because you are in a literal cult pretending to object but just obsessively committed to a project that is the least morally redeemable or utility having one in all of crypto for literally no reason than ego and entrenched specific coin cultism. Really odd and gay.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891755&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890083&lt;br&gt;Extreme cope. SWIFT said it would take 15 years MINIMUM to even get a product active. I am not sorry to let you know that by that time SWIFT will have 100% missed the boat and payments will have been completely revolutionized, not needing them. You hitched your dingy to a big ship, but it turned out it was the Titanic, which we all always said. Way too little way too late presuming the ethgate lawfare would win but it didn&amp;#x27;t. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890250&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;MPT/permissioned dex is the standard&lt;br&gt;No it hasn&amp;#x27;t. You literally don&amp;#x27;t know what either of those things are. No other ledger at scale has a built in dex and amm and protocol layer compliance like permissioned dex nor the broadness of the MPT standard. It definitely has been The Standard, but not in the way you think. MPT is not &amp;quot;wrapped assets.&amp;quot; Here is an AI slop video that is actually informative which possibly someone at your level of research will be able to be spoonfed by:&lt;br&gt;https://youtu.be/3kYXW_o-N4Y&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890519&lt;br&gt;Top cope in thread&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891887&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890891&lt;br&gt;Everything written proves it&amp;#x27;s a security anon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891914&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890307&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890390&lt;br&gt;The only thing that needs to happen to settle the debate is someone suing. And given chainlink seemingly gives zero fucks about it&amp;#x27;s holders it&amp;#x27;s probably long overdue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892108&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891887&lt;br&gt;It has an etf already bro it’s a defacto commodity and will soon be enshrined in law as a commodity. Also may I just congratulate you on your point that ripple is incentivised to increase the price of Xrp since that is most of their treasury, unlike CLL who also has most of their treasury in Link but is not incentivised to increase the price. I thought that was most salient.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892122&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889600&lt;br&gt;Dunno man, but the best times with link have been when I forgot about it during the bear and came back to big gains&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>I just bought some LINK tokens. — 14 replies — 56.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891507</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891507?lm=1771874257</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 19:17:37 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;I just bought some LINK tokens.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891507'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 14 • Updated: 2026-02-23 19:17 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;I just bought some LINK tokens.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891546&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891507&lt;br&gt;ygmi&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891559&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891507&lt;br&gt;retard, it&amp;#x27;s going to $2&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891571&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891559&lt;br&gt;I think I&amp;#x27;m gonna be buying some each month this year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891575&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891507&lt;br&gt;interesting. do you waste your money often? is this a .. sexual fetish of yours?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891581&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891559&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m thinking $4 but yeah buying now isn&amp;#x27;t a good idea&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891593&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891507&lt;br&gt;Same. It feels like stealing at those prices.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891606&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891575&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;do you waste your money often?&lt;br&gt;I am a gay muslim actually.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891855&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891507&lt;br&gt;Even when given another opportunity to buy a good coin low you double down on the same mistake. Why (serious question)?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891858&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891507&lt;br&gt;Sorry for your loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891872&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891855&lt;br&gt;Shill me a good coin, I&amp;#x27;m all ears.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891978&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891872&lt;br&gt;HBAR, CC and XDC are good bets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892033&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891507&lt;br&gt;Keep stacking king&lt;br&gt;I boughteded too, waiting for tax returns to slurp again&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892072&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891978&lt;br&gt;can the HBAR meme die already&lt;br&gt;it&amp;#x27;s an even worse chart than link&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892075&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891507&lt;br&gt;Silly OP, should have bought at $6&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>I don't think BTC is how Satoshi described Bitcoin to be in 2008/9. — 19 replies — 38.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890488</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890488?lm=1771873283</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 19:01:23 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t think BTC is how Satoshi described Bitcoin to be in 2008/9.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890488'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 19 • Updated: 2026-02-23 19:01 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890544&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;you can&amp;#x27;t read c++&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890560&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890488&lt;br&gt;satoshi was kind of retarded about scaling, remember he actually envisioned that people were grinding hashes on their home CPU and be competitive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890570&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890488&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I don&amp;#x27;t think BTC is how Satoshi described Bitcoin to be in 2008/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was created as an alternative back then. A decentralized tool that cannot be sanctioned taxed or stolen by governments.&lt;br&gt;Until the Governments stepped in and convinced the people to start mining it and shorting it for them. Small miners were replaced by big corporations and venture capitals.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kikes are gifted. They always find ways to destroy good ideas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890647&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890488&lt;br&gt;Bitcoin doesn&amp;#x27;t even work that way, only difficulty scales not transaction rate. The fact the supposed creator would say something completely wrong about it shows it wasn&amp;#x27;t actually created by a single person but an organization consisting of individuals with varying levels of understanding of how it works&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890651&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890544&lt;br&gt;Don&amp;#x27;t need to unc, I have claude&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890835&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890651&lt;br&gt;claude will tell you that nothing has fundamentally changed &lt;br&gt;aside from the P2P hardfork and code cleanup&lt;br&gt;you probably don&amp;#x27;t even know that a 0.8 can still participate in the network &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890570&lt;br&gt;you don&amp;#x27;t even know what &amp;quot;decentralization&amp;quot; means, astroturf jew&lt;br&gt;you are blockchain illiterate&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890882&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890560&lt;br&gt;This, Bitcoin has evolved to becoming a kwh futures market backstopping the grid with 0 chance of a 51% attack. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890647&lt;br&gt;Even Hal Finney suggested Bitcoin banks to address scaling, but everyone has their own opinions and hybrid models. &lt;br&gt;What&amp;#x27;s more interesting than outdated blocksize drama is the op_return drama. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;There&amp;#x27;s a little civil war going on how big the op_return data field should be and what should be allowed in it. &lt;br&gt;Tether started on BTC only and now utilizes a few different chains &lt;br&gt;There are a bunch of projects arguing how much data should be allowed to be inscribed into the op_return field that is causing arguments in the community. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is because some op_return data is just garbage, but it has to be validated. &lt;br&gt;On the other hand some data in that field will open up a great deal of security for these projects to reference. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;So OP is a fag, but there are still arguments on how this project is going develop.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891661&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oh my, this thread attracted a lot of copers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891725&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890488&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;it never really hits a scale ceiling&amp;quot; &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;meanwhile king shitcoin is doing 7 TPS&lt;br&gt;Satoshi was a dumb faggot with zero understanding of scaling of distributed systems&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891730&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890488&lt;br&gt;I think XRP is.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891761&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890570&lt;br&gt;It just means the idea wasn&amp;#x27;t that good.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891885&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890488&lt;br&gt;It isn&amp;#x27;t. It was literally subverted by Epstein and co. who controlled a majority of its code build (like 75%) to make it unusable as money without scaling into shitty centralized L2s that are still uncompetitive and cost a fucking ton. It has zero use case or reason to exist next to others that are more actually decentralized and scale at L1 without the shitty centralized service end product it and eth try to drive us into. The CCP and JPM literally bought 95% of all eth at the ICO and tried to force us into L2 surveillance money hell.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891730&lt;br&gt;This.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891890&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890488&lt;br&gt;won&amp;#x27;t somebody please buy my vaporware?!?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891893&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891885&lt;br&gt;Big blocks were never going to solve scaling you retard. And blockstream getting 500k from a guy who got money from Epstein doesnt mean that Blockstream was able to brainwash every node operator to decline bigger blocks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891898&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890488&lt;br&gt;Even if it was widely usable, that wouldn&amp;#x27;t change its inherent value potential. If anything, it would undermine it because big swings in value make it less useful as a currency.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bitcoin has virtually zero inherent value. It is not unique. It is not backed by anything. It produces nothing and cannot be applied to anything other than its core capability.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As a method of transferring value from one place to another, it has a use. But even in that use, there&amp;#x27;s better and cheaper options.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The comparisons to gold (e.g. when it is referred to as &amp;#x27;digital gold&amp;#x27;) are farcical. Gold is gold. There&amp;#x27;s no other metal that is gold. You can&amp;#x27;t replicate gold efficiently. Gold has held a value in society and in markets for millennia.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bitcoin is easily replicable, by almost anyone. There&amp;#x27;s hundreds of other coins which do exactly the same thing, for a fraction of the cost. Moreover, it&amp;#x27;s original value proposition (namely its decentralised, anonymous nature) has been materially eroded in most parts of the world with regulation and government oversight; in my country, for example, if you want to trade it (i.e. use it) you need to identify yourself in some way or you&amp;#x27;re committing a crime. It&amp;#x27;s certainly more traceable than cash, and significantly less functional.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the future, Bitcoin will be an interesting oddity of the past. A relic. A curio. People will be amazed at the kind of value that some ascribed to something imaginary that was backed by nothing by excitement and a good story. Until that time, however, watching the madness in play is lots of fun.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891924&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890488&lt;br&gt;Nobody cares what satoshi made. BTC is better than Bitcoin could ever have been. Good luck changing the name.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891944&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890488&lt;br&gt;Im reminded of that retard who invented the Segway and thought entire cities would be designed around them. Bitcoin is the Segway of currency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891973&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890488&lt;br&gt;Monero is the true heir to the throne of digital cash.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891893&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;500k&lt;br&gt;The 500k isn&amp;#x27;t what did it. It&amp;#x27;s the fact that Epstein had video tape evidence of Adam Back (Satoshi) and other Blockstream executives fucking kids on his island.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Strange how Bitcoiners keep ignoring that part...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891977&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;how do retards not realize after 20 years that bitcoin was a tech demo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Is this biz approved? — 9 replies — 36.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890765</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890765?lm=1771874759</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 19:25:59 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Is this biz approved?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890765'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 9 • Updated: 2026-02-23 19:25 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;Making myself stand out in the freezing cold and pouring rain when I&amp;#x27;m too tired to study so I know how it feels to be homeless if I fail&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Should she instead play a violent pvp video game then take a nap to know how it feels to hurt evil people in a game and then be asleep for a really long time?&lt;br&gt;Should she instead message a random anonymous man through an encrypted messaging app and send him a couple hours worth of pics, videos and video calls doing whatever he requests of her so she knows how it feels to have an OF and be a camgirl?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890875&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890765&lt;br&gt;Women and social media were such a mistake, holy fucking shit why would anyone make a video like this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890903&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She should suck my dick behind a dumpster while I finger her asshole until I cum in her throat to know how it will feel to be a $20 street hooker when she NGMI&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890927&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890765&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;making myself listen to a woman talk for one entire minute when I&amp;#x27;m tired of looking at charts so I know how it feels to work for a female middle manager if I don&amp;#x27;t make it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890931&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890765&lt;br&gt;that particular approach seems retarded for sure.&lt;br&gt;but in general it&amp;#x27;s a good idea to think about what you want out of life, think about how you can reach it, and then simply work through that plan.&lt;br&gt;otherwise you end up aimlessly dicking around never really getting anywhere. look at how many cryptoshitters sat through their rise and peak all the way to the bottom again, because they didn&amp;#x27;t even have any clear goals for what target they want to hit.&lt;br&gt;it was always just &amp;quot;even more would be even nicer&amp;quot; and then &amp;quot;well, at least back to the prior ATH!&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890875&lt;br&gt;also this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890941&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890765&lt;br&gt;Being a woman in 2026 is so easy, simps will always elevate you, society revolves the legal system around you, and if all else fails you can do OnlyFans. The only requirement in life for a woman is not to be fat but even then there&amp;#x27;s a niche degenerate market for fat women.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891118&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890765&lt;br&gt;I knew it would be an indian.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891418&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891118&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891567&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891418&lt;br&gt;The Indian looks so masculine holy fuck&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892121&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891567&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;re 100% homosexual&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>PYPL merger edition 1 — 13 replies — 29.4/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891682</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891682?lm=1771873493</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 19:04:53 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;PYPL merger edition 1&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891682'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 13 • Updated: 2026-02-23 19:04 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here we go!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891698&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Do it Ryan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891737&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891682&lt;br&gt;who is going to be acquiring them?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891738&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;10 March.&lt;br&gt;Buy buy buy!!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891742&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891682&lt;br&gt;Ripple Labs will buy PayPal. Screen Cap this.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I hate the Antichrist and his Ashkenazi Servants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891750&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891737&lt;br&gt;Elon musk for X.&lt;br&gt;150 or 300$ x. Share&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891794&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891737&lt;br&gt;Possibly GME. Not kidding.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891797&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891737&lt;br&gt;chainlink&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;either that or big silver&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891827&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891794&lt;br&gt;41B ?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891975&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891827&lt;br&gt;Leveraged buyout, reverse triangular merger, etc.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>&gt;IF YOU BOUGHT 1 BITCOIN IN 2023 YOU WOULD HAVE 1 BITCOIN TODAY — 7 replies — 20.9/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891666</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891666?lm=1771873875</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 19:11:15 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;&amp;gt;IF YOU BOUGHT 1 BITCOIN IN 2023 YOU WOULD HAVE 1 BITCOIN TODAY&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891666'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 7 • Updated: 2026-02-23 19:11 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;IF YOU BOUGHT 1 BITCOIN IN 2023 YOU WOULD HAVE 1 BITCOIN TODAY&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891701&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;is mek me lol so hard&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891713&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;1 bitcoin in 2023 = 1 goygold in 2026&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891736&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891666&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;BTC 5Y +12.3%&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;VOO 5Y +76.6%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891751&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891736&lt;br&gt;Now do 6 years&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891782&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891751&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Zoom out&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;ZOOM OUT FURTHER&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;ZOOM OUT SPECIFICALLY TO A POINT IN TIME WHEN IT WASNT EMBARRASSING TO OWN BITSTEIN&lt;br&gt;I think the 5Y is plenty long enough Jeffy boy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891860&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891782&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;zooming in to specifically 5 years&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;don&amp;#x27;t zoom into 3, 6 or 4 years goy&lt;br&gt;Reminder it took decades for metalniggers to get the first 4x of their entire lives&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892031&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891666&lt;br&gt; If if true&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Wut Gud out of Pumped Dead Coins? — 7 replies — 18.8/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890886</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890886?lm=1771873743</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 19:09:03 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Wut Gud out of Pumped Dead Coins?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890886'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 7 • Updated: 2026-02-23 19:09 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;HBAR - seems to actually do something, though I am not sure what. Something about Lemon and all the crypto problems being solved - nobody uses it though. Least embarrassing price action on list&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALGO - tranny dump already happened, was leading DiFi platform and was pretty decent for dApps. Dead now that all of that is dead.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;ICP - muh Caffeine app builder and distributed compute. Only &amp;quot;real&amp;quot; token to do a 1/1000x (2k -&amp;gt; $2)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;LINK - honestly, I am not sure what LINK does, something about oracles and sending JSON objects&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;GOLD - more gooder if Iran bombed?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;XRP - I don&amp;#x27;t know what XRP does, is it like a replacement for USDC for replacing FedWire? Banks aren&amp;#x27;t ready to adopt it yet and still use USDC. Also not sure what it does.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;???&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Serious question though, which of these or similar can pump?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Also, if you want to tell me what they do, I would genuinely appreciate it. I only really understand ALGO and ICP.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890916&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890886&lt;br&gt;definitely not QNT&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890935&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890886&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;tfw no clussy&lt;br&gt;Also&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;LINK - honestly, I am not sure what LINK does, something about oracles and sending JSON objects&lt;br&gt;We&amp;#x27;re still so fucking early&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891060&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Banks are adopting Ripple atable coins. Not CRP. Although there is an option to ise On Demand Liquidity which replies on XRP. Obviously this is supplemental at best and can&amp;#x27;t supplant transferring actually USD available.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891937&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890886&lt;br&gt;Imo buying across any mix of the following will be solid longterm:&lt;br&gt;XRP, QNT, CC, XDC, ALGO (possibly dead, but in quantum age may shine for sake of superior tech), DAG, HBAR, XLM, SUI, SEI, APT, FLR, ONDO, NOM, ADA, HYPE, SOL, POL, ATOM, DAG, AAVE, DOT, VET, ZRO, RED, HYPE.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here is a pretty good rundown of the XRP use cases at present from specifically Ripple&amp;#x27;s operation perspective:&lt;br&gt;https://ripple.com/insights/institutional-defi-on-xrpl-scaling-real-world-finance-with-xrp-at-the-core/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891947&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891060&lt;br&gt;Ripple&amp;#x27;s whole strategy is (just like RLUSD launching on Eth and moving to XRPL) to meet the liquidity where it is and move it to the XRPL. Multiple banks already use XRP but many cannot until Clarity passes. XRPL optimizes using XRP and minted assets autobridge using it between different stable coin or minted asset issuances etc.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891961&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890935&lt;br&gt;Link doesn&amp;#x27;t do ANYTHING. It has ZERO utility and no one who invests in it even understands it, they just hear names that CLL has fireside chats with and presume this translates to token value despite it not doing so. The coin exists as a literally unnecessary rent seeker fee insertion. It doesn&amp;#x27;t solve efficiencies or have a basis for use, it is literally just specific jewry&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892018&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890886&lt;br&gt;A LUST PROVOKING VIDEO?!?!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;FUCK YEAH!!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Day 517 Of Bobo Rekt in Anus Posting Until BTC is at 180K — 5 replies — 13.6/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891862</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891862?lm=1771873760</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 19:09:20 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Day 517 Of Bobo Rekt in Anus Posting Until BTC is at 180K&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891862'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 5 • Updated: 2026-02-23 19:09 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891865&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891862&lt;br&gt;KILL YOURSELF YOU STOIPUD PIECE OF SHIUT&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891938&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891865&lt;br&gt;you sound nervous&lt;br&gt;it&amp;#x27;s going for a rally again&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891962&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891938&lt;br&gt;ITS GOING TO FUCKING ZEROoo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892012&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;funny this guy calls himself a statistician, kept calling the bottom from 90k to 80k to 76k back in feb and march 2025, said the july crabbing was bullish, thought we would start mooning in january, told you to sell gold for bitcoin saying it was topping out when it was in the 4000s while btc was bottomed in the 80-90k&amp;#x27;s, thought we would no longer have 50% drawdowns, supercycle hopium, this time is unironically different hopium, hash rate hopium, bayesian trend hopium etc&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892022&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61892012&lt;br&gt;you want him soooo bad&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Ai is about to crash the economy — 11 replies — 9.7/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889737</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889737?lm=1771870986</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 18:23:06 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Ai is about to crash the economy&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889737'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 11 • Updated: 2026-02-23 18:23 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was released today by citrini&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI gets good. Companies lay off workers. Margins expand. Stocks rip. S&amp;amp;P hits 8,000. Everyone celebrates.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;• But fired workers stop spending. Companies weaken. They buy more AI to cut costs. More layoffs. Less spending. A negative feedback loop with no natural brake.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;• The top 10% of earners drive 50%+ of all consumer spending. They&amp;#x27;re the ones getting replaced. A $180K product manager ends up driving Uber for $45K. Multiply that across every major city.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;• Ghost GDP emerges - the economy is &amp;quot;growing&amp;quot; on paper, but the money never reaches real people. Productivity is booming. Wages are collapsing.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;• Then it hits housing. $13 trillion in mortgages, all underwritten on one assumption: you keep your job for 30 years. In 2008, the loans were bad on day one. In 2028, the loans were good. The world just changed after they were written.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;• S&amp;amp;P crashes 38% from highs. Unemployment hits 10.2%. Markets barely react anymore.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;• The punchline: you&amp;#x27;re not reading this in 2028. You&amp;#x27;re reading it in February 2026. Every domino they describe has already started falling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889750&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WAOW! Link me to this guy&amp;#x27;s substack payment page immediately!!!!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889754&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There&amp;#x27;s over a billion jeets you can just keep vacuuming up the top 10% of them to always have an american middle class&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889766&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is this from that monotone Chinese guy on youtube&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889795&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889737&lt;br&gt;nigga, I am 400K deep into PLTR, you don&amp;#x27;t have to sell me on it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889802&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889737&lt;br&gt;the crazy part no ones even trying to stop it, what you are saying here isn&amp;#x27;t some major breakthrough its plainly obvious to anyone with a brain. another plainly obvious problem with a.i that most people are missing is that its not creative in the same way a person is, a.i cannot invent the airplane so you aren&amp;#x27;t just replacing a high value earner but someone that has tools that a.i doesn&amp;#x27;t have, intuition, creativity all things a.i cannot do and will never be able to do with any accuracy its a complete meme.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889812&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889737&lt;br&gt;None of that has happened, it&amp;#x27;s a fake cover story for the drunken spending companies did post covid. They hired way too many people for bullshit jobs and are now cutting back while saying it&amp;#x27;s because of AI.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rest of the shit is due to inflation, first from covid supply shocks, then companies trying to squeeze every last dollar they could out of the consumer and now trump tariffs. AI hasn&amp;#x27;t even begun to displace people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889814&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Melanin inclined individuals all in on ai are so screwed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889824&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889814&lt;br&gt;America fixed this problem already&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890898&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889750&lt;br&gt;This one is free https://www.citriniresearch.com/p/2028gic&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890971&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889802&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; you aren&amp;#x27;t just replacing a high value earner but someone that has tools that a.i doesn&amp;#x27;t have&lt;br&gt;They also take up 10x more energy heating their house&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891766&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just tax AI and automation and introduce UBI. Problem solved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>&gt;lost life savings of $250k on BTC calls at the top Im killing myself — 6 replies — 9.6/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891249</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891249?lm=1771872843</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 18:54:03 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;&amp;gt;lost life savings of $250k on BTC calls at the top Im killing myself&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891249'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 6 • Updated: 2026-02-23 18:54 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;lost life savings of $250k on BTC calls at the top&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Im killing myself&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891258&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891249&lt;br&gt;Are you leveraged? If no then you didn&amp;#x27;t lose a penny. If you do nothing, you win&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891265&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891249&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891273&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891258&lt;br&gt;Of course it was leveraged&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891311&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Variations of this are always said but it&amp;#x27;s worth repeating: you only fail when you give up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891317&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891249&lt;br&gt;Moron. Keep staying poor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891931&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891249&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;lost life savings of $250k&lt;br&gt;you were gonna die anyway&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>European funds for an american — 19 replies — 72.8/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890472</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890472?lm=1771874144</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 19:15:44 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;European funds for an american&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890472'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 19 • Updated: 2026-02-23 19:15 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;I want to put 20% of my account in foreign, but not all foreign is created equal. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I predicted the rise in the polish economy. It&amp;#x27;s very simple, a homogenous white country free from communism is always going to become rich. A diverse country full of communists like Canada and South Africa is going to get worse and worse. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I also predicted that the real-estate market in Croatia would sky rocket due to whites fleeing countries like the UK. I was right. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;So.... are there any good mutual/index funds that target the white regions of Europe, that an American can invest in? Is there a Balkans fund? A Baltic fund? Norway/Finland fund (not Sweden or Denmark)? I do not want to invest in the UK, France, Germany, or Spain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890485&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;finland&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;white&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890499&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;please buy my bag&lt;br&gt;nein. Death to every communist, that includes every single member of a political party, everyone over 50, every bureaucrat and every single subsidized &amp;quot;private&amp;quot; which in europe is every company.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890518&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No fucking way those numbers on finland are right. I live in Helsinki and it’s like 25% brown.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890524&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890472&lt;br&gt;You are correct about Poland but everybody knew and knows about Poland but nobody wants to talk about why they&amp;#x27;ve been the hottest economy in Europe for 15 years (white and Christian).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anyway. You&amp;#x27;ve never heard of EPOL?&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;ve owned the Polish index tracker ETFs for 8 years and it has done nicely.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Otherwise, Baltics do have stock markets but they are Frontier markets (this is below emerging markets) and you basically can&amp;#x27;t buy them if you&amp;#x27;re not in the country.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Norway invests in U.S. stocks. So does Sweden and their banks. Hottest Swedish bank stock is 100% invested in NYSE traded companies. So it&amp;#x27;s circular. If you invest in European banks or Norway you&amp;#x27;re actually buying U.S. stocks with extra steps. EPOL is heavily weighted towards Polish banks and you guessed it - they all hold U.S. company stocks.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;European Bank customers are just a source of capital to invest in the New York Stock Exchange. And I&amp;#x27;m an insider so I know.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you want an actual good EU based investment buy WDEF. European defense spending will be hot for 15 years. Otherwise buy Spotify and the upcoming revolut IPO.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890543&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890524&lt;br&gt;Any funds for manufacturing from the regions I mentioned in the OP, or medical services?&lt;br&gt;Medical services will always be the last to go even under socialism since Europeans will bankrupt their country with debt before they let a hospital go bankrupt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890855&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890543&lt;br&gt;You clearly don&amp;#x27;t understand the region. You&amp;#x27;re way out of your depth and element. I&amp;#x27;m sorry but it would take me hours to explain this to you.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;t. American in Latvia who knows Poland pretty well (dated a Polish chick and been there many times).&lt;br&gt;You assume Eastern Europe has the economic model of America or Germany, just poorer and white. You&amp;#x27;re way off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890868&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890472&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;France &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;85%&lt;br&gt;lmaoooo&lt;br&gt;this is the 1972 census?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890982&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890524&lt;br&gt;This map is from 10 or 15 years ago, it&amp;#x27;s actually changing rapidly now. Im from a small town and back then i haven&amp;#x27;t ever saw any foreign looking face apart from an occasional gypsy. Now we have filipino, indian, and central asian &amp;quot;guest&amp;quot; workers coming here to the middle of nowhere.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890989&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890868&lt;br&gt;France is pretty much 100% white outside of Paris and the south&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891003&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890989&lt;br&gt;not at all. Even the smallest, most remote villages are chokefull of shitskins. There isn&amp;#x27;t a single STREET in the countryside not populated with at least 2-3 shitskins/niggers.&lt;br&gt;I know becuz i live in one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891134&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890472&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;a homogenous white country free from communism&lt;br&gt;not Sweden&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891154&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890855&lt;br&gt;I have friends who moved to Croatia. Reason? White flight from the UK. Highly productive middle class white people pouring out of one area and into another, means good things for one economy and bad things for the other. It&amp;#x27;s no different than watching the small cities that surround Akron, Cleveland, Chicago, Detroit, Oakland, Baltimore, etc... All get richer and richer and have better and better economies due to all of the whites in those cities pouring out into the surrounding areas. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You say it&amp;#x27;s not that simple, yet I&amp;#x27;ve told people this will happen and for 30 years, I&amp;#x27;ve been right. I watched the real estate market in Croatia skyrocket into the stratosphere. I&amp;#x27;ve also made a lot of money on real-estate outside of Cleveland and Akron just by investing in the white flight destinations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891164&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890868&lt;br&gt;This is in fact, old data. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891134&lt;br&gt;Yes. That&amp;#x27;s why I said funds that invest in Norway and Finland, but not Denmark and Sweden. I know Finland isn&amp;#x27;t really Nordic but they&amp;#x27;re next door.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891236&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891154&lt;br&gt;That&amp;#x27;s fine but from the average person&amp;#x27;s perspective you can&amp;#x27;t understand the bigger economic picture and appreciate the vast differences in market size and capital flows.&lt;br&gt;Life for average people may be more or less similar in Croatia and England but the English stock exchange is in another universe compared to these small economies.&lt;br&gt;As I said, I&amp;#x27;m an American living in Latvia. My life is better in Latvia. I&amp;#x27;m just a normal guy. The top 1% and .01% would see things quite differently. Where does one park $100,000,000 in the Baltics?&lt;br&gt;Answer: you don&amp;#x27;t. And downstream from that is YOU don&amp;#x27;t get to invest $50,000 in an Estonia market ETF either. These are frontier markets not even as developed as Brazil or India.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891243&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891003&lt;br&gt;Euskadi&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891374&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891236&lt;br&gt;I think real-estate, and downstream from that medical services, are pretty simple by and large because they&amp;#x27;re mostly just a matter of predicting the migration patterns of middle class white people, while avoiding the political behavior of lumpenprole voters. At a bare minimum investing in medical services and realestate are a safe bet in any communist free white flight destination. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Question then becomes, what financial products are available to me that resemble that in any way. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;There&amp;#x27;s a fund called NHCBHFFT that invests in real estate in estonia, for example.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891396&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890472&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I do not want to invest in the UK&lt;br&gt;FTSE100 has been outperforming the S&amp;amp;P500 for a while now but okay&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891622&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891396&lt;br&gt;I want a stock that will perform well long term, the UK, like Canada and South Africa, has not future unless it claws it&amp;#x27;s way back from Weimar conditions. The massive white flight that has already taken place and has been accelerating, looks exactly how things looked for Detroit, Chicago, Oakland, Baltimore, etc... &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ghettofication is an economy killer. Because people ignore it and it makes people irrational, that is the area an investor can exploit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892062&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890472&lt;br&gt;Brown migration is stagnating across Europe and so is the birthrate of migrants of the 2nd/3rd generation. The number of migrants are not big enough to not be outbred in the long run.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>KASPA — 38 replies — 36.8/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61885700</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61885700?lm=1771871362</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 18:29:22 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;KASPA&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61885700'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 38 • Updated: 2026-02-23 18:29 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;were gonna be so rich when Kaspa kicks off this season, rolling dubs for prime Jewess pussy that I will purchase with a few dozen Kaspa&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885703&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885700&lt;br&gt;kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885758&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rolling for kaspa jewssy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885760&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885700&lt;br&gt;Scamcoin that does nothing&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886010&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;honestly i can live with that&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886492&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885766&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;fair launch no pre-mine&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;implying&lt;br&gt;I like KAS but the chain history is serious FUD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886517&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885700&lt;br&gt;Rolling for Yentapie&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886691&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roll&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887123&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61886492&lt;br&gt;This is debunked 2021 FUD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887138&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885700&lt;br&gt;6 7 maybe 0 if Im drunk&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887379&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885700&lt;br&gt;0&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887403&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885700&lt;br&gt;9&amp;gt;7 whatever&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887409&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885700&lt;br&gt;i would fuck 9&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887450&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The all look dysgenic and possibly inbred, what&amp;#x27;s wrong with them?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887454&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887450&lt;br&gt;They&amp;#x27;re all Jewish&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887455&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885700&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;when Kaspa kicks off this season&lt;br&gt;which is when exactly?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887465&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887455&lt;br&gt;When all of retail have been completely rinsed and sold their bags. This week or next week&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887589&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885700&lt;br&gt;roll&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887591&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887589&lt;br&gt;LUCKYYY!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887799&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887123&lt;br&gt;Not according to Yonotan, who&amp;#x27;s answer is&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Kaspa full nodes verify only recent history, because the goal of Consensus is to reach Agreement, not to print a medal of historical aesthetic integrity that satisfies the aesthetic tastes of cryptographers with no tangible integrity value to speak of.&lt;br&gt;TL;DR stop noticing&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887812&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887799&lt;br&gt;So who got 52% and reorganised blocks then? Which wallets?&lt;br&gt;Dumb fag&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;TL;DR: block chains are vulnerable to 51% attacks Jeetish FUD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887838&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887812&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;why worry about something that isn&amp;#x27;t going to happen?&lt;br&gt;Fact is, there is no full chain history and the implications of that are still unknown. Maybe it&amp;#x27;s nothing, maybe it&amp;#x27;s going to be devastating in the future. We just don&amp;#x27;t know&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887853&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Honestly I like this shit. And I made money on it last year buying in hard at 5 cents and holding until 12 cents. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The tech is good - it’s magic to watch hard wallet confirmations happen instantly. The chart still looks painful though, but I’m actively considering starting to acquire again. It’s a spiffy first party wallet to be honest. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Any word on level 2 shit?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887873&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887799&lt;br&gt;Yonatan here, this is misleading.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kaspa supports archival nodes and pruned nodes. Bitcoin, Ethereum and most modern Blockchain also prune.&lt;br&gt;So this is not unique to Kaspa.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The most important distinction you need to realise is that pruning old block data does NOT mean skipping consensus verification. Nodes still validate consensus, enforce rules and track UTXO state. They just don&amp;#x27;t keep every ancient block at once.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887902&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887873&lt;br&gt;As we&amp;#x27;ve established, Mr Sompolinsky, it&amp;#x27;s not that the old blocks weren&amp;#x27;t kept; they were lost. And a great deal of work has been done to recover what has been lost, but not all of it has been recovered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888092&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If anyone of you are lurking, it’s quite clear /biz/ is JIDF headquarters. They think their jewish humor doesn’t glow. Death to Judaism and all of its followers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888189&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What do you guys think about Xelis?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888282&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885700&lt;br&gt;7 and maybe 0 if she’s a squirter&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888292&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885700&lt;br&gt;Rolan&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888770&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885700&lt;br&gt;9 is the only one I&amp;#x27;d have sex with.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889128&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885700&lt;br&gt;7 and 9, that&amp;#x27;s it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891242&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885700&lt;br&gt;shalom goyim&lt;br&gt;roll for 7,0 and dubs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891402&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885700&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;ll take anything at this point...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891815&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885700&lt;br&gt;DUBS JEWESS&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Financial independence / retire early — 38 replies — 24.2/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61884958</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61884958?lm=1771869427</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 17:57:07 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Financial independence / retire early&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61884958'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 38 • Updated: 2026-02-23 17:57 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;How&amp;#x27;s FIRE going for you, anons?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884964&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884958&lt;br&gt;Well I&amp;#x27;m looking into LCOL countries I can retire to because waiting until I&amp;#x27;m a multi millionaire in the states is not viable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884966&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884958&lt;br&gt;Just need a 7x then I&amp;#x27;m good. Already have rope if ready if I don&amp;#x27;t reach the goal in 5 years&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884967&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884958&lt;br&gt;i have about 3m networth but haven&amp;#x27;t quit my job yet. making too much money but want to quit real bad. i took a 4 day weekend recently and got bored because i have no life and hobbies because my job dominates my life and i have no energy left over to develop my personal life after work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884986&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884958&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m just living off NEETbux+savings. It doesn&amp;#x27;t completely cover rent, so once my savings are gone I&amp;#x27;m going to just KYS myself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884996&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884974&lt;br&gt;Interesting. I never thought of Japan as having a low cost of living. And I&amp;#x27;ve heard Thailand is not as cheap as it was.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884999&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884976&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884986&lt;br&gt;I listened to a Grant Cardone video on YouTube about pulling IRA retirement money into self-directed fund then you can use it to buy real estate without getting the penalty but you have to go big and do multi-dwelling unit or else IRS flags you. I&amp;#x27;m too chicken shit to try it (yet) but if you&amp;#x27;re going to an hero anyway fuck it try it&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;pull life retirement savings&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;buy 10 unit apartment building&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;give self job fixing toilets&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;collect rent from tenants &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;profit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885003&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ok maybe a 3 unit building&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885030&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884999&lt;br&gt;You literally cannot fix the toilets yourself. Under IRC §4975 you are considered a &amp;quot;disqualified&amp;quot; person. Basically you can own it but you can never touch it. Very gay way to &amp;#x27;own&amp;#x27; something.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885054&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;way ahead of schedule.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Full time job income (104K + 11K in retirement)&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Cost of living 32K&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Fully owned apartment(450K)&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;308K in liquidish assets&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;90K in retirement&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;2K coming in every month from passive revenue from a side business (vidya gaems)&lt;br&gt;In 7-8 years i will probably reach full FIRE. But i&amp;#x27;m releasing new products this year. If i can have similar success i will probably just Barista FIRE living the gamedev dream.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885059&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884967&lt;br&gt;Dude, just quit. You&amp;#x27;ll probably decompress after a month or two, then you can re-evaluate. If you decide you need to work, then you can just go apply to some jobs. Maybe you&amp;#x27;ll decide you want to work in a library or something stupid like that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885062&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885030&lt;br&gt;that fucking sucks what is Cardone talking about then?&lt;br&gt;retirement money is just going to the bank then when I starve to death. maybe that was their plan all along. &lt;br&gt;take the 10% penalty + taxes ? now it&amp;#x27;s a duplex maybe in a cold flyover state&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885102&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just had my 2nd kid.&lt;br&gt;Already gave up and accepted that I&amp;#x27;ll be waging til I die.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885131&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884958&lt;br&gt;Pretty good despite the recent market drawdown. I stopped working 9 months ago and moved to a luxury condo in Thailand. Expenses are relatively low but I&amp;#x27;m still paying my mortgage and car note in America. I get a little bit of income from trading options and renting out my house to my younger sister. I&amp;#x27;m financially set for the rest of my life but I&amp;#x27;m still figuring out what I want to do as far as family, kids, etc.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885135&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885062&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885030&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884986&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;ok I found this. instead of self directed IRA to have to roll it into a business startup&lt;br&gt;so don&amp;#x27;t an hero yet &lt;br&gt;or put me down as your beneficiary first&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;https://www.bankrate.com/loans/small-business/what-are-robs/#:~:text=Key%20takeaways,penalties%20are%20associated%20with%20ROBS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885141&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884967&lt;br&gt;Nigger. Based on the 4% rule you can draw about 120k yearly off investments and statistically never run out of money. Wife and I retired early w/ Lite Fire. No debt. Last year our gross income was $55,000. We bought and sold a RV, Saw the Grand Canyon, Zion, Bryce Canyon, Rushmore. Took a 21 day cruise from west coast through Panama Canal, Cruised out of Florida for 3 weeks and hung out in Fort Lauderdale for 2. Did 2 more week in the Caribbean. Have a 20 day transatlantic cruise from NYC to Sicily booked with stops in 9 ports in April. Tons of midweek short trips seeing cool shit. Leaving work is an adjustment definitely but I have never been happier. See the world, meet people, always with an eye to relocation. Picrel is heading into Cartagena Columbia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885152&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884967&lt;br&gt;I was just like you before I decided to walk away. I call it &amp;quot;golden handcuffs&amp;quot; when a job pays so well that it makes you feel obligated to keep going even though you don&amp;#x27;t need the money. Your job feels like your identity but I promise you&amp;#x27;ll forget about it after you quit and find new hobbies and a gf.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887260&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884974&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884996&lt;br&gt;Japan is not a lcol area. Its cheaper compared to the west but not Thailand/Vietnam cheap. My plan is to live 90 days visa free there a year and live frugally elsewhere for the rest of the year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887270&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884958&lt;br&gt;Closing in on luxury fat FIRE thanks to gold/silver/oil/uranium. Fuck crypto.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887292&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t want to retire early, cuz id probably just be doing the same thing without getting paid for it, but i have enough money to be comfortable for now&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887302&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I am starting to realize the whole game plan of FIRE is just giving me reason to wake up in the morning, something to look forward to. I dont think I will really be that much happier once I achieve my dream of semi financial freedom.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887313&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887292&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;id probably just be doing the same thing without getting paid for it&lt;br&gt;Your job is your hobby? Congrats. What do you do?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887338&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s not really going.&lt;br&gt;Would take me getting my inheritance and buying the bottom of the next global market crash and riding the recovery wave with everything I can throw in during it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887601&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;uhh im 38. been retired since 32. probably unretiring soon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887625&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887313&lt;br&gt;gay prostitute&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890044&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887302&lt;br&gt;frugality is like a game, to see how little i can spend each month&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890071&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885054&lt;br&gt;what&amp;#x27;s your side business anon? reseller?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890085&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;is 1.5M too little to retire?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I round tripped 8 figs being greedy&lt;br&gt;its all i have left&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890089&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890085&lt;br&gt;depends where you live&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890151&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885102&lt;br&gt;My #2 is 4 months old now. Thanks to the fire-induced frugality I was able to reduce my hours for half a year by 10 hours a week which was priceless in itself. Will probably also wage forever but probably only 20 hours or so per week.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884958&lt;br&gt;We managed to pay off the house @32. other than that I only have 15k cash and 50k in the MSCI. &lt;br&gt;The plan was to retire @40 but unrealistic unless I win the lottery ( and I don&amp;#x27;t even play)&lt;br&gt;So yes full fire is impossible right now, but on the plus side: we need less than 2k/ month for a very comfortable life. &lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m converting a part of the house to a rental flat atm which should bring another 600 per month and allow for tax deductions.&lt;br&gt;After installing solar this year my electricity bill should drop from 110 to 40 per month. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;So all in all we can have a cozy lifestyle for an acceptable trade off in lifetime. &lt;br&gt;Wife would like to work 20 hours/week in 10 years or so, I should be able to fully switch to do freelance consultant work in my niche ( or not. Her meager wage combined with the surplus of the next 10 years should easily pay for everything and give the kids a nice tailwind) &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m putting 180 bucks/month per kind into an ETF which should become a nice 150k downpayment (infl.adj.) when they turn 27&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890181&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Never gonna happen on my income. Millennials are fucked out of retirement. At least I own all my shit and have actual children and a loyal wife.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890213&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I dont know what number to stop at..&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891226&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884968&lt;br&gt;Balkan and Baltic countries are cheap and super white. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fuck off if you&amp;#x27;re not white though. They&amp;#x27;re the most racist countries and that&amp;#x27;s what makes them awesome.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891591&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885054&lt;br&gt;What games?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>&gt;FIRE &gt;saving &gt;"options are gambling" &gt;savings account` &gt;HYSA &gt;properties &gt;real estate &gt;bonds &gt;dividend ETFs &gt;"branching… — 6 replies — 24.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891613</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891613?lm=1771875064</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 19:31:04 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;&amp;gt;FIRE &amp;gt;saving &amp;gt;&amp;quot;options are gambling&amp;quot; &amp;gt;savings account` &amp;gt;HYSA &amp;gt;properties &amp;gt;real estate &amp;gt;bonds &amp;gt;dividend ETFs &amp;gt;&amp;quot;branching…&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891613'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 6 • Updated: 2026-02-23 19:31 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;FIRE&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;saving&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;options are gambling&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;savings account`&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;HYSA&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;properties&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;real estate&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;bonds&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;dividend ETFs&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;branching out into other sectors&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;diversification&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Europe&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;The AI bubble&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;mortgage&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891626&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;So true oomfie&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891629&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;sucking cock&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891650&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891613&lt;br&gt;fuck i forgot a few obvious ones&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;stop loss&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;trailing stop loss&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;stop gain&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;time in the market beats timing the market&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891658&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891650&lt;br&gt;Ehhhmmmm last one&amp;#x27;s right doe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891672&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891613&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;K-shaped economy &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Immigration is good for the economy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61892142&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reddits advice is better and it&amp;#x27;s not even close. This board shilled rugpull shitcoins daily. Reddit preached sound investment strategies that made countless folks wealthy. You are a faggot pink wojaks farmer. kys&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>