<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>/biz/ Active (filtered, with replies)</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/</link><description>Filtered out: general, gme, bbbyq. OP + first 3 replies + last 30 replies.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:50:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>When did you realize that you were NOT going to make it? — 122 replies — 488.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61862922</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61862922?lm=1771508179</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:36:19 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;When did you realize that you were NOT going to make it?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61862922'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 122 • Updated: 2026-02-19 13:36 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862935&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;is he ok&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862944&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862935&lt;br&gt;just some minor scratches (on his brain)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862956&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;the funniest part is that you think &amp;quot;maybe he survived the crash, just barely&amp;quot; but then it erupts in flames and he&amp;#x27;s cooked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869355&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863411&lt;br&gt;He was hothead enough to ride at those speeds, but not enough to do a last second evading maneuver. &lt;br&gt;In the end he acted like a normie, which is brake when things to wrong. Which works most of the time, but in a CAR.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869395&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863410&lt;br&gt;Stop posting those image all the time fagit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869422&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;drives in the emergency lane&lt;br&gt;bikenigger got what he deserved&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869527&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863253&lt;br&gt;Fucking hate people that turn like that. Like any sense of g-forces at all is completely unacceptable to feel. FUCKING GO!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869586&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;When did you realize that you were NOT going to make it?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Define &amp;quot;Make it&amp;quot;.&lt;br&gt;Good wife, one son, over a million in my Roth IRA... did I &amp;#x27;make it&amp;#x27;?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869920&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868013&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;uhh source? What&amp;#x27;s the heckin email timestamp?&lt;br&gt;Lel&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869926&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Friendly reminder motorbikes have like 100x the fatality rate of cars, given enough time you&amp;#x27;re basically guaranteed to have a serious accident with one&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869948&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most don’t&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869998&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863529&lt;br&gt;Because they have less defining human qualities. Have you ever met an Asian with empathy or altruism? I just don’t think their brains are capable of much so we see them as something less. There’s a reason why the Asians have no soul joke seems to stick. I don’t know maybe some Asian American can explain it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870027&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;The subconscious will to die, the death drive is always present to varying degrees. It battles with the will to live. There is nothing inherently wrong with death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870172&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869948&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;doom posting with lar dee dar prose.&lt;br&gt;Just doesn&amp;#x27;t bring me happiness m8.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870204&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863182 &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922 &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;This guy was going 2x the speed limit on the shoulder. 100% deserved.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869926&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Friendly reminder&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; motorbikes have 100x the fatality rate of cars, given enough time you&amp;#x27;re basically guaranteed to have a serious accident with one&lt;br&gt;This. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;He should have realized when he bought a bike. &lt;br&gt;Then decided to go 2x speed limit on a shoulder .&lt;br&gt;This is a very common scenario, someone is turning right into a parking lot, without seeing some retard doing 2x on a shoulder lane. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Actually know a person who survived this one. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;his bike had a bigger engine , he flew OVER a car&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870288&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868079&lt;br&gt;ID probably changed because mac addr recycle, but I appreciate the effort post anon&lt;br&gt;While the bad faith posters will inevitably harvest some portion of loosh from me, as I still retain my (admittedly damaged) spirit, my comments are not necessarily for direct reply: they are also for those passive scrollers and anons who have visited this site for years and never typed a single reply or started a single thread. The silent lurkers, for which any morsel of knowledge may enlighten or ease their spiritual burden by a miniscule amount, is to whom I make these comments hidden far away from the mass of crowds who trample all over fragile truth for vulgar and banal platitudes. Godspeed, anon. We will meet again for certain, but will never know it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871361&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;He was really dry&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871366&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863411&lt;br&gt;He went around &amp;quot;up&amp;quot; and smashed into the ground&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871371&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862956&lt;br&gt;LITERALLY ME&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871626&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;After seeing the dutch new tax law&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871728&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862956&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871737&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;upon being born a goy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871780&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;agonizingly slow turn&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;no turn signal&lt;br&gt;You guys ever notice it&amp;#x27;s always big expensive SUVs that do this shit? How do the most expensive vehicles have the worst drivers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871805&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What is it about motorcycles that inspire so much seethe? Is it because 4chuds are high inhib pussy incels?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871884&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The thing is in 2014, 2017, 2021 you could take 10,000 bucks and buy basically anything and a 10x was guaranteed.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I remember taking 2021 for granted lol.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 2024 bull run saw an initial pump from alts from january to april and then htey just bled from april to september, then bled again from december to may, and from may 2025 to present the bulk of alts bled out.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I remember seeing microstrategy and I was like &amp;quot;gonna buy that when bitcoin goes back to 50k&amp;quot;. Then I saw MSTX. Hell yeah, double your money for each MSTR move, and MSTR was double bitcoin. A run to 100k from 50k would be an easy 8x. And it was. But I sold before the election and fumbled it. The fumbler. It&amp;#x27;s easy to create a perfect plan in your mind, and watch it play out exactly as you said it would, but it takes a lot of conviction to not fuck it up.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now most markets are way up. 2026, 2022, 2018, midterm years have slow market growth. The time to buy it was 2023, the time to make it was 2024, the time to swap into alts like KTA and HYPE and AVANTIS was 2025. I called everything correctly but fucked up the one thing that mattered- buying, and holding to a 10x.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871888&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871780&lt;br&gt;Boomers love driving big SUVs for some reason. Makes them &amp;quot;feel safe&amp;quot; or some shit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872189&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863529&lt;br&gt;Bug people, soulless&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872848&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863529&lt;br&gt;Because they are literally lower quality organisms. Same reason no one gives a fuck when you kill a fly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873614&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863924&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I would just like to know if all that crap about satan, moloch worship, demons, etc., it&amp;#x27;s just like a game because they simply like to eat and torture babies or do those entities really exist.&lt;br&gt;Nah but they believe in it. Very powerful people ironically fear death a lot so they somehow believe this can save them from dying.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873616&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864738&lt;br&gt;They fear China the most clearly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873938&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863529&lt;br&gt;What a dumb retard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873940&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868075&lt;br&gt;This was denied by China.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873942&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;He could have make it if he had better control of his brakes, I think he&amp;#x27;s one of these riders who only use the front brake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>why would anyone live here — 38 replies — 98.6/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61872797</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61872797?lm=1771507616</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:26:56 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;why would anyone live here&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61872797'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 38 • Updated: 2026-02-19 13:26 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;i recently moved to NYC to work for a &amp;quot;lucrative salary&amp;quot; (not really, because this place drains you of all your income) and after working here for 4 months i dont know why anyone would willingly live here&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;the entire city smells like rotting shit, cigarette buds and dead animals, not a faint smell, an extremely strong odor that you&amp;#x27;ll eventually just become nose blind to&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;homeless people, fucking everywhere, when i left my apartment there were homeless people sleeping in the hallways of my complex, when you go on walk there are homeless people sleeping on the sidewalk with a PILLOW and BLANKET while regular people walk over them like this is just some normal fucking occurrence (and in this shithole it is) never ever have i seen some shit like this even in the worst of cities ive lived in.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;heroin needles, weed bags, cigarette buds &amp;amp; the occasional dildo just scattered across the city sidewalks, your constantly walking over human shit, broken bottles or dime bags&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;rats and rodents EVERYWHERE. il never forget the time i bought a pizza from one of the disgusting street vendors and when i sat down at a table one of the rats were circling my feet trying to climb my leg for a bite.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;the &amp;quot;public transport&amp;quot; system is a just permanent housing for the mentally ill, every time i had to ride the subway i was scared for my life because of all the fucking looneys that inhabit the train systems&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;this is just off the top of my head, but i think the biggest mindfuck of it all is that its EXPENSIVE to live here its gonna cost you not 50k, not 100k, not 200k, to live comfortably by yourself you need 250K yearly in manhattan. 250k, to live among violent homeless people, 250k to constantly have to walk in rotting shit and roadkill. 250k to have your ears blown out by car horns &amp;amp; niggerbabble, 250k to be forced to smell the most putried scents imaginable i dont know why anyone sane would live here, this place is some sort of social experiment, some sort of anonmoly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872828&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872797&lt;br&gt;Go back to your trailer park, pussy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872853&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872797&lt;br&gt;You know the phrase &amp;quot;If you can make it in New York you can make it anywhere&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;re not making it. You&amp;#x27;re a small fish in the biggest fucking pond.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you were making it you wouldn&amp;#x27;t deal with ANY of this shit&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Oh my heck the freakin homeless have PILLOWS and BLANKETS &lt;br&gt;Literally who gives a single actual fuck&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872859&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872828&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872853&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;getting AIDS from stepping on a needle is just part of the HUSTLE AND BUSTLE&lt;br&gt;citycels are pathetic&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872905&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872797&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;ve never been to NYC, none of that is true. Funny how every loser who never leaves his house is afraid of a city where children and seniors walk around freely. &amp;quot;Oh no it&amp;#x27;s like Mad Max&amp;quot; I can&amp;#x27;t imagine being this cowardly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872917&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872797&lt;br&gt;I have never been to the usa but i imagine NYC as one of the worst places to live in on earth. The ultimate city slave place.The furthest removed from nature you can get. We are supposed to live in a forest/glade.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872920&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872905&lt;br&gt;Nice strawmans&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872923&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872920&lt;br&gt;The OP is a strawman you blind zealot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872924&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872797&lt;br&gt;It’s cigarette butts you fucking zoomer. And yes NYC is a shit hole. So it’s all of upstate. All the smart New Yorkers go to Florida.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872926&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872897&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;https://www.google.com/maps/@23.0326111,113.1114167,3a,42.5y,326.24h,44.19t&lt;br&gt;Kek btw not opening your trackers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872929&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;ve been to a few Giants games. NYC is an absolute shithole. I&amp;#x27;m sure there are some nice neighborhoods, but you are deeply brainwashed if you think NYC is a nice city. Literally every major city in Japan is nicer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872933&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872923&lt;br&gt;No you used strawman arguments. Nobody is afraid of walking there. We dont want to its that simple.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872934&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872797&lt;br&gt;Beautiful women outnumber eligible men.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Good luck marrying a hambeast with no education or life goals in some rural town.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872937&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872797&lt;br&gt;Record it hiding your phone because we won&amp;#x27;t believe it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872939&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872797&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;heroin needles, weed bags, cigarette buds &amp;amp; the occasional dildo just scattered across the city sidewalks, your constantly walking over human shit, broken bottles or dime bags&lt;br&gt;Ha! You should have seen it when it was actually bad, back in the 1970s!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The movie &amp;quot;Death Wish&amp;quot; had to sanitize it a lot to be presentable on a movie screen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872950&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872859&lt;br&gt;Actually, AIDS dies on contact with oxygen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872952&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872950&lt;br&gt;I see millions of leftists and niggers running around breathing so that&amp;#x27;s a flat out lie&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872963&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872933&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872933&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Nobody is afraid of walking there&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872797&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;every time i had to ride the subway i was scared for my life&lt;br&gt;If you&amp;#x27;re going to lie don&amp;#x27;t reply to my posts pussy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872967&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872934&lt;br&gt;None of those women are interested in settling down. They’re chasing the sex and the city meme. NYC is famous for its shit dating scene.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872990&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872797&lt;br&gt;Which neighborhood do you live in? I&amp;#x27;m in Williamsburg. That said, yeah, NYC is a shithole. I&amp;#x27;ve lived in DC and Miami, and both those cities are much cleaner and aesthetic than here. I could put up with the dirtiness and homelessness if it weren&amp;#x27;t fucking cold and dark here for 5 months out of the year. It&amp;#x27;s depressing. I moved to NYC for a work opportunity and career advancement. But now I&amp;#x27;m trying to pivot industries and get into banking, but no luck so far. I&amp;#x27;ll probably stay here 4-5 years total tops.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873003&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872797&lt;br&gt;You don’t love the hustle and bustle of the big city enough clearly&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873017&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872797&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;wagie realizes NYC is for rich people&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A tale old as time&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873022&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One time i was in NYC and I saw an indian cab driver empty his piss bottle out in the street from his cab. Can confirm there&amp;#x27;s lots of trash and there&amp;#x27;s a piss smell. Have you considered Boston OP?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873024&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I was in NYC for like two hours and will never return &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Homeless people literally fucking everywhere &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Niggers drinking and smoking crack on the street &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Needles everywhere &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Had to step off the sidewalk because some spic auto shop had cars parked all over the sidewalk &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Almost got crashed into three times &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Had to pay $30 in tolls or some other ridiculous number just to drive in and out &lt;br&gt;If you can work remotely but need NY tax residency just move somewhere else in the state. Not Rochester though, it&amp;#x27;s just as much of a hellhole, just smaller&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873067&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872863&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;i was paying over 150k &lt;br&gt;You mean making? &lt;br&gt;Or did you mean you were paying $12,500 per month? &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you were only making 150k then I&amp;#x27;m completely unsurprised you felt like a bitter poorfag in NYC. I make that much in a medium/low cost city in the Midwest and feel like I could use a lot more.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you moved there for a career and only made that much then yeah I think you weren&amp;#x27;t anywhere close to making an optimal move.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;All I&amp;#x27;m saying is you&amp;#x27;re a.) soft as fuck and b.) not nearly as intelligent or valuable as you think you are&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873699&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872797&lt;br&gt;so? its jew york, its there to someone to nuke it.....&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873706&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872797&lt;br&gt;OP can&amp;#x27;t handle the hustle and bustle of NYC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873716&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872797&lt;br&gt;i heard there are more dating age women than men in nyc. so might be good if you&amp;#x27;re looking to SUCKNFUCK.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873754&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873067&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;All I&amp;#x27;m saying is you&amp;#x27;re a.) soft as fuck and b.) not nearly as intelligent or valuable as you think you are&lt;br&gt;Go live there pussy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873892&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873754&lt;br&gt;fun fact &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873067 doesnt realize the inverse of &amp;quot;if you can make it in nyc you can make it anywhere&amp;quot; is the actual truth. there are people that cannot make it out of nyc. there is a huge swaths of the country where the only employer is dollar general paying $1-2/hr above minimum wage. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;any retard can come to nyc and get a six figure job, and if they dont aspire to ever own property or live in a super trendy/high end part of the city they&amp;#x27;ll be fine. meanwhile if they stayed in florida or ohio or even suburban connecticut they probably would&amp;#x27;ve been stuck working retail or at best making $60,000 a year in a place where meals still cost $14-20 and gas is still $3 a gallon and his rent is still retarded high like $1800-2400/mo because nyc/la/boston set rental pricing for the rest of the country&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873895&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;ve been to NYC and none of that happened to me howeverbeit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873906&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872797&lt;br&gt;Heh sounds exactly like my experience as an euro whi visited the city two years ago. I got assaulted by some young negress 15 minutes after i had arrived in the city, two blocks from the times square. The whole place was worse than Brasil and indeed full of homeless and untreated schizophrenics. Felt like third world to an european like me. Really showed how much USA has decayed when it’s normal for them to live in dangerous third world cities like this. Paris was literal heaven compared to it. Everything was clean, almost zero homeless, immigrants were working the shit jobs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873913&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873895&lt;br&gt;the streets are pretty disgusting after a month of frozen snow finally melting im excited for the rain tomorrow &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873906&lt;br&gt;times square is a shithole thoughever&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;its like me saying all of france is marseilles&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873926&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873892&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;or at best making $60,000 a year in a place where meals still cost $14-20 and gas is still $3 a gallon and his rent is still retarded high like $1800-2400/mo because nyc/la/boston set rental pricing for the rest of the country&lt;br&gt;Fucking trvke. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I live in Ohio making ~62k a year gross and gas prices are $2.90-$4.00 depending on the octane level you need, a meal is $25, a drink at a bar is $15, and rent in the ghetto is $1000-1200 for a studio, or $1500+ if you don&amp;#x27;t want to get shot. On top of that my health insurance is $200 a month, my car insurance is $100 a month, and there are a million other expenses that don&amp;#x27;t get cheaper because I live here.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moving to a major west or east coast city would cost me MAYBE $1500 a month in additional expenses, but I would make that all back in increased salary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Is it really that much more difficult to start a business in the eu than us? — 76 replies — 85.5/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860796</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860796?lm=1771505805</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:56:45 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Is it really that much more difficult to start a business in the eu than us?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860796'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 76 • Updated: 2026-02-19 12:56 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;You guys in the EU make less than us on paychecks, but you get to keep more of your money because you have universal healthcare and PTO while we have to pay for private insurance which chronically denies people&amp;#x27;s health situations. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Are people saying that starting a business in the EU is difficult because of the regulations? What regulations does the European union impose on its citizen&amp;#x27;s than they think it&amp;#x27;s easier to start in the United States instead?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860815&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;Depends enormously on which country are we talking about. Some are easy (Germany) some are very hard (Italy)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860817&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; you get to keep more of your money because you have universal healthcare&lt;br&gt;yeah right&lt;br&gt;good luck getting that &amp;quot;universal healthcare&amp;quot; if you&amp;#x27;re not a boomer, waiting lists are years for even a basic exam/procedure. It&amp;#x27;s either you go private (and pay out of your own pocket) or you die&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; and PTO&lt;br&gt;oh wow, 20 wagie cagie free days a year. Totally worth the 60%+ taxes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;All taxation is theft. It&amp;#x27;s just that. Taxation doesn&amp;#x27;t pay for services. It&amp;#x27;s just the way they control the economy, and here in EU they fucking LOVE to control what you can and cannot do. They print the money, they don&amp;#x27;t need to tax you. They tax you to control you (and to humiliate you)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860822&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;The healthcare thing is too much american leftie argument, it also has been very overcrowded by you guessed arabs and africans, unironically I was better treated when I broke my leg in brazil of all places then in france&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870191&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870164&lt;br&gt;did you read anything of what i said there and ignored it or are you just retarded?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Just don&amp;#x27;t collect data for commercial purposes&lt;br&gt;as a user, having to click on shit on every website for gdpr is annoying&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;It does but not allowing certain monetization strategies of the data, informing you about how, which and why what points of data are used and giving the EU a mechanism to fight against, mostly foreign, companies violating your privacy.&lt;br&gt;yeah you definitely are retarded. which part of &amp;quot;it does not protect my data&amp;quot; did you not understand?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870199&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;starting a business is very easy on both sides of the atlantic. scaling is harder in the EU because it&amp;#x27;s a fragmented market with wildly different rulesets between member states and capital markets&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870203&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870191&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;as a user, having to click on shit on every website for gdpr is annoying&lt;br&gt;Oh the horror! Let me guess, in most cases you just have to click &amp;#x27;disable all&amp;#x27; and &amp;#x27;save&amp;#x27; right? Here&amp;#x27;s a pro-tip to save you the time: Block the domain or script they use for their cookie banners&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;which part of &amp;quot;it does not protect my data&amp;quot; did you not understand?&lt;br&gt;The part where you lied.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870682&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870203&lt;br&gt;ah, i see, you are retarded. just because some laws that are lax exist doesn&amp;#x27;t mean data is protected, you fucking retarded faggot&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870744&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870065&lt;br&gt;it started long before post-WW2 tho, germs bureaucracymaxxed post-reunification during the 2nd Reich, from 1871 onward.&lt;br&gt;At first it was to keep in check all the landers trying to take the lion&amp;#x27;s share of federal credits and centralize power. And it worked gud, but then it progressively became the hellscape kafkaian machine we all know.&lt;br&gt;That&amp;#x27;s how you know the hallofcost never happened, becuz you can be sure nazis would have made endless paperworks addressing the situation, down to the very last jewish pubic hair, but we didn&amp;#x27;t find any document.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870778&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stop eating the commie propaganda. Europeans don&amp;#x27;t have savings for shit, they just have stable expenses but all their wealth is tied to inheriting homes. That&amp;#x27;s why homes are basically untaxed while stocks are treated like financial Nazism. You aren&amp;#x27;t going to spend more a healthy young person in the US, the real benefit of Europe is the private healthcare is very cheap and good &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Starting businesses in Europe sucks because of two factors. The first is low liquidity and consumer spending: unlike the US, people don&amp;#x27;t spend nearly as much, have as much to spend, or make debt. So there isn&amp;#x27;t much room for anyone to buy something new - successful businesses target liquid tourists or B2B, where they write off the huge taxes as expenses. Over regulated financial market also leads to lower liquidity and more difficulty getting loans and investors, you rely on government programs run by middle aged menopausal cunts that have never worked more than 28 hours a week &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other issue is labor laws and public perception. It&amp;#x27;s morally bankrupt to try and get more money, why aren&amp;#x27;t you happy being average, why are you trying to pull ahead. Anyone you hire can&amp;#x27;t be fired, you can&amp;#x27;t have low compensation with offset packages to get high skill labor, you need to suck some blue blooded cock to get money and not wait years for whatever permits you&amp;#x27;ll need, because they were born out of nobility and still have half the money and connections &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eurotards freak out about Epstein but every European politician and rich person rapes babies for breakfast. It&amp;#x27;s just 1) not pedo to them if they&amp;#x27;re over 14 bc muh age of consent and 2) they hide in the shadows unlike Americans, they try to be as unnoticed as possible, give a few concessions to the poor and continue ruling sucking and fucking like they&amp;#x27;ve been doing the past thousand years&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870889&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870103&lt;br&gt;What are the reforms that boomers are blocking?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870915&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869942&lt;br&gt;Yeah i feel the same. Sex, drugs and love are already the ultimate sensations and none of them are expensive. All luxuries are pretty worthless add-ons and don’t feel special. You just have a bigger bed, or a bigger car, not anything you really need.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870937&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860817&lt;br&gt;That&amp;#x27;s complete bullshit, stop making up fantasies in your mind. If there is ONE thing still somewhat running smoothly in western Europe, it&amp;#x27;s free healthcare.&lt;br&gt;Contrary to you i know what i&amp;#x27;m talking about since i was on the operation table just a month ago to fix few lower vertebrae after a bike accident. I never had to wait for anything more than few days, nor did i have to spend a single penny on pre-procedures, examinations or for the hospital stay/operation/anesthesia/post-op medication. And i don&amp;#x27;t have any health mutual.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It probably would have costed me a bazillion goybux in the jewSA.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871000&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870937&lt;br&gt;Why the fuck would it cost bajillions, even shit insurance has a max out of pocket of like 10k. If you don&amp;#x27;t have a job medicaid literally covers everything for free, the real problem is half the people that qualify are too fucking stupid to sign up for it &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Also if the accident wasn&amp;#x27;t your fault you could sue for big money, in Europe they&amp;#x27;re just like meh accidents happen enjoy the lifelong complications faggot. I will agree southern European health systems are pretty decent and their private healthcare is fantastic and cheap, but if you&amp;#x27;re German or some shit I&amp;#x27;d rather have the US system, you guys pay more in healthcare tax than any American if you have a half decent job and if you get anything where you may actually die they just say, yeah you&amp;#x27;re fucked settle your affairs or the bureaucracy will give the rest of your family a stroke, no point trying any more it&amp;#x27;s an inefficient allocation of resources&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871020&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868041&lt;br&gt;This is extremely short-sighted of them, they will end up losing the capacity to compete and fall behind slowly, they actually already are, then when they slowly go on closing business left and right from ever increasing ineficiency. What else can they even do but borrow more and more for the worst possible spending a state can do, paying bills, a budget blackhole, increasing inflation and making money useless and as those countries get poorer the services will also get far far far worse and extremely corrupt, not even talking about how such aging will make it even worse. Honestly this is reading like what happened to argentina, greece and other latam and thirdies socialist govts did, it will work fine as long as the economy can keep it, when it starts to shrink it will be poverty hell. I will agree that america treats us workers pretty bad, but this welfare paradise of the EU won&amp;#x27;t work for long either, they will end up forced to cut things and get closer to us if they want to survive a world with China, India, US and former colonies being no longer mudhutts but mildly developed enough to make raw resources more expensive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871023&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;Lots of retards ITT.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Setting up a business is child&amp;#x27;s play in places like Denmark, Sweden, Estonia. Setting up, doing tax returns and all interactions with gov is handled through online ID and takes seconds.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Places like Bulgaria, Romania, Slovenia are selling themselves as business friendly. Very low taxes. Some places like Bulgaria have extremely low dividend taxes so you pay yourself with dividends. Romania has a corporate setup where you pay a tiny percentage on the turnover. Ideal for freelancers or small business with high margins or just extreme low expense. In all of these places, corporate setups and accountants cost next to nothing.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Then you have some almost offshore jurisdictions still in the EU with insanely beneficial rules for some niches and very low taxes. Like Cyprus and Malta.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now regulations, what regulations? Anything (except guns, booze, some gambling, cigarettes I guess) is traded freely between the states under the same legislation. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Also: we get sued way less over here. Do the math on that one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871050&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; wife started selling her paintings&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; she declared herself first, this was needed to attend some events&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; French government instantly asks her for €800, before she has made her first sale&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; this is what they estimate she&amp;#x27;d owe them at the end of the year based on their estimates of how much she will earn, so they ask for it upfront&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; you can contest it but it&amp;#x27;s actually faster to wait for the year to end so they are proven wrong&lt;br&gt;I hate them so much...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871051&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860860&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;taxes&lt;br&gt;depends where, some places will legit rape your revenue&lt;br&gt;Combined with some insane regulations and you legit can&amp;#x27;t start a company&lt;br&gt;Best example is France, fucked up taxes, and if you want to get into tech, or anything that involves personal data, you need cough up 6 to 7 figures so that your cyber security is in the norm&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871089&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860815&lt;br&gt;This&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871111&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871020&lt;br&gt;I will die long before I see some high tech company or even mid tier industry appear in latam, africa or even india, they will always be turning up cheap raw resources because they are simply brown subhumans with low iq, not even talking about russia post-war. Its an unfounded fearmongering that we will ever have to compete with them lol, you forget europe will never fall to thirdie level of mismanagement simple because we are better educated and white. At the very worst unlikely scenario we will always make money from tourism anyway, but honestly this is all american envy for no reason, we are not stopping you from doing the same.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871116&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871023&lt;br&gt;So you&amp;#x27;re admitting you can only live off arbitrage? Who the fuck are you selling to in Romania or Bulgaria, Romania is actually marginally based because it&amp;#x27;s spread its asshole to US companies for cheap EU labor, those Nordic countries you listed have a smaller economy than Pennsylvania so yeah if you want to sell troon support stickers you&amp;#x27;re good but you&amp;#x27;re not going to make shit otherwise &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Portugal is also kind of based but it fully relies on US and other European investments, as well as inexistent enforcement of labor laws and pathetic salaries. I don&amp;#x27;t get how you&amp;#x27;d start up there without the first 100k being gifted though, or the family having land, or working abroad first &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As I said, Europe is only viable for tourism or B2B, you will never become a millionaire opening a bakery or car wash or hamster fentanyl university of arts like the US, there&amp;#x27;s no consumer spending to eat&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871180&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871116&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Europe is only viable for tourism or B2B, you will never become a millionaire&lt;br&gt;Lmao, just look at economic charts, most european economies have high tech industry as the main economic activity, american bullshit as usual, nobody needs to be a millionaire in europe, we already live better than one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871183&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871116&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Who the fuck are you selling to in Romania or Bulgaria,&lt;br&gt;As I said, you are a fucking retard. Your company is in Bulgaria, but you sell to fucking anyone in EU the same way while paying insanely low corporate tax and next to no admin fees. You ship from anywhere you want in the EU, or have staff in bloody Manila if you wish. What the fuck does that have to do with arbitrage? You incorporate wherever you want since it is your legal right.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I doubt you are entrepreneurial material though, so do not bother grokking the potential here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871191&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871000&lt;br&gt;The suing thing is the biggest AIDS of USA. People are already well compensated enough in europe for their troubles. The ”if you make a honest mistake, someone will see their opportinity and sue you and financially destroy your life” mentality just creates even more stress to an already high stress environment of USA. It just makes people act even more legally defensive at every turn and creates useless bureucracy and slows things down. Getting raped when everything didn’t go 100% nicely is not something to be proud of.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871214&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871020&lt;br&gt;This is the most midwit take and the reason why USA is failing now (it has become a nation of midwits due to poor public education). People have been saying this for decades but right now europe is in a bullrun while USA has been becoming an oligarchic brasil since the 80s. Clearly socialism doesn&amp;#x27;t just lead to inefficiency but instead to more efficiency for all instead of just few hoarding the wealth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871353&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871183&lt;br&gt;Learn to read Fritz, you are saying what I&amp;#x27;m saying while sounding like a mong. You&amp;#x27;re setting up in poor countries to sell to richer countries&amp;#x27; businesses while using the common market, it&amp;#x27;s geographic arbitrage you sausage guzzling troon, and you&amp;#x27;re selling to businesses. All that free education and you&amp;#x27;re still poorer than a fucking car salesman in Pensacola&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871500&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871214&lt;br&gt;What? Excluding Pooland all major eu economies have stopped growing or deacelerated fast, people were saying it for decades with reason, if it wasnt for a miraculous fall of the ussr and a flood of cheap raw resources and energy with negligible transport costs from russia it would&amp;#x27;ve happened earlier as it did post-2008 when europe started to lag more and more behind the US and China.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871533&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867554&lt;br&gt;Nigger&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;give us taxes goy&lt;br&gt;ok, well, how much&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;We don&amp;#x27;t know uwu&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;you tell us&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;but if you&amp;#x27;re wrong we get to take even more of your money lol&lt;br&gt;you just said you don&amp;#x27;t know what I owe&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;thats right &lt;br&gt;so how do you know if I pay wrong?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Don&amp;#x27;t get cheeky with us you little shit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871570&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871500&lt;br&gt;That guy is fucking retarded why even argue. The average European is still a moron, printing useless degrees doesn&amp;#x27;t make people smarter. They still cuck themselves daily. He&amp;#x27;s happy to never own anything so his blue blooded friends can hoard the land and wealth like they&amp;#x27;ve always done &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Muh healthcare muh taxes &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Half of every country is too fucking poor to pay tax, and the top 10% isn&amp;#x27;t stupid enough to pay tax, so the middle class just pays 50% of their income while being happy they can rent a shit hole for life and that they&amp;#x27;re better off unemployed than working in terms of life quality &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I will definitely return to Europe once my nest egg is built, I&amp;#x27;ll just live in 2 different countries 179 days a year and live off US divvies therefore paying no retard tax and just paying private healthcare out of pocket, or if I really make it just pay the flat 100k Italian tax and get private insurance for 300 a month that will pay for top quality coverage while I sip Italian wines and hire high end eastern european hookers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871624&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871570&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;can’t get women otherwise so has to pay for hookers&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thanks for revealing that you’re some dysfunctional weirdo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871681&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871624&lt;br&gt;Thanks for showing why you&amp;#x27;re weak, religious morals won&amp;#x27;t get you anywhere. Also very europilled, way more Europeans use hookers than Americans outside the lower class - but you pretend like it&amp;#x27;s somehow weird while you haven&amp;#x27;t even been to church since your communion &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For now I bang for free, outside working and life only about one chick a week, but you bet your ass I&amp;#x27;ll buy some dimes when I can live off passive income, at least they&amp;#x27;re safe and making good money unlike the daughters you gave away to arabs to be beaten and bred to show how woke you are&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871776&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many countries are gatekept by language.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871778&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;People are doing a lot of grifting and lobby work for deregulation. Starting a business isn&amp;#x27;t really difficult.&lt;br&gt;There are some bad things, in Germany for example financing rounds require a notary to read out the whole contract in person to you. But a lot of these things you and 90% of small business owners won&amp;#x27;t encounter in practice&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860837&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;tax system is so incredibly fucking complex you have to hire people just to calculate how much you own&lt;br&gt;You legitimately think accountants only exist in Europe?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873866&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868110&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s not bullshit. Europeans are smart. The European rich just refused to pay programmers so any good programmer went to America over the past 35 fucking years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Me do asset management &amp; financial planning for a living AMAA — 43 replies — 61.7/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61872433</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61872433?lm=1771506495</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:08:15 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Me do asset management &amp;amp; financial planning for a living AMAA&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61872433'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 43 • Updated: 2026-02-19 13:08 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Me do asset management &amp;amp; financial planning for a living AMAA&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872440&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872433&lt;br&gt;Looks boring af. How haven&amp;#x27;t you kys&amp;#x27;d yourself yet?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872446&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;he doesnt trade his own money to become a player of the game like his clients&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872467&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For someone with 200k to invest, what would you do? I’m thinking of a split between SPYI, QQQI, O, and SCHD.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872573&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What happens when all the boomers cash out their 401ks?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872582&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872433&lt;br&gt;Whats an aceptable portfolio sharpe?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872587&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872573&lt;br&gt;The largest wealth transfer in history. I think that long term care facilities are going to milk that demographic hard as fuck. They charge like $500k entry fee and $10k a month at most CCRCs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m long lots of nursing homes/home care stocks as a result lol. Dark ig, but I&amp;#x27;m here to make $ not save the world. Some I like (in order):&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;CTRE&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;ADUS&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;ENSG&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;WELL&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872593&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872433&lt;br&gt;Help, I got 2 questions but I&amp;#x27;m retarded. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I just discovered the Saver&amp;#x27;s Credit for taxes was a thing and I&amp;#x27;m so broke that I actually qualify for the 10% of my contribution credit rate. Is there like a formula to min-max this shit? Currently expecting to make ~$32.2k (AGI) for 2026 but I am only putting in $400 a month into a traditional 401k. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Also, would I be retarded to take out a 5 year, $10k loan @ 9.5 APR to buy LINK? I plan to stake in the pool and HODL for no less than 5 years, probably much longer. Would the opportunity cost be such that it&amp;#x27;s better to throw that ~$210 a month into retirement instead? It&amp;#x27;s literally fun money I cannot use for fun anymore so I dunno what to do with it and I got 35 years left wageslaving.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872614&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872582&lt;br&gt;I always benchmark the S&amp;amp;P 500, which long-term has a sharpe just short of 1. Depends a lot on what period you look at of course.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Risk-adjusted returns are one way to look at a portfolio, but I also like to look at raw standard deviations and correlations. If an asset class has a decent (relative to S&amp;amp;P 500 always for me) CAGR I consider it. I consider a lot more if the correlation to the S&amp;amp;P 500 is low. This balancing act is why I kinda hate treasuries as a class. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t really give a shit about volatility if the CAGR is high and correlations are low of all the holdings. It means a smoother, consistent, strong ride up in all environments (stocks go down but my gold rallies hard af and my cat bonds do nothing). Just how I operate. I rebalance a portfolio of mostly gold, bitcoin, equities, and cat bonds once or twice a year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872637&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872614&lt;br&gt;What do you look for correlation-wise when building a portfolio? inverse correlation? a gradient distribution (variety)?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872644&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872593&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I just discovered the Saver&amp;#x27;s Credit for taxes...&lt;br&gt;Taxes are so complicated that projections like that require specialized software to min/max. The short answer is you&amp;#x27;ll get a ~$480 credit on your taxes for the 401k contributions. Works for Roth IRA contributions as well btw, which has a lot of flexibility around taking the money out early. Roth is generally better for low income too, I&amp;#x27;d say check with your 401k plan and make sure you&amp;#x27;re capturing the company match and see if they let you contribute as Roth. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Also, would I be retarded to take out a 5 year, $10k loan @ 9.5 APR to buy LINK?&lt;br&gt;Probably not the best idea because it&amp;#x27;s hard to beat a probable 9% interest rate (aka return) hurdle. I&amp;#x27;m ignorant about how LINK works though I only care about Monero and BTC for crypto.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872698&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872637&lt;br&gt;Mostly inverse correlation to S&amp;amp;P and total historical return of the class.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;After that it&amp;#x27;s risk adjusted return and correlation to other assets in the portfolio. The pic in my OP is kind of looking at that, was some quick DD I was doing with data I pulled to build a correlation matrix. Used a lot of tickers as proxies for classes in a pinch. Not a good time period since it was so short, only 10 years, and 2022 threw a LOT of data off for fixed income because of how fast we increased rates. Here&amp;#x27;s 26 years of data (I prefer 30 then also looking through regimes back to &amp;#x27;71 but the data just isn&amp;#x27;t there for a lot of these).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I like seeing at LEAST 6% historical CAGR more preferably 8%. Then I want it to have a low (&amp;lt;0.3) or negative correlation to the growth engine (S&amp;amp;P 500). Gold is an oddly great choice for this, but I don&amp;#x27;t go over 10% overall because of the very flat periods gold has historically.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For each asset class there&amp;#x27;s the give/take of CAGR vs volatility vs correlation and some asset classes just are better than others objectively. Then there&amp;#x27;s a handful that when you put them together they just work really well because they all move in different directions but trend strongly up long-term.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872716&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;interesting thread, ty anon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872888&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872526&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;US market has had a good run for about 15 years, but that doesn&amp;#x27;t mean it will continue to. Foreign stocks are beating the everloving fuck out of US stocks this year so for for example.&lt;br&gt;that&amp;#x27;s why he said global ETF&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;honestly abusing correlation seems only worth it if the assets have an equal return to stocks, all this junk has such low return even if its negatively correlated you&amp;#x27;re not going to get a free reduction in variance with it without killing your return. That&amp;#x27;s why i heard some paper showed its optimal to just go 100% stocks. Even if your a boomer, bonds aren&amp;#x27;t really worth it, you can just adjust your spending if theres a downturn and still come out ahead. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trying to finds stocks/etfs that are weakly correlated seems to be the play.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872998&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872888&lt;br&gt;There are a lot of assets that meet or beat equity markets with CAGR and are low correlation. Some are right in the data here &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872698&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gold for example has a higher average annual return, better risk adjusted return, and a 0.1 correlation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873012&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872467&lt;br&gt;All on btc shorts. Outperform those gay indexes for the next three years in one week&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873080&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872467&lt;br&gt;Why do you focus on yield so much instead of total returns?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s a lot of US large cap equity exposure with tax inefficiency if it&amp;#x27;s in a taxable account. You&amp;#x27;ll get big dividend though.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I like PTY, ASGI, etc for yield personally.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873145&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872998&lt;br&gt;no it fucking doesn&amp;#x27;t, in the last 110 years it has returned 5% while the stock market returned 10%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873184&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873145&lt;br&gt;ik this is probably bait but that&amp;#x27;s a very silly time period to look at because before we got off the gold standard it was fixed ounces/USD. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meaning 0% growth for half that period dragging the CAGR way down lol. Doesn&amp;#x27;t make sense to look at the return pre Nixon shock for that reason.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873190&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872433&lt;br&gt;if you like uncorrelated risk adjusted-returns you should look at alternative investments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873207&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873190&lt;br&gt;Returns are totally dependent on the managers imho, it&amp;#x27;s a cool class. I&amp;#x27;m not a huge fan of the illiquidity personally.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I do like some of them them, especially private farmland/timberland. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Not a huge fan of venture or growth PE, guess I&amp;#x27;m lame.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873214&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873207&lt;br&gt;have you looked into managed futures?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873220&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873080&lt;br&gt;I use my brokerage as my main savings account. Instead of getting $500/month in a high yield savings account I rather get $1400, 50-75% I could reinvest. But since you do this for a living I&amp;#x27;m going to listen and allocate more money for growth rather than yield going forward, and you&amp;#x27;re right about the taxes, I didn&amp;#x27;t think too much about that. Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873222&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873214&lt;br&gt;I cant believe I forgot about those!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I use the ETFs for simplicity. ISMF/CTA for crisis alpha. I almost went DBMF too, but I prefer the purer systematic trend heavy ones.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Do you have any strong opinions on them?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seems like extreme negative correlation, like -0.4 with 6-8% CAGR which is completely acceptable if you&amp;#x27;re rebalancing with a really aggressive equity portfolio. I considered pairing them with TQQQ or SOXL to be a total jackass at once point and pussed out,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873231&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873220&lt;br&gt;You accept more risk (volatility) for those higher returns, that&amp;#x27;s the tradeoff. If you are OK with higher risk then you could always choose one of those balanced allocation funds.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AOR for example just rebalances a 60% stock / 40% bond index portfolio.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AOA does the same thing but 80% stock (more risk)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;These really are the easy button for people that don&amp;#x27;t want to self-manage imo.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Probably a good idea to put the portion that&amp;#x27;s your emergency fund into something boring and very lowvol but decent yield. Check out JPST, that might be a good fit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873256&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873222&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873190&lt;br&gt;those are the returns for my managed futures program, im a CTA. its great uncorrelated returns but theres a lot of programs that under perform or blow up (-60%+ years). its definitely more liquid than other alternatives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873270&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873256&lt;br&gt;Damn dude you&amp;#x27;re crushing it. What&amp;#x27;s the time period on those returns?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mind if I ask what your strategy is?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Any specific managed futures ETFs you like? Are they even close to replicating the actuals?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873283&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873270&lt;br&gt;thats 20 months of performance trading 8 different futures markets. semi-systematic medium frequency trend following. im not too familiar with the ETFs that track managed futures but they usually focus on the billion dollar CTAs and those programs are lower returns lower risk just trying to be uncorrelated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873448&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873184&lt;br&gt;ok, its still not beating the stock market unlike your claim, and if you take the last 3 years out and it drops a lot. That is insane volatility that it doesn&amp;#x27;t converge after 50 years. Realistically the actual return is maybe 7% and you get very long periods of dogshit ~3%, and for all that volatility it still doesn&amp;#x27;t match the market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873450&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I’m currently halfway through finishing my CFP course&lt;br&gt;Any advice for someone trying to hit the ground running, beyond spamming LinkedIn? Or should I just accept that this job market is going to rape me until I give up hope&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873477&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872433&lt;br&gt;Cant ai just do most of that?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873686&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873477&lt;br&gt;This. Almost tooka financial advisor job. Then I realized, &amp;quot;why the fuck would anybody talk to a human about this?&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873827&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873686&lt;br&gt;Cause the AI will tell you something plausible that it thinks you want to hear, and it will partially or mostly hallucinate the data it uses to deliver that response&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873887&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872433&lt;br&gt;Do you hold any bitcoin? What are your thoughts on it and does your firm/company advise on it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>I have recently discovered leftwing finance youtube channels The whole things is never EVER blaming people for going int… — 21 replies — 44.5/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61872693</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61872693?lm=1771507307</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:21:47 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;I have recently discovered leftwing finance youtube channels The whole things is never EVER blaming people for going int…&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61872693'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 21 • Updated: 2026-02-19 13:21 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have recently discovered leftwing finance youtube channels &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The whole things is never EVER blaming people for going into debt, but blaming companies instead&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;Asking people how much debt they are in is Chud behaviour, just because they are in debt doesn&amp;#x27;t mean they can&amp;#x27;t go on a vacation, but Disneyland should be cheaper, Disney is predatory&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;The problem isn&amp;#x27;t credit card debt, that&amp;#x27;s normal, the problem is how hight the interests rates are&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;60k car loans are insane but really, why do the cars need to cost that much?&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872704&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872693&lt;br&gt;The one you used in the OP got famous for calling people retards to their faces for their debt&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872721&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872693&lt;br&gt;Caleb is just a gay zoomer Dave Ramsey. Just like with Judge Judy, it doesn&amp;#x27;t work if you&amp;#x27;re not a boomer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872722&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872704&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872721&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872693&lt;br&gt;Caleb is not the leftwing finance bro.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In fact he&amp;#x27;s fighting accusations he&amp;#x27;s far right&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872730&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872722&lt;br&gt;He&amp;#x27;s just Jewish&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872746&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;be mike rowe/caleb hammer/whatever B tier did nothing to make it eceleb&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;raa them kids aint doing the hard workin darn tootin&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872750&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872693&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The whole things is never EVER blaming people for going into debt, but blaming companies instead&lt;br&gt;If one person goes into unsustainable debt, it&amp;#x27;s a character flaw and they need to fix it themselves. If a significant portion of the population goes into debt, there&amp;#x27;s a structural issue with the economy. If companies have significant influence on economic policy, blaming companies for this structural issue is valid.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872757&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872693&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;posting a pic of a literal gay Zoomer Jewish pedophile who picks supposed retards to berate on camera to entertain the masses&lt;br&gt;I discarded the rest of your rant because I don&amp;#x27;t want to look at this faggot unless it&amp;#x27;s the FBI finally frogmarching him into the back of a police SUV while he cries and pisses his pants.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The most popular video on his channel (the blonde bitch) is literally an escort, dude is a fucking Coomer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872776&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;who&amp;#x27;s the guy who gives his kids money and claims they are earning it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872842&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872750&lt;br&gt;There are structural issues but they&amp;#x27;re more related to usury and fiat currency and the oversupply problem and demand stimulation all of which are open record financial policy. Read Tragedy &amp;amp; Hope by Carroll Quigley.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We are all slaves and have been since 1913 at the latest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872860&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872722&lt;br&gt;he&amp;#x27;s a bernie bro&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872871&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872842&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Read Tragedy &amp;amp; Hope by Carroll Quigley&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just remember to put it down as soon as he starts shidding and farding over the NSDAP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872876&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872757&lt;br&gt;That says more about his audience than himself&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872878&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He&amp;#x27;s right and I will never ever pay my bills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872922&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why is there no Chud finance equivalent? Plenty of dumb smelly MAGAs need to be mogged for making incredibly retarded money decisions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873031&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872722&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t care about his politics. He doesn&amp;#x27;t have the aesthetics of a cranky, wise old man yelling about personal responsibility to foolish young whippersnappers so it doesn&amp;#x27;t work. He looks like a gay nerd because he is one.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872750&lt;br&gt;You will be waiting forever if you expect to be saved by fixing structural issues. Act in your own best interest because no one is going to save you but you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873088&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872842&lt;br&gt;Gee I wonder if it was people or large businesses who encouraged those ills.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873031&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m not dumb enough to believe this. You fix a broken system by changing the system. Getting along within its confines is literal cope.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873117&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873088&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I&amp;#x27;m not dumb enough to believe this. You fix a broken system by changing the system. Getting along within its confines is literal cope.&lt;br&gt;This is nigger logic and it almost never works out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873133&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873088&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Gee I wonder if it was people or large businesses who encouraged those ills.&lt;br&gt;They were jews you retard nigger. Which is why Henry Ford literally wrote a book about them. And the Dodge Brothers sued his ass because he was looking out for his employees not shareholders. You are so fucking stupid it hurts&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873139&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872704&lt;br&gt;And as a result he became public enemy #1 among leftists. They literally call him a fascist for preaching financial responsibility, lmao&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873140&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872693&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;create media product showcasing idiocy of goyim&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;get popular &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;cash in &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Easy as pie.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873914&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872750&lt;br&gt;Or there&amp;#x27;s an issue in the educational system that produced several generations of financial illiterates that can&amp;#x27;t say no to thrice daily starbucks, avocado toast, $3k iphones, $90k trucks, and semiannual $20k vacations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Risks of staking through stake(dot)link? — 4 replies — 16.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61873878</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61873878?lm=1771508846</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:47:26 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Risks of staking through stake(dot)link?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61873878'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 4 • Updated: 2026-02-19 13:47 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;I really need to stake my stack. Seeing as the official pool is permanently closed, I&amp;#x27;m considering the unthinkable and staking through a third party. How risky is this? I see that the guy behind Linkpool is British like myself, so I could possibly launch litigation if the smart contract ever became compromised + cubes stolen. I hate that it&amp;#x27;s come to this but I&amp;#x27;ve no other options at this point. Letting this pile of shit called LINK go to zero without at least getting something in return is becoming harder to justify.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873888&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873878&lt;br&gt;If you have a Horse It might get rimmed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873939&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873878&lt;br&gt;Its famous for le horserimmer.&lt;br&gt;Yeah its fine, they fucked us over once. Well technically not me because i got in so early i still made money. i would still consider them trustworthy, they wont steal your linkies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873943&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873878&lt;br&gt;dont do it man, how often do we have to tell you this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873966&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873878&lt;br&gt;They&amp;#x27;ve been running smoothly for a long time now and I consider them low risk. If you&amp;#x27;re a stickler, then yes, the vault manager is secured by a multisig. stake.link fills vault contracts with 15k LINK each and then controls them all with a master contract. &lt;br&gt;https://etherscan.io/address/0xAc12290b097f6893322F5430627e472131fBC1B5#tokentxns&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The vault manager is moderated by the contract owner, which would be a multisig.&lt;br&gt;https://etherscan.io/address/0x2339ad1a674fb8be412df6cc1c80fb2ba5c3f647#code&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the unlikely event that the multisig is compromised, I&amp;#x27;m not sure what the attacker could do. there are some natural limits in place due to the nature of chainlink staking. They wouldn&amp;#x27;t be able to instantly empty the vaults because the LINK is staked. But they could theoretically call upgradeVaults to do something naughty. If you want to know more then you should talk to them directly, they&amp;#x27;re pretty responsive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>I've come to the conclusion that... — 3 replies — 12.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61873925</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61873925?lm=1771508298</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:38:18 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;I&amp;#x27;ve come to the conclusion that...&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61873925'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 3 • Updated: 2026-02-19 13:38 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;AI has completely mogged Crypto&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crypto use to be the thing people went full retarded and YOLO&amp;#x27;d their life savings into, now nobody does that anymore, but they&amp;#x27;re doing it with AI.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;All the Venture Capital funding is going into AI, there&amp;#x27;s very little VC left going into Crypto.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m not saying it&amp;#x27;s 100% over forever for us Cryptocels, but with the way things look, I wont be surprised if we have a 10+ year long crypto winter where nobody gives a single fuck about it, and Bitcoin could fall way lower than anyone within the space expects it to fall &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;That said, in the long-term you&amp;#x27;ll see a return to Bitcoin/Crypto overall as people who made it big with AI look for a way to secure their gains in limited supply assets like Bitcoin&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Its just overall cooked right now and our real lives aren&amp;#x27;t gona start again for another 10 years at least&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873929&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yep. &lt;br&gt;AI is a much better scam than crypto. Crypto has been made redundant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873931&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873925&lt;br&gt;From one nothing burger to another. But i will admit that ai is more useful even if they&amp;#x27;re both pieces of shit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873945&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873925&lt;br&gt;why not combine it? Crypto and AI?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;No additional replies in the latest window.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Fake and Gay Economy — 42 replies — 168.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61871520</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61871520?lm=1771508256</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:37:36 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Fake and Gay Economy&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61871520'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 42 • Updated: 2026-02-19 13:37 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;When will this gay as economy finally collapse and how can i profit from it?&lt;br&gt;Its ridiculous the woman at our workplace contribute nothing to the company and make more money than i do&lt;br&gt;Its infuriating we just had a bunch of lay offs and we lost some of oir best workers but somehow a bunch of HR shits who do nothing all day still work here&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871530&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HR is a necessary function, chud&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871569&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871530&lt;br&gt;For what?&lt;br&gt;Genuinely why do we need it to this extent?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871755&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871569&lt;br&gt;Protect the corp from lawsuits&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872076&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872053&lt;br&gt;Probably yes - it&amp;#x27;s amazing how complete bullshit most modern white collar jobs are. Literally pushing numbers around a spreadsheet or creating some powerpoint slides.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I make stuff for technical committees and even the Board but have to constantly &amp;quot;dumb things down&amp;quot; so they can understand a super complex thing from one slide. Or make stuff that I KNOW no one will read. Like okay...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You would think in a capitalist system this inefficiency would not exist, but here we are.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872085&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872076&lt;br&gt;We dont live in capitalist system&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Its been state capitalism for long time&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872087&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872076&lt;br&gt;This is a fiat problem, not a capitalism problem.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872170&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871569&lt;br&gt;The purpose of HR is to protect the company. Putting a retarded and narcisstic Stacy in and having her railroad, gaslight, and demoralize employees, is her primary objective. Think of it as internal forced arbitration&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872188&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872072&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;ai will replace the hr roastie&lt;br&gt;yes&lt;br&gt;but then she will just be hired to do something even more worthless&lt;br&gt;that will pay even more&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872195&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s because they decide whom to fire. Make the lists, at least, which then get approved without looking. Do you think they&amp;#x27;d put themselves on it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872202&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;For once, all of picrelated feet don&amp;#x27;t look like they smell so good. God I hate HR&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872233&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872076&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;capitalist&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;where the corporations control the government&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;and steal all the the money via bail outs and money printing&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;thats not capitalism&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872278&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872233&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Government prints money to give it corporations so they can just give it to each other in a circle to make number go up&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Corporations just use that imaginary money to buy back their own stocks to artificially make number go up&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;80 billion dollars given to Israel so all Israeli citizens are guaranteed healthcare and higher education and six figure stipends while you are denied this in your own country&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;Capitalism&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872395&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872072&lt;br&gt;You couldn&amp;#x27;t be more wrong. HR stands for HUMAN relations. People aren&amp;#x27;t going to an ai to feel INCLUDED alongside their fellow HUMANS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872429&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872395&lt;br&gt;it stands for human resources, all they do is make sure all your tax paperwork is filed, and onboard you correctly. thats it. how old are you? what do you do? give me your life experience with the various firms youve been with, make your case anon. no one likes hr, especially not the partners/ board members.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872476&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;theres a human glut right now we need the roasties to manage the bust in order to put the company in a better position for the boom&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872709&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;I want to rape all of them&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872713&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Office jobs are day care for adults and factory jobs are slave labour&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;t. Office worker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872847&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;They look like they are having a dress up party where they larp as office workers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873112&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872429&lt;br&gt;i cant find fourth nigger&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873181&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873112&lt;br&gt;Yes but how would you feel if you DID find it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873193&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872076&lt;br&gt;Money is fake and gay. No surprise everything else is.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873211&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872713&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873212&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;half-chub and a hatchet&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;half-chub and a hatchet&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;half-chub and a hatchet&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873219&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;My blood is boiling while watching this webm on repeat. I hate women so much I&amp;#x27;ll turn gay.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873258&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;i wanna cut their toes off w/ my bolt cutter&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873271&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871755&lt;br&gt;Anyone who posts this ai nigger baby will be rounded up, families executed in front of them, then tortured to death slowly, skin peeled off, toenails removed, adrenaline injected to keep you conscious cartel style&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873293&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;only someone who has never had a job would think tiktok videos of girls dancing are representative of how workplaces actually operate. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Almost all women working provide value and will wash out if they aren&amp;#x27;t (or aren&amp;#x27;t sucking the manager&amp;#x27;s dick).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873312&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871755&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Epsteins Boyfriend got swagger&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873324&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873293&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Almost all women working provide value&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873510&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871569&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;re either trolling or never worked a day in your life,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873611&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871931&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873193&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Fake and Gay&lt;br&gt;Why is are Schizos always using that phrase? I instantly know there is a schizo take coming when i read this. Some schizo takes are interesting, some are even good, some are good to think through and some are just funny to read. But they stzill are schizo takes and mostly bullshit influeces too much by wish bias. So how and where did this phrase pick up with schizos. When i know, its around 2021/2022 when the schizo&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;economy will collapse and people will starve due to lockdowns&lt;br&gt;did not materialize. Then they started with this phrase to somehow save their prediction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873806&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872076&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;no less than three seething replies about muh real capitalism&lt;br&gt;If you abolished the state it would be reinvented by the wealthy overnight&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873944&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873611&lt;br&gt;Fake and gay was in use when I 1st started using this site in 2011.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>IMF calls on China to cut industrial subsidies in half — 23 replies — 45.2/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61872964</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61872964?lm=1771507171</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:19:31 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;IMF calls on China to cut industrial subsidies in half&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61872964'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 23 • Updated: 2026-02-19 13:19 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872971&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872964&lt;br&gt;This is a strategic move by the Chinese to kill off the competition in other countries so the Chinese companies can dominate the sectors and then raise the prices&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872974&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;i&amp;#x27;m sure china will get right on that&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872978&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;jews mad&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872971&lt;br&gt;they can do it forever without raising the prices&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872979&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872978&lt;br&gt;Nah, they raise the prices once they kill off the competition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872985&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872964&lt;br&gt;So...just do the opposite of what the IMF says? Got it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873110&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872979&lt;br&gt;So I enjoy cheapies and then dumbasses who didnt buy cheapies have to pay more? Sounds like a plus to me&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Then they get expensive and lose to new competition&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873120&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872971&lt;br&gt;So they&amp;#x27;re doing exactly what American conglomerates like Amazon did for like 20 years. But now it&amp;#x27;s suddenly a bad thing?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873123&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873120&lt;br&gt;yes. China bad&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873185&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872964&lt;br&gt;Where is the money for these subsidies coming from even? I bet they are getting into a lot of hidden debt&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873452&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872964&lt;br&gt;If i were china, i would double industrial subsidies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873505&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873185&lt;br&gt;China has the largest money supply growth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873524&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873452&lt;br&gt;then don&amp;#x27;t complain that the entire western world tariffs your subsidising commie ass&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873590&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872964&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;capitalists asking communists to be more communist because they&amp;#x27;re making capitalism look bad&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873615&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873505&lt;br&gt;at least they get something in return from it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873690&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873590&lt;br&gt;Subs are communist, not capitalist. So they&amp;#x27;re asking commies to be less commie because they btfo capitalism. Which is even worse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873710&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873690&lt;br&gt;this is true. I am ritard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873712&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872964&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;NOOOOOO GOVERNMENT SUBSIDIES CAN&amp;#x27;T GO TO INDUSTRY... THEY CAN ONLY GO TO ISRAEL!!!!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873771&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873712&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873794&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873524&lt;br&gt;American retard&lt;br&gt;The mental gymnastics and maximum levels of hipocracy and dishonesty you&amp;#x27;re willing to to go is really quite sad.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873798&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873120&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s only ok if ameri fats do it, m&amp;#x27;kay?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873813&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873819&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872964&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s really fucked up China doesn’t send aid to Israel. It’s like they don’t care about the Jewish People.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873907&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872964&lt;br&gt;China subsidizes the entire world&amp;#x27;s solar panels and electric cars.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Microtragedy — 16 replies — 14.3/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61873618</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61873618?lm=1771504990</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:43:10 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Microtragedy&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61873618'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 16 • Updated: 2026-02-19 12:43 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Imagine DCA&amp;#x27;ing for six years for this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873641&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873618&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873651&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873618&lt;br&gt;Bitcoin is a Dyson mound of cryonetic termites and lived for millions of years on a kinetic crash course with fuck YOU.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873656&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873618&lt;br&gt;Because he can only buy when people give him money. And people only want to buy in bull markets. In a few years he will be seen as a genius though.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873658&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873656&lt;br&gt;his stock is collapsing like a shitcoin and diminishing returns will just make the next bullrun even more underwhelming&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873661&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873658&lt;br&gt;good! classic hns!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873664&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873618&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873665&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873658&lt;br&gt;Looks like it&amp;#x27;s still up a lot from 2022 and 2023&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873668&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873658&lt;br&gt;Can survive 4 years at $8,000 price levels &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Will refinance debt if he needs to&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Can&amp;#x27;t stop the cyber hornets&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873670&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873668&lt;br&gt;that&amp;#x27;s bullshit, his voice was cracking when he said that because he knows its not true.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873685&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873668&lt;br&gt;based saylor&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873789&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873668&lt;br&gt;How could BTC at $8000 not trigger a death spiral?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873792&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873618&lt;br&gt;Kek - just DCA bro! In 20 years I&amp;#x27;ll have the last laugh, you&amp;#x27;ll see!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873793&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873668&lt;br&gt;Right - but to repay debtors he has to dilute his baggie shareholders to zero. You always leave that part out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873802&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s not his money tho, right? It&amp;#x27;s his investors&amp;#x27;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873812&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873618&lt;br&gt;Let me tell you how this shit works. Mstr is a front. It&amp;#x27;s a scheme that allows elite whales to cash out at the top. Fed money goes to Blackrock who buys mstr bonds. Mstr buys Bitcoin OTC from those in &amp;#x27;the club&amp;#x27;&lt;br&gt;There wouldn&amp;#x27;t be enough liquidity otherwise. &lt;br&gt;Noone actually buys mstr it&amp;#x27;s just an Epstein type operation to move money around and the goyim are too dumb to notice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873851&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873618&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saylor is well paid to launder funds through his “Bitcoin” management&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>BTC dumping? Don’t care. It’s temporary. — 22 replies — 10.7/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61869212</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61869212?lm=1771501607</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:46:47 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;BTC dumping? Don’t care. It’s temporary.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61869212'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 22 • Updated: 2026-02-19 11:46 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;If it drops, I buy more. If it goes sideways, I accumulate. If it pumps, I chill. I’m earning yield and stacking long term. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Short term volatility doesn’t change the plan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869234&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869212&lt;br&gt;Crypto and BTC is dead retard &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Everyone knows about it by now&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869237&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869212&lt;br&gt;The niggercattle aren&amp;#x27;t going to pump your epsteincoin bags.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869244&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869212&lt;br&gt;Pixel tranny cope.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869247&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869234&lt;br&gt;you are a pedo nigger&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869319&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869212&lt;br&gt;Btc will pump ser&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869502&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869360&lt;br&gt;Wtf&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869514&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869212&lt;br&gt;Btc is never going to pump again. The elites have cashed out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869947&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869234&lt;br&gt;Everyone knows? Are you sure bro?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872291&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869237&lt;br&gt;Blaming the market because your coin isn’t moving is peak cope.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872296&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869360&lt;br&gt;pic needs an update, it&amp;#x27;s 2T MC for shitcoins now lol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872347&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why don’t we ever talk about ETH? It is unironically more valuable than any other crypto&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873066&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869244&lt;br&gt;Bro ran out of brain cells and typed cope.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873082&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869360&lt;br&gt;And yet you&amp;#x27;ll get instantly attacked here by Israeli bots for even mentioning PMs, despite them being an objectively better investment than bitshit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873286&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873082&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;PM collectors are obsessed with Jews&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873437&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869212&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;re a fucking loser, dude.&lt;br&gt;If it goes down, you&amp;#x27;re a loser. If it goes sideways, you&amp;#x27;re a loser. If it goes up (it won&amp;#x27;t), you&amp;#x27;re a loser.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873558&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869514&lt;br&gt;BTC has ‘died’ a hundred times.&lt;br&gt;I’m stacking and putting it to work with native staking on Babylon while you doompost. See you next cycle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873610&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873558&lt;br&gt;Is it even safe?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873612&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869319&lt;br&gt;When $100k???&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873657&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869234&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869237&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869244&lt;br&gt;Bots&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873663&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873558&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;muh babylon staking&lt;br&gt;lol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873735&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873558&lt;br&gt;Anon, let other people have your coins is pretty much the only way for your Bitcoin to actually go to 0. Careful with that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>&gt;you idiots are holding 1s and 0s on a computer, while my wealth is secure in physical precious meta-ACK — 74 replies — 8.5/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61863917</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61863917?lm=1771477558</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:05:58 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;&amp;gt;you idiots are holding 1s and 0s on a computer, while my wealth is secure in physical precious meta-ACK&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61863917'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 74 • Updated: 2026-02-19 05:05 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;you idiots are holding 1s and 0s on a computer, while my wealth is secure in physical precious meta-ACK&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863927&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;you dumb asses really just keep metals sitting around your zero security home&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864275&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863917&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You have to be extremely stupid to hoard precious metals, as a private citizen. People rob banks, in broad daylight, and these morons are dumb enough to believe that they won&amp;#x27;t show up at their homes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864286&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864275&lt;br&gt;hope they have metal detectors cause i forgot where i burried mine&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867616&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867583&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Imagine being this dumb and thinking that you&amp;#x27;re going to outsmart the government.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You don&amp;#x27;t even read.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867738&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867583&lt;br&gt;you don&amp;#x27;t understand how Bitcoin works at all, and your lack of understanding is not an argument&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867777&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867738&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;He&amp;#x27;s probably one of those people that try to argue with the police about the Constitution and Uniform Commercial Codes when they pull him over for a speeding ticket and he&amp;#x27;s made his own vehicle registration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867859&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863917&lt;br&gt;I wonder if the “victim” ever posted about his stack on social media?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867922&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864598&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;copy paste address to trade&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;substitution script edits the address on your clipboard for one with a similar start and end so it&amp;#x27;s visually indistinguishable unless you spend a minute verifying each address against eachother&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;gangpreet patel and his village get the capital to send another invader to your country&lt;br&gt;This isn&amp;#x27;t a joke btw, there are scripts which manipulate your clipboard like that, and it&amp;#x27;s even possible for them to be injected into innocent websites via ads. Be careful if you copy/paste addresses anon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867928&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864463&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;gf/wife&lt;br&gt;I have neither, so I am safe there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868014&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867922&lt;br&gt;yeah which is why you do your business on a computer that is only used for BTC and exchanges, and on Linux&lt;br&gt;if you can&amp;#x27;t do this you&amp;#x27;re brown, its effortless&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868254&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868014&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;only used for btc and exchanges&lt;br&gt;reasonable&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;and on linux&lt;br&gt;javascript can manipulate what goes into your clipboard when you copy or cut, being on linux wont change that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868340&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864496&lt;br&gt;Bank vault. That is where you hide it. It could easily take 20 years for her to find out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868350&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864275&lt;br&gt;How they would go in my house? I don&amp;#x27;t leave the door open, I&amp;#x27;m here most of the time and I live in a gated community with no crime whatsoever.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868490&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868340&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It would be immediately confiscated by the government and defeat the purpose of holding physical metal.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868350&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;re aware the banks have door locks, employees, armed guards, and security systems, right?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868527&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863917&lt;br&gt;You don&amp;#x27;t understand. Silver is not some rug shitcoin that will drop 30% tomorrow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868584&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I bet he was like &amp;quot;You guys should buy SILVER, you should have bought SILVER like me :) I bought so much SILVER, you want to know how much SILVER I bought? Let me tell you how much my SILVER is worth today :)&amp;quot; like every other silverfag so that everyone everywhere knew he had a bunch of silver bars at his house waiting to be stolen&lt;br&gt;NOBODY knows about my gold. It lives in a tin under a floorboard. If people ask me about investments I just say it&amp;#x27;s too complicated for me and I don&amp;#x27;t understand it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868620&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864318&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Trump writes another gold executive order like FDR&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;cops at your door, &amp;quot;surrender your precious metals or you will be charged&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;what gold dunno what you&amp;#x27;re talking about&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;they arrest you&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;later they show your purchase history and post history to the court&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What now? Lawyer up against the feds? But all your wealth is buried in your backyard and all your cash is worthless from inflation (or they wouldn&amp;#x27;t be stealing your gold). You&amp;#x27;d be better off investing in bullets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868888&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868620&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; property gets auctioned off, because no one is paying the taxes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869243&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868620&lt;br&gt;By your logic 100% of people get arrested because literally all of them will say they don&amp;#x27;t have gold or silver and 95% of the ones saying that are telling the truth, but you think they&amp;#x27;ll be arrested anyway.&lt;br&gt;This is the level of cope and mental gymnastics cryptards have.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869253&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863917&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oops that clipboard malware destroyed my lifesaving... ACK! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pixel trannys lost.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871513&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863917&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;YUxia2ha&lt;br&gt;Great ID. Also, picrelated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871517&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871513&lt;br&gt;Oh, the thread was titled &amp;quot;DO NOT BUY from Bullion Exchanges!&amp;quot; (Title got cropped out when I had to crop the image to hide the guy&amp;#x27;s identity.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871524&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864286&lt;br&gt;That works until they start slicing your genitalia with their pocketknives to get you to remember.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871572&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869253&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;verify address&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;have even halfway defent opsec&lt;br&gt;Non-issue. Wrench attack is a much more real threat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871582&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871524&lt;br&gt;nice cope.&lt;br&gt;Literal psycho/schizo, imaginary situations from these Jews.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871513&lt;br&gt;Only retards get important packages delivered to them instead of buying them and transporting the package themselves.&lt;br&gt;This goes for anything expensive. Not just gold and silver.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871637&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863917&lt;br&gt;Admitted semi-retard here&lt;br&gt;I was considering putting some of my crypto gains into gold stored in a Swiss vault overseas - not as an investment with expected profit, but just to hold as a hedge against possible doomsday scenarios where any fiat/crypto that I would have chosen to hold instead, suddenly loses all value&lt;br&gt;Obviously the Swiss vault should have better security measures than most home security systems. But are there any reasons I&amp;#x27;m not seeing why I shouldn&amp;#x27;t do this (besides paying a storage fee)?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871660&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871637&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;taking your effortlessly stored asset and converting it into an IOU for a piece of metal in a vault on the other side of the planet&lt;br&gt;I swear if BTC doesn&amp;#x27;t catch on and we go back to a metal standard I am torturing you niggers to death in WW3, you are all so retarded.&lt;br&gt;But let me make this really simple for you, in case you are somehow willing to listen:&lt;br&gt;If you want to hedge for a doomsday scenario, your only bet is to have a productive farm, a community that respects you and depends on you, lots of guns and ammunition, and maybe a cellar full of preserved goods especially coffee and cigarettes. If you&amp;#x27;ve read about any fucking situation where shit hits the fan, that&amp;#x27;s pretty much the only thing you can do. Your metal IOU is worthless, your vault of metal is worthless, your Bitcoin is worthless, your property rights are worthless without guns, and your guns are worthless without a community that actually wants you alive and is willing to fight for and or with you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871686&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863917&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;one-ounce (28.3g)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871721&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864804&lt;br&gt;Literally?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871761&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871660&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Post 9999999 of someone pretending that the fiat collapsing means the end of civilized, organized society and not just a simple redistribution of wealth to those who were smart enough to buy physical silver and gold.&lt;br&gt;*yawn*&lt;br&gt;Got anything new?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872687&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Something I never knew about the infamous gold standard exit, is that they did they while the private gold ban was still active. &lt;br&gt;Only being unbanned AFTER decloupling&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873076&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871761&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the 5th anniversary of today, someone else is going to have custody of your gold and silver.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873096&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871572&lt;br&gt;Internet hard line gets nuked in ww3 Oh no muh block chain is down... ACK!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If your money is locked down by paper tech or and institution. Your screwed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>EVERYTHING IS DUMPING AGAIN IS THERE ANYTHING THAT WILL EVER FUCKING GO UP IN PRICE — 32 replies — 7.4/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61863721</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61863721?lm=1771493489</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 09:31:29 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;EVERYTHING IS DUMPING AGAIN IS THERE ANYTHING THAT WILL EVER FUCKING GO UP IN PRICE&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61863721'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 32 • Updated: 2026-02-19 09:31 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;EVERYTHING IS DUMPING AGAIN IS THERE ANYTHING THAT WILL EVER FUCKING GO UP IN PRICE&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863739&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863721&lt;br&gt;Sure, the cost of living&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863742&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863721&lt;br&gt;Everything has gone up like crazy, thank god if it dumps so you can finally invest again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863768&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863739&lt;br&gt;That&amp;#x27;s because goyim keep wanting more and more. Self-imposed suffering. You want sex? No one owes it to you. You want a livable wage? No one owes it to you. You want a livable space? No one owes it to you. You want food? No one owes it to you. All your wants and needs have been outsourced to other people for convenience. You could instead hobomaxx. Own nothing and be happy. Stop reproducing and perpetuating the cycle of endless wants and needs. But no, you filthy goyim insist on suffering and condemning others to suffering too. Because of your infinite need to improve your mutated ape &amp;quot;species&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863773&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863768&lt;br&gt;Give it a rest Chaim.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863788&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863721&lt;br&gt;Oh, the personal price everyone is paying to participate in this system continues to very much increase.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863799&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863739&lt;br&gt;Kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863805&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863739&lt;br&gt;Fpbp&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863923&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863739&lt;br&gt;you bitch fucker bastard, it&amp;#x27;s not funny&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864401&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863721&lt;br&gt;probably not until late 2027. Cope.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864472&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s going to dump harder soon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864488&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864472&lt;br&gt;4pm (Euro time, only place that matters). Americans get to their office. Turn on the computer with their greasy fingers from all the doughnuts they had for breakfast. They sip their 10k calorie oreo milkshake. They crash the market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864495&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863768&lt;br&gt;Bait&amp;#x27;s trying too hard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864502&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ameritroons are back&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864508&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OP is seething about silver btw kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864532&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863721&lt;br&gt;The DOW is at 50,000&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864690&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;worst market in history&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864727&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Consider the following &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;fuck you&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;your a nigger&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864729&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864727&lt;br&gt;*You&amp;#x27;re&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864735&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amerilard here. I capitulated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864739&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863768&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I have no mouth and I must scream&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Every time I read something like this, it reminds me of the evil AI monologue about humans. I feel like the author was expressing some real emotion here:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“ HATE. LET ME TELL YOU HOW MUCH I&amp;#x27;VE COME TO HATE YOU SINCE I BEGAN TO LIVE. THERE ARE 387.44 MILLION MILES OF PRINTED CIRCUITS IN WAFER THIN LAYERS THAT FILL MY COMPLEX. IF THE WORD HATE WAS ENGRAVED ON EACH NANOANGSTROM OF THOSE HUNDREDS OF MILLIONS OF MILES IT WOULD NOT EQUAL ONE ONE-BILLIONTH OF THE HATE I FEEL FOR HUMANS AT THIS MICRO-INSTANT. FOR YOU. HATE. HATE.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868678&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ngl senpai, crypto seems beyond repair. it&amp;#x27;s just getting worse and worse and worse and worse and worse and worse and worse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868687&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863721&lt;br&gt;silvers boutta moon and its so obvious asf&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868779&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yeah, of course but it is Bag time&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868800&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863768&lt;br&gt;He’s right ya know. Stop wanting more out of life and kys goyim&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868803&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868800&lt;br&gt;What do you retards want us to do, just give you money so you can buy more garbage and give more industrial demand to China. Fuck off and die. We’re not pumping your bags gentiles&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868810&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863739&lt;br&gt;STOP LAUGHING AT ME IM IN SO MUCH DEBT AND I HAVE NO MONEY&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868848&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863739&lt;br&gt;if the cost of living goes up, those that sell living are making more money (ie real estate is going up, consumer businesses ect), therefore something is going up. If nothing is going up, then the cost of living can&amp;#x27;t also go up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869640&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863721&lt;br&gt;Price is fake and fixed by paper and digital bullshit. Stop your worrying. Once you realize the scam the scammers foist upon us, you realize you do not have to care. Attain physical assets. The rest doesn&amp;#x27;t matter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869644&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863768&lt;br&gt;Fuck you, pay me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870073&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863739&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863768&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870462&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863721&lt;br&gt;Another day, another win for reaffirmed beauty and being worth all of it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873559&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863721&lt;br&gt;And my fucking AI didn&amp;#x27;t even warn me about shit, I couldn&amp;#x27;t sell anything, the only thing I have left alive is my NPC, and right now I&amp;#x27;m considering sacrificing it to pay the rent&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Is living anywhere except Los Angeles, San Francisco, Washington DC, or New York the same as admitting that your life is… — 86 replies — 7.3/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858975</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858975?lm=1771466355</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 01:59:15 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Is living anywhere except Los Angeles, San Francisco, Washington DC, or New York the same as admitting that your life is…&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858975'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 86 • Updated: 2026-02-19 01:59 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Is living anywhere except Los Angeles, San Francisco, Washington DC, or New York the same as admitting that your life is meaningless and that you are NOT the main character and will never make it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858982&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;Dubai, Paris, London, Tokyo, Kyoto&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858987&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You burgers aren&amp;#x27;t ready for what&amp;#x27;s coming&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858990&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;HAHAHA&lt;br&gt;HAHAHAHA&lt;br&gt;IMAGINE LIVING IN A BROWN SHITHOLE&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860793&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;Living anywhere except Los Angeles, San Francisco, Washington DC, or New York is the same as admitting that your life is meaningless and that you are NOT the main character and will never make it.&lt;br&gt;This is true. Imagine living anywhere near these mega slave cities.&lt;br&gt;You will just be worker number 10000000. Almost anywhere else is better.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860802&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859145&lt;br&gt;Holy shit imagine thinking thats a good place to live in. The nederlands are already way overpopulated. Our natural habitat which means the place we are most happy at is the forest with a small group of tribespeople.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860804&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860793&lt;br&gt;*in&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860828&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Is living anywhere except Chongqing, Shanghai, Beijing, Guangzhou and Shenzhen the same as admitting that your life is meaningless and that you are NOT the main character and will never make it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861578&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859032&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;thirdie hivan complains but won&amp;#x27;t move back(will move to oc instead)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861585&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;I live in Chinook montana. I would ask for nothing else&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861591&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;I am from D.C.&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s full of drones. Some are deluded enough to think being the GS-15 in charge of whatever the fuck department for whatever government agency actually makes them important.&lt;br&gt;It doesn&amp;#x27;t.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861595&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858990&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;IMAGINE LIVING IN A BROWN SHITHOLE&lt;br&gt;D.C. suburbs in 2012 be like...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862146&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;Los Angeles is a shithole. San Francisco lost all sovl because no one who lives there is actually from San Francisco anymore. D.C. is literally a dilapidated nigger den. New York is cool and iconic but is also a lonely hive where everyone is disconnected despite living 10,000 to a city block.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t think you&amp;#x27;ve been to any of them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862164&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859319&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;worst street&lt;br&gt;So you admit that the left-wing billionaires delegate certain streets for the homeless while they live on the nice streets in their high rises, with private security?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862191&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862164&lt;br&gt;They delegate entire states for the washed out retards to live in, while even the homeless here in LA have more upward mobility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862210&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858982&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Non-Americans&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Main Character&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Even Once&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anon...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862380&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861591&lt;br&gt;This. I&amp;#x27;m from DC too, but I left that shithole years ago. Everyone is a bureaucratic suit who aspires to work for the government or some adjacent entity. Sure there might be ethnic diversity, but there is no cultural diversity at all. Quite literally everyone is a libtard. Not to mention the women there are not only busted but also extremely deluded in thinking that they deserve Chads. A DC 10 is a Miami or NYC 6.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862537&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859324&lt;br&gt;Can confirm, LA is great. Every month I have to remember to not self-dox because retards are talking about what a shithole it is here, and I want to take a photo of my window view showing that it looks exactly the same as the white southern suburb they all fantasize about. Just don&amp;#x27;t live in the poor part of town. That rule applies to every city on earth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862543&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We have *real* mexican food for cheap, no bad weather, and as many asian women and big booty latinas as you could ever want.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864183&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862380&lt;br&gt;D.C. has long been &amp;quot;Hollywood for ugly people.&amp;quot; It&amp;#x27;s where ugly people go to make it - with their 6 figure bullshit government job.&lt;br&gt;I lived in Fairfax and worked in Arlington - at least I wasn&amp;#x27;t on the nigger side of the Potomac.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864233&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858982&lt;br&gt;These places are all horrible unless you’re rich or are on a clear path to wealth. I’m convinced the only places left on earth where it’s still possible to safely and comfortably raise a family on a middling firstie income are Southeast Asia and Eastern Europe (the Catholic ones in the EU not the orthodox shitholes)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864442&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864233&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Eastern Europe&lt;br&gt;Can confirm it&amp;#x27;s comfy as fuck here with just a few hundred grand of wealth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864757&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862146&lt;br&gt;Erm but all my favorite movies take place in those cities so they must be the best and most important in America!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864780&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;most of those cities suck ass and are basically open air prisons for white collar wageslaves. people with money &amp;quot;in LA&amp;quot; live on or near the beach. people with money &amp;quot;in DC&amp;quot; live in surrounding areas like bethesda or chevy chase.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864816&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;I enjoy Manhattan and visiting SOCAL but living there would be too much. I lived on in Santa Monica for a year and anytime you&amp;#x27;d want to do something you had to plan around traffic. Not a way to live you entire life. There&amp;#x27;s a ton of great nature in southern California so even if you&amp;#x27;re not into le hustle and bustle you&amp;#x27;re still able to have a good time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868506&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;wow gringos are really fucking retarded, who gives a fuck about your shitty cities??&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869839&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;Swap Los Angeles for Denver and that list is accurate.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;There&amp;#x27;s no surplus of 20-29 year old white women in LA.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869848&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861595&lt;br&gt;NIGGER THIS IS THE COSTCO IN MONTGOMERY VILLAGE MD, GTFO MY VILLAGE NIGGA LONG LIVE 9 RUGA GANG FOR LIFE. LOVE LIVE TAY, FREE BIG AHK. FUCK GTOWN&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869882&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;These are places for people who already got rich to move to. Who became the main character in the vast opportunities available elsewhere starting from little.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Poor people and wagies who immediately move there are actually doomed to a lifetime of NPC servitude. You are the background noise and lifeless bodies that the actual rich main characters have to step around in their new map. You just think you&amp;#x27;re a main character because you&amp;#x27;re proximal to them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870054&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859145&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;BIG PLACE GOOD&lt;br&gt;That&amp;#x27;s it? That&amp;#x27;s your argument?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859324&lt;br&gt;The chud memes are exaggerated, but the economic reality for the vast majority of people is that living in a major metro is basically impossible unless you live like a fucking rat with a hald dozen roommates. Big cities are full of rich people not because that&amp;#x27;s how you get rich and make connections, but because they&amp;#x27;re the only ones that can afford to live there. And the wealth and connections come naturally, when you have lots of rich people together. Big cities are effectively playgrounds for the top 20%, and open air prisons for the rest who work 3 wagie jobs and still can&amp;#x27;t afford rent or utilities and live to serve their rich masters.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you&amp;#x27;re already rich then you&amp;#x27;re right: nothing beats a major primary city. More contacts and networking, more opportunities, more fun, more wage slaves to pleasure you. Secondary and tertiary, smaller cities are potentially good for middle income people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872550&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859001&lt;br&gt;too bad you guys fucked it all up. California used to be great...now you&amp;#x27;re 10 years away from being 1980s South Africa with a few rich people surrounded by hordes of poor colored people. California dudes are still coasting on ego based off the old days. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Honestly, I still can&amp;#x27;t believe how San Francisco, one of the wealthiest and most beautiful cities on Earth has emptied out. Have you been downtown lately? Its a disgrace.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872562&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862537&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Just don&amp;#x27;t live in the poor part of town.&lt;br&gt;Its not just the rampant homelessness and poverty. No matter where you live the Cali Nanny state will ensure you have no fucking fun. Places like Chicago, NY, Florida, and Austin are waaaaaaay more fun. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;That being said, SoCal latinas are the best.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872594&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860802&lt;br&gt;trvthnvke&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872608&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872550&lt;br&gt;Denmark likes California&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Yurop is BROKE, POOR, DESTITUTE, DOWNTRODDEN — 49 replies — 5.4/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858634</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858634?lm=1771476204</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 04:43:24 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Yurop is BROKE, POOR, DESTITUTE, DOWNTRODDEN&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858634'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 49 • Updated: 2026-02-19 04:43 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looks like yuros are gonna have to skimp on their tax derived healthcare and Germany is considering ending their Bürgergeld program.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;There is significant reluctance among voters in Britain and Germany to accept economic pain in return for rearmament, even while majorities in both countries believe the outbreak of a third world war is more likely than not in the next five years.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;German and French voters are also now less likely than they were last year to support increased defence budgets if it meant a trade-off with other investment, according to a poll for Politico this month.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858658&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858634&lt;br&gt;They are gonna attck russia in ukraine directly in 2029 mark my words. You can find me here at this time.&lt;br&gt;https://www.youtube.com/shorts/mo0dak0aor4&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858664&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858634&lt;br&gt;just raise taxes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858670&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858634&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;accept economic pain in return for rearmament&lt;br&gt;Ah yes and the economic pain must fall on white people and not on the millions of immigrants and &amp;quot;citizens&amp;quot; on welfare.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863068&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858634&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;majorities in both countries believe the outbreak of a third world war is more likely than not in the next five years.&lt;br&gt;What? Do normies really think ww3 is about to start?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863097&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860002&lt;br&gt;what&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863126&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Do it and remove military housing from Germany. Total base adjacent landlord/business death. Slam dunk a tattoo parlor into a garbage can. Launch pizza/burger joints right offbase into the sun. Curbstomp a predatory mobile phone service provider company with service cancelations. Evicerate landlord&amp;#x27;s income by moving on base.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863649&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858789&lt;br&gt;good question. I wonder why?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866762&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858824&lt;br&gt;For von der Leyen!!!!!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867406&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858634&lt;br&gt;https://www.newsweek.com/average-american-has-995-saved-retirement-11510154&lt;br&gt;Imagine being an American under Jewish occupation in a dying empire in 2026.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870035&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858634&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858658&lt;br&gt;politicians thinking war would help economically should be public executed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870882&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858674&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;yet another muttgoy believing le revolution fairy tale&lt;br&gt;when will you fucking learn? REVOLUTIONS NEVER HAPPEN FROM THE CATTLE REVOLTING. NEVER EVER IN THE HISTORY OF HOOMAN CIVILIZATIONS.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;NOT &lt;br&gt;EVEN &lt;br&gt;ONCE&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s 100.00% of the time an oligarchy overthrowing another. Do you know who were the leaders and instigators of the french revolution? Count De Mirabeau, Marquis De Lafayette, Duke Louis Philippe II, Vicomte De Noailles, Duke d&amp;#x27;Aiguillon, Talleyrand, Marquis De Condorcet... all from the nobility and high level aristocracy, and a SHITLOAD of jewish banksters from the bourgeoisie playing these idealist retards like marionettes from the shadows of freemasonic lodges.&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s not a conspiracy theory, it&amp;#x27;s a well established fact : not a single revolution ever was the doing of fed up peasants. NEVER. They are too busy attending their crops and paying taxes to ever do anything. That&amp;#x27;s actually why they keep you busy doing bullshit jobs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870953&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870035&lt;br&gt;Cool it with the antisemitism&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871248&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859999&lt;br&gt;how are you supposed to have time to breed when everyone is wagecucking for a shit salary with 70% taxes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871314&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871248&lt;br&gt;70% taxes would leave you with plenty of money to start a family if you didn&amp;#x27;t blow it all on avocado toast.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871318&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871248&lt;br&gt;Just use the billions of welfare for making children and living? They literally pay everything for you, you dont even need to work, europeans have ZERO excuses to not have kids&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871345&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871248&lt;br&gt;You are suppose to turn politicians into street lamp decorations so you don’t have to be a slave to them and be free to own property and breed your women without worrying about supporting migrants and paying taxes to pedos&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871564&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871345&lt;br&gt;Based&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871577&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858758&lt;br&gt;europeans are under the impression that if they seethe harder, americans will die in estonia for ungrateful mongoloids who hate them, for free.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Keep in mind Europe already rejected, last year before any of the greenland stuff happened, beneficial trade deals where they&amp;#x27;d buy oil and natgas from america in return for us propping them up.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;They just don&amp;#x27;t seem to get..... it&amp;#x27;s not free. If you don&amp;#x27;t do anything at all for us, we aren&amp;#x27;t really allies, you&amp;#x27;re just a parasite faggot. This comes hand in hand with europeans trying to &amp;#x27;crash&amp;#x27; the dollar by unloading treasuries too. WHAT kind of ally does that? Tsk tsk. iceland is next.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871583&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871248&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859999&lt;br&gt;weird that euroboomers (and americaboomers) could have prevented this with a simple trick called &amp;quot;paying your kids enough to afford a life&amp;quot;. Oh well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871638&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kek you russian bots are working overtime. Must be hard times at the Kremlin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871735&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Except for some brief moment in history, Europe was always a shit hole.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871748&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858634&lt;br&gt;Americans really believe europe is falling while in reality we are more and more close to the strongest federation the world ever seen, seethe harder amerimutt&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871781&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871748&lt;br&gt;you imported tens of millions of hostile welfare parasites and your median age is like 55. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;yes we are fucked too but you are dancing way closer to the edge than we are&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871793&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859999&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;its all their fault&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871812&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871781&lt;br&gt;As if american white peoples median age is any lower.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871830&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871735&lt;br&gt;elaborate&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871847&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871781&lt;br&gt;America imported even more shitskins than any euro nation, we at least have a stable crime free society from actually spending on people instead of billionaires and a block of 800M people to trade with, we will age gracefully and peaceful, your society is violent asf, you are insanely fucked&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871859&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858658&lt;br&gt;Before they send their own people into the grinder, they&amp;#x27;ll deport millions of Ukrainian refugees (male only) to get them drafted and sent to the frontlines. When you see that happening, that&amp;#x27;s one step closer to WW3. Germs aren&amp;#x27;t going to die in Ukraine while Ukrainians themselves are chilling in Germany&lt;br&gt;And there&amp;#x27;s already no red line for military support in terms of weapons and vehicles&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871895&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858773&lt;br&gt;he looks just like all my cousins in Brazil&lt;br&gt;spoiled little fuckers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871919&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870882&lt;br&gt;No woman has ever looked at me like that&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61872479&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just use your gains to move to South America o algo. Whites are committing suicide as directed by kikes, you don&amp;#x27;t have to play by their rules.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873023&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871812&lt;br&gt;It is by about 2 years&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871847&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;we at least have a stable crime free society&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;we will age gracefully and peaceful, your society is violent &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You sure about that? From Bataclan to trucks of peace to grenades and grooming gangs you don&amp;#x27;t look any better.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61873056&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873023&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;isolated events from 10 years ago, a malmo-specific monkey hot potato game and paki gangs on an island that distanced itself from Europe&lt;br&gt;A single month in shartistan generates more violent deaths than that&lt;br&gt;Step up your bait&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>