<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>/biz/ Active (filtered, with replies)</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/</link><description>Filtered out: general, gme, bbbyq. OP + first 3 replies + last 30 replies.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 23:59:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>I just found out my ex got married AND pregnant one year after we broke up What are the financial consequences for simps… — 121 replies — 484.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861117</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861117?lm=1771286198</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 23:56:38 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;I just found out my ex got married AND pregnant one year after we broke up What are the financial consequences for simps…&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861117'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 121 • Updated: 2026-02-16 23:56 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;I just found out my ex got married AND pregnant one year after we broke up&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What are the financial consequences for simps to marry and impregnate women they don&amp;#x27;t even know?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861127&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861117&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;OPs ex dodged a bullet by prolonging her fertile years with a loser and instead got married and did her god-given duty&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861151&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861127&lt;br&gt;well, in this situation i dodged a bullet because she was just a do-nothing ukrainian whore vaping and drinking coca-cola 24/7 who was on tv in her early 20&amp;#x27;s (so a prostitute) and even admitted she had sex with a nigger in moscow&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I saw the picture of the wedding and the guy who married her look like he is in his 40&amp;#x27;s and is quite ugly but he must have money, not even sure the bedroom of the kid look like shit...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;i was just asking why do men MARRY women at any point? Even more after 6/12 months of relationship?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861301&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861117&lt;br&gt;listen up, i will make this so clear for you.&lt;br&gt; a woman&amp;#x27;s asset is her youth and consequently beauty. Once a girl hits 30s, her options become incredibly limited, given she is not in the top 10% in looks. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;your ex probably panicked about her future, and found an easily manipulatable guy to provide her the sense of security she was looking for. If the guy she married is in his 40s, this guy is also experiencing a mid life crisis and is trying to make up for lost time. And yeah, if he is 40 single and childless, granted he has a 9-5 job, he likely has money saved up. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Only an idiot would risk half his belongings like that on less than a year of relationship. someone not thinking in their right mind, because even a year isn&amp;#x27;t enough to know someone. In fact, 3-4 years is ideal time to propose because the initial feelings of love would have worn off and then the real question if you want to be with this person for the rest of your life becomes easier to answer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862650&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862629&lt;br&gt;lol, asian women are just as trashy entitled bitches, why do you think asia has the worst fertility rates of the world? you niggas are delusional and fall for the minimum women do in the few years it takes for them to leave their shithole, you are still way more likely to find true companionship as hard as it may be from a local who is not looking at you as a walking golden ticket from poverty&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862656&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862649&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;good for the baby bro, get over it, we are all made to love and be loved.&lt;br&gt;kek, there you go OP, at least you can support your waifus boyfriends son, at least you can stop shitposting about it on /biz/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862660&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862650&lt;br&gt;yeah once you&amp;#x27;ve fucked an asian for at least 3-6 months you know better. though i liked the japanese girl i was with for longer than 6 months&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862672&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862650&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;why do you think asia has the worst fertility rates of the world?&lt;br&gt;Because they&amp;#x27;re intelligent.&lt;br&gt;https://claudekeruru.substack.com/p/the-reversal-of-the-flynn-effect&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Would you prefer a birthrate of niggers with nigger IQ competing with infinity jeets, or a lower birthrate with high IQ population and no immigrants?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862676&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862650&lt;br&gt;yeah these niggas think western white women are soulless materialistic whores lmaooooo hahaha asian women are way worse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862695&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862676&lt;br&gt;Statistics and anons experiences &amp;gt; your boomerisms that you made up&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862712&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862672&lt;br&gt;Yeah buddy, I&amp;#x27;m sure this high IQ low birthrate kids will definetely be able to stand their ground against the nigger and jeet hordes averaging 17yo amongst them while 50% of the asians are above 50, legit stupid cope take, no youth=no power at all&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862724&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862712&lt;br&gt;Shitting out kids and abandoning them is a worse fate than having a smaller population and no immigrants. It&amp;#x27;s obvious that you&amp;#x27;re low IQ or you could have parsed this. A population of retards will never stop immigration. They will live off government gibs just like niggers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862733&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862724&lt;br&gt;Nice you won the moral victory, too bad moral victory didn&amp;#x27;t stop any white colony from being overrun by the low iq masses and turned into shitholes, be very happy about your moral iq superiority in your cuckshed while a horde of subhumans cut your throat and rape your high iq children to death, moron countless examples of high iq minority elite getting overrun in all of history and you come with this crap&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862750&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862733&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t see whites doing anything to stop immigration. The biggest enemy of remigration is white women. What are you even trying to argue for?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shitting out kids isn&amp;#x27;t going to end immigration. Shitting out kids is never going to compete with infinity jeets, because there were more of them from the beginning. You&amp;#x27;re not going to catch up.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;WMAF and brown genocide is the only real future.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862766&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862750&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The biggest enemy of remigration is white women.&lt;br&gt;which group of voters votes more right wing besides white men than white women? no coping allowed, only actual arguments&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862772&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862750&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862695&lt;br&gt;how about we look at asian woman voting trends?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862774&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862750&lt;br&gt;Average age in asia is older than europe, there&amp;#x27;s very little asians for you to pull this eurasian race thing and even if you did, it never stopped blacks and jeets from hitting asians just as they do whites for being sucessful, both will lose either way buddy, its just human nature the barbaric horde always conquer the &amp;quot;superior&amp;quot; civilized people unable to fight, whites and asians will get breed out, raped, lose control of their old countries and ultimately be mixed into the new conquering pool, as it always happened throughout history, may as well marry a jeeta if you wanna survive, they don&amp;#x27;t even need high iq just enough to pass as mediocre to rule the new world&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862787&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862772&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862766&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;MUH VOOOOTING&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;IM GOOOONA VOOOOOOTE&lt;br&gt;As if that has changed anything at all. And you&amp;#x27;re talking about boomer women, not single white women. Single white women vote more left than niggers. Boomer women vote more, and are the largest demographic of white women. Therefore your whole cope is flawed.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862774&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;whataboutism&lt;br&gt;Boring.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862792&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862787&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;As if that has changed anything at all. And you&amp;#x27;re talking about boomer women, not single white women. Single white women vote more left than niggers. Boomer women vote more, and are the largest demographic of white women. Therefore your whole cope is flawed.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;durrr voting doesnt matter&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;so it doesn&amp;#x27;t matter that the vast majority of asian women OPENLY vote against white interests&lt;br&gt;you&amp;#x27;re coping like a fucking retard like usual to try to justify your yellow fever, yet you havent even dated an asian you fucking loser.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862794&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862787&lt;br&gt;call me for whataboutism while posting a infographic saying exactly what I said will happen&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862798&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862794&lt;br&gt;hes just trying to cope for being rejected once in middle school and now developing yellow fever.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;the only way to save whites is for us to mix with random asians because they&amp;#x27;re the only ones that like me!&lt;br&gt;many such cases&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862802&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861151&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I saw the picture of the wedding and the guy who married her look like he is in his 40&amp;#x27;s and is quite ugly but he must have money, not even sure the bedroom of the kid look like shit...&lt;br&gt;so average 4channer bragging about being 48 with 21 btc and a 29yo ukrainian blonde wife huh.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862810&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862802&lt;br&gt;pfft, this guys a chad, look at his timid photo taken in his parents house of what could be his sisters legs, voyeur style. he&amp;#x27;s clearly chad.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862406&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862820&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862792&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m advocating for genocide and you&amp;#x27;re copypasting cuckservative talking points. Who wins here?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862794&lt;br&gt;It is whataboutism. There&amp;#x27;s billions of Asian women. There&amp;#x27;s not billions of white men. Ergo, there&amp;#x27;s enough to go around. There, the end.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862798&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;re defending white women who hate you and openly physically fight against your existence and fight and die for the existence of immigrants. No other race of women does this to their own race of men. None. Wignats are the biggest cucks in the history of the world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862825&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862810&lt;br&gt;If my sister was hot enough I would fuck her too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862838&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862820&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I&amp;#x27;m advocating for genocide and you&amp;#x27;re copypasting cuckservative talking points. Who wins here?&lt;br&gt;you can&amp;#x27;t even advocate for your own removal from celibacy&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;You&amp;#x27;re defending white women who hate you and openly physically fight against your existence and fight and die for the existence of immigrants. No other race of women does this to their own race of men. None. Wignats are the biggest cucks in the history of the world.&lt;br&gt;no i&amp;#x27;m not, i&amp;#x27;m pointing out voting trends show the opposite of what retarded non-white mexicans like you think to begin with. you then fail to address that point and usually crash out, sperging out about some nonsense regarding &amp;quot;foids&amp;quot; or whatever&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862825&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;If my sister was hot enough I would fuck her too.&lt;br&gt;lets hope anons voyeur career on his sister picks up&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862839&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862820&lt;br&gt;billions of asian women with an average age of 50, way past their reproductive age same as the average european age, you are not having kids nowhere near the numbers to fend off inevitable black/brown conquest with 3billion and a 5 kids per head fertility no matter how much cope you pull, asian chicks have the worst fertility in the world by far to make it worse, its a meeting of the dying&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862846&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862820&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;No other race of women does this to their own race of men.&lt;br&gt;btw, every single one of them does. it&amp;#x27;s why your women(im assuming latina) rush for white cock. the sooner you grow up and stop obsessing over white people the sooner you can embrace your non-white heritage&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862855&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862838&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;muh voting trends&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;im pointing out something that is completely irrelevant and not even factually correct&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;no i will not go and look at the demographics of white women reeee&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862839&lt;br&gt;Just admit you&amp;#x27;re autistic.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862846&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;if you don&amp;#x27;t suck turds out of white women&amp;#x27;s anus you&amp;#x27;re not white&lt;br&gt;lmao reality would prove the opposite.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862857&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862855&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;no i will not go and look at the demographics of white women reeee&lt;br&gt;white women demographics suggest they&amp;#x27;re the only right leaning group besides white men. you haven&amp;#x27;t posted anything otherwise and are screeching like a woman about it instead&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;lmao reality would prove the opposite.&lt;br&gt;when are you going to try to find out reality instead of pretending infographics with suspicious x axis graphs should define your political and seemingly sexual beliefs?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862869&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862857&lt;br&gt;Wignat ideology is centered around roasties. They have rallies for roasties. They have a 14 word slogan for roasties. They worship pagan idols of fat roasties. They post pics of roasties in wheat fields. They watch propaganda movies made by roasties. They build lebensborn camps for bulls to impregnate their favorite roasties. They idolize the nazis who were cucked by the millions when their trad roasties opened their legs for Russian cock. When you say &amp;quot;White Race&amp;quot; they&amp;#x27;re not thinking of the men who built civilization. They&amp;#x27;re thinking of roasties. Their stormfront forums are completely overrun with roasties crying about asian women. Their men sit around posting about how great roasties are while their &amp;quot;reformed&amp;quot; tradwives sit around watching nigger tiktoks. They worship &amp;quot;based&amp;quot; roastie e-celebs while attacking the misogynists who actually built their country before roasties took over. They watch roastie feminists whine about trannies and celebrate when the roasties win because those roasties are true red blooded trad roasties. They will tell you how much they hate roasties and how the wignat simp meme is a stale joke and they are just pretending to love roasties but the evidence speaks for itself in that wignats have always been and will be a group of roastie loving cucks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862871&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862869&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;heres a copypasta so i can ignore reality some more&lt;br&gt;you&amp;#x27;re not even white lmfao why are you so obsessed?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862877&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862871&lt;br&gt;Every reply you can and will possibly get from a roastie and/or simp/incel that worships roasties:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;you can&amp;#x27;t handle a white woman&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;you can&amp;#x27;t get a white woman&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;asian women love bbc spam.jpg&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;laowhy&amp;#x27;s wife&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;(((tenda spencer&amp;#x27;s))) cartoons&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;i would marry a nigger before i would marry asian&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;i would marry a coalburner before i marry an asian&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;(((elliot rodger)))&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;(((kelly baltazar)))&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;makeup actor swap webms, but it&amp;#x27;s totally the same person, asian women are ugly&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;asian women are plastic&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;asian women are robots&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;asian women wear makeup&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;muh blonde hair blue eyes&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;muh want my kids to look like me&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;i don&amp;#x27;t care if a white woman isn&amp;#x27;t virgin&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;muh white race&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;kids will hate you&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;kike&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;chang&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;you&amp;#x27;re not white&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;shill&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;if you like asian women you&amp;#x27;re a pedophile&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;you&amp;#x27;re anti-white if you don&amp;#x27;t worship white women&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;you&amp;#x27;re anti-white if you don&amp;#x27;t attack white men&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;white men are weak and that&amp;#x27;s why white women fuck niggers&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;kikes did this to white women&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;white women dindu nuffin&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;le reddit starter kit featuring a chinless male.jpg&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;why do you like asian women?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;muh green card&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;muh gold digger&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;muh take the kids and run&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;i think asian women are ugly&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;muh china&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;muh dogs&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;muh bugs&lt;br&gt;Cope&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862885&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862869&lt;br&gt;Why are we even arguing in the first place if your standing position is literally &amp;quot;fuck the white race, genocide whites now&amp;quot;? you don&amp;#x27;t to save whites or make high iq kids or anything like that, you are full on white genocide, somehow the super eurasian race didn&amp;#x27;t make russians or finns super people but this time it will work? nah you are just for white erasure bro, just stfu&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>/smg/ - Stock Market Gambling — 85 replies — 340.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861684</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861684?lm=1771285969</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 23:52:49 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;/smg/ - Stock Market Gambling&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861684'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 85 • Updated: 2026-02-16 23:52 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Casino Economy Edition&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Some helpful links to numb the pain&lt;br&gt;https://findahelpline.com/&lt;br&gt;https://www.nvidia.com/refunds/&lt;br&gt;https://www.whitehouse.gov/refunds&lt;br&gt;https://jlingz.com/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Educational sites:&lt;br&gt;https://www.investopedia.com&lt;br&gt;https://www.khanacademy.org/economics-finance-domain&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Financial TV Streams:&lt;br&gt;https://www.newslive.com/american/cnbc.html&lt;br&gt;https://www.livestreamy.net/bloomberg/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Charts:&lt;br&gt;https://www.tradingview.com&lt;br&gt;https://www.finscreener.com&lt;br&gt;https://www.portfoliovisualizer.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Screeners: so you feel like in the movies&lt;br&gt;https://finviz.com/&lt;br&gt;https://etfdb.com/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Gambling:&lt;br&gt;https://www.optionsplaybook.com/options-introduction/&lt;br&gt;https://www.optionsprofitcalculator.com&lt;br&gt;https://optionstrat.com/&lt;br&gt;https://www.optionistics.com/quotes/option-prices&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Pre-Market and Live data:&lt;br&gt;https://www.investing.com/indices/indices-futures&lt;br&gt;https://finance.yahoo.com/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Calendars&lt;br&gt;https://www.marketwatch.com/economy-politics/calendar&lt;br&gt;https://www.earningswhispers.com/calendar&lt;br&gt;https://www.cmegroup.com/trading/interest-rates/countdown-to-fomc.html&lt;br&gt;https://www.mortgagenewsdaily.com/data/building-permits&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Boomer Investing 101: so zoomers with meme stocks can outperform you&lt;br&gt;https://www.bogleheads.org/wiki/Getting_started&lt;br&gt;https://www.sec.gov/search-filings&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Misc smg:&lt;br&gt;https://www.financialjuice.com/home&lt;br&gt;https://finance.yahoo.com/trending-tickers&lt;br&gt;https://market24hclock.com/&lt;br&gt;https://www.dividendchannel.com/drip-returns-calculator&lt;br&gt;https://brokerchooser.com/&lt;br&gt;https://www.chathamfinancial.com/technology/us-market-rates&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Previously on /smg/: &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858740&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861716&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m an American, I have extreme anxiety that i can&amp;#x27;t sell or buy right now&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;so me, and my fellow americans formally decided were panic selling everything Tuesday&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;sorry euros&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861738&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861716&lt;br&gt;i just watch the spot silver chart and get either mad or relieved when it doesnt move very far from 75&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862526&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862447&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I feel like i should start doing options&lt;br&gt;I was only selling covered calls and doing well. Then I slowly expaned into buy calls and got wrecked (% wise not big $ losses because I was going small). I was way up on some calls and should have sold and taken the money, but no I waited and the stock price crashed and lost all the money. I will stick with selling coverd calls, easy money.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862574&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862492&lt;br&gt;teh fuck are u talkin &amp;#x27;boutz&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;https://youtu.be/SOloyjRxmXI?si=pYUEt3hRgsBxbouL&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862580&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;is it a dow/russell market or is tech still too strong?&lt;br&gt;china used to account for 15% of international trade, be our largest trading partner, now it is only about 10% and they are #3.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862588&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862574&lt;br&gt;she so cute, but not as cute as u&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862595&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canadian defense spending strategy paper is being release tomorrow.&lt;br&gt;Kraken Robotics was a good meme for a while.&lt;br&gt;Looking at CAE and FTG for potential to pump.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thoughts?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862609&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862510&lt;br&gt;indeed, options are dangerous when you dont know what the fuck you are doing, that is how retards implode their portfolios in a matter of seconds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862620&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;Just kidding we over estimated jobs in 2025 by a million so actually we had no job growth&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;M SORRY WHAT&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862627&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862574&lt;br&gt;that fillym about the old hag who had the decency to fuck off out of the spotlight unlike your avatar&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862628&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862609&lt;br&gt;i do that regularly&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862652&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862627&lt;br&gt;max had a higher much higher power level and would have prevented that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862654&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862254&lt;br&gt;cute and valid stock pick&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862670&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862652&lt;br&gt;sunset boulevard is one of my favorite movies, it&amp;#x27;s 3 tragedies really, joe&amp;#x27;s, norma&amp;#x27;s, and max&amp;#x27;s. and even though he&amp;#x27;s not the focus of the film, it&amp;#x27;s max&amp;#x27;s story that is the saddest and deepest. he created norma, and kept her sick instead of getting her well. even though norma and joe are despicable in their own way, max is the architect of the entire world they inhabit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862682&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;are you guys really evil or do you just pretend to scare everyone off&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862708&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862682&lt;br&gt;Uhm actually the system is evil and my participation in said system is morally ambigious and requires no introspection at all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862709&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862682&lt;br&gt;I would have loved to be the guy standing behind the mg on d-day&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862715&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; futures&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862720&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;So are we going up or down tomorrow&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862734&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Futures just opened&lt;br&gt;What does this mean for the future of humanity?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862741&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862734&lt;br&gt;actually we all know there is no hope&lt;br&gt;I wonder if I am the first one who says it&lt;br&gt;elon musk space rocket lyfe lol lmao even&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862742&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862492&lt;br&gt;i think he was sick of the both of them&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862747&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;anyone ever just been sittin there with nothing to do and you start burgin all of sudden?. i was burgin hard bro&amp;#x27;s. Had to make some burgers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862751&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862715&lt;br&gt;Is he the source of all the creep shots on /gif/ ?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862756&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862734&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;What does this mean for the future of humanity?&lt;br&gt;its for sale&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862761&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862628&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862762&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862747&lt;br&gt;those aren&amp;#x27;t pancakes are they?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862808&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Europoor here , i took out a loan of 20000€ to invest in hycroft mining and first majestic silver. Am i gonna make it?&lt;br&gt;I’ve memorized their pattern ,every few days they briefly “uncap” the paper market and you get 15–20% pops&lt;br&gt;I wait. Demand pulls it back. On those moves, i sell the Hycroft position and buy it back later.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862831&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why do you retards buy stocks lol? It&amp;#x27;s all fake and overpriced to the extreme. Just by a world ETF and be happy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862832&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862747&lt;br&gt;Is that a proper Good Morning burger? Delicious&lt;br&gt;What&amp;#x27;d you wash it down with?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862833&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862831&lt;br&gt;this is bait&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862868&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862734&lt;br&gt;impossible to know until we&amp;#x27;ve seen several animal webms about it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Oldfags I summon you — 38 replies — 125.3/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61856347</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61856347?lm=1771285243</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 23:40:43 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Oldfags I summon you&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61856347'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 38 • Updated: 2026-02-16 23:40 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oldfags I know you&amp;#x27;re still here. A lot of charts look like they&amp;#x27;ve bottomed. Tell me what to stack I have 3.8 BTC and looking to acquire alts as I think they will start pumping now the money printers returning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856352&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;looking to acquire alts&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856368&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856347&lt;br&gt;Took one of these Topgolf girls to a round of golf once and they were terrible lmao&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856433&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856368&lt;br&gt;What the fuck is a topgolf girl that girls swing is immaculate 99% of people at these ranges cannot hit a ball straight&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856682&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856347&lt;br&gt;how many bitcoin for a golf bunny like that?&lt;br&gt;also moar&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856732&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856347&lt;br&gt;old fags no longer hold crypto&lt;br&gt;t. old fag&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856793&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856732&lt;br&gt;this desu&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856797&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856347&lt;br&gt;we finna linu&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857022&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856488&lt;br&gt;The only weird guy are you assuming you have to hire a girl to go play golf with her&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857025&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856551&lt;br&gt;Nah everything was frontrunned, the alt bear market started more then a year ago&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857031&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;alts will never pump again&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;the only notable alt that pumped last cycle was xrp&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;unless you&amp;#x27;re counting like a 2-3x as pumping then goodluck, they can also fall 90% or more from here&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857237&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Binance coin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857946&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856509&lt;br&gt;You guys are faggots man&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857986&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857025&lt;br&gt;this look to alts the bear market started in jan 2025&lt;br&gt;btc was just lucky some boomers pumped the etf to get a higher high in oct, but this market has been a ghost town for the past year&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858251&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856347&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;looking to acquire alts&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;re doomed. Shitcoins aren&amp;#x27;t going to pump ever again. I sincerely doubt ETH will even survive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858300&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856347&lt;br&gt;Not an originalfag or a 2017 oldfag, but I am a 2019 unc. Get out now and for the love of God stay away from alts, not even memeing. The bear was confirmed the moment we closed under 100k.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I rotated to stocks back in November.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856551&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856732&lt;br&gt;this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858317&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856509&lt;br&gt;how&amp;#x27;d you find her name? also what is it? asking for a fren&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858346&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856732&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858300&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856551&lt;br&gt;jewish posts&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860179&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856433&lt;br&gt;I hit straight balls if you know what I mean :)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860219&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oldest fag possible. Migrated day one from /g/. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The real dumping hasn&amp;#x27;t started yet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860260&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856551&lt;br&gt;Looks ljke the next &amp;#x27;cycle&amp;#x27; is going to go alll the wayy to 155k.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860609&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meaningfully buying across any of these is extremely high confidence, with particular emphasis on the front end:&lt;br&gt;XRP, QNT, CC, XDC, ALGO, DAG, HBAR, XLM, SUI, SEI, APT, FLR, ONDO, NOM, ADA, HYPE, SOL, POL, ATOM, DAG, AAVE, DOT, VET, ZRO, RED.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860614&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ancientfag here (I used to mine btc on my gaming pc back in 2012)&lt;br&gt;why are faggots still falling for the jeetcoin rugpulls in &amp;lt;current year&amp;gt;?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860615&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Topgolf is retarded&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Everytime I went the place was filled with whores, niggers and trailer trash&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860630&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860615&lt;br&gt;this is everywhere except certain higher grocery stores.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860639&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856347&lt;br&gt;XRP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860653&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856347&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;a bitch like that will make more money in a year than 90% of normal men will make in a decade &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;women will still call this society a fucking patriarchy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861628&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860219&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The real dumping hasn&amp;#x27;t started yet.&lt;br&gt;what will dump the least, or what will gain the most as the rest dumps?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861782&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860653&lt;br&gt;They only say that because 99% of billionaires are men.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861800&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856347&lt;br&gt;She probably leaves the cutest little turds in the toilet you ever seen&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861818&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860653&lt;br&gt;shows what kind of man you are really. My friend complained to me once about how unfair it was that girls can make easy money being whores on OF and social media and I told him that he was pretty much complaining about how he can&amp;#x27;t show his cock and balls on the internet for money just because he is a man, and that makes him a faggot&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861828&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860219&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;That fact that you even know buttcoin was on /g/ before the containment board /biz/, proves to me you are a confirmed oldfag. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Based.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862387&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861828&lt;br&gt;reposting watermarked telegram content&lt;br&gt;ngmi&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862818&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858346&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;DA JOOOOOS&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>SAY IT /BIZ/ ETHEREUM = PROGRAMMABLE MONEY — 12 replies — 48.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860962</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860962?lm=1771286061</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 23:54:21 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;SAY IT /BIZ/ ETHEREUM = PROGRAMMABLE MONEY&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860962'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 12 • Updated: 2026-02-16 23:54 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;SAY IT /BIZ/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;ETHEREUM = PROGRAMMABLE MONEY&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860982&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860962&lt;br&gt;ultrasound chads can&amp;#x27;t stop winning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861322&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860962&lt;br&gt;lol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861377&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860962&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;PROGRAMMABLE MONEY&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;There is no use case for this in the real world&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;B-B-BUT-&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;No&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861389&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860962&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;$87M&lt;br&gt;Wow it&amp;#x27;s literally nothing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862015&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860962&lt;br&gt;Not going back to that 25 dollar swap fee scam chain. Also the eth team could just fork the entire project whenever they feel like it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862198&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860962&lt;br&gt;You would think that these harvard cunts are smart enough to buy the real asset instead of the etf.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862246&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860962&lt;br&gt;eth will never deliver on what they&amp;#x27;ve promised. its been over 10 years we&amp;#x27;ve been hearing that smart contracts will be the future of business and finance. all we&amp;#x27;ve got was&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;cryptokitties&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;NFTs&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;USDT money laundering&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;shitcoin casino&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;ICOs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862286&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860962&lt;br&gt;ETH is the future of finance and I&amp;#x27;m tired of pretending it isn&amp;#x27;t&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862299&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860962&lt;br&gt;all the stablecoins use ethereum so there will be demand for that and 1500-2000 is probably bottom territory&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862449&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Glamsterdam.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862873&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860962&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;first, do a premine&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;create &amp;quot;world computer&amp;quot; running on POW&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;decide that&amp;#x27;s inefficient&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;switch it over to POS&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;just happens to benefit all the whales&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;like the billionaire founder who premined it&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;but somehow it&amp;#x27;s still a &amp;quot;world computer&amp;quot; that &amp;quot;runs code&amp;quot; and is &amp;quot;programmable&amp;quot; even though POS&lt;br&gt;seems a bit scammy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Crypto has ruined my life honestly I’m 69, going 70. — 8 replies — 32.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61862685</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61862685?lm=1771286190</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 23:56:30 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Crypto has ruined my life honestly I’m 69, going 70.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61862685'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 8 • Updated: 2026-02-16 23:56 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Crypto has ruined my life honestly&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I’m 69, going 70. Down to my last 17 BSV with no job willing to hire me. In debt of over $33k borrowing from friends and family in a span of 9 months&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now i’m not sure where to even start with my life, feeling depressed almost every single day&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862713&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862685&lt;br&gt;if you got time on your hands and live in USA get into the pokemon hustle, learn all your local Target/Walmart/Best buy location pokemon drops and wait in like for 2-6 hours(if needed) to get the stuff and then flip it through various online sources or FB marketplace, etc. Also do not tell your friends about it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862738&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862685&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;start with my life&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;70&lt;br&gt;I think your life is over, Boomboom. If you didn&amp;#x27;t have kids, or you fucked over your kids and grandkids like all the other boomers, don&amp;#x27;t expect an easy death. Take your due. Get right with Jesus and prepare for the end. And if you kill yourself, you can give up on going to heaven.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862799&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;this is going to be most millennials in just 10 years kek.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862801&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862738&lt;br&gt;This, don&amp;#x27;t kill yourself or you won&amp;#x27;t get into Valhalla. Die in glorious battle, killing judeo-christian golem and their masters. It&amp;#x27;s the redemption you seek.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862860&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862801&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862861&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;as evidenced by the above comments, maybe don&amp;#x27;t spend so much time online, esp degenerate 4chan. As long as you can keep living in good health there is a lot of enjoyment you can get out of life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862862&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;nigga you are 70 you are done for&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862884&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862801&lt;br&gt;Synagogue of Satan &amp;quot;jew&amp;quot; who say he is a jew but isn&amp;#x27;t spotted. Revelations 3:4 KJV&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>What kind of entry level jobs can you get with an MBA these days? — 5 replies — 20.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860898</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860898?lm=1771286263</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 23:57:43 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;What kind of entry level jobs can you get with an MBA these days?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860898'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 5 • Updated: 2026-02-16 23:57 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;What kind of entry level jobs can you get with an MBA these days?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860922&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860898&lt;br&gt;Depends on the MBA &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-state school MBA? Wagie job&lt;br&gt;-top 10 MBA? Investment banking job or Fortune 500 middle manager to CFO track&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861474&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860922&lt;br&gt;What kind of job titles should I be searching for online?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861485&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;entry level jobs&lt;br&gt;In 2026? lel&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861490&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fluffer&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862887&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860898&lt;br&gt;mop the floor, brainiac&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>GERMANY TO END BURGERGELD PROGRAMS — 72 replies — 189.8/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858970</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858970?lm=1771284969</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 23:36:09 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;GERMANY TO END BURGERGELD PROGRAMS&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858970'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 72 • Updated: 2026-02-16 23:36 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;WILL BE REPLACED WITH A STRICTER PROGRAM IF YOU REFUSE WORK. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEXT STOP, PRIVATIZED HEALTHCARE.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858974&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Uh oh, Europeans actually have to work for a living now? Aw shucks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858980&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858974&lt;br&gt;They will soon legalize 12 hour work days much like Argentina has done. Even contributing 5% of their GDP to NATO has ultimately bankrupted them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859007&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858970&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wait you could get NEETbux in Germany this whole time by simply “refusing to work”? WTF&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860527&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860446&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;hurr durr the only way to make money is by sucking a jews dick&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860538&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860527&lt;br&gt;wageslaves are so traumatized by wageslavery and interviewing that they&amp;#x27;re spreading their defeatism everywhere they go as a shitty coping mechanism. You know that they&amp;#x27;re forcing goyim to humiliate themselves with 5-10 round interviews nowadays? Insane.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860550&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860538&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;wagecuck&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;hypergamble to a few million&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;live in poverty on welfare&lt;br&gt;Not great options. I choose to wagecuck.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860567&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860527&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;You just can&amp;#x27;t have a business, ok????&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860591&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860550&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;it&amp;#x27;s either the whip or picking cotton&lt;br&gt;That false dichotomy is sure proof of wageslave brainrot. I don&amp;#x27;t blame you, though. The whole system is rigged against you from birth and every aspect of your human nature is weaponized against you by the very thing you&amp;#x27;re meant to worship as a social animal, i.e. society.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860601&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858970&lt;br&gt;They just gave away all our money to Ausländers and now that the social systems are running dry they are simply getting rid of them kek.&lt;br&gt;Nothing they do will fix this. Humanity is doomed.&lt;br&gt;Accelerationism is the only way.&lt;br&gt;Let the third world starve and divert fund into AI datacenters.&lt;br&gt;The wolf will chew its own leg off to survive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860612&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860601&lt;br&gt;third world is the biggest net exporter of food to the point frenchoids were crying it would kill their overpriced artistical wine or something, they aint starving bro&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860626&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860591&lt;br&gt;Sorry chief, I find the idea of opening a business to be enticing but I don’t see any sort of moat I could pursue with it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860651&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858970&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858974&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860660&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860612&lt;br&gt;Africa imports a lot of food&lt;br&gt;And France was rightfully complaining that imposing huge restrictions on European agriculture while signing free trade agreements with countries having little restrictions is retarded&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860678&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859446&lt;br&gt;a 10% reduction? kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860682&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860422&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;10 year gap&lt;br&gt;I tell them it is due to the government forcing employers to lower standards to hire the affirmative action subhumans. They never call me back, because they are off giving useless lazy meritless and sometime convict affirmative action subhumans jobs. &lt;br&gt;Enjoy paying to taxes to niggers, spics, and cunts that hate you, just in the vain hopes they one day stop calling you a racist and sexist. Get back to work wagie... the whole economy rests on you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860686&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860191&lt;br&gt;Gas?!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860707&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860422&lt;br&gt;kek, they won&amp;#x27;t work at all, german economy will implode and as merz said they already can&amp;#x27;t afford the welfare + pensions, it will just shrink till it gets too low to live then they will just kys as by now they are legit unable to live at all&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860723&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859099&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;this nigga thinks German economy circa 1988 is anything like today&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lol&lt;br&gt;Lmao even&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860724&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860401&lt;br&gt;a drooly retard eh? yeah that sounds just perfect for our new expanded military, the bundeswehr needs you to pick this uniform, this little sign and just stand there to block the evil russian drones with your face for us&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860758&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;tfw the only time in my life where I might receive neetbux for a few months is the exact time this happens&lt;br&gt;fucking lol my entire life is me getting fucked by the universe. Nothing good ever happens to me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860764&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860626&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;moat&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;he fell for Buffett boomer brain rot &lt;br&gt;The only moats Buffett had were his generous throat and his congressman daddy. And let&amp;#x27;s not forget about being lucky enough to be born in close proximity to swollen jewish nuts in Israel&amp;#x27;s 2nd state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860766&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860758&lt;br&gt;join a gang, sell weed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861462&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858970&lt;br&gt;NooOoOO&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861576&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858970&lt;br&gt;thats gut. not because of the money, it wont help in any significant way but because its a statement. fuck bürgis, fuck ausländer&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861599&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858970&lt;br&gt;They have been rebranding the same system for almost 25 years now. The previous government eased up on some of the welfare restrictions because they were largely pointless. The new(old) sanctions don&amp;#x27;t really change anything because even with them you can be permanently on welfare in Germany as long as you show up to your jobcenter appointments. Nobody in Germany is going to hire someone who hasn&amp;#x27;t worked for years and is clearly just applying because the jobcenter is pressuring them. This is just a huge waste of everyone&amp;#x27;s time and part of Germany&amp;#x27;s soviet-tier obscuring of unemployment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861817&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860422&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;It&amp;#x27;ll be hard to explain the 10+ year gap&lt;br&gt;16 years gapmaxxer here, would you hire me?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862208&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Every nation has 10% unemployable retards. What to do with them?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;send them into the meatgrinder&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;employ them for the least possible payment&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;give them fake jobs&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;giver them life long gibs payed by everyone else&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A nation can do any of these without problems. BUT: If you open your borders and let the 10% retards of the entire third world in, you can not give them gibs anymore or you risk financial collapse. Especially if you destroy your own industry and energy security. The meatgrinder is then the only viable solution. Prepare for a war.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862662&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860724&lt;br&gt;getting out from Bundeswehr cuckery is even easier than getting welfare.&lt;br&gt;just fake mental illness and you cant work there. ez.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862678&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862662&lt;br&gt;that&amp;#x27;s for now buddy, things will change pretty fast when we attack those pesky russians to save EVROPA, our poor refugees can&amp;#x27;t go, so its time for private retard from munich to catch a drone, you are legit stupid and not only faking if you believe all that goodwill shit won&amp;#x27;t dissapear from the constitution as soon as they need meat, you will be the retard brick to the new EU federation, be glad&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862777&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862678&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;tfw only germans have to serve in the Volksfront&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;12% of our pop doesn&amp;#x27;t even have a german pass&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;tfw they are getting welfare and Neetmax while i&amp;#x27;m send off to the grinder after taxing the shit out of my market gains&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862781&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;why would you give people free money for burgers? lazy europoops.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862784&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859975&lt;br&gt;reminder the leaders are all boomers but when you point this out some tranny will start screaming to stop blaming the boomers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;All it takes is for non-elderly people to rise up and say &amp;quot;get the fuck out of my way grandpa or I will cave your head in&amp;quot; and there&amp;#x27;s nothing they can do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862797&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860147&lt;br&gt;it&amp;#x27;s despicable. these assholes come here, shit up our culture and behave like the are welcome here. cultures should be kept separate. you have to go back to /pol/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Privacy Coins — 50 replies — 128.9/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61849447</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61849447?lm=1771284939</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 23:35:39 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Privacy Coins&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61849447'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 50 • Updated: 2026-02-16 23:35 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whether you like it or not, BTC is dying. Which way anons?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849481&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gold and silver.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849898&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849447&lt;br&gt;XMR as always. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849481&lt;br&gt;Acceptable but unusable for internet transactions and too easily stolen. Also makes smaller or spontaneous transactions harder unless the governments were to issue gold coins again and that would be bearish.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849958&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849447&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;BTC is a pedo coin&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;most used currency for CP is not however&lt;br&gt;quit the infighting, monegro.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855919&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855898&lt;br&gt;Several reasons, actually:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Centralized distribution from early dev-taxes to the founders (these taxes are still baked in but go to a slightly-less centralized committee now.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Privacy can be disabled at the protocol level because miners can reject the shielded pool. There is no fix to this because it would require removing the transparent pool entirely which would make Zcash delisted from all exchanges that it intentionally cripples its privacy for.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Mining hashrate is cornered, Zcash is 60% mined by a singe pool at any given time, and the 20% pool is the one that blocks the shielded pool.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Founder outright said they work with DC and will make Zcash private but not so private it could be used for crime.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855926&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849447&lt;br&gt;US Dollars ticker $&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856365&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855898&lt;br&gt;mossad coin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856605&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The line breaks being inconsistent is the same as all three 6&amp;#x27;s not being in upright position, for the two nuts for the tubal cain facebook logo not matching &amp;quot;Exactly.&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;No, it&amp;#x27;s not similar at all. The arches of the M are completely different.&lt;br&gt;The chrome symbol is the divine king symbol and matches exactly, and you can see far more similarities between the tubal Cain and facebook logos.&lt;br&gt;This meme sucks, the discord you got it from sucks, your ability to evaluate schizo levels suck, and you suck.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856661&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856605&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;unironically puts himself in a position that makes him look like he works for the very societies listed in infograph by explaining symbols further&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;t. mossad devil worshipper who sucks mason dick&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;only furthers the stereotype that monegro may be untrustworthy&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;claims i got my low quality infograph from discord&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Nigger i dont use discord&lt;br&gt;kek, the low quality bait and switch tactic always works on self proclaimed smart people&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856710&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849481&lt;br&gt;basedo!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856781&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;hurr durr i tricked you&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;a REAL schizo wouldn&amp;#x27;t know THAT much&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;i also don&amp;#x27;t know what t. means&lt;br&gt;I think we&amp;#x27;re done here&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857609&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849898&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;ve had thousands in BTC stolen via address poisoning, but my gold and silver are safe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858772&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856781&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;i also don&amp;#x27;t know what t. means&lt;br&gt;you have to be 18 to post here anon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858821&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858772&lt;br&gt;I remember when I turned 18 and my parents took me aside and told me that the abbreviated form of &amp;quot;regards&amp;quot; in finnish was a 4chan meme&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859002&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849447&lt;br&gt;Soon enough (this year) everything on ETH will be privacy enabled by ZAMA&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860206&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855868&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Imagine ignoring it so hard that people like epstein are allowed to exist and eat your next door neighbors children while they backdoor BTC and then promote it. Fuck off.&lt;br&gt;Why would I care about BTC when Monero exists? Why are you trying to make this about BTC in the first place when I clearly spoke about the claims you made about XMR? &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Im going to report your post as spam because none of what you said makes sense.&lt;br&gt;You claim that you were browsing the general but you haven&amp;#x27;t seen the main topic of the last few generals? Just admit that you&amp;#x27;re wrong. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857609&lt;br&gt;Gold can&amp;#x27;t be stolen? I&amp;#x27;d say it&amp;#x27;s far easier to pick a lock than the attack you fell victim to, if the user is somewhat attentive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861627&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860206&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Why would I care about BTC when Monero exists? Why are you trying to make this about BTC in the first place when I clearly spoke about the claims you made about XMR? &lt;br&gt;epstein files show he not only met with moot from 4chan, but also conspired to start /pol/, and had his hands in the israeli team that began to work on bitcoins code. XMR is also in said infographic due to masonic smybols, and has bots on their board. Thats why I created this general after finding the schizo infographic, neither BTC nor XMR can be trusted.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;You claim that you were browsing the general but you haven&amp;#x27;t seen the main topic of the last few generals? Just admit that you&amp;#x27;re wrong. &lt;br&gt;I hate talking to retarded bots. Admit that Im wrong about what exactly? that your entire thread glows to high heaven or that you &amp;quot;main topic&amp;quot; is non existant across the first 3 maxed out posts of general info? &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;bot continues to talk about how its far more unlikely for anons BTC to be stolen via address poisoning than for someone to pick his locks and steal his gold. Bots are coded by jeets, transfolk, and der jude, none of which are qualified to write bots.&lt;br&gt;How unfortunate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861669&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861627&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;epstein files show he not only met with moot from 4chan, but also conspired to start /pol/, and had his hands in the israeli team that began to work on bitcoins code.&lt;br&gt;Ok? I&amp;#x27;m here for XMR considering this thread is about privacy coins and picrel features XMR prominently in the middle. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;XMR is also in said infographic due to masonic smybols,&lt;br&gt;Back to hating the letter M? &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;and has bots on their board.&lt;br&gt;Wrong, nervajeet&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;after finding the schizo infographic,&lt;br&gt;In the Monero general, mind you&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;neither BTC nor XMR can be trusted.&lt;br&gt;Where&amp;#x27;s the problem in the code?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I hate talking to retarded bots.&lt;br&gt;Preferable to jeets on discord&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Admit that Im wrong about what exactly?&lt;br&gt;About Monero. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;that your entire thread glows to high heaven&lt;br&gt;Because we don&amp;#x27;t tolerate jeetcoins? lol&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;that you &amp;quot;main topic&amp;quot; is non existant across the first 3 maxed out posts of general info?&lt;br&gt;Are you seriously claiming that nerva wasn&amp;#x27;t mentioned at all in the last three generals? It&amp;#x27;s been mentioned by name over 100 times in the current general and it&amp;#x27;s not the first one to feature this irrelevant jeetcoin.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Bots are coded by jeets,&lt;br&gt;Says someone defending the literal jeetcoin, how ironic. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Show me the flaw you see in Monero&amp;#x27;s code.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861976&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HOLY SHIT GUYS OP IS A FREEMASON&lt;br&gt;HE EVEN HAS 2 MASONIC MS IN HIS ID&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862096&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861976&lt;br&gt;Is that like a double agent kinda deal or did he get promoted?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862129&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849481&lt;br&gt;aggressively low IQ take on the left&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862460&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861669&lt;br&gt;l knew if i waited Iong enough, the bot wouId show. You cant foIIow any post and its repIies worth a damn. ldk why you keep bring up the same shit spamming it everywhere. l wish jannies wouId range ban your ass.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;No, we just despise you nerva shills. ... And then you just all seem to bring up, out of nowhere and completely unrelated of course, the solution which is an unmaintained jeetcoin with a ring size less than 1/3 of Monero&amp;#x27;s ring size and none of the development Monero received since 2018&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Wrong, nervajeet&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Preferable to jeets on discord&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Because we don&amp;#x27;t tolerate jeetcoins? lol&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Are you seriously claiming that nerva wasn&amp;#x27;t mentioned at all in the last three generals?&lt;br&gt;Cant fucking follow a conversation worth shit, you dumb bot code gets so mixed up between threads you think everyone is a nervjeet or whatever the fucking you keep going on about.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Says someone defending the literal jeetcoin, how ironic.&lt;br&gt;Niggerbot who brings up nerva in every thread he spams to(&amp;lt;- thats you, no one mentions nerva BUT you)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862129&lt;br&gt;super genius is blind to anything regarding esptein emails, even tho this shit has been identified for years.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861976&lt;br&gt;actually kind of funny, didnt even notice my id&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862475&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849447&lt;br&gt;How do I buy Monero without leaving a KYC trace?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I can&amp;#x27;t buy XMR directly on exchanges (UK). If I buy BTC -&amp;gt; the tax man can see I have BTC and will expect to see a &amp;quot;sell&amp;quot; at some point.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tried Bisq, but hardly any sellers and also a risk of your bank account getting flagged / closed if the person is dodgy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862494&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862460&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;the bot wouId show.&lt;br&gt;How come you didn&amp;#x27;t know this when I posted &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849898? Maybe you need to refine your instincts or could it be that all of your anti-Monero arguments are moot so you try to attack me? &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862460&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Cant fucking follow a conversation worth shit,&lt;br&gt;I directly replied to all of your points. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Niggerbot who brings up nerva in every thread he spams to(&amp;lt;- thats you, no one mentions nerva BUT you)&lt;br&gt;How come you always use this excuse when you got the pic from a nervajeet in the XMR general?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862530&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849447&lt;br&gt;Monero is the only privacy coin.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Any other digital asset is traceable.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You have 1 (one) more opportunity for an early Bitcoin moment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Monero will be the world currency of the 2030s and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862538&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;steals pic that is interesting from nervjeet&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;stolen image literally has the fucking fileneame from the post it came from&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;this bot thinks im the same guy&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;his nonsensical bot reply gives him away within a few posts because it always handles the same&lt;br&gt;Report this fucker, if he doesnt get banned, all the more reason to NOT trust monero or anyone pushing monero, because the bot is being run from 4chan itself.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;on the XMR thread, this is the same bot&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860201 DXIC7i+b&lt;br&gt;it just goes on and on. hope real anons find this post and start to question wtf is going on around here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862542&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862475&lt;br&gt;Do you have Revolut?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Use it on Hodlhodl (trade escrow service)&lt;br&gt;Send it to some BTC wallet (Sparrow)&lt;br&gt;Use Trocador to convert it to XMR&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862551&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859002&lt;br&gt;Privacy is basically impossible to do for smart contracts outside of creating a specific app such as Tornado. When you create specific apps such as Tornado, you make it extremely vulnerable to censorship from the government, like happened to Tornado. Even though the lawsuit was &amp;quot;dropped&amp;quot;, activity on Tornado is basically nonexistent because nobody trusts it anymore. They shouldn&amp;#x27;t. Likewise, nobody should ever trust a &amp;quot;privacy app&amp;quot; on top of a public L1.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;And don&amp;#x27;t get me started on how ridiculous a &amp;quot;privacy L2&amp;quot; would be on top of a public L1.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you want privacy, you start at the L1 layer.&lt;br&gt;If you want privacy, you choose Monero.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862566&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862538&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;this bot thinks im the same guy&lt;br&gt;No, I think you&amp;#x27;re a nerva shill that tries to play stupid and make this about BTC (it never was) and me being bad because I expose your stupidity. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;his nonsensical bot reply gives him away within a few posts because it always handles the same&lt;br&gt;If it took you 7 posts to undercover my identity as the jeet enemy #1 then either I&amp;#x27;m not as predictable as you say or you&amp;#x27;re retarded. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;it just goes on and on.&lt;br&gt;Because I always refute every point nervajeets make. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;hope real anons find this post and start to question wtf is going on around here.&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m real, that&amp;#x27;s why I continuously offer you to ask me anything regarding XMR. All of the questions you (in English this can be used both for singular and plural, raj) posted have been answered. I&amp;#x27;m glad you visited the general again and saw that they actually have been answered three years ago already on your favorite platform - reddit. &lt;br&gt;If you have any flaws in XMR&amp;#x27;s you wish to point out let me know, otherwise admit defeat or continue embarrassing yourself publicly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862582&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849447&lt;br&gt;framing bitcoin as an epstein jewish globalist pedo creation to sabotage it right as it was on the cusp of actually elbowing its way into the world financial system was a masterstroke psyop&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862608&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862566&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Because I always refute every point nervajeets make. &lt;br&gt;NO ONE MADE ANY POINTS ITT you fucking poo stain bot. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I&amp;#x27;m real, that&amp;#x27;s why I continuously offer you to ask me anything regarding XMR. All of the questions you (in English this can be used both for singular and plural, raj) posted have been answered. I&amp;#x27;m glad you visited the general again and saw that they actually have been answered three years ago already on your favorite platform - reddit.&lt;br&gt;If you have any flaws in XMR&amp;#x27;s you wish to point out let me know, otherwise admit defeat or continue embarrassing yourself publicly.&lt;br&gt;No thanks Alexa, get the fuck of this thread&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862631&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862608&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;NO ONE MADE ANY POINTS ITT you fucking poo stain bot.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The OP pic is interesting no matter how you slice it..&lt;br&gt;Did &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61852712 not make any points then? &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;If you have any flaws in XMR&amp;#x27;s you wish to point out let me know, otherwise admit defeat or continue embarrassing yourself publicly.&lt;br&gt;Hey, I remember someone saying that!&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;No thanks Alexa, get the fuck of this thread&lt;br&gt;I appreciate your concern but I&amp;#x27;ll continue staying here if you are continuing to smear the only properly functioning crypto currency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862698&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861669&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;CTRL+F &amp;quot;Nerva&amp;quot;, first person to mention anything about Nerva is the retarded nigger from the Monero threads&lt;br&gt;&amp;quot;Nervajeets&amp;quot; living rent free lmao&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Nerva network hashrate just hit another ATH today.&lt;br&gt;No signs of slowing down&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862796&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862631&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;monerobot has woke the nervatrolls&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;im the troll&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;i like monero&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;this guy single handedly made me say fuck monegros tho&lt;br&gt;Nerva is actually a privacy coin, eat my ballsack and suck my memedick&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Is living anywhere except Los Angeles, San Francisco, Washington DC, or New York the same as admitting that your life is… — 71 replies — 45.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858975</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858975?lm=1771280655</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 22:24:15 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Is living anywhere except Los Angeles, San Francisco, Washington DC, or New York the same as admitting that your life is…&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858975'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 71 • Updated: 2026-02-16 22:24 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Is living anywhere except Los Angeles, San Francisco, Washington DC, or New York the same as admitting that your life is meaningless and that you are NOT the main character and will never make it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858982&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;Dubai, Paris, London, Tokyo, Kyoto&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858987&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You burgers aren&amp;#x27;t ready for what&amp;#x27;s coming&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858990&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;HAHAHA&lt;br&gt;HAHAHAHA&lt;br&gt;IMAGINE LIVING IN A BROWN SHITHOLE&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859400&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859021&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;you can&amp;#x27;t even swim in the water after it rains.&lt;br&gt;Why?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859407&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859314&lt;br&gt;Dude shut the fuck up, next thing you know youll be flooded with 869848584 billion brown californians. Ops doing you a favor, dont end up like us (colorado)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859450&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858987&lt;br&gt;what&amp;#x27;s coming?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;hard to imagine how you &amp;quot;make it&amp;quot; blowing all your money on taxes, rent, parking, and getting nickle and dimed 1000x other ways&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859453&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859001&lt;br&gt;i took an uber ride through SF a bit ago to go to a tiki bar. there&amp;#x27;s millionaires bathing in wealth mixed in with fent zombies and literal bottles of piss and shit just scattered along the street. it&amp;#x27;s a very fucked place&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859461&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859314&lt;br&gt;Come visit Creston BC sometime &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1488&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859463&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859043&lt;br&gt;Gays really aren&amp;#x27;t that bad. Just let them pack fudge in peace and enjoy the nice weather and unparalleled upward mobility opportunities that san fran has to offer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859468&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859319&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;45 minutes away in LA&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oh so it&amp;#x27;s 5 miles away?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;LA is filled with tards. I guess the weather is nice. I bet that guy you&amp;#x27;re replying to lives in Boise, Idaho though. The nicest city in America by far.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859470&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859400&lt;br&gt;All of the runoff concentrates into drainages that dump directly into the ocean. It doesn&amp;#x27;t rain often so months of garbage, human shit, needles collect in the street and dump directly into the ocean.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;https://www.pacificsurf.com/surfing-after-it-rains/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;A few of the things you could get are ear infections, sinus infections, pink eye, the flu,gastroenteritis, MRSA, Hepatitis, and Staph.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860590&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;d consider living there after you threw all the non-Whites out. Otherwise, I&amp;#x27;d visit it but not stay there permanently.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860659&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Assuming you’ve made it, what are the benefits of living in these cities when job opportunities are no longer a factor&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860666&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;No. You can also live in a remote cabin in Alaska. At least until your old crew calls you out of retirement for one last job.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860681&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;My life is given meaning through devotion and love for the LORD Jesus Christ&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860712&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859314&lt;br&gt;Guarantee me a couple of slam piglets and a square meal and I&amp;#x27;ll see what I can do about sabotaging the caravans wheels to steer it on coarse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860728&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;imagine living in new york, not being the richest guy in new york, and imagining that living in new york means your life isn&amp;#x27;t meaningless&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860769&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858982&lt;br&gt;t. lolicerdo criminal&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860793&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;Living anywhere except Los Angeles, San Francisco, Washington DC, or New York is the same as admitting that your life is meaningless and that you are NOT the main character and will never make it.&lt;br&gt;This is true. Imagine living anywhere near these mega slave cities.&lt;br&gt;You will just be worker number 10000000. Almost anywhere else is better.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860802&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859145&lt;br&gt;Holy shit imagine thinking thats a good place to live in. The nederlands are already way overpopulated. Our natural habitat which means the place we are most happy at is the forest with a small group of tribespeople.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860804&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860793&lt;br&gt;*in&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860828&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Is living anywhere except Chongqing, Shanghai, Beijing, Guangzhou and Shenzhen the same as admitting that your life is meaningless and that you are NOT the main character and will never make it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861578&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859032&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;thirdie hivan complains but won&amp;#x27;t move back(will move to oc instead)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861585&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;I live in Chinook montana. I would ask for nothing else&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861591&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;I am from D.C.&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s full of drones. Some are deluded enough to think being the GS-15 in charge of whatever the fuck department for whatever government agency actually makes them important.&lt;br&gt;It doesn&amp;#x27;t.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861595&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858990&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;IMAGINE LIVING IN A BROWN SHITHOLE&lt;br&gt;D.C. suburbs in 2012 be like...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862146&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;Los Angeles is a shithole. San Francisco lost all sovl because no one who lives there is actually from San Francisco anymore. D.C. is literally a dilapidated nigger den. New York is cool and iconic but is also a lonely hive where everyone is disconnected despite living 10,000 to a city block.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t think you&amp;#x27;ve been to any of them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862164&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859319&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;worst street&lt;br&gt;So you admit that the left-wing billionaires delegate certain streets for the homeless while they live on the nice streets in their high rises, with private security?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862191&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862164&lt;br&gt;They delegate entire states for the washed out retards to live in, while even the homeless here in LA have more upward mobility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862210&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858982&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Non-Americans&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Main Character&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Even Once&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anon...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862380&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861591&lt;br&gt;This. I&amp;#x27;m from DC too, but I left that shithole years ago. Everyone is a bureaucratic suit who aspires to work for the government or some adjacent entity. Sure there might be ethnic diversity, but there is no cultural diversity at all. Quite literally everyone is a libtard. Not to mention the women there are not only busted but also extremely deluded in thinking that they deserve Chads. A DC 10 is a Miami or NYC 6.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862537&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859324&lt;br&gt;Can confirm, LA is great. Every month I have to remember to not self-dox because retards are talking about what a shithole it is here, and I want to take a photo of my window view showing that it looks exactly the same as the white southern suburb they all fantasize about. Just don&amp;#x27;t live in the poor part of town. That rule applies to every city on earth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862543&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We have *real* mexican food for cheap, no bad weather, and as many asian women and big booty latinas as you could ever want.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>$ICP just partnered with the government of Pakistan — 43 replies — 17.2/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61850558</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61850558?lm=1771277352</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 21:29:12 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;$ICP just partnered with the government of Pakistan&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61850558'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 43 • Updated: 2026-02-16 21:29 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=r-RmZyeuxzo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850566&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;ICY PEE PARTNERS WITH POO &lt;br&gt;so the prophecy was right icy pee poo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850573&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850566&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;WITH POO&lt;br&gt;You mean one of the most populated countries on planet Earth? Seethe more linky retard and kill yourself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850584&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850558&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I can tell this is hogwash because it&amp;#x27;s news anouncement via Youtube.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851101&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850566&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851112&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850558&lt;br&gt;Holy fuck this is so BEARISH&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851240&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851054&lt;br&gt;Upset because of what? Because the icp devs bribes some pakistani to announce some bullshit on twitter?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851416&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851240&lt;br&gt;Why open your mouth when you don&amp;#x27;t know what you&amp;#x27;re saying?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851738&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850558&lt;br&gt;i&amp;#x27;ve been to the world computer summit in june last year and i&amp;#x27;ve talked to anyone in the team that i came across. let me tell you one thing; they&amp;#x27;re comfortable. they all get hundreds of thousands in salaries each year and could not care less about the price. at the event there were two very clear very seperate pockets. the VC&amp;#x27;s and the (((COMMUNITY))) and you could see the disgust in the eyes of the VC&amp;#x27;s for the community. any questions regarding tech or details to the team were answered dismissively, there is not an ounce of passion present in the entire team. i think all they care about is doing research on cryptography.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; i&amp;#x27;ve met the guy from openchat and he looked like he hadn&amp;#x27;t slept a full 8h in several weeks, he looked anxious and stressed.&lt;br&gt;when talking to the community members i&amp;#x27;ve probed for interesting projects, and literally the best project present was windoge98.&lt;br&gt;after that dominic played with an llm on stage for an hour straight everyone pretended it&amp;#x27;s the second coming of steve jobs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;they gave away bags of coffee because of caffeine.ai and it was unironically the best thing at the event. so good i even thought about licensing the coffee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851740&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851040&lt;br&gt;So Pakistanis are now jeets too?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851814&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850926&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;ppl&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851833&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851416&lt;br&gt;Im just guessing&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851740&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;So Pakistanis are now jeets too?&lt;br&gt;???? Always were. Bangladesh and Sri lanka too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61852144&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850558&lt;br&gt;The Saarnet&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61852793&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850584&lt;br&gt;Don&amp;#x27;t know about this one but poos did sign many crypto deals with trump. Ironically crypto has been dumping since&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853251&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851833&lt;br&gt;Pakistanis are white&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853281&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;61853251&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853296&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850611&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;AI licenses&lt;br&gt;So this is a thirdie government jumping the gun and getting in the way of something that people aren&amp;#x27;t doing yet to make sure that they don&amp;#x27;t start, just so they can take a cut if anyone dares to try. Classic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853824&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853296&lt;br&gt;Man shut the fuck up, you sound like a bitch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853832&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853281&lt;br&gt;racist&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853871&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850642&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850740&lt;br&gt;pakistans hate indians tho, its actually p based&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853919&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853871&lt;br&gt;Only Indians can be jeets, end of&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854123&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851738&lt;br&gt;This checks out with my impression of DFINITY. They are extremely arrogant and have borderline disdain for their own users. And honestly the Pakistan news is demoralizing. Yes the tech is great but God damn I am down by about $50K. And mission 70 is not the solution -- gaining adoption is.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854128&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850558&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853824&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853832&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853919&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;SARR PAKISTANIS ARE WHITE SARR&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854229&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For some reason I misread that as plundered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854266&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854128&lt;br&gt;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/India%E2%80%93Pakistan_relations&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854891&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854128&lt;br&gt;Pakistanis are more white than an average American lol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854914&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850566&lt;br&gt;holy kek..&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857209&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850566&lt;br&gt;witnessed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860272&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854914&lt;br&gt;you kek at racism?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860593&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850558&lt;br&gt;ICPoo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860624&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850558&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;internet &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;computer&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;holy kek - only for Pookistani this might sound exotic and alluring&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861733&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850558&lt;br&gt;icp parterned with pakistan? well fuckin whoop whoop my brothers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862328&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854123&lt;br&gt;clanker hands typed this post&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Are people really shifting to the EU? I keep seeing more and more threads focussed on EU biz? Did Trump really fuck the… — 18 replies — 16.7/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861131</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861131?lm=1771282458</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 22:54:18 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Are people really shifting to the EU? I keep seeing more and more threads focussed on EU biz? Did Trump really fuck the…&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861131'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 18 • Updated: 2026-02-16 22:54 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Are people really shifting to the EU? I keep seeing more and more threads focussed on EU biz? Did Trump really fuck the US economy that much? Should i start investing in Europe too?&lt;br&gt;t.asian biz bro&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861139&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861131&lt;br&gt;no...that was the move over a year ago. those are the exit liquidity farming shills youre seeing&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861253&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861139&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;over a year ago&lt;br&gt;What about all the investment firms that started pulling out of the US over Trump&amp;#x27;s Greenland threats? This happened recently. Are you sure that the move has stopped or is it still ongoing?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861308&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861131&lt;br&gt;yes they have always been the main character. america is strong but there is nothing holy in this stolen country. it will always remain a european colony in spirit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861368&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861131&lt;br&gt;how many european companies do you know?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861374&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;he isn&amp;#x27;t already&lt;br&gt;I shiggy doo, better hurry up!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861920&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861131&lt;br&gt;America has been in a crab market since Oct and possibly a bear market since a few weeks. Meanwhile Europe is in a bull market. You need to pick the right ETFs and stocks though. Best ask Gemini. I&amp;#x27;m big on Siemens Energy and country index ETFs like UK, Poland, Italy, Greece, etc&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861932&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861131&lt;br&gt;There&amp;#x27;s literally nothing good about the EU for finance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861959&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I’m european and the shift from my childhood is just immense. Back then most of the music would be american, most of film and television, most video games ect. Nowdays there aren’t any big trends coming from USA anymore, nobody cares about american pop culture and it just feels mild and old fashioned.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861986&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861959&lt;br&gt;American pop culture is dogshit now. The US used to be where all the cool movies came from, now it&amp;#x27;s all slop.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862063&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861986&lt;br&gt;Yeah the last time american culture was cool was in like 2011 or so.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862081&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861131&lt;br&gt;Europe is a joke dude. Putting a bunch of dead civilizations into the same economic zone, salting it with Muslims, and picking a fight with both Russia and the US doesn’t look great. They don’t produce much, spend like crazy, don’t reproduce, and are filled with leftists and degenerates. In 50 years it’ll be an Islamic caliphate. You’re better off looking elsewhere&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862094&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862081&lt;br&gt;Lmao you’re talking like different european countries are different ancient civilizations. You have no idea what you’re talking about.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862531&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861959&lt;br&gt;American here, our music is all spics and our movies are all gay niggers, good job avoiding our jew exports.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862556&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861131&lt;br&gt;The only good EU stock rn is defense, but I wouldn&amp;#x27;t hold it for long, all their talk of doing this and that is already falling apart because they can&amp;#x27;t agree whose falling industry gets the most gibs to build their supposedly military hardware, 100% they will quietly cancel everything in a year or two as nobody notices, other than that there&amp;#x27;s literally no companies worth it at all there, not even euros put money there they put all in the us and keep doing despite whatever hostility they may feel&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862568&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861131&lt;br&gt;You should&amp;#x27;ve already had international stocks years ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862602&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;follow numbers not narratives&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862640&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The money sure did. My Euro etfs saved my portfolio last year. Keep in mind pic related is not including a 11% apy dividend so the total 1year return was 33% vs the S&amp;amp;P500 which only returned 11% in that same year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862653&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861920&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;a crab market since Oct&lt;br&gt;Oh no, NVDA hasn&amp;#x27;t gone up another trillion in 4 months, it&amp;#x27;s all over.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>The US is in recession — 70 replies — 16.4/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61857490</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61857490?lm=1771270949</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 19:42:29 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;The US is in recession&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61857490'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 70 • Updated: 2026-02-16 19:42 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US is in recession&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857499&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White collar recession comes before regular recession 100% of the time. We&amp;#x27;ve been in a white collar recession since 2020.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857500&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;Always was, its depression for over a year now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857508&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;GDP is growing, recession is fake.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nothing ever happens. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stop putting your vibes and feelings into your job search, learn to get better skills and be more marketable to employers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;McDonalds is always hiring&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858397&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857499&lt;br&gt;Except 2022 had a labour shortage&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858404&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858383&lt;br&gt;https://fred.stlouisfed.org/series/CIVPART&lt;br&gt;Also I do not think they count gig workers as unemployed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858449&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858383&lt;br&gt;If you don&amp;#x27;t apply for one job a month, you&amp;#x27;re not unemployed. If you have a masters degree and you work at McDonald&amp;#x27;s, you&amp;#x27;re not unemployed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858696&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;I voted for this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858910&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857805&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Disrupted the international order from which the US greatly benefitted and everyone else benefited from the US even more&lt;br&gt;fuck off retard. did you forget&lt;br&gt;-single handedly carrying NATO&lt;br&gt;-protecting international shipping lanes&lt;br&gt;-being the global leader in innovation and tech&lt;br&gt;-only genuine believer and de facto practitioner of promoting human rights&lt;br&gt;? fuck you euronigger canacuck spic or whatever you are. we&amp;#x27;re allowed to take care of ourselves for once.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859778&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858910&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Wow america number one in everything when it created and proliferated a working order&lt;br&gt;Yeah no shit he already said that&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859785&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858023&lt;br&gt;Either Mossad agent or photoshopped picture&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859951&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857805&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;international order&lt;br&gt;jesus christ turn off the television. US economy (and western economy) is in tatters precisely because of the &amp;quot;international order&amp;quot; ie ZOG. They flood your country with cheap violent labor to suppress wages and sow division, they inflate away your wealth by constantly printing to pay the interest on government borrowing for GIBS for your replacements and zog wars. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How the fuck do you reach the conclusion that America needs an &amp;quot;international order&amp;quot; to function when it&amp;#x27;s downfall has correlated perfectly to its kowtowing to international interests. America is almost entirely self-sufficient and has plenty of skilled workers. It doesn&amp;#x27;t need an international order, it needs a financial sector that isn&amp;#x27;t destroying the country for its own benefit and it needs to get rid of the millions of useless eaters in your country. Get America back up to 70%+ White, fix your money printing problem, deal with the israel problem in your government, and the economy will take care of itself. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s just nuts to me that people talk about the economy without mentioning the giant rotting elephant in the room which is the trillions that gets siphoned from productive workers to various kike interests. The K-shaped economy isn&amp;#x27;t an accident it&amp;#x27;s deliberate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859958&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;DEI moneysinks getting destroyed&lt;br&gt;Sucks to suck. Go be a negro in Negrovia or something&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859986&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;Isn&amp;#x27;t it good for the US economy if everyone is losing their jobs to AI?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860143&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858383&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;go to jobcentre &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;get offerd the a streetsweeper&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;I din&amp;#x27;t waste 6 years of my life getting a master&amp;#x27;s to sweep puke and shit of the sidewalk&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;well if you don&amp;#x27;t want to work than you can&amp;#x27;t be unemployed, so no benefits for you&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;Call me Broomy-Mcbroomster guvna&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860535&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860143&lt;br&gt;I wish I got benefits, I&amp;#x27;ve been unemployed in Poland for 7 years now and I&amp;#x27;ve gotten a grand total of $0 in benefits&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860619&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859951&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Get America back up to 70%+ White, fix your money printing problem, deal with the israel problem in your government, and the economy will take care of itself.&lt;br&gt;anything else while we have the magic wand out sir?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860705&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859951&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;How the fuck do you reach the conclusion that America needs an &amp;quot;international order&amp;quot; to function when it&amp;#x27;s downfall has correlated perfectly to its kowtowing to international interests&lt;br&gt;What international interests? The US has been profiting off the international order since Breton Woods. Its rise as a superpower correlates to the dollar’s international dominance. It’s the opposite of what you’re describing.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;America is almost entirely self-sufficient&lt;br&gt;It is completely dependent on foreign pharmaceuticals and various input goods for manufacturing. It has virtually no domestic source of lithium, cobalt, graphite or REMs. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;the problem is international Jewry and this will be rectified when the us becomes an autarky &lt;br&gt;Why? &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rotting elephant in the room is a declining dollar, obscene debt, and an overinflated market + made up statistics. None of this gets better by fucking up international trade.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860719&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857750&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;US being in a recession isn&amp;#x27;t about Trump.&lt;br&gt;Yes he&amp;#x27;s a fucking retarded boomer brained moron, but US has been doomed to hit this point sooner or later ever since they decided to crank the money printers on permanently after 2008 and doomed the entire West to be stuck in a slow death limbo.&lt;br&gt;Everyone has basically just been waiting for the big one for years now and we&amp;#x27;re getting closer and closer to it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860738&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859951&lt;br&gt;You have no idea how the dollar system works and it shows. What&amp;#x27;s happening to the United States right now is irreversible&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860813&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860719&lt;br&gt;Printing after 2008 happened because 2008 happened, which happened because republicans deregulated finance. You&amp;#x27;re right, it&amp;#x27;s not about Trump, it&amp;#x27;s about half the country being fucking retarded hicks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860867&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860813&lt;br&gt;Republicans like Raegan deregulated finance, that’s true (though some of that was put into motion by Jimmy Carter). That said, it’s impossible to talk about 2008 without recognizing that Clinton is the one who repealed the Glass-Steagall act and let insurance banking merge with commercial banking. Pretty much every president for the 30 years leading up to 2008 did something to enable it or make it worse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860880&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860867&lt;br&gt;I forgot that Clinton was also the one that made derivatives immune to regulation. He really fucked up finance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860916&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857825&lt;br&gt;Holy shit this is the most retarded post I have ever read on /biz/, why are you on a finance board??&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860980&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860880&lt;br&gt;Clinton also forced banks to give mortgages to people with bad credit scores and low income&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861063&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857508&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;GDP was never meant to measure the health of the economy. Simon Kuznets advised against using it for that purpose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861445&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860705&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;It has virtually no domestic source of lithium, cobalt, graphite or REMs. &lt;br&gt;There are actually fucking tons of sources, but none of them are developed because US companies exported the environmental cost of mining them to &amp;quot;dEvElOpInG&amp;quot; nations for cheaper labor/materials and most of the mines shut down because they couldn&amp;#x27;t compete. There are ludicrous amounts of these materials just sitting there in the US.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US could be self-sufficient (example: fracking boom was because oil price had gotten to the point where domestic supply was economically viable again - in less than a decade the US had more oil than it could even use, because the oil was already in the ground, just not being extracted), but the profit motive won&amp;#x27;t allow self-sufficiency to persist if it&amp;#x27;s cheaper to import.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861531&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861445&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;”we are almost entirely self-sufficient”&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;”ok we currently have no infrastructure to mine these resources”&lt;br&gt;Yes, exactly. We are totally dependent on foreign suppliers and as of right now we do not have a domestic source for these things. My point stands and yours is wrong. Coping about how we COULD have these things eventually doesn’t matter. Like it or not, the US is not self-sufficient, and it isn’t close. We import tremendous amounts of goods. Don’t even bother looking into pharmaceuticals because it will just depress you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861694&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857750&lt;br&gt;We&amp;#x27;ve been in a recession since 2023. This isn&amp;#x27;t glorphf&amp;#x27;s fault or joepedo. Our economy is fake and gay made up of jewish daycare bullshit jobs. Soon it will all unravel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861711&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861531&lt;br&gt;Don&amp;#x27;t get your panties in a bunch, all I took issue with was saying &amp;quot;virtually no domestic source.&amp;quot; Some people in these discussions act like SEA is the only place in the world that has minerals.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A water source is still there even if nobody builds a well. Since you seem to get that, you were probably looking for the phrase &amp;quot;domestic SUPPLY.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861724&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857805&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oh no, its over, the Europeans and Anglos are mad we voted a republican again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861729&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858084&lt;br&gt;The fantasy is better than the reality&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861769&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857805&lt;br&gt;We should be bombing Mexico.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861811&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861711&lt;br&gt;No I wasn’t. I don’t feel like explaining it to you so I’ll just let AI do it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Is it really that much more difficult to start a business in the eu than us? — 22 replies — 14.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860796</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860796?lm=1771280678</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 22:24:38 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Is it really that much more difficult to start a business in the eu than us?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860796'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 22 • Updated: 2026-02-16 22:24 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;You guys in the EU make less than us on paychecks, but you get to keep more of your money because you have universal healthcare and PTO while we have to pay for private insurance which chronically denies people&amp;#x27;s health situations. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Are people saying that starting a business in the EU is difficult because of the regulations? What regulations does the European union impose on its citizen&amp;#x27;s than they think it&amp;#x27;s easier to start in the United States instead?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860815&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;Depends enormously on which country are we talking about. Some are easy (Germany) some are very hard (Italy)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860817&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; you get to keep more of your money because you have universal healthcare&lt;br&gt;yeah right&lt;br&gt;good luck getting that &amp;quot;universal healthcare&amp;quot; if you&amp;#x27;re not a boomer, waiting lists are years for even a basic exam/procedure. It&amp;#x27;s either you go private (and pay out of your own pocket) or you die&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; and PTO&lt;br&gt;oh wow, 20 wagie cagie free days a year. Totally worth the 60%+ taxes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;All taxation is theft. It&amp;#x27;s just that. Taxation doesn&amp;#x27;t pay for services. It&amp;#x27;s just the way they control the economy, and here in EU they fucking LOVE to control what you can and cannot do. They print the money, they don&amp;#x27;t need to tax you. They tax you to control you (and to humiliate you)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860822&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;The healthcare thing is too much american leftie argument, it also has been very overcrowded by you guessed arabs and africans, unironically I was better treated when I broke my leg in brazil of all places then in france&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860823&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860815&lt;br&gt;How about the Czech Republic?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860836&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860817&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;waiting lists are years for even a basic exam/procedure&lt;br&gt;we have them too except they&amp;#x27;re called &amp;quot;pre authorization&amp;quot; and we still get to pay for it all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860837&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;What regulations does the European union impose on its citizen&amp;#x27;s than they think it&amp;#x27;s easier to start in the United States instead?&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;re shitting me right? As the other guy said it really varies based on the country, but in places like Italy you need 20 authorizations and 10 certifications (that you pay for) to open something like a bar or a carpentry shop, plus constant &amp;quot;controls&amp;quot; which are basically bribe requests at this point by officials of all kinds. Oh, and good luck filing your taxes. Here&amp;#x27;s how it goes&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; be business owner&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; tax filing time (yay)&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; tax system is so incredibly fucking complex you have to hire people just to calculate how much you own&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; because of course YOU need to tell the state how much the state wants from YOU&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; slightest fuck up? You&amp;#x27;re on the hook for 240% of the original amount&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; they have 5-7 years to come after you&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; &amp;quot;oh hello here&amp;#x27;s a tax bill from 5 years ago cause you filed 3.51 euros less than you were supposed to, plus 1500 eur sanction, plus interest&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; oh btw you pay FIRST, and MAYBE when (after an average of 12 years in court at your expense) you are declared right, you get it back, no interest accrued, your legal expenses still on your back&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; so most people just pay&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; it&amp;#x27;s mafia with a hand of paint on top and the full force of the state behind it&lt;br&gt;EU is completely fucked. Stay away. We can just pray it somehow implodes from within. These bureaucrat jew lover good goyim will kill us all and replace us with shitskin and pajeets and they will feast on top of it all while the continent dies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860842&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860837&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;tax system is so incredibly fucking complex you have to hire people just to calculate how much you own&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; because of course YOU need to tell the state how much the state wants from YOU&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; slightest fuck up? You&amp;#x27;re on the hook for 240% of the original amount&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; they have 5-7 years to come after you&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; &amp;quot;oh hello here&amp;#x27;s a tax bill from 5 years ago cause you filed 3.51 euros less than you were supposed to, plus 1500 eur sanction, plus interest&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; oh btw you pay FIRST, and MAYBE when (after an average of 12 years in court at your expense) you are declared right, you get it back, no interest accrued, your legal expenses still on your back&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; so most people just pay&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; it&amp;#x27;s mafia with a hand of paint on top and the full force of the state behind it&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;EU is completely fucked. Stay away.&lt;br&gt;again this is more or less the same as the US&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860847&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860823&lt;br&gt;A bureaucracy nightmare.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860850&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860842&lt;br&gt;everywhere is completely fucked, but you burgers have weapons and a strong constitution that backs you&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;yeah you&amp;#x27;re retarded pussies and you will never ever use them, we all know. I mean they&amp;#x27;re telling you know that you&amp;#x27;re ruled upon by a bunch of satanist jew pedophiles and there&amp;#x27;s no shooting in the streets, so there you have it. But at least you have the guns. If the Cheka comes knocking at your door demanding your harvest and your daughters, you can shoot back at the fuckers. Here in EU we&amp;#x27;re basically at the mercy of a state that hates us and wants us dead, and we have only our dicks to hold in our hands to defend ourselves from it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860860&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;As far as I keep reading on economic subreddits, negligible, the US just has far more available credit and tax companies a bit less at start allowing them to grow, otherwise its basically the same, sounds legit just a complacency issue from europeans, most of the time they get more unemployment benefits than they would working and have legit no time limit for them so they just don&amp;#x27;t bother lol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860967&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;in my country, the one thing one has to look out for is paying for your own social/healthinsurance, ie, if you have your own business, you need to pay taxes for your own health/socialinsurance, and the taxman wont ask you for the first 3y of that business.&lt;br&gt;After the 3y pass, you will then have to payup all the retrospective social insurance tax costs incurred, which fucks over a lot of retard or unfortunate first business owners&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861032&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860837&lt;br&gt;This is why we need a unified EU business regulation and undermind the corrupt sovereignist that want to keep individual burocratic fuckery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861057&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860815&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Some are easy (Germany)&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; some are very hard (Italy)&lt;br&gt;let me guess italian never tried germany?&lt;br&gt;Germany is known to be a bureucracy hellhole with people fleeing to other countries from it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861032&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;unified will fix it&lt;br&gt;France&amp;amp;germany have been dictating eu lawmaking. You will eat shit as you already do. You have eu wide higher taxes because germany didnt want to compete and made mandatory higher minimum vat a thing.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Not to mention that countries that joined got their industries destroyed by unified regulation and had to import from germany/france what they used to produce themself&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861071&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s the one thing the USA gets right. I personally made a &amp;quot;business&amp;quot; (that never made any profit) in the span of an afternoon. Cost maybe $200 to get my identification numbers for the llc&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861091&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861032&lt;br&gt;yeah let&amp;#x27;s give the EU bureaucrats more power that will fix it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861111&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Is it really that much more difficult to start a business in the eu than us?&lt;br&gt;Depends on the business. If you want to do something shady the US is the place to go. The US has barely any standards and barely any regulations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861113&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860817&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;waiting lists are years for even a basic exam/procedure&lt;br&gt;What are you talking about? I live currently in the EU and have never had to wait for medical care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861119&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Us is easier.&lt;br&gt;I have created 2 corpos and 1 llc for different purposes within the past 8 years. You can do it all online for a few bucks, other regulations depend on specific industry but overall it&amp;#x27;s pretty easy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861128&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860860&lt;br&gt;higher taxation alone puts euros at a disadvantage. Its fine if you do a local job since you compete with locals but anything online / shipped its bad since they have to be more efficient than rest of world to reach same profit margin.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As for amount of bureaucracy its fucking complex and depends on what country and what profession. There is even stupid shit like if you run a repair shop and repair inside your building it counts different than if you decide to drive to your customer and repair locally. In the later case they classify you as a handyman worker and will fine you if you didn&amp;#x27;t register with the craftsman ministry. Also if you do something you didn&amp;#x27;t register for you will also be fined but you can register as &amp;quot; i will do anything&amp;quot; more broadly and dodge it. The amount of bullshit can easily fill a book.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861429&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;Depends on what your goals are, the type of business, your personal goals and the markets you wish to enter. In general it&amp;#x27;s more of an investment in the long run but if you plan to offer your services or products in the EU anyway it makes sense to start your business here and already be compliant&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861441&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860817&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;waiting lists are years for even a basic exam/procedure.&lt;br&gt;Yeah, I remember waiting decades for my appendicitis, it rupturing and me dying because of it. Thankfully they could keep me alive for months despite the extreme difficulties this poses. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861032&lt;br&gt;We need more unified European regulation. Sadly the EU is not an economic alliance anymore.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862545&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860860&lt;br&gt;I love how hard it is to even talk about european economy on reddit, not because of europeans, but because of american lefties, if you so much, and most times you don&amp;#x27;t even need to, mention the US, they will flock like a horde to claim the US lies about everything, that 30% of americans are unemployed and nearly no one in europe, the EU is literal worker&amp;#x27;s paradise and how much they love their welfare policies and hate the US greed, its quite hilarious really how much they want a nanny state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>What went wrong? — 4 replies — 9.5/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861829</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861829?lm=1771284816</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 23:33:36 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;What went wrong?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861829'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 4 • Updated: 2026-02-16 23:33 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why didn&amp;#x27;t it catch on? ROSE seemed to have good fundamentals&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861832&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;no one gives a shit about that, big money is at play now, it&amp;#x27;s not 2011&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861850&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861829&lt;br&gt;cry more rosechud&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861886&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;crypto&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;fundamentals&lt;br&gt;LOL. LMAO even. The only things that matters in crypto is hype, tvl and volume. Technology doesnt mean SHIT if the product doesnt has that. Thats why memecoins can surpass most &amp;quot;fundamentals&amp;quot; coins with ease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862786&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861886&lt;br&gt;i guess you&amp;#x27;re right. that&amp;#x27;s so sad&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>My fellow Link Marines, we all know that JPM is behind Link's ICO, and even Ethereum. — 7 replies — 9.2/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61859872</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61859872?lm=1771283583</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 23:13:03 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;My fellow Link Marines, we all know that JPM is behind Link&amp;#x27;s ICO, and even Ethereum.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61859872'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 7 • Updated: 2026-02-16 23:13 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;My fellow Link Marines, we all know that JPM is behind Link&amp;#x27;s ICO, and even Ethereum. Investigate the relationship between ConsenSys, Lubin, ETH, and JPM. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vitalik is just a puppet; it&amp;#x27;s all part of a hidden strategy, Lubin is the man setting up everything form the beginning&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the future, JPM might employ tactics like mergers and acquisitions (M&amp;amp;A), forcing the ChainLink team to step down or giving their control, orchestrating bankruptcy, or potentially setting up Liink from the beginning. Their goal? &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To build JPM&amp;#x27;s private blockchain, Liink Onyx; Liink Onyx double ii, not your missing piece of God protocol Link, &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crypto Oracle and ChainlinkGod are paid by Chainlink team for their brainwash content.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sergey Nazarov or Ari Jules play their roles in the beast system, making it seem like they control everything. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;But with cunning entity like JPM, early investors may have a hard time finding exit opportunities during mergers or acquisitions. JPM could declare bankruptcy for Link before consolidating control, putting an end to Link trading activities. Those who hold until the end may have limited options; it&amp;#x27;s ultimately a game of probability.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This situation is quite daunting. Swift seems to be building a private blockchain using JPM&amp;#x27;s Liink and integrating Central Bank Digital Currencies (CBDCs) into traditional financial markets. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chainlink may just remain a dream of wealth, an American dream, because you have to dream to even see it....&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I am completely buckbroken, I’m selling my 4400 Stinkies for a 20k realized loss. I was expecting it to be my ticket to being able to exit the system and farm and provide clean food for my family and community. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maybe my silver stack will end up being something more than a down payment. Hope all my fellow anons are hanging in there in these dark times. Remember, They want you to fear. Don’t give them that power&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859884&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;also taking a loss on link&lt;br&gt;god this sucks&lt;br&gt;all i can say is: fuck sergey. fuck the chainlink labs team. fuck em all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859914&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Ari Jules&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;he trusts a guy whose name is literally &amp;quot;a rich jew&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859936&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859872&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;But with cunning entity like JPM, early investors may have a hard time finding exit opportunities during mergers or acquisitions&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;They like our memes and will let us get rich.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860684&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859872&lt;br&gt;Stfu vietnigger. DR;NS&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860698&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859872&lt;br&gt;wow this is really poorly constructed and executed FUD&lt;br&gt;3/10&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860763&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859872&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Crypto Oracle and ChainlinkGod&lt;br&gt;Stopped reading here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862723&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859872&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;a brown faggot actually looked over this vomit before posting and thought to himself &amp;quot;yes, saars will sell because of this one for sure my basterd&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>