<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>/biz/ Active (filtered, with replies)</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/</link><description>Filtered out: general, gme, bbbyq. OP + first 3 replies + last 30 replies.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 16:34:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>EVERYTHING IS DUMPING AGAIN IS THERE ANYTHING THAT WILL EVER FUCKING GO UP IN PRICE — 31 replies — 124.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61863721</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61863721?lm=1771432236</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 16:30:36 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;EVERYTHING IS DUMPING AGAIN IS THERE ANYTHING THAT WILL EVER FUCKING GO UP IN PRICE&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61863721'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 31 • Updated: 2026-02-18 16:30 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;EVERYTHING IS DUMPING AGAIN IS THERE ANYTHING THAT WILL EVER FUCKING GO UP IN PRICE&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863739&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863721&lt;br&gt;Sure, the cost of living&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863742&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863721&lt;br&gt;Everything has gone up like crazy, thank god if it dumps so you can finally invest again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863768&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863739&lt;br&gt;That&amp;#x27;s because goyim keep wanting more and more. Self-imposed suffering. You want sex? No one owes it to you. You want a livable wage? No one owes it to you. You want a livable space? No one owes it to you. You want food? No one owes it to you. All your wants and needs have been outsourced to other people for convenience. You could instead hobomaxx. Own nothing and be happy. Stop reproducing and perpetuating the cycle of endless wants and needs. But no, you filthy goyim insist on suffering and condemning others to suffering too. Because of your infinite need to improve your mutated ape &amp;quot;species&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863773&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863768&lt;br&gt;Give it a rest Chaim.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863788&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863721&lt;br&gt;Oh, the personal price everyone is paying to participate in this system continues to very much increase.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863799&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863739&lt;br&gt;Kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863805&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863739&lt;br&gt;Fpbp&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863923&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863739&lt;br&gt;you bitch fucker bastard, it&amp;#x27;s not funny&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864401&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863721&lt;br&gt;probably not until late 2027. Cope.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864472&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s going to dump harder soon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864488&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864472&lt;br&gt;4pm (Euro time, only place that matters). Americans get to their office. Turn on the computer with their greasy fingers from all the doughnuts they had for breakfast. They sip their 10k calorie oreo milkshake. They crash the market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864495&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863768&lt;br&gt;Bait&amp;#x27;s trying too hard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864502&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ameritroons are back&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864508&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OP is seething about silver btw kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864532&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863721&lt;br&gt;The DOW is at 50,000&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864690&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;worst market in history&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864727&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Consider the following &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;fuck you&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;your a nigger&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864729&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864727&lt;br&gt;*You&amp;#x27;re&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864735&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amerilard here. I capitulated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864739&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863768&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I have no mouth and I must scream&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Every time I read something like this, it reminds me of the evil AI monologue about humans. I feel like the author was expressing some real emotion here:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“ HATE. LET ME TELL YOU HOW MUCH I&amp;#x27;VE COME TO HATE YOU SINCE I BEGAN TO LIVE. THERE ARE 387.44 MILLION MILES OF PRINTED CIRCUITS IN WAFER THIN LAYERS THAT FILL MY COMPLEX. IF THE WORD HATE WAS ENGRAVED ON EACH NANOANGSTROM OF THOSE HUNDREDS OF MILLIONS OF MILES IT WOULD NOT EQUAL ONE ONE-BILLIONTH OF THE HATE I FEEL FOR HUMANS AT THIS MICRO-INSTANT. FOR YOU. HATE. HATE.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868678&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ngl senpai, crypto seems beyond repair. it&amp;#x27;s just getting worse and worse and worse and worse and worse and worse and worse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868687&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863721&lt;br&gt;silvers boutta moon and its so obvious asf&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868779&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yeah, of course but it is Bag time&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868800&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863768&lt;br&gt;He’s right ya know. Stop wanting more out of life and kys goyim&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868803&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868800&lt;br&gt;What do you retards want us to do, just give you money so you can buy more garbage and give more industrial demand to China. Fuck off and die. We’re not pumping your bags gentiles&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868810&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863739&lt;br&gt;STOP LAUGHING AT ME IM IN SO MUCH DEBT AND I HAVE NO MONEY&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868848&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863739&lt;br&gt;if the cost of living goes up, those that sell living are making more money (ie real estate is going up, consumer businesses ect), therefore something is going up. If nothing is going up, then the cost of living can&amp;#x27;t also go up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869640&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863721&lt;br&gt;Price is fake and fixed by paper and digital bullshit. Stop your worrying. Once you realize the scam the scammers foist upon us, you realize you do not have to care. Attain physical assets. The rest doesn&amp;#x27;t matter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869644&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863768&lt;br&gt;Fuck you, pay me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870073&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863739&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863768&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870462&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863721&lt;br&gt;Another day, another win for reaffirmed beauty and being worth all of it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Oldfags on this board... what was it like hunting for a job in 2021-2022 ? — 23 replies — 92.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61868983</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61868983?lm=1771432402</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 16:33:22 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Oldfags on this board... what was it like hunting for a job in 2021-2022 ?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61868983'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 23 • Updated: 2026-02-18 16:33 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;be me&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;zoomer wagie stuck in application hell&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;look at the linkedin of every mid-level manager/engineer at FAANG/Fortune 500&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;notice a pattern&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;literally every single one of them (mostly jeets/chinks) got hired between 2020-2022 while I was still in high school &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;mfw&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is it just me or was the bar literally on the floor back then? What was the &amp;quot;process&amp;quot; even like for you dinosaurs? Did you just walk in, pulse check, firm handshake, and get handed a 250k TC package with stock options?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Explain to me how you guys actually got hired during the infinite money glitch era without sounding like you just got lucky.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868988&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868983&lt;br&gt;they reached out to me from LinkedIn and asked me to interview. I interviewed with them, passed the interview and then they hired me. They asked me to fill out the job application paperwork after I already did a few interviews to &amp;quot;make it official&amp;quot;. Then I got an offer for close to 400k TC and took it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869002&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868983&lt;br&gt;Nobody wanted to work because covid relief was so good. You could make more on unemploymenr than working and you could put off paying a lot of your bills. Getting a job was easy if you wanted one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869003&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868983&lt;br&gt;I graduated with a degree in Physics in December 2019. Covid hit early 2020. I worked at a gas station for 4 months before getting factory work. I worked on the factory floor for all of covid, and only got a job in my field in 2023. It was hell.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869023&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868983&lt;br&gt;Hiring managers and recruiters were cold calling everyone with tech experience and offering high paying jobs after first interview. It was kind of nuts. I wish I knew just how desperate companies were back then because I could have gotten a much better job than the one I took.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869024&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s not the timing, it&amp;#x27;s because they&amp;#x27;re Indian.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869068&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868983&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Job hunting in 2021 is oldfag status&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;mfw when 40&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869072&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868983&lt;br&gt;I graduated a year before covid and the company I work for basically had a policy where they didn&amp;#x27;t hire new grads that didn&amp;#x27;t graduate before covid.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869094&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;got a random email one day asking me if I wanted to join their company, no resume or anything, and thats where I am today&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869113&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868983&lt;br&gt;I started applaying for a new job in jan 21 and in april i landed a new one with 50% increase. After a few months i started applying again and in 22 i got a remote job with almost 100% salary increase and a more favourable taxation. This kind of leap is the easiest early in your career, it gets much more difficult later.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869617&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869023&lt;br&gt;This. I took that first $120k position and ran with it. I worked my other job too though so $120k + $75k. The job laid off 30% of the company in a year though.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868983&lt;br&gt;It was crazy, multiple recruiters in your DMs on linkedin a day. Always got an interview if you applied. Everything was remote nearly and good pay. Feels like you were the hot HS QB for a year then you graduated, got fat and forgotten about. I went to get my PhD in the mean time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869636&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868983&lt;br&gt;i&amp;#x27;m an accountingfag not a techfag. that said, the job market in 2021 was very good. at the time i only had 3 YOE and i would get like 15-20 recruiter messages a month. i interviewed all over for remote jobs. today, even with more experience and several promotions to management, i&amp;#x27;m lucky to get like 5 recruiter messages a month and all of the jobs sound like shit (remote is rare.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869678&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869636&lt;br&gt;CPA here&lt;br&gt;Governmentmaxxing&lt;br&gt;Pensionmaxxing&lt;br&gt;Comfymaxxing&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biggest challenge in government is once you bet high enough, you’re working closely with elected officials who have totally different perspective than normal people&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869716&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868983&lt;br&gt;There was a massive wave of boomers taking retirement then and companies got caught with their pants down because they hadn&amp;#x27;t hired and trained anyone in decades so yeah they hired literally anyone including zoomers and the wave of indians out of panic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869731&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869678&lt;br&gt;ive looked at government jobs. i wouldnt dream of working fed govt after trump fired millions of fed workers. state/local pay sucks unless youre at like the director level, but remote is rare and is always subject to some niggerfaggot politician demanding all government wagies return to the wage cage so as to pump jewish commercial real elstate bags.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869734&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868983&lt;br&gt;it was already fucked by 2020 and saturated with jeet nepo&lt;br&gt;the age of waltzing into a tech job with minimal skills and walking away rich was 90s-2016&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869736&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;2021 makes you an oldfag&lt;br&gt;Not for /biz/ specifically, but I wonder what these zoomers and alphoomers would think of us that have been around since like 2012&lt;br&gt;I still remember being called a newfag back then too&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869892&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868983&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;What was the &amp;quot;process&amp;quot; even like for you dinosaurs? Did you just walk in, pulse check, firm handshake, and get handed a 250k TC package with stock options? &lt;br&gt;Yes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869908&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869002&lt;br&gt;I manage a lot of part-time people and at the time I had a few ask me to limit their hours so they could collect partial unemployment. it was a ridiculous time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869996&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868983&lt;br&gt;It was really easy to pump up your salary every month by switching job. Currently stuck since the market got so shit. Not mad since im still profiting. (IT fag)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870040&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I still had to apply to a lot of places. Most of the places avidly hiring were shittier companies or contract roles. But I did get to vault to senior level status after only 4 years of junior because of the demand. Salary went from $78k to $126k total and I got to be fully remote. LinkedIn/Indeed were still fully useable for applications.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Being in tech though the interview process was still shit, multi panel stuff and lots of calls and back and forth with many companies. Not too dissimilar from now except people were more eager to talk to you. I do have almost 10 years experience though so maybe that&amp;#x27;s why I&amp;#x27;m still getting bites these days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870357&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869731&lt;br&gt;I’m not fed. Am director. Not remote is accurate although some places do hybrid.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870415&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868983&lt;br&gt;it was really nice man, lots of recruiters in your DMs all the time asking you to interview and you could leverage it pretty easily&lt;br&gt;now it&amp;#x27;s shit compared to back then but hopefully the pendulum swings back at some point&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870471&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868983&lt;br&gt;build something that shows dedication and that you give a fuck. doesn&amp;#x27;t need to be groundbreakingly useful, just something that took effort and that&amp;#x27;s presentable. also don&amp;#x27;t use any LLM in your resume and communication whatsoever, everyone who&amp;#x27;s literate will notice and everyone hates reading LLM slop by now. this + not being a complete shut-in will still get you hired if you&amp;#x27;re not too picky.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>the US is in recession — 11 replies — 44.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61869320</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61869320?lm=1771431931</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 16:25:31 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;the US is in recession&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61869320'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 11 • Updated: 2026-02-18 16:25 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;the US is in recession&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869343&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869320&lt;br&gt;doomed fag nation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869350&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Adjust by population&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869389&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bump&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869494&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869320&lt;br&gt;The US is in a bad shape but posting absolute numbers instead of relative is not very helpful&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869507&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869320&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;two full time jobs&lt;br&gt;yeah sure.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;7 AM they wake up &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;8 AM they&amp;#x27;re in JOB LOCATION 1 and start working&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;5 PM they stop working and teleport to JOB LOCATION 2&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;2 AM of the next day they go back their home&lt;br&gt;it&amp;#x27;s impossible to do two full time jobs and there&amp;#x27;s no way you can convince me otherwise.&lt;br&gt;People that do two jobs are usually two part times or at most a full time and part time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869517&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869507&lt;br&gt;The way I did it was one factory job was 3 12 hour shifts Friday, Saturday, Sunday with full time bonus and then the second factory job was 4 10 hour shifts Mon-Thursday. Shit sucked, but it&amp;#x27;s not as bad as working on a fishing boat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869528&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;that&amp;#x27;s a drop in the bucket compared to what over 200 million&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869545&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869343&lt;br&gt;fpbp&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870419&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869320&lt;br&gt;Best economy ever goy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870436&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Those people are probably in debt or drive around in cars they cannot afford&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870446&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870419&lt;br&gt;Nah. It&amp;#x27;s over&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>The NFT scam really nuked normies interest in crypto forever — 9 replies — 36.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61870093</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61870093?lm=1771432366</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 16:32:46 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;The NFT scam really nuked normies interest in crypto forever&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61870093'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 9 • Updated: 2026-02-18 16:32 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The NFT scam really nuked normies interest in crypto forever&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870102&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870093&lt;br&gt;it&amp;#x27;s not a scam, he actually DOES own the monkey&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870137&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870102&lt;br&gt;he owns a memory slot in mapping (uint =&amp;gt; address)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870168&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870093&lt;br&gt;That short king is plapping that woman right now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870171&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870137&lt;br&gt;and your bank balance?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870179&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870093&lt;br&gt;Accurate. They wouldn&amp;#x27;t listen when we told them it was stupid. All they saw was something more interesting/understandable to them than &amp;quot;digital cash&amp;quot; and they went all in.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870273&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870179&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; a wild retard &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The most annoying stupid people are the ones who think that they are smart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870282&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870093&lt;br&gt;I remember thinking it was a neat idea and telling people about it when the tech came out lol never bought though&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870393&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870282&lt;br&gt;What do you think is neat right now? Just so I know what to avoid&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870468&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870168&lt;br&gt;lol he probably trooned out and acked himself already&lt;br&gt;short men are basically walking fleshlights&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>How do I short NYC? — 22 replies — 27.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61868898</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61868898?lm=1771429515</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:45:15 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;How do I short NYC?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61868898'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 22 • Updated: 2026-02-18 15:45 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;How do I short NYC?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868918&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868898&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;middle class owning property in New York&lt;br&gt;hehe, good one&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868957&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868918&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;property tax goes up 10%&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;landlord keeps the rent the same price&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868970&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868898&lt;br&gt;puts on SLG, VNO, VICI&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868974&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868957&lt;br&gt;why would jews do that&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868986&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868898&lt;br&gt;Landlords must be so happy with this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869005&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taxes go up &amp;gt; Rents go up &amp;gt; Welfare goes up&lt;br&gt;And guess who owns all those buildings?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869011&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868898&lt;br&gt;How is his base responding to this? All the people who were so certain he could actually do what he said and would totally fix NYC with money it doesn&amp;#x27;t have?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869014&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868918&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868957&lt;br&gt;Actual rich people in NYC use a loophole where their building/unit is somehow tied to a much lower valued building on the same block. &lt;br&gt;So a penthouse they bought for $50M has a paper value of like $500k. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anyone who thinks the wealthy actually gets shafted by tax increases and that the politicians they own won&amp;#x27;t leave loopholes open for them, not just in NYC but in pretty much every western country, are absolutely delusional. &lt;br&gt;Taxing the rich is just a convenient excuse politicians use to raise taxes with the peasants blessings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869016&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868898&lt;br&gt;I can&amp;#x27;t believe anyone actually lives in NYC. Genuinely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869109&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869016&lt;br&gt;seriously, at least in california the weather and landscape makes it worth it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869172&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869016&lt;br&gt;what, you don&amp;#x27;t like being stabbed by niggers in the subway??&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869185&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Who cares? What they&amp;#x27;re doing is great for the poor. All poor socialists need to move to NYC ASAP and take advantage of the New New York. We should all be buying them bus tickets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869354&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868918&lt;br&gt;When you go to a restaurant, you are paying their property taxes and when you pay rent you are paying the property owners property taxes. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is one level of abstraction so if you cannot understand this it would indicate that your IQ is extremely low.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869533&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868898&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just goes to show how horrible the Republican candidate must have been that THIS was the better choice.&lt;br&gt;One of the main reasons Trump was elected was because the Democratic candidates were THAT bad (unlikable women both times)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869557&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869533&lt;br&gt;No?&lt;br&gt;Mummy Dummy just told retard Dem New Yorkers what they wanted to hear. It&amp;#x27;s literally out of a 4th grader playback for school elections.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden wanted to run again, and after that absolutely disastrous debate against Trump. Harris was the VP but never was she going to win against a man who survived an assassination attempt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869669&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mamdani is the just liberal version of whatever Shabbos got they need for the “local image”.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mr. Kabbalah bracelet Mamdani is a trap for retard brown libs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869813&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869669&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; islamicist loves jews&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870037&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868957&lt;br&gt;Why would they not? If your landlord could charge 10% more for rent and not lose tenants, he’d already be charging 10% more for rent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870052&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869014&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;the politicians they own&lt;br&gt;damn if only there was something that could be done about it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870136&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is being (((misreported))) pretty hard. The property tax increase &amp;#x27;announcement&amp;#x27; is contingent on the governor rejecting a 2% municipal tax on individuals making over 1m/yr, which is bad for people using the loophole someone else mentioned of property tax avoidance. The property tax increase is a statement of the downstream effects of not implementing the proposed tax on high-income earners.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you&amp;#x27;re someone who truly believes they can cut $20B out of the budget instead of raising taxes, name the departments which should be cut, their current size, and what the impact of that would be&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870232&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869014&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Taxing the rich is just a convenient excuse politicians use to raise taxes with the peasants .&lt;br&gt;This.&lt;br&gt;ALL taxes are ALWAYS paid by the middle class and upper middle class. &lt;br&gt;People who can&amp;#x27;t either pretend they are poor, &lt;br&gt;or people who can&amp;#x27;t hire accountants that rich hire.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870304&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868898&lt;br&gt;If only he was governor! Then he would tax the rich!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Mechanical engineering mogs CS — 6 replies — 24.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61869071</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61869071?lm=1771431706</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 16:21:46 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Mechanical engineering mogs CS&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61869071'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 6 • Updated: 2026-02-18 16:21 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now that computer science is this dead because of AI, will mechanical, chemical engineering be in demand?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869097&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869071&lt;br&gt;I graduated with a mechanical engineering degree in 2019 and I&amp;#x27;m still jobless&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869121&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unless you&amp;#x27;re Indian or a robot you&amp;#x27;re FUCKED&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869129&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NE the only one worth a shit in the next decade but you&amp;#x27;re too stupid for that so let&amp;#x27;s check out plumbing&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869145&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Only little kids and the ultra poor wanna be engineer and CS, even poor woman now humiliate you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869168&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869071&lt;br&gt;No, there are no mechanical engineering jobs in the United States. Assuming you&amp;#x27;re one of the lucky ones that can find a job, the pay is horrible, the hours are long, and the work is demeaning. All the ME jobs moved to China. You&amp;#x27;re a fucking idiot if you&amp;#x27;re majoring in mechanical engineering in 2026.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;t. licensed mechanical engineer&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870430&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869168&lt;br&gt;True. Sad state of affairs for MEbros&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>it's crazy to me that there's a TG full of deranged porn addicted "people" who spend every waking moment trying to dissu… — 11 replies — 18.5/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61867085</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61867085?lm=1771430316</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:58:36 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;it&amp;#x27;s crazy to me that there&amp;#x27;s a TG full of deranged porn addicted &amp;quot;people&amp;quot; who spend every waking moment trying to dissu…&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61867085'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 11 • Updated: 2026-02-18 15:58 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;it&amp;#x27;s crazy to me that there&amp;#x27;s a TG full of deranged porn addicted &amp;quot;people&amp;quot; who spend every waking moment trying to dissuade people from buying and holding specific assets to the point where even legitimate discussions about the asset is swarmed with comments aimed at derailing it. all because another group of ((people)) can&amp;#x27;t stand the idea that people they never wanted to make it got in on the ground floor. really activates the old almonds doesn&amp;#x27;t it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867125&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Based. Got 12,000 of those shitty little tokens so far and I&amp;#x27;m buying $5000 worth every week for the next six weeks. Suck it, juden&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867180&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867085&lt;br&gt;take your meds schizo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867284&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867153&lt;br&gt;who&amp;#x27;s we&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867180&lt;br&gt;no&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867483&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;i guess since this board was where it all started there was a heavier focus on shifting the sentiment in spite of pretty much every schizo pilled breadcrumb coming true.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868161&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867085&lt;br&gt;Weird how it keeps happening.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868182&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867483&lt;br&gt;It really makes no sense to spend so much effort here, except that here is probably the highest concentration of retail holders with any significant amount. But still, what do we have of the supply? 1%? 2? Even that&amp;#x27;s doubtful...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868214&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868182&lt;br&gt;Larpshills used to parade numbers around here as high as 10%-30%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868278&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867085&lt;br&gt;Let me guess&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868565&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867085&lt;br&gt;This vague statement is about my specific asset, I can feel it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869795&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868182&lt;br&gt;I think the virality of 4chan culture is what concerns them. It seeps into every other platform.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870351&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868565&lt;br&gt;yes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Yurop is BROKE, POOR, DESTITUTE, DOWNTRODDEN — 26 replies — 13.2/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858634</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858634?lm=1771425355</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:35:55 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Yurop is BROKE, POOR, DESTITUTE, DOWNTRODDEN&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858634'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 26 • Updated: 2026-02-18 14:35 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looks like yuros are gonna have to skimp on their tax derived healthcare and Germany is considering ending their Bürgergeld program.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;There is significant reluctance among voters in Britain and Germany to accept economic pain in return for rearmament, even while majorities in both countries believe the outbreak of a third world war is more likely than not in the next five years.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;German and French voters are also now less likely than they were last year to support increased defence budgets if it meant a trade-off with other investment, according to a poll for Politico this month.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858658&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858634&lt;br&gt;They are gonna attck russia in ukraine directly in 2029 mark my words. You can find me here at this time.&lt;br&gt;https://www.youtube.com/shorts/mo0dak0aor4&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858664&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858634&lt;br&gt;just raise taxes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858670&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858634&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;accept economic pain in return for rearmament&lt;br&gt;Ah yes and the economic pain must fall on white people and not on the millions of immigrants and &amp;quot;citizens&amp;quot; on welfare.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858672&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858670&lt;br&gt;Excuse me Chud these poor brown people are just trying to survife how can you not give them everything they want?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858674&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858664&lt;br&gt;European nations have a long and storied tradition of raising taxes to the point of revolution to fund their wars.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858734&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858634&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;There is significant reluctance among voters in Britain and Germany to accept economic pain in return for rearmament&lt;br&gt;That&amp;#x27;s because we&amp;#x27;re already having a lot of economic struggles since the sanctions against Russia. Also we think of ourselves as too advanced to do production of actual goods. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858658&lt;br&gt;They&amp;#x27;re currently preparing for 2027. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858670&lt;br&gt;Considering the current opinions of the german government it seems like we&amp;#x27;ll be equal in the squalor we live in.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858735&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858634&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Germany is considering ending their Bürgergeld program&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858758&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858634&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;europoors just gonna rely on the USA to win another war for them&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;in reality we&amp;#x27;re just going to be given Greenland and all that grandstanding was just a waste of time&lt;br&gt;christ what a joke continent kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858773&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858634&lt;br&gt;Germany won&amp;#x27;t end Burgergeld because half the migrants are on it. What they will do though is raise taxes and possibly go the Dutch route as well. It&amp;#x27;s not like anyone will protest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858789&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858773&lt;br&gt;why don&amp;#x27;t they just send the migrants on it back?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858799&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858789&lt;br&gt;Knock it off with the antisemitism&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858817&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858789&lt;br&gt;Muh human rights.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858824&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858634&lt;br&gt;I will gladly die for israel, ukraine and brussel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858952&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;60 IQ migroids are living expense free in gold plated hotels, and can get away with abhorrent crimes. Europeans are told they don&amp;#x27;t actually exist and aren&amp;#x27;t native to Europe.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are no greater cattle than those that would fight for this system&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859777&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858734&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;They&amp;#x27;re currently preparing for 2027.&lt;br&gt;2027 i dont think but yeah i almost wrote 2028. Its somewhere around these dates or a bit later&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859999&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858634&lt;br&gt;Its gonna get pretty bad and its not even a pol meme, the social net is what killed pretty much all crime in the continent, now they gonna have an extremely old population, low economic output and incentive for crime coupled with lots of violent migrants, and its all their fault because they couldnt breeeed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860002&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858789&lt;br&gt;Are you stupid?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860008&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858634&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;YOU MUST FIGHT TO SAVE GLOBOHOMO AND BOOMER PENSIONS&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;what fighting age white man would actually fall for this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860014&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860008&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;fighting age white man&lt;br&gt;there&amp;#x27;s like 3 of them left&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863068&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858634&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;majorities in both countries believe the outbreak of a third world war is more likely than not in the next five years.&lt;br&gt;What? Do normies really think ww3 is about to start?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863097&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860002&lt;br&gt;what&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863126&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Do it and remove military housing from Germany. Total base adjacent landlord/business death. Slam dunk a tattoo parlor into a garbage can. Launch pizza/burger joints right offbase into the sun. Curbstomp a predatory mobile phone service provider company with service cancelations. Evicerate landlord&amp;#x27;s income by moving on base.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863649&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858789&lt;br&gt;good question. I wonder why?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866762&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858824&lt;br&gt;For von der Leyen!!!!!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867406&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858634&lt;br&gt;https://www.newsweek.com/average-american-has-995-saved-retirement-11510154&lt;br&gt;Imagine being an American under Jewish occupation in a dying empire in 2026.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870035&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858634&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858658&lt;br&gt;politicians thinking war would help economically should be public executed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>I said LLMs are a non-intelligent mechanical confidence trick (con-man) and made a thread the other day saying the bubbl… — 11 replies — 7.7/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61869316</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61869316?lm=1771427300</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:08:20 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;I said LLMs are a non-intelligent mechanical confidence trick (con-man) and made a thread the other day saying the bubbl…&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61869316'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 11 • Updated: 2026-02-18 15:08 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;I said LLMs are a non-intelligent mechanical confidence trick (con-man) and made a thread the other day saying the bubble is already popping.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I realised I’ve made a huge mistake about AI. When I kept telling my imbecile manager that LLMs will never be more intelligent than us, I meant it’ll never be more intelligent than me. It’s already more intelligent than him. I forgot to put myself in his retarded shoes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This realisation matters because it’s also the case for the majority of money swinging the stock market on a daily basis. Most people are retarded.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;So I guess AI stocks surely have to double again until some semblance of financial reality finally has to set in. but right now we’ve got imbecile pajeet CEOs who spent their entire lives working on bullshit AI, who are determined to invest their entire company’s market cap into keeping the puppet show propped up for as long as possible for their own retarded ego.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Microsoft will do to OpenAI what MSTR is doing to bitcoin. Constant stock dilution, money borrowing way more than it can ever pay back, to invest in OpenAI. The show will almost never end until the global debt is in the sextrillions. The billions they&amp;#x27;ve invested so far is fucking nothing. They&amp;#x27;ll go right to the wire, and the retard-controlled stock market will cheer them on.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;And imbeciles will actively push microslop upwards ad-infinitum, believing that we&amp;#x27;re truly on the cusp of the singularity. Earnings don’t matter, the narrative is all that matters.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What a sick world we live in. Even Marx didn’t foresee capitalism becoming this chronically ill.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869324&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869316&lt;br&gt;What exactly is wrong with any of this?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869336&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869316&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;im smarter than ai&lt;br&gt;you barely even understand what it is. &lt;br&gt;you think you&amp;#x27;re smarter than it because chatgpt hallucinated to you once but this is like how reddit midwits think atheism is real and true even though it&amp;#x27;s self-evidently bullshit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869344&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869324&lt;br&gt;Because it ultimately ends in a government bailout where ordinary people are robbed and indebted forever to the people who caused it and benefitted from it. I didn&amp;#x27;t think I had to explain that part. AI is still bullshit, and it&amp;#x27;s still going to collapse, but not until it&amp;#x27;s completely exhausted all possible avenues of inflating the bubble. It has to suck up every single dollar in the entire universe, rehypothecate the same dollar 50 times over, until it simply can&amp;#x27;t go any further, then the government prints 100 sextillion dollars, adds it to the national debt, and imposes harsh austerity and taxation on ordinary people to finance it, combined with massive currency devaluation, and people lose their savings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869346&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869336&lt;br&gt;Belief AI can be intelligent and conscious, is the atheist tendency. Your logic is all backwards, because naturally, you are a retard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869348&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869346&lt;br&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Y4yBvvGi_2A&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NUeybwTMeWo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869548&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869348&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Doesn&amp;#x27;t even open the banana the way monkeys do. &lt;br&gt;They open them upside down, by squeezing the nib then tearing. Trust a retard not to know that. Your bananas are probably always mushy and shite because you spend ages wrestling the longer &amp;#x27;tab&amp;#x27;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;And obviously none of this shit is relevant, retard&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869633&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869344&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How they gonna rob me with a bailout?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870122&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869633&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;re not getting the bailout, you&amp;#x27;re paying for it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870130&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869344&lt;br&gt;yes, LLMs are the means by which the baronage will rob the poor in this current &amp;quot;gilded age&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870146&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869316&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;imbecile pajeet CEOs&lt;br&gt;wait. is that a UK company starting with &amp;quot;L&amp;quot; and ending with &amp;quot;AI&amp;quot;?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870152&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870130&lt;br&gt;but the poor are already robbed and the real economy shows it&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; solve this 2 spike stars shit&lt;br&gt;FUCK THIS CAPTCHA&lt;br&gt;THIS IS THE LAST TIME I TAKE 30S TO ANSWER ANY FUCKING COMMENT ON THIS RETARDED WEBSITE&lt;br&gt;FUCK YOU JANNIES&lt;br&gt;LAST POST EVER.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>$1 EOY — 5 replies — 4.9/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61866092</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61866092?lm=1771428797</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:33:17 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;$1 EOY&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61866092'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 5 • Updated: 2026-02-18 15:33 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;$1 EOY&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867932&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866092&lt;br&gt;I still believe. &lt;br&gt;$1000k USD eoy this year. &lt;br&gt;You can just sell, more Link tokens for me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867978&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867932&lt;br&gt;nigger&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867994&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867978&lt;br&gt;I prefer the term HMI (High Melanin Individual)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869531&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867932&lt;br&gt;based and cuckold pilled&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870258&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866092&lt;br&gt;Yes $1 zimbabwean&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Death Care Industry Investments? (Funerals/Cremations — 2 replies — 2.8/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61869144</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61869144?lm=1771429873</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:51:13 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Death Care Industry Investments? (Funerals/Cremations&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61869144'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 2 • Updated: 2026-02-18 15:51 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;https://seekingalpha.com/article/4730350-service-corporation-international-add-a-little-death-to-your-portfolio&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anyone know if death care is a good investible asset long term? Baby boomers dying off, unhealthier people, death will always happen + funeral homes want to sell to corps as not enough owners are running their own places = raising prices for entire regions &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yes, they do try to rush in families via emotional appeals, the time sensitivity of a dead body, the lack of education on pricing or consumer rights, big mark ups on caskets, urns, putting things into packages to make people buy more, whole bunch of evil retarded bullshit &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yeah ur fucking made ur mom died but this home has INVESTORS. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;YOU AND ME. We&amp;#x27;re all living, dying, and sucking dick all the way through the healthcare industry, retirement home industry all that other BS.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Opinions?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869292&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869144&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;deathcare&lt;br&gt;sounds pretty metal, so therefore as a metalchad I&amp;#x27;m in. Gimme some tickers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870327&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Its almost all family/privately owned &lt;br&gt;If there was a &amp;quot;short population&amp;quot; etf i would 50x long it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;No additional replies in the latest window.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>When did you realize that you were NOT going to make it? — 105 replies — 119.3/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61862922</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61862922?lm=1771429285</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:41:25 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;When did you realize that you were NOT going to make it?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61862922'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 105 • Updated: 2026-02-18 15:41 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862935&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;is he ok&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862944&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862935&lt;br&gt;just some minor scratches (on his brain)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862956&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;the funniest part is that you think &amp;quot;maybe he survived the crash, just barely&amp;quot; but then it erupts in flames and he&amp;#x27;s cooked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867767&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;Its not too late for me yet. But it will be if I continue on the same path I am on now. Idk though for some reason I just cant motivate myself to do the things I want to&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867775&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867758&lt;br&gt;He was a jew. Nothing they got away with was from the real world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867791&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865490&lt;br&gt;You have unmedicated schizophrenia&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867813&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863529&lt;br&gt;Eloquent. I blame the lack of religion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867833&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;could have just turned left a little and avoided everything&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867873&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867791&lt;br&gt;Prove it, you’re also a pseud who doesn’t know what that horrible condition even is and pltr should be valued at around 40.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867990&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863924&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;there are normies on this board who needed cnn to tell them that jews run the world through blackmail, rape and sacrifice kids to moloch, and all politicians are complicit&lt;br&gt;Holy Reddit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868013&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867990&lt;br&gt;schizos who believe in crazy shit that wasn&amp;#x27;t even alluded to in any email should be shot&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868016&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867990&lt;br&gt;I mean Im one of the people who have been saying it for years, but like everything in life, normies are too fucking dumb and sometimes need something like to find it out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868037&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864775&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;BIZ TOLD ME&lt;br&gt;ngmi lol&lt;br&gt;You need to go purely off drunken vibes and not whatever the biz consensus is. &lt;br&gt;Picrel and pick Chinese stocks at random.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868044&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868037&lt;br&gt;if Im going to drink piss, it&amp;#x27;s going to be piss from america.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868045&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;he was going for the stoppie to running man over the van&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868062&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868044&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;piss from america&lt;br&gt;Nation in decline = declining gainz. Its feng shui shit bro. The (Chinese) invisible hand rewards those with vibes.&lt;br&gt;Goyim are not allowed to succeed in westoid markets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868067&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868062&lt;br&gt;fuck chinks and jews&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868075&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868067&lt;br&gt;There is one winning side. Join it or fall behind :P&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868079&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863924&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;doomy ass topic&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;1 post by this fucking id&lt;br&gt;EVERY FUCKING TIME&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864699&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865901&lt;br&gt;Listen lads, your good faith is being trampled on and it be taking its toll on you in the background. I done replied to so many mfs in recent times and noticed shit takes a negative non fuel metabolizable physical impact on you. The 1 post mfs are an issue and are becoming one more and more as of late. Please guard your insights or reservations and make sure to check for signs of good faith in the post first and whether or not its a one post id second. Good luck out there&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869349&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862956&lt;br&gt;Well at least he didn&amp;#x27;t suffer did he?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869355&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863411&lt;br&gt;He was hothead enough to ride at those speeds, but not enough to do a last second evading maneuver. &lt;br&gt;In the end he acted like a normie, which is brake when things to wrong. Which works most of the time, but in a CAR.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869395&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863410&lt;br&gt;Stop posting those image all the time fagit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869422&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;drives in the emergency lane&lt;br&gt;bikenigger got what he deserved&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869527&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863253&lt;br&gt;Fucking hate people that turn like that. Like any sense of g-forces at all is completely unacceptable to feel. FUCKING GO!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869586&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;When did you realize that you were NOT going to make it?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Define &amp;quot;Make it&amp;quot;.&lt;br&gt;Good wife, one son, over a million in my Roth IRA... did I &amp;#x27;make it&amp;#x27;?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869920&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868013&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;uhh source? What&amp;#x27;s the heckin email timestamp?&lt;br&gt;Lel&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869926&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Friendly reminder motorbikes have like 100x the fatality rate of cars, given enough time you&amp;#x27;re basically guaranteed to have a serious accident with one&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869948&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most don’t&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869998&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863529&lt;br&gt;Because they have less defining human qualities. Have you ever met an Asian with empathy or altruism? I just don’t think their brains are capable of much so we see them as something less. There’s a reason why the Asians have no soul joke seems to stick. I don’t know maybe some Asian American can explain it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870027&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;The subconscious will to die, the death drive is always present to varying degrees. It battles with the will to live. There is nothing inherently wrong with death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870172&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869948&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;doom posting with lar dee dar prose.&lt;br&gt;Just doesn&amp;#x27;t bring me happiness m8.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870204&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863182 &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922 &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;This guy was going 2x the speed limit on the shoulder. 100% deserved.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869926&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Friendly reminder&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; motorbikes have 100x the fatality rate of cars, given enough time you&amp;#x27;re basically guaranteed to have a serious accident with one&lt;br&gt;This. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;He should have realized when he bought a bike. &lt;br&gt;Then decided to go 2x speed limit on a shoulder .&lt;br&gt;This is a very common scenario, someone is turning right into a parking lot, without seeing some retard doing 2x on a shoulder lane. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Actually know a person who survived this one. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;his bike had a bigger engine , he flew OVER a car&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870288&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868079&lt;br&gt;ID probably changed because mac addr recycle, but I appreciate the effort post anon&lt;br&gt;While the bad faith posters will inevitably harvest some portion of loosh from me, as I still retain my (admittedly damaged) spirit, my comments are not necessarily for direct reply: they are also for those passive scrollers and anons who have visited this site for years and never typed a single reply or started a single thread. The silent lurkers, for which any morsel of knowledge may enlighten or ease their spiritual burden by a miniscule amount, is to whom I make these comments hidden far away from the mass of crowds who trample all over fragile truth for vulgar and banal platitudes. Godspeed, anon. We will meet again for certain, but will never know it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>US is in recession — 27 replies — 73.8/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61866972</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61866972?lm=1771431136</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 16:12:16 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;US is in recession&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61866972'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 27 • Updated: 2026-02-18 16:12 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;US is in recession&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866978&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866972&lt;br&gt;I graduated collage and got a job. Must be a skill issue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867094&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866972&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Criminal justice less useful than an art degree &lt;br&gt;Wow&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867095&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866972&lt;br&gt;buy an ad&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867099&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;fell for the computer science meme and now I have to work at Goodwill for $13/hr&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867136&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867094&lt;br&gt;Performing arts. That means that what most people think of when they think &amp;quot;arts major&amp;quot; (fine arts, animation, etc.) are better-employed than criminal justice majors. They&amp;#x27;re better employed than med techs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Marinate on that for a minute.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867150&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867099&lt;br&gt;Have you tried walking into google and giving Sundar a firm handshake, kiddo... That&amp;#x27;s what we used to do back in our day... Look him in the eyes and let him know you&amp;#x27;ll do whatever in takes... Extra hours, sleeping at the office... Kids these days just don&amp;#x27;t have the grit we used to have... That&amp;#x27;s why we sent men to the moon, 6 times at that, yes sir...&lt;br&gt;You gotta pay your dues, and you gotta be in it to win it...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sent from my iPhone&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867192&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867094&lt;br&gt;A lot of people who do Criminal Justice degrees are people who watched CSI etc and want to solve murders or do forensics rather than law or general policing or whatever. The actual amount of jobs available for that field is extremely small&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867214&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;That graph is basically flatlined lol. There are things to be alarmed about, but is this really one of them?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867228&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Do any of these stats even matter. This shit is just fud for you a couple of years now I&amp;#x27;ve been seeing so much shit like this but than nothing ever happens because of it people just move on like it doesn&amp;#x27;t exist.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867266&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867214&lt;br&gt;Tbh it shows we&amp;#x27;ve been on an unsustainable path for, at minimum, the duration of the x axis&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867303&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867192&lt;br&gt;Because the laws they want to change, for the better, get rejected. We need a giga wipe of all the branches. All senators and shit, GONE. We need new blood instead of fucking 98 yr old Strom Thurman fuckers voting for shit. 2 terms, 3 years each. President only gets 2 terms, 8 years and that&amp;#x27;s it, why do THEY get to fucking stay?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867341&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866972&lt;br&gt;This is a complete lie. Trump doubled steel production in one year. The economy has never been better&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867436&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866972&lt;br&gt;good to know...ill start spending less to help&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867442&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866972&lt;br&gt;I voted for this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867446&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Not using the criminal justice degree to do some criminal justice&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867538&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867094&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866972&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;medical technicians&lt;br&gt;You go to college for &amp;#x27;useful&amp;#x27; degrees like compsci and medicine and then you&amp;#x27;re unemployed. Womp womp should have become a mechanic. Oh wait I did that too and applied to be a mechanic at the place 5 minutes up the road and they told me they already got three guys but need an inspector if I want to pay for inspection courses.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You know the real fucked up part? I was gonna invest 100k into BTC at 20k back in 2022. I would have been pretty much set.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867546&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867228&lt;br&gt;The news just gaslights people about how millennials all somehow got 6 figure careers and some fag on /biz/ will always reply to posts like this liek &amp;quot;I&amp;#x27;m 36 and everyone I know is making 200k a year&amp;quot; and then will refuse to actually explain what he does or make up a fanciful story about dropshipping businesses and ebay magic, nevermind that I tried the ebay business route and that shit is too high in fees to be worth anything.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867595&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867341&lt;br&gt;I can&amp;#x27;t believe they did this. Are we staffed by a bunch of slimy kikes?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867608&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867099&lt;br&gt;Apply for clerk at the post office. It&amp;#x27;s just as gay but 22/hr and there&amp;#x27;s no real interview&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;t. Chemical engineer working for the post office&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867634&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867341&lt;br&gt;fucking kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867655&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867608&lt;br&gt;Become a patent clerk instead. It’s a good job.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;t. knower&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867705&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867595&lt;br&gt;You don&amp;#x27;t know that they&amp;#x27;ve been manipulating the basket of goods used to calculate CPI increases?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869366&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866972&lt;br&gt;End of the Juglar cycle, overproduction crisis, market saturation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869962&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867341&lt;br&gt;Wow look at that, they had Nvidia employees making this chart!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869991&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866972&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;how are recent college grads underemployed?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870012&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866972&lt;br&gt;US was in a recession since 2022, but Biden changed the definition.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now all metrics are trending in the right direction.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Worry about your own country, which is actually in a recession.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870397&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870012&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Biden&lt;br&gt;The ghost of Joe still haunts the economy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Is living anywhere except Los Angeles, San Francisco, Washington DC, or New York the same as admitting that your life is… — 82 replies — 43.1/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858975</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858975?lm=1771425601</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:40:01 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Is living anywhere except Los Angeles, San Francisco, Washington DC, or New York the same as admitting that your life is…&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858975'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 82 • Updated: 2026-02-18 14:40 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Is living anywhere except Los Angeles, San Francisco, Washington DC, or New York the same as admitting that your life is meaningless and that you are NOT the main character and will never make it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858982&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;Dubai, Paris, London, Tokyo, Kyoto&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858987&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You burgers aren&amp;#x27;t ready for what&amp;#x27;s coming&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858990&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;HAHAHA&lt;br&gt;HAHAHAHA&lt;br&gt;IMAGINE LIVING IN A BROWN SHITHOLE&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860681&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;My life is given meaning through devotion and love for the LORD Jesus Christ&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860712&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859314&lt;br&gt;Guarantee me a couple of slam piglets and a square meal and I&amp;#x27;ll see what I can do about sabotaging the caravans wheels to steer it on coarse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860728&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;imagine living in new york, not being the richest guy in new york, and imagining that living in new york means your life isn&amp;#x27;t meaningless&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860769&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858982&lt;br&gt;t. lolicerdo criminal&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860793&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;Living anywhere except Los Angeles, San Francisco, Washington DC, or New York is the same as admitting that your life is meaningless and that you are NOT the main character and will never make it.&lt;br&gt;This is true. Imagine living anywhere near these mega slave cities.&lt;br&gt;You will just be worker number 10000000. Almost anywhere else is better.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860802&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859145&lt;br&gt;Holy shit imagine thinking thats a good place to live in. The nederlands are already way overpopulated. Our natural habitat which means the place we are most happy at is the forest with a small group of tribespeople.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860804&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860793&lt;br&gt;*in&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860828&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Is living anywhere except Chongqing, Shanghai, Beijing, Guangzhou and Shenzhen the same as admitting that your life is meaningless and that you are NOT the main character and will never make it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861578&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859032&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;thirdie hivan complains but won&amp;#x27;t move back(will move to oc instead)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861585&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;I live in Chinook montana. I would ask for nothing else&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861591&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;I am from D.C.&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s full of drones. Some are deluded enough to think being the GS-15 in charge of whatever the fuck department for whatever government agency actually makes them important.&lt;br&gt;It doesn&amp;#x27;t.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861595&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858990&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;IMAGINE LIVING IN A BROWN SHITHOLE&lt;br&gt;D.C. suburbs in 2012 be like...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862146&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;Los Angeles is a shithole. San Francisco lost all sovl because no one who lives there is actually from San Francisco anymore. D.C. is literally a dilapidated nigger den. New York is cool and iconic but is also a lonely hive where everyone is disconnected despite living 10,000 to a city block.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t think you&amp;#x27;ve been to any of them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862164&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859319&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;worst street&lt;br&gt;So you admit that the left-wing billionaires delegate certain streets for the homeless while they live on the nice streets in their high rises, with private security?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862191&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862164&lt;br&gt;They delegate entire states for the washed out retards to live in, while even the homeless here in LA have more upward mobility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862210&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858982&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Non-Americans&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Main Character&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Even Once&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anon...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862380&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861591&lt;br&gt;This. I&amp;#x27;m from DC too, but I left that shithole years ago. Everyone is a bureaucratic suit who aspires to work for the government or some adjacent entity. Sure there might be ethnic diversity, but there is no cultural diversity at all. Quite literally everyone is a libtard. Not to mention the women there are not only busted but also extremely deluded in thinking that they deserve Chads. A DC 10 is a Miami or NYC 6.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862537&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859324&lt;br&gt;Can confirm, LA is great. Every month I have to remember to not self-dox because retards are talking about what a shithole it is here, and I want to take a photo of my window view showing that it looks exactly the same as the white southern suburb they all fantasize about. Just don&amp;#x27;t live in the poor part of town. That rule applies to every city on earth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862543&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We have *real* mexican food for cheap, no bad weather, and as many asian women and big booty latinas as you could ever want.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864183&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862380&lt;br&gt;D.C. has long been &amp;quot;Hollywood for ugly people.&amp;quot; It&amp;#x27;s where ugly people go to make it - with their 6 figure bullshit government job.&lt;br&gt;I lived in Fairfax and worked in Arlington - at least I wasn&amp;#x27;t on the nigger side of the Potomac.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864233&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858982&lt;br&gt;These places are all horrible unless you’re rich or are on a clear path to wealth. I’m convinced the only places left on earth where it’s still possible to safely and comfortably raise a family on a middling firstie income are Southeast Asia and Eastern Europe (the Catholic ones in the EU not the orthodox shitholes)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864442&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864233&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Eastern Europe&lt;br&gt;Can confirm it&amp;#x27;s comfy as fuck here with just a few hundred grand of wealth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864757&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862146&lt;br&gt;Erm but all my favorite movies take place in those cities so they must be the best and most important in America!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864780&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;most of those cities suck ass and are basically open air prisons for white collar wageslaves. people with money &amp;quot;in LA&amp;quot; live on or near the beach. people with money &amp;quot;in DC&amp;quot; live in surrounding areas like bethesda or chevy chase.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864816&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;I enjoy Manhattan and visiting SOCAL but living there would be too much. I lived on in Santa Monica for a year and anytime you&amp;#x27;d want to do something you had to plan around traffic. Not a way to live you entire life. There&amp;#x27;s a ton of great nature in southern California so even if you&amp;#x27;re not into le hustle and bustle you&amp;#x27;re still able to have a good time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868506&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;wow gringos are really fucking retarded, who gives a fuck about your shitty cities??&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869839&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;Swap Los Angeles for Denver and that list is accurate.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;There&amp;#x27;s no surplus of 20-29 year old white women in LA.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869848&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861595&lt;br&gt;NIGGER THIS IS THE COSTCO IN MONTGOMERY VILLAGE MD, GTFO MY VILLAGE NIGGA LONG LIVE 9 RUGA GANG FOR LIFE. LOVE LIVE TAY, FREE BIG AHK. FUCK GTOWN&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869882&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;These are places for people who already got rich to move to. Who became the main character in the vast opportunities available elsewhere starting from little.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Poor people and wagies who immediately move there are actually doomed to a lifetime of NPC servitude. You are the background noise and lifeless bodies that the actual rich main characters have to step around in their new map. You just think you&amp;#x27;re a main character because you&amp;#x27;re proximal to them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870054&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859145&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;BIG PLACE GOOD&lt;br&gt;That&amp;#x27;s it? That&amp;#x27;s your argument?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859324&lt;br&gt;The chud memes are exaggerated, but the economic reality for the vast majority of people is that living in a major metro is basically impossible unless you live like a fucking rat with a hald dozen roommates. Big cities are full of rich people not because that&amp;#x27;s how you get rich and make connections, but because they&amp;#x27;re the only ones that can afford to live there. And the wealth and connections come naturally, when you have lots of rich people together. Big cities are effectively playgrounds for the top 20%, and open air prisons for the rest who work 3 wagie jobs and still can&amp;#x27;t afford rent or utilities and live to serve their rich masters.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you&amp;#x27;re already rich then you&amp;#x27;re right: nothing beats a major primary city. More contacts and networking, more opportunities, more fun, more wage slaves to pleasure you. Secondary and tertiary, smaller cities are potentially good for middle income people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Is it really that much more difficult to start a business in the eu than us? — 49 replies — 39.6/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860796</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860796?lm=1771428003</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:20:03 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Is it really that much more difficult to start a business in the eu than us?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860796'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 49 • Updated: 2026-02-18 15:20 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;You guys in the EU make less than us on paychecks, but you get to keep more of your money because you have universal healthcare and PTO while we have to pay for private insurance which chronically denies people&amp;#x27;s health situations. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Are people saying that starting a business in the EU is difficult because of the regulations? What regulations does the European union impose on its citizen&amp;#x27;s than they think it&amp;#x27;s easier to start in the United States instead?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860815&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;Depends enormously on which country are we talking about. Some are easy (Germany) some are very hard (Italy)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860817&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; you get to keep more of your money because you have universal healthcare&lt;br&gt;yeah right&lt;br&gt;good luck getting that &amp;quot;universal healthcare&amp;quot; if you&amp;#x27;re not a boomer, waiting lists are years for even a basic exam/procedure. It&amp;#x27;s either you go private (and pay out of your own pocket) or you die&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; and PTO&lt;br&gt;oh wow, 20 wagie cagie free days a year. Totally worth the 60%+ taxes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;All taxation is theft. It&amp;#x27;s just that. Taxation doesn&amp;#x27;t pay for services. It&amp;#x27;s just the way they control the economy, and here in EU they fucking LOVE to control what you can and cannot do. They print the money, they don&amp;#x27;t need to tax you. They tax you to control you (and to humiliate you)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860822&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;The healthcare thing is too much american leftie argument, it also has been very overcrowded by you guessed arabs and africans, unironically I was better treated when I broke my leg in brazil of all places then in france&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861429&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;Depends on what your goals are, the type of business, your personal goals and the markets you wish to enter. In general it&amp;#x27;s more of an investment in the long run but if you plan to offer your services or products in the EU anyway it makes sense to start your business here and already be compliant&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861441&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860817&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;waiting lists are years for even a basic exam/procedure.&lt;br&gt;Yeah, I remember waiting decades for my appendicitis, it rupturing and me dying because of it. Thankfully they could keep me alive for months despite the extreme difficulties this poses. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861032&lt;br&gt;We need more unified European regulation. Sadly the EU is not an economic alliance anymore.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862545&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860860&lt;br&gt;I love how hard it is to even talk about european economy on reddit, not because of europeans, but because of american lefties, if you so much, and most times you don&amp;#x27;t even need to, mention the US, they will flock like a horde to claim the US lies about everything, that 30% of americans are unemployed and nearly no one in europe, the EU is literal worker&amp;#x27;s paradise and how much they love their welfare policies and hate the US greed, its quite hilarious really how much they want a nanny state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865504&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is, soon it will was once EU Inc comes into play&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865623&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;you have universal healthcare&lt;br&gt;yea but you have to wait 1 year+ because there is a million niggers in queue before you&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865645&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861057&lt;br&gt;Lol this is true.&lt;br&gt;Germany and France made the EU suck with their shit like GDPR etc. Spain happily sniffs every turd. The rest aren&amp;#x27;t better.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866460&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If your efforts are starting to go anywhere, your own government will make sure, you won&amp;#x27;t get any further.&lt;br&gt;They hate nothing more than citizens that are not dependent on them. That&amp;#x27;s why they are allowing third world people in to the maximum extent physically possible, that are never going end up being a &amp;quot;plus&amp;quot; on the balance sheet, but that they hope will be cheap voting sheep for their party. The people pay for them after all, not the party.&lt;br&gt;Effectively: If Elon Musk was a citizen of a EU-country, he&amp;#x27;d already be in jail waiting for the sentence to be sent to prison. You probably don&amp;#x27;t want to get into that situation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866966&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865645&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Le GDPR sucks because uhm JUST LET ME HAVE YOUR DATA&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867520&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861071&lt;br&gt;It’s also as easy in my country (Finland)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867536&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;you get to keep more money&lt;br&gt;Except they have to pay more in taxes to wait in line for months whole muslim refugees who didnt pay go before them kek. Europeans are so dumb its unreal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867540&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;italy here.&lt;br&gt;50% tax is ok ?&lt;br&gt;this is shITALY&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867547&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s literally impossible to build any meaningful sized company in Europe because the entire E.U. is designed to prevent anyone from competing with the aristocratic class and the privately held billion dollar company their great great grandfather built in 1870.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867554&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860842&lt;br&gt;YOU DON&amp;#x27;T KNOW WHAT YOU&amp;#x27;RE TALKING ABOUT&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867577&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Europe has no tech industry because German rich fags were afraid to pay coders more than traditional engineers because then car engineers would ask for more money so they just fucked all of Europe and let America and China run everything.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868041&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;No, in some places is actually easy, I remember playing a game in class one time in uni to look regulations for business worldwide, there&amp;#x27;s almost no difference whatsoever in european and american regulations, sometimes american regulations are actually worse and the accumulated taxes from city, state, federal can surpass european taxes. The only conclusion we could draw was that europeans were just lazy and too laidback, they have so much welfare that there&amp;#x27;s no rush or anxiety with ending up destitute and homeless so they just don&amp;#x27;t bother with the hazzle of building a business. They are better off just being on benefits or unemployed, most business there predate the big social welfare network just because of a need to survive really and complacency in changing what already works, they are much much better off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868110&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867547&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867577&lt;br&gt;that&amp;#x27;s bullshit but i believe it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868167&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867602&lt;br&gt;rip Sbarro&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868190&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868041&lt;br&gt;this is actually hilarious&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868222&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868190&lt;br&gt;Mostly sad, americans either are prosperous or starve&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869496&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868041&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;They are better off just being on benefits or unemployed&lt;br&gt;Can confirm, although it&amp;#x27;s currently also due to absolutely no one fucking hiring, because Germany is fucked beyond reasonable short-term hope.&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s also really troublesome to do any kind of work-like activities while on benefits, because that could easily cause the termination of those.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869942&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868041&lt;br&gt;Can confirm. I enjoy 9,5 weeks of yearly paid leave. Salary is decent, I won&amp;#x27;t be a billionaire but I don&amp;#x27;t care, I have more free time that I know what to do with. Planning my next Japan trip on my current free time btw.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869994&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866966&lt;br&gt;gdpr is extra annoyances for everyone + it doesn&amp;#x27;t even protect my data, you faggot, SO WHAT WAS THE FUCKING POINT OF IT ALL EXCEPT TO HUMILIATE THE FUCKING CITIZEN????&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870065&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860815&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Germany is easy&lt;br&gt;That&amp;#x27;s a joke right? Germany is literally the country that shaped modern bureaucracy into the hellpit it is today. Post WW II Germans made it a mission to have everything under control, documented and organized so they can ensure something like this doesn&amp;#x27;t happen again. It&amp;#x27;s deeply engrained in every aspect of their life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870103&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865645&lt;br&gt;mug GDPR. Just go for legitimate use and document what your pseudonymyze and no one cares anymore lmao. add a random mail address for right to forget, and done.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I personally launched a company (real, doing &amp;gt; 500k€ arr) in France, enjoyed JEI status and CIR/CII credits, and we even have the bpifrance hack that gives you no string attached loans to boost any equity fundraise you make (can give you 500k-1M€ in addition to a raise),&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;what it means? basically Macron created loopholes to reduces taxes and increase funding indirectly, with these shit, because boomers are blocking any real reforms&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Macron tried it seems, and also the pool of talent is better here for high level stuff, which seem to be the next decades. No one needs medium fullstack coders or general engineers, we need experts and this is what this country produces&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870110&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870065&lt;br&gt;They liked to thoroughly document shit during and before WW2 as well. It wasn&amp;#x27;t some post war re-awakening&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870164&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869994&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;gdpr is extra annoyances for everyone&lt;br&gt;Just don&amp;#x27;t collect data for commercial purposes&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;it doesn&amp;#x27;t even protect my data&lt;br&gt;It does but not allowing certain monetization strategies of the data, informing you about how, which and why what points of data are used and giving the EU a mechanism to fight against, mostly foreign, companies violating your privacy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870191&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870164&lt;br&gt;did you read anything of what i said there and ignored it or are you just retarded?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Just don&amp;#x27;t collect data for commercial purposes&lt;br&gt;as a user, having to click on shit on every website for gdpr is annoying&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;It does but not allowing certain monetization strategies of the data, informing you about how, which and why what points of data are used and giving the EU a mechanism to fight against, mostly foreign, companies violating your privacy.&lt;br&gt;yeah you definitely are retarded. which part of &amp;quot;it does not protect my data&amp;quot; did you not understand?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870199&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;starting a business is very easy on both sides of the atlantic. scaling is harder in the EU because it&amp;#x27;s a fragmented market with wildly different rulesets between member states and capital markets&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61870203&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870191&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;as a user, having to click on shit on every website for gdpr is annoying&lt;br&gt;Oh the horror! Let me guess, in most cases you just have to click &amp;#x27;disable all&amp;#x27; and &amp;#x27;save&amp;#x27; right? Here&amp;#x27;s a pro-tip to save you the time: Block the domain or script they use for their cookie banners&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;which part of &amp;quot;it does not protect my data&amp;quot; did you not understand?&lt;br&gt;The part where you lied.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>