<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>/biz/ Active (filtered, with replies)</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/</link><description>Filtered out: general, gme, bbbyq. OP + first 3 replies + last 30 replies.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 21:58:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>I just found out my ex got married AND pregnant one year after we broke up What are the financial consequences for simps… — 68 replies — 272.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861117</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861117?lm=1771278853</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 21:54:13 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;I just found out my ex got married AND pregnant one year after we broke up What are the financial consequences for simps…&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861117'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 68 • Updated: 2026-02-16 21:54 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;I just found out my ex got married AND pregnant one year after we broke up&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What are the financial consequences for simps to marry and impregnate women they don&amp;#x27;t even know?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861127&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861117&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;OPs ex dodged a bullet by prolonging her fertile years with a loser and instead got married and did her god-given duty&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861151&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861127&lt;br&gt;well, in this situation i dodged a bullet because she was just a do-nothing ukrainian whore vaping and drinking coca-cola 24/7 who was on tv in her early 20&amp;#x27;s (so a prostitute) and even admitted she had sex with a nigger in moscow&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I saw the picture of the wedding and the guy who married her look like he is in his 40&amp;#x27;s and is quite ugly but he must have money, not even sure the bedroom of the kid look like shit...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;i was just asking why do men MARRY women at any point? Even more after 6/12 months of relationship?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861301&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861117&lt;br&gt;listen up, i will make this so clear for you.&lt;br&gt; a woman&amp;#x27;s asset is her youth and consequently beauty. Once a girl hits 30s, her options become incredibly limited, given she is not in the top 10% in looks. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;your ex probably panicked about her future, and found an easily manipulatable guy to provide her the sense of security she was looking for. If the guy she married is in his 40s, this guy is also experiencing a mid life crisis and is trying to make up for lost time. And yeah, if he is 40 single and childless, granted he has a 9-5 job, he likely has money saved up. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Only an idiot would risk half his belongings like that on less than a year of relationship. someone not thinking in their right mind, because even a year isn&amp;#x27;t enough to know someone. In fact, 3-4 years is ideal time to propose because the initial feelings of love would have worn off and then the real question if you want to be with this person for the rest of your life becomes easier to answer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862056&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862047&lt;br&gt;you are writing a lot, thank you for bumping my thread&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862066&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862056&lt;br&gt;i see you have no further response and want to just sling shit at the wall. i hope you know you&amp;#x27;re pathetic and everyone here can see how transparent you are in regards to being hung up over your ex. your ex, by the way, has no doubt fucked countless men, likely while you were together and you were whining about her &amp;quot;vaping&amp;quot; or whatever the fuck. maybe go take your emotional trauma to /soc/ instead of the finance board of 4chan?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862077&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862066&lt;br&gt;incel much, you smell like jealousy&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;quot;no its not possible that she was trash, they are all queens and you need to simp for them and for sure she dumped you&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862080&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862077&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;incel much, you smell like jealousy&lt;br&gt;nobody here is jealous of someone so hung up on their ex they make /biz/ threads about them&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;no its not possible that she was trash&lt;br&gt;of course she&amp;#x27;s trash, she dated you, my point is you being hung up on her and making crying threads about it makes YOU look even worse. she was definitely cheating on you btw.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;heres another bump! :)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862104&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862080&lt;br&gt;thank you for bumping incel bro&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;and yes she was cheating for sure when i was going to shower 5 men were fucking her in the sofa&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862113&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862104&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;thank you for bumping incel bro&lt;br&gt;i know you say incel bro because you&amp;#x27;re single and incel now, but i&amp;#x27;m married friend. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;i just wanted to remind you that one year from now she&amp;#x27;ll have a fulfilling life raising a child and you&amp;#x27;ll...well...you&amp;#x27;ll have these threads where you talk about her and seethe&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;yes she was cheating for sure when i was going to shower 5 men were fucking her in the sofa&lt;br&gt;oh no bro she was TOTALLY faithful that&amp;#x27;s why you&amp;#x27;re trashing her a long time after the fact. cause she would never have done that since she was just so boring sitting at home vaping right? lmfao, please bump this more bro&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862117&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862104&lt;br&gt;is it hard to balance &amp;quot;I FUCKING HATE MY BITCH EX&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;nooo she wouldn&amp;#x27;t have cheated...she just didnt have the time!&amp;quot;?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862122&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862113&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862117&lt;br&gt;two bumps in one minute, bro you obsessed?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862128&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;oh i got it&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;you are MARRIED you fucking cuck &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;that&amp;#x27;s why you are seething so hard, how didn&amp;#x27;t i see this earlier&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;sorry man, you are now stuck with your trash until death separate you or.... you will sign her a big fat check &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;cuck&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862131&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862122&lt;br&gt;i just thought it was a funny point to add that you&amp;#x27;d struggle to even respond to, given the obvious patheticness in its content. you made this thread to seethe about her, but you&amp;#x27;re telling everyone she wasn&amp;#x27;t cheating on you? but shes married and has a kid now after a year right? and you&amp;#x27;re still here seething about her where she&amp;#x27;ll never even see it right? let me know, heres another bump! =)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862137&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862128&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;cuck&lt;br&gt;but didnt your girlfriend fuck other men while you dated here? didn&amp;#x27;t your girlfriend lounge around vaping and doing fuck all, then within a year of you two breaking up she gets married and impregnated? just wanna confirm, friend!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862147&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;heres another bump friend, since i know you want this topic as visible as possible! we, at /biz/ will get to the bottom of it!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862148&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862131&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862137&lt;br&gt;we haven&amp;#x27;t been together for two years, not one year&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;how much did you pay for:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;honeymoon&lt;br&gt;ring&lt;br&gt;wedding&lt;br&gt;chastity cage&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862156&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862148&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;we haven&amp;#x27;t been together for two years, not one year&lt;br&gt;wow and you&amp;#x27;re posting about her unrelated on the finance board of 4chan 2 years later?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;how much did you pay for:&lt;br&gt;kek my wife is the one happy to marry me, so i didn&amp;#x27;t spend anything, i did buy her a goofy ass ring, but we actually just pool together when it comes to finances, it&amp;#x27;s why we own 3 houses now.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;how many nights did you come home without her there and then made a seething thread like this? is there any universe where you posting a seething thread like this isn&amp;#x27;t universally a sign that you&amp;#x27;ve been cucked and are thinking of it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862159&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862148&lt;br&gt;do you think your ex used chastity cages or that she fucked her husband silly on their wedding night? interesting things to ponder no doubt! very relevant to finances!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862174&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862156&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862159&lt;br&gt;3 homes wow, so 1.5 home each?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;man you are a big baller i see&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;enjoy paying the mortgage and the used up hag&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;+ you don&amp;#x27;t even have kids, loser&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;why would you marry a bitch if it&amp;#x27;s not to have kids&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862179&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862174&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;3 homes wow, so 1.5 home each?&lt;br&gt;some are for summer lol, we have a lot of seasons here &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;man you are a big baller i see&lt;br&gt;no i did much worse than i could&amp;#x27;ve done, but pairing up made things easier&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; the used up hag&lt;br&gt;but i thought your ex was already married now and had a kid? &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;+ you don&amp;#x27;t even have kids, loser&lt;br&gt;do you? do you even have a girlfriend or a wife..?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;why would you marry a bitch if it&amp;#x27;s not to have kids&lt;br&gt;bro im not the guy fucking your ex, besides he dropped tons of loads into her since shes preggo right?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862188&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862174&lt;br&gt;but for real, do you think your ex had a sterile wedding day, or, do you think it was the biggest night of passion she ever had? just wondering, i think its rare for a girl, especially a whorish one like your ex, to not go all out and lick balls and ass on wedding night, you know?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862212&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862188&lt;br&gt;you try to bait me but i don&amp;#x27;t care about her&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;but i trapped you because:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;you are a paypig husband who locked himself in an infertile wedding with a bitch that he hates and that he only use to get mortgages as the slave goyim they are, why do you even need 3 houses dumb fuck lol&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;man, you are more pathetic than an incel, at least the incel doesn&amp;#x27;t have to hear a bitch nagging all day about her work or the zestimate kek&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AHAHAHAHAHAH imagine being stuck in an infertile wedding and thinking you are a big boy on 4channel&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;have a good night with your unfuckable, infertile, nagging anglo whore&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862222&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862212&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;you try to bait me but i don&amp;#x27;t care about her&lt;br&gt;clearly, since this board on the financial board is one you made about her&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;you are a paypig husband &lt;br&gt;i was actually broke when i met her kek&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;he only use to get mortgages as the slave goyim they are&lt;br&gt;so you&amp;#x27;re paying rent right now, alone, right?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; why do you even need 3 houses dumb fuck lol&lt;br&gt;because we go on vacation during summer and sometimes winter kek. what do you do during summer?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;AHAHAHAHAHAH imagine being stuck&lt;br&gt;imagine being so buckbroken by a ukrainian ex you make a thread when you stalk her social media and find out someone married her and fucked her and dumped enough loads in her to ge ther pregnant, all while you&amp;#x27;re alone shitposting about her on 4chans finance board..&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;have a good night with your unfuckable, infertile, nagging anglo whore&lt;br&gt;kek what makes you think shes anglo? i&amp;#x27;ll have a wonderful night, let me know when you want me to stop bumping the thread with you crashing out over being a lonely incel&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862238&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862222&lt;br&gt;an infertile wedding must be so sad bro, i have pity for you&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;it&amp;#x27;s like being a wagie but without paycheck&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;i paid cash for my house, you are so poor you couldn&amp;#x27;t even imagine this possibility...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;grim&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862241&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862212&lt;br&gt;let me bump this thread again and remind you that if the guy that dumped loads into her and got her preggo left her, you&amp;#x27;d probably be right there the second she messaged you lmao&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862251&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862238&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;an infertile wedding must be so sad bro, i have pity for you&lt;br&gt;i&amp;#x27;m just glad your ex could bypass such a thing KEK&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;it&amp;#x27;s like being a wagie but without paycheck&lt;br&gt;so you don&amp;#x27;t work either? but you don&amp;#x27;t own your own home? and you&amp;#x27;re renting? starting to think you live with your parents bro! &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;i paid cash for my house,&lt;br&gt;i think you&amp;#x27;re lying now to try to save face, i bet even if you had the actual cash to buy a house you wouldn&amp;#x27;t know how to maintain it and it would fall into disrepair while you shitposted about your ex moving on from you on /biz/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862277&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861117&lt;br&gt;you loosened her up thanks &lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m a simp because my first wife died so I married a second time I don&amp;#x27;t really know why. I felt safe and easy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862304&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862277&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;my first wife died&lt;br&gt;sad bro, how&amp;#x27;d she pass?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862336&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862304&lt;br&gt;simp cancer, the same you have&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862357&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862336&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;he says as he whine posts on /biz/ while someone fucks his ex girlfriend and impregnates her&lt;br&gt;tell me more bro, how much rent do you pay a month btw? do you think they have their own house yet for their baby or no?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862406&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862357&lt;br&gt;i paid cash i said&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;and i jave a gf&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862419&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862406&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;i paid cash i said&lt;br&gt;i know you said that&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;and i jave a gf&lt;br&gt;holy kek what a dumpster she must be for you to be pining after your ex on the fucking 4chan /biz/ board lmfao. so i guess you&amp;#x27;re a simp calling others simp while you financially secure this random girl who you don&amp;#x27;t even think about the same as your ex, who btw, just to remind you is getting fucked and impregnated right now. just wanna understand fully&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862435&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862406&lt;br&gt;Post fee...&lt;br&gt;Oh.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>/smg/ - Stock Market Gambling — 47 replies — 188.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861684</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861684?lm=1771278542</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 21:49:02 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;/smg/ - Stock Market Gambling&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861684'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 47 • Updated: 2026-02-16 21:49 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Casino Economy Edition&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Some helpful links to numb the pain&lt;br&gt;https://findahelpline.com/&lt;br&gt;https://www.nvidia.com/refunds/&lt;br&gt;https://www.whitehouse.gov/refunds&lt;br&gt;https://jlingz.com/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Educational sites:&lt;br&gt;https://www.investopedia.com&lt;br&gt;https://www.khanacademy.org/economics-finance-domain&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Financial TV Streams:&lt;br&gt;https://www.newslive.com/american/cnbc.html&lt;br&gt;https://www.livestreamy.net/bloomberg/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Charts:&lt;br&gt;https://www.tradingview.com&lt;br&gt;https://www.finscreener.com&lt;br&gt;https://www.portfoliovisualizer.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Screeners: so you feel like in the movies&lt;br&gt;https://finviz.com/&lt;br&gt;https://etfdb.com/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Gambling:&lt;br&gt;https://www.optionsplaybook.com/options-introduction/&lt;br&gt;https://www.optionsprofitcalculator.com&lt;br&gt;https://optionstrat.com/&lt;br&gt;https://www.optionistics.com/quotes/option-prices&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Pre-Market and Live data:&lt;br&gt;https://www.investing.com/indices/indices-futures&lt;br&gt;https://finance.yahoo.com/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Calendars&lt;br&gt;https://www.marketwatch.com/economy-politics/calendar&lt;br&gt;https://www.earningswhispers.com/calendar&lt;br&gt;https://www.cmegroup.com/trading/interest-rates/countdown-to-fomc.html&lt;br&gt;https://www.mortgagenewsdaily.com/data/building-permits&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Boomer Investing 101: so zoomers with meme stocks can outperform you&lt;br&gt;https://www.bogleheads.org/wiki/Getting_started&lt;br&gt;https://www.sec.gov/search-filings&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Misc smg:&lt;br&gt;https://www.financialjuice.com/home&lt;br&gt;https://finance.yahoo.com/trending-tickers&lt;br&gt;https://market24hclock.com/&lt;br&gt;https://www.dividendchannel.com/drip-returns-calculator&lt;br&gt;https://brokerchooser.com/&lt;br&gt;https://www.chathamfinancial.com/technology/us-market-rates&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Previously on /smg/: &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858740&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861716&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m an American, I have extreme anxiety that i can&amp;#x27;t sell or buy right now&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;so me, and my fellow americans formally decided were panic selling everything Tuesday&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;sorry euros&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861738&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861716&lt;br&gt;i just watch the spot silver chart and get either mad or relieved when it doesnt move very far from 75&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862136&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861974&lt;br&gt;what do you expect me to do?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I expect you to coom&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862140&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862116&lt;br&gt;no&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862150&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I was driving home early Sunday morning through Bakersfield&lt;br&gt;Listening to gospel music on the colored radio station&lt;br&gt;And the preacher said, &amp;quot;You know, you always have the&lt;br&gt;Lord by your side,&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;And I was so pleased to be informed of this&lt;br&gt;That I ran twenty red lights in his honor&lt;br&gt;Thank you Jesus, thank you Lord&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862170&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Proceeds on options are always so much better when the markets are closed. This is like a teaser rate for a poor man’s credit card. Why are (they) like this?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862185&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862150&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Bakersfield&lt;br&gt;My condolences&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862207&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862034&lt;br&gt;crypto actually outperforming it&amp;#x27;s stock equivalent, lmfao get fucked&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862211&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858916&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858916&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858916&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I hate tripfags. I hate tripfags that are right even more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862213&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862185&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Bakersfield&lt;br&gt;such a great place even the rolling stones sang about it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862217&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862039&lt;br&gt;I wanted to test out dividend stocks last year and was looking for something Canadian to avoid paying the foreign dividend tax. As a joke I bought HMAX because it yielded 14% at the time. I thought I was just going to lose all the money I invested due to the high yield, but with the dividends, I outperformed SPY last year.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The yield has gone down a bit down to 12.5% or so, but its still currently outperforming SPY YTD. With 16k invested I made more in interest than with 6 figures sitting in my HYSA at my bank. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Its holdings are purely banks like RBC, TD, etc. and its payout is monthly. Its still a relatively new stock being just over 3 years old, so there isn&amp;#x27;t much chart data to go off of and I most certainly wouldn&amp;#x27;t recommend it on a long term horizon (5+ years). But if you wanna allocate some of your port to dividends, its a decent pick from my 1 year experience of holding it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;HDIV is similar except it has a lower yield at 10% and it outperformed HMAX over the same 1 year time frame (30% vs 23% in HMAX). Also I should note that I hold it in my FHSA and not TFSA.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862219&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862207&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862034&lt;br&gt;Shoo shoo poojeets before I summon a toilet witch to deal with you&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862223&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anyone familiar with Copper options? Thinking of going with one of these three tomorrow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862228&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862219&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;got btfo last thread&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;muh poojeets&lt;br&gt;I wouldnt be dunking on you if you smg didn&amp;#x27;t have cope posters complaining about crypto being a bear market&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862233&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862207&lt;br&gt;babe I love you but this isn&amp;#x27;t real, it&amp;#x27;s a complete fiction please i&amp;#x27;m begging you take your meds and come back to me&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862242&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862228&lt;br&gt;No one in /smg/ cares about crypto&lt;br&gt;Go get dysentery Ranjesh&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862252&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862213&lt;br&gt;The rolling stones were on so many drugs that I wouldn&amp;#x27;t trust anything they said boss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862254&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862217&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;something Canadian to avoid paying the foreign dividend tax.&lt;br&gt;ENB if you think oil prices rise&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862280&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862211&lt;br&gt;FUD from the upcoming deflation age&lt;br&gt;next he&amp;#x27;s gonna tell us boomerchads to stop spending money&lt;br&gt;fuck zoomers&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;https://youtu.be/lK0sUU0K5SY?si=bksw0rfbKYGclUAa&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862284&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862252&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The rolling stones were on so many drugs that I wouldn&amp;#x27;t trust anything they said boss.&lt;br&gt;They were a cover band, running out of steam, drugz unleashed their creativity and their best music was with mick taylor on geetar. Its just a band, entertainment, no trust required. Bongos and banana outfits mandatory - appreciate the visual art component as well&lt;br&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Jwtyn-L-2gQ&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862321&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862217&lt;br&gt;that&amp;#x27;s... significantly more mundane than I thought it would be desu. but hey at least I have a good option for dividends I guess&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862332&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862284&lt;br&gt;incredibly effeminate faggots&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862341&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861998&lt;br&gt;nflx is going outta business&lt;br&gt;gen alpha doesn&amp;#x27;t watch plot based media anymore.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862349&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862284&lt;br&gt;I remember this video so much better&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862382&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862170&lt;br&gt;putting in $5 mio to gain $25000, seems odd.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862385&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; me at the battlestation ready to trade for the day&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862395&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862341&lt;br&gt;You say that like they arent about to buy warner bros&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862397&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862332&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;effeminate faggots&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862349&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I like this video so much better&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;its just music. I dont care about what they are really like. if you learn to appreciate the visual art components of some of the artists it makes their shows much more entertaining. Who cares what they do on their own time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862402&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862385&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;0:25 Instinctive urge to rub hands together again tries to re-inforce itself&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862407&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862341&lt;br&gt;they&amp;#x27;ll be alright once they rollout their equivalent of shorts/scrolling&lt;br&gt;by then it&amp;#x27;ll be trading near $25-30 and we&amp;#x27;ll be well into next year&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862413&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862397&lt;br&gt;gays are gross queer&lt;br&gt;even grosser than girls&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862416&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862385&lt;br&gt;lol jeff is listening to ghostface and he knows all the lyrics&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Oldfags I summon you — 37 replies — 119.5/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61856347</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61856347?lm=1771278004</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 21:40:04 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Oldfags I summon you&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61856347'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 37 • Updated: 2026-02-16 21:40 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oldfags I know you&amp;#x27;re still here. A lot of charts look like they&amp;#x27;ve bottomed. Tell me what to stack I have 3.8 BTC and looking to acquire alts as I think they will start pumping now the money printers returning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856352&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;looking to acquire alts&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856368&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856347&lt;br&gt;Took one of these Topgolf girls to a round of golf once and they were terrible lmao&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856433&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856368&lt;br&gt;What the fuck is a topgolf girl that girls swing is immaculate 99% of people at these ranges cannot hit a ball straight&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856551&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856347&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;looks like it bottomed&lt;br&gt;Holy shit I swear biz is full of handicapped newfags. Just check the previous cycles, the bear market started THREE MONTHS ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856682&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856347&lt;br&gt;how many bitcoin for a golf bunny like that?&lt;br&gt;also moar&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856732&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856347&lt;br&gt;old fags no longer hold crypto&lt;br&gt;t. old fag&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856793&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856732&lt;br&gt;this desu&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856797&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856347&lt;br&gt;we finna linu&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857022&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856488&lt;br&gt;The only weird guy are you assuming you have to hire a girl to go play golf with her&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857025&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856551&lt;br&gt;Nah everything was frontrunned, the alt bear market started more then a year ago&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857031&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;alts will never pump again&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;the only notable alt that pumped last cycle was xrp&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;unless you&amp;#x27;re counting like a 2-3x as pumping then goodluck, they can also fall 90% or more from here&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857237&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Binance coin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857946&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856509&lt;br&gt;You guys are faggots man&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857986&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857025&lt;br&gt;this look to alts the bear market started in jan 2025&lt;br&gt;btc was just lucky some boomers pumped the etf to get a higher high in oct, but this market has been a ghost town for the past year&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858251&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856347&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;looking to acquire alts&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;re doomed. Shitcoins aren&amp;#x27;t going to pump ever again. I sincerely doubt ETH will even survive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858300&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856347&lt;br&gt;Not an originalfag or a 2017 oldfag, but I am a 2019 unc. Get out now and for the love of God stay away from alts, not even memeing. The bear was confirmed the moment we closed under 100k.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I rotated to stocks back in November.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856551&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856732&lt;br&gt;this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858317&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856509&lt;br&gt;how&amp;#x27;d you find her name? also what is it? asking for a fren&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858346&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856732&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858300&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856551&lt;br&gt;jewish posts&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860179&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856433&lt;br&gt;I hit straight balls if you know what I mean :)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860219&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oldest fag possible. Migrated day one from /g/. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The real dumping hasn&amp;#x27;t started yet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860260&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856551&lt;br&gt;Looks ljke the next &amp;#x27;cycle&amp;#x27; is going to go alll the wayy to 155k.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860609&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meaningfully buying across any of these is extremely high confidence, with particular emphasis on the front end:&lt;br&gt;XRP, QNT, CC, XDC, ALGO, DAG, HBAR, XLM, SUI, SEI, APT, FLR, ONDO, NOM, ADA, HYPE, SOL, POL, ATOM, DAG, AAVE, DOT, VET, ZRO, RED.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860614&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ancientfag here (I used to mine btc on my gaming pc back in 2012)&lt;br&gt;why are faggots still falling for the jeetcoin rugpulls in &amp;lt;current year&amp;gt;?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860615&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Topgolf is retarded&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Everytime I went the place was filled with whores, niggers and trailer trash&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860630&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860615&lt;br&gt;this is everywhere except certain higher grocery stores.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860639&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856347&lt;br&gt;XRP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860653&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856347&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;a bitch like that will make more money in a year than 90% of normal men will make in a decade &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;women will still call this society a fucking patriarchy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861628&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860219&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The real dumping hasn&amp;#x27;t started yet.&lt;br&gt;what will dump the least, or what will gain the most as the rest dumps?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861782&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860653&lt;br&gt;They only say that because 99% of billionaires are men.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861800&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856347&lt;br&gt;She probably leaves the cutest little turds in the toilet you ever seen&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861818&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860653&lt;br&gt;shows what kind of man you are really. My friend complained to me once about how unfair it was that girls can make easy money being whores on OF and social media and I told him that he was pretty much complaining about how he can&amp;#x27;t show his cock and balls on the internet for money just because he is a man, and that makes him a faggot&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861828&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860219&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;That fact that you even know buttcoin was on /g/ before the containment board /biz/, proves to me you are a confirmed oldfag. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Based.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862387&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861828&lt;br&gt;reposting watermarked telegram content&lt;br&gt;ngmi&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>ITT: We pretend we’re zoomers — 14 replies — 56.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61862245</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61862245?lm=1771278888</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 21:54:48 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;ITT: We pretend we’re zoomers&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61862245'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 14 • Updated: 2026-02-16 21:54 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;why does entry level require skills&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;just spent rent on Funko Pops&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;avocado toast is non-negotiable&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;compound interest feels aggressive&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;401k is a scam because waiting&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;my credit score is just a number&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;boomers bought houses with vibes&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I want passive income without effort&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;the Fed should pivot for me&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862271&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862245&lt;br&gt;Those are millennial things doe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862295&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862271&lt;br&gt;this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862300&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862245&lt;br&gt;why won&amp;#x27;t my parents die so I can sell their house?&lt;br&gt;I deserve to not work&lt;br&gt;but with money&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862308&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862245&lt;br&gt;the 401k is a scam because some big investment firm gets free dry powder from both you and your job and you don&amp;#x27;t get the voting rights you normally would plus they will even manage it for you for a fee and if you ever want to leave early it&amp;#x27;s a 10% penalty. you can use the money when you&amp;#x27;re 59 1/2 but you&amp;#x27;re already basically dead then.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862326&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862245&lt;br&gt;I must convince myself that physical silver and gold are just boomer rocks so I have an excuse for myself for being too lazy to go anywhere and interact with anyone in person for my investment.&lt;br&gt;I simply MUST sit here and push buttons on a screen for investing and keep faith in my digital generation&amp;#x27;s digital bullshit and convince myself it&amp;#x27;s going to be worth something some day!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862356&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862308&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;OOC: meanwhile, Biden at 60&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862361&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Day of the pillow is coming, boomer faggot&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862379&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862326&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;not buying from apmex&lt;br&gt;enjoy that tungsten bud&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862394&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862245&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Another dumb boomer who can&amp;#x27;t die fast enough confusing us with Millennials&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s all so tiresome.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862396&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862326&lt;br&gt;I earned 1000 bucks doing that this month. Not my fault HR bitches throw my resumes in the trash. I will steal from them via welfare taxes and looting company stocks. Should have just given me an interview and a damn job. I could have been a happy wage cuck but you were too psycho for even that. So I found ways to legally steal from them. Don&amp;#x27;t bother wasting my time lecturing me. You did that enough already before I became your problem.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862401&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862245&lt;br&gt;Can you guys at least try to be funny and more creative with your ragebait&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862422&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862271&lt;br&gt;Yup.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Zoomer things are:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Zoomer stare&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;No self initiative to self-learn, despite having entire worlds knowledge at their fingertips&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Learned helplessness&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Shit with technology&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Shit memes&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some of the zoomer females are pretty hot though ongod, frfr.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862433&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862394&lt;br&gt;They have been fighting us Millennials for so long in class warfare that not only have we not grown out of it but are teaching Zoomers how to fight back. Middle aged people giving elderly advice for things on how to destroy and loot the gatekeepers of a rotten system. Normally this does not happen at a mass scale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862437&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862422&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Young people can be retarded, my god&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Should I go CFA or actuary? — 5 replies — 20.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61862318</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61862318?lm=1771279000</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 21:56:40 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Should I go CFA or actuary?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61862318'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 5 • Updated: 2026-02-16 21:56 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Should I go CFA or actuary?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862391&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862318&lt;br&gt;I couldn&amp;#x27;t pass Level 2. &lt;br&gt;Therefore you should not do it either. &lt;br&gt;All is lost.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862393&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862318&lt;br&gt;They&amp;#x27;re both going to be rendered obsolete by AI.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862421&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862391&lt;br&gt;Just try again, bro&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862393&lt;br&gt;Don&amp;#x27;t care&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862424&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862318&lt;br&gt;CFA if you can pass all 3 levels&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862443&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862424&lt;br&gt;Reasoning?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Is living anywhere except Los Angeles, San Francisco, Washington DC, or New York the same as admitting that your life is… — 69 replies — 199.4/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858975</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858975?lm=1771277873</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 21:37:53 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Is living anywhere except Los Angeles, San Francisco, Washington DC, or New York the same as admitting that your life is…&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858975'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 69 • Updated: 2026-02-16 21:37 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Is living anywhere except Los Angeles, San Francisco, Washington DC, or New York the same as admitting that your life is meaningless and that you are NOT the main character and will never make it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858982&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;Dubai, Paris, London, Tokyo, Kyoto&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858987&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You burgers aren&amp;#x27;t ready for what&amp;#x27;s coming&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858990&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;HAHAHA&lt;br&gt;HAHAHAHA&lt;br&gt;IMAGINE LIVING IN A BROWN SHITHOLE&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859355&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;All of these cities are NPC central dude. The objective in life is to live as far away from bug men as possible, in peace, and with a lot of land. You are insane to want to live in these places&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859373&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859314&lt;br&gt;Sounds comfy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859400&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859021&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;you can&amp;#x27;t even swim in the water after it rains.&lt;br&gt;Why?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859407&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859314&lt;br&gt;Dude shut the fuck up, next thing you know youll be flooded with 869848584 billion brown californians. Ops doing you a favor, dont end up like us (colorado)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859450&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858987&lt;br&gt;what&amp;#x27;s coming?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;hard to imagine how you &amp;quot;make it&amp;quot; blowing all your money on taxes, rent, parking, and getting nickle and dimed 1000x other ways&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859453&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859001&lt;br&gt;i took an uber ride through SF a bit ago to go to a tiki bar. there&amp;#x27;s millionaires bathing in wealth mixed in with fent zombies and literal bottles of piss and shit just scattered along the street. it&amp;#x27;s a very fucked place&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859461&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859314&lt;br&gt;Come visit Creston BC sometime &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1488&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859463&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859043&lt;br&gt;Gays really aren&amp;#x27;t that bad. Just let them pack fudge in peace and enjoy the nice weather and unparalleled upward mobility opportunities that san fran has to offer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859468&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859319&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;45 minutes away in LA&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oh so it&amp;#x27;s 5 miles away?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;LA is filled with tards. I guess the weather is nice. I bet that guy you&amp;#x27;re replying to lives in Boise, Idaho though. The nicest city in America by far.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859470&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859400&lt;br&gt;All of the runoff concentrates into drainages that dump directly into the ocean. It doesn&amp;#x27;t rain often so months of garbage, human shit, needles collect in the street and dump directly into the ocean.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;https://www.pacificsurf.com/surfing-after-it-rains/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;A few of the things you could get are ear infections, sinus infections, pink eye, the flu,gastroenteritis, MRSA, Hepatitis, and Staph.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860590&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;d consider living there after you threw all the non-Whites out. Otherwise, I&amp;#x27;d visit it but not stay there permanently.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860659&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Assuming you’ve made it, what are the benefits of living in these cities when job opportunities are no longer a factor&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860666&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;No. You can also live in a remote cabin in Alaska. At least until your old crew calls you out of retirement for one last job.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860681&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;My life is given meaning through devotion and love for the LORD Jesus Christ&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860712&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859314&lt;br&gt;Guarantee me a couple of slam piglets and a square meal and I&amp;#x27;ll see what I can do about sabotaging the caravans wheels to steer it on coarse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860728&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;imagine living in new york, not being the richest guy in new york, and imagining that living in new york means your life isn&amp;#x27;t meaningless&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860769&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858982&lt;br&gt;t. lolicerdo criminal&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860793&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;Living anywhere except Los Angeles, San Francisco, Washington DC, or New York is the same as admitting that your life is meaningless and that you are NOT the main character and will never make it.&lt;br&gt;This is true. Imagine living anywhere near these mega slave cities.&lt;br&gt;You will just be worker number 10000000. Almost anywhere else is better.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860802&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859145&lt;br&gt;Holy shit imagine thinking thats a good place to live in. The nederlands are already way overpopulated. Our natural habitat which means the place we are most happy at is the forest with a small group of tribespeople.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860804&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860793&lt;br&gt;*in&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860828&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Is living anywhere except Chongqing, Shanghai, Beijing, Guangzhou and Shenzhen the same as admitting that your life is meaningless and that you are NOT the main character and will never make it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861578&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859032&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;thirdie hivan complains but won&amp;#x27;t move back(will move to oc instead)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861585&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;I live in Chinook montana. I would ask for nothing else&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861591&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;I am from D.C.&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s full of drones. Some are deluded enough to think being the GS-15 in charge of whatever the fuck department for whatever government agency actually makes them important.&lt;br&gt;It doesn&amp;#x27;t.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861595&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858990&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;IMAGINE LIVING IN A BROWN SHITHOLE&lt;br&gt;D.C. suburbs in 2012 be like...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862146&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;Los Angeles is a shithole. San Francisco lost all sovl because no one who lives there is actually from San Francisco anymore. D.C. is literally a dilapidated nigger den. New York is cool and iconic but is also a lonely hive where everyone is disconnected despite living 10,000 to a city block.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t think you&amp;#x27;ve been to any of them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862164&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859319&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;worst street&lt;br&gt;So you admit that the left-wing billionaires delegate certain streets for the homeless while they live on the nice streets in their high rises, with private security?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862191&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862164&lt;br&gt;They delegate entire states for the washed out retards to live in, while even the homeless here in LA have more upward mobility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862210&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858982&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Non-Americans&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Main Character&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Even Once&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anon...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862380&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861591&lt;br&gt;This. I&amp;#x27;m from DC too, but I left that shithole years ago. Everyone is a bureaucratic suit who aspires to work for the government or some adjacent entity. Sure there might be ethnic diversity, but there is no cultural diversity at all. Quite literally everyone is a libtard. Not to mention the women there are not only busted but also extremely deluded in thinking that they deserve Chads. A DC 10 is a Miami or NYC 6.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>$ICP just partnered with the government of Pakistan — 43 replies — 87.6/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61850558</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61850558?lm=1771277352</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 21:29:12 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;$ICP just partnered with the government of Pakistan&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61850558'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 43 • Updated: 2026-02-16 21:29 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=r-RmZyeuxzo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850566&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;ICY PEE PARTNERS WITH POO &lt;br&gt;so the prophecy was right icy pee poo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850573&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850566&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;WITH POO&lt;br&gt;You mean one of the most populated countries on planet Earth? Seethe more linky retard and kill yourself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850584&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850558&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I can tell this is hogwash because it&amp;#x27;s news anouncement via Youtube.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851101&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850566&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851112&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850558&lt;br&gt;Holy fuck this is so BEARISH&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851240&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851054&lt;br&gt;Upset because of what? Because the icp devs bribes some pakistani to announce some bullshit on twitter?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851416&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851240&lt;br&gt;Why open your mouth when you don&amp;#x27;t know what you&amp;#x27;re saying?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851738&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850558&lt;br&gt;i&amp;#x27;ve been to the world computer summit in june last year and i&amp;#x27;ve talked to anyone in the team that i came across. let me tell you one thing; they&amp;#x27;re comfortable. they all get hundreds of thousands in salaries each year and could not care less about the price. at the event there were two very clear very seperate pockets. the VC&amp;#x27;s and the (((COMMUNITY))) and you could see the disgust in the eyes of the VC&amp;#x27;s for the community. any questions regarding tech or details to the team were answered dismissively, there is not an ounce of passion present in the entire team. i think all they care about is doing research on cryptography.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; i&amp;#x27;ve met the guy from openchat and he looked like he hadn&amp;#x27;t slept a full 8h in several weeks, he looked anxious and stressed.&lt;br&gt;when talking to the community members i&amp;#x27;ve probed for interesting projects, and literally the best project present was windoge98.&lt;br&gt;after that dominic played with an llm on stage for an hour straight everyone pretended it&amp;#x27;s the second coming of steve jobs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;they gave away bags of coffee because of caffeine.ai and it was unironically the best thing at the event. so good i even thought about licensing the coffee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851740&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851040&lt;br&gt;So Pakistanis are now jeets too?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851814&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850926&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;ppl&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851833&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851416&lt;br&gt;Im just guessing&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851740&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;So Pakistanis are now jeets too?&lt;br&gt;???? Always were. Bangladesh and Sri lanka too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61852144&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850558&lt;br&gt;The Saarnet&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61852793&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850584&lt;br&gt;Don&amp;#x27;t know about this one but poos did sign many crypto deals with trump. Ironically crypto has been dumping since&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853251&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851833&lt;br&gt;Pakistanis are white&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853281&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;61853251&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853296&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850611&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;AI licenses&lt;br&gt;So this is a thirdie government jumping the gun and getting in the way of something that people aren&amp;#x27;t doing yet to make sure that they don&amp;#x27;t start, just so they can take a cut if anyone dares to try. Classic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853824&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853296&lt;br&gt;Man shut the fuck up, you sound like a bitch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853832&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853281&lt;br&gt;racist&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853871&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850642&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850740&lt;br&gt;pakistans hate indians tho, its actually p based&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853919&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853871&lt;br&gt;Only Indians can be jeets, end of&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854123&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851738&lt;br&gt;This checks out with my impression of DFINITY. They are extremely arrogant and have borderline disdain for their own users. And honestly the Pakistan news is demoralizing. Yes the tech is great but God damn I am down by about $50K. And mission 70 is not the solution -- gaining adoption is.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854128&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850558&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853824&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853832&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853919&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;SARR PAKISTANIS ARE WHITE SARR&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854229&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For some reason I misread that as plundered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854266&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854128&lt;br&gt;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/India%E2%80%93Pakistan_relations&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854891&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854128&lt;br&gt;Pakistanis are more white than an average American lol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854914&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850566&lt;br&gt;holy kek..&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857209&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850566&lt;br&gt;witnessed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860272&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854914&lt;br&gt;you kek at racism?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860593&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850558&lt;br&gt;ICPoo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860624&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850558&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;internet &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;computer&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;holy kek - only for Pookistani this might sound exotic and alluring&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861733&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850558&lt;br&gt;icp parterned with pakistan? well fuckin whoop whoop my brothers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862328&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854123&lt;br&gt;clanker hands typed this post&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>GERMANY TO END BURGERGELD PROGRAMS — 66 replies — 75.9/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858970</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858970?lm=1771275987</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 21:06:27 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;GERMANY TO END BURGERGELD PROGRAMS&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858970'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 66 • Updated: 2026-02-16 21:06 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;WILL BE REPLACED WITH A STRICTER PROGRAM IF YOU REFUSE WORK. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEXT STOP, PRIVATIZED HEALTHCARE.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858974&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Uh oh, Europeans actually have to work for a living now? Aw shucks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858980&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858974&lt;br&gt;They will soon legalize 12 hour work days much like Argentina has done. Even contributing 5% of their GDP to NATO has ultimately bankrupted them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859007&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858970&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wait you could get NEETbux in Germany this whole time by simply “refusing to work”? WTF&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860191&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Germnanys real current issue is that they might run out of Gas and then its lights out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860401&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858970&lt;br&gt;still easy to get around that.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;go to job center appointment smelling like smegma and piss&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;send half assed CV to places that hire&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;nobody will hire you anyway&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;if they invite you to some interview just pretend to be officer doofy tier retarded&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;continue getting NEETbucks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860422&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859979&lt;br&gt;Shouldn&amp;#x27;t you be updating your resume instead of wasting time on 4chan? It&amp;#x27;ll be hard to explain the 10+ year gap in employment to interviewers, but I&amp;#x27;m sure you&amp;#x27;ll come up with something.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860441&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860422&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;It&amp;#x27;ll be hard to explain the 10+ year gap &lt;br&gt;a 10+ year gap is good and makes you unemployable.&lt;br&gt;also talk really slow like a retard and pretend not to know more complicated words. like just play an idiot. you will never have to wagecuck again and can collect neetbux freely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860446&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860441&lt;br&gt;Why are you on this board if you aim to live in poverty?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860499&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860422&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;the super sewious big boy wageslave loses his shit on 4chan&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;the post wasn&amp;#x27;t even directed at him &lt;br&gt;lol lmao even&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860527&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860446&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;hurr durr the only way to make money is by sucking a jews dick&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860538&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860527&lt;br&gt;wageslaves are so traumatized by wageslavery and interviewing that they&amp;#x27;re spreading their defeatism everywhere they go as a shitty coping mechanism. You know that they&amp;#x27;re forcing goyim to humiliate themselves with 5-10 round interviews nowadays? Insane.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860550&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860538&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;wagecuck&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;hypergamble to a few million&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;live in poverty on welfare&lt;br&gt;Not great options. I choose to wagecuck.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860567&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860527&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;You just can&amp;#x27;t have a business, ok????&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860591&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860550&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;it&amp;#x27;s either the whip or picking cotton&lt;br&gt;That false dichotomy is sure proof of wageslave brainrot. I don&amp;#x27;t blame you, though. The whole system is rigged against you from birth and every aspect of your human nature is weaponized against you by the very thing you&amp;#x27;re meant to worship as a social animal, i.e. society.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860601&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858970&lt;br&gt;They just gave away all our money to Ausländers and now that the social systems are running dry they are simply getting rid of them kek.&lt;br&gt;Nothing they do will fix this. Humanity is doomed.&lt;br&gt;Accelerationism is the only way.&lt;br&gt;Let the third world starve and divert fund into AI datacenters.&lt;br&gt;The wolf will chew its own leg off to survive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860612&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860601&lt;br&gt;third world is the biggest net exporter of food to the point frenchoids were crying it would kill their overpriced artistical wine or something, they aint starving bro&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860626&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860591&lt;br&gt;Sorry chief, I find the idea of opening a business to be enticing but I don’t see any sort of moat I could pursue with it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860651&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858970&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858974&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860660&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860612&lt;br&gt;Africa imports a lot of food&lt;br&gt;And France was rightfully complaining that imposing huge restrictions on European agriculture while signing free trade agreements with countries having little restrictions is retarded&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860678&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859446&lt;br&gt;a 10% reduction? kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860682&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860422&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;10 year gap&lt;br&gt;I tell them it is due to the government forcing employers to lower standards to hire the affirmative action subhumans. They never call me back, because they are off giving useless lazy meritless and sometime convict affirmative action subhumans jobs. &lt;br&gt;Enjoy paying to taxes to niggers, spics, and cunts that hate you, just in the vain hopes they one day stop calling you a racist and sexist. Get back to work wagie... the whole economy rests on you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860686&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860191&lt;br&gt;Gas?!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860707&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860422&lt;br&gt;kek, they won&amp;#x27;t work at all, german economy will implode and as merz said they already can&amp;#x27;t afford the welfare + pensions, it will just shrink till it gets too low to live then they will just kys as by now they are legit unable to live at all&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860723&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859099&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;this nigga thinks German economy circa 1988 is anything like today&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lol&lt;br&gt;Lmao even&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860724&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860401&lt;br&gt;a drooly retard eh? yeah that sounds just perfect for our new expanded military, the bundeswehr needs you to pick this uniform, this little sign and just stand there to block the evil russian drones with your face for us&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860758&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;tfw the only time in my life where I might receive neetbux for a few months is the exact time this happens&lt;br&gt;fucking lol my entire life is me getting fucked by the universe. Nothing good ever happens to me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860764&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860626&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;moat&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;he fell for Buffett boomer brain rot &lt;br&gt;The only moats Buffett had were his generous throat and his congressman daddy. And let&amp;#x27;s not forget about being lucky enough to be born in close proximity to swollen jewish nuts in Israel&amp;#x27;s 2nd state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860766&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860758&lt;br&gt;join a gang, sell weed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861462&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858970&lt;br&gt;NooOoOO&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861576&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858970&lt;br&gt;thats gut. not because of the money, it wont help in any significant way but because its a statement. fuck bürgis, fuck ausländer&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861599&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858970&lt;br&gt;They have been rebranding the same system for almost 25 years now. The previous government eased up on some of the welfare restrictions because they were largely pointless. The new(old) sanctions don&amp;#x27;t really change anything because even with them you can be permanently on welfare in Germany as long as you show up to your jobcenter appointments. Nobody in Germany is going to hire someone who hasn&amp;#x27;t worked for years and is clearly just applying because the jobcenter is pressuring them. This is just a huge waste of everyone&amp;#x27;s time and part of Germany&amp;#x27;s soviet-tier obscuring of unemployment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861817&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860422&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;It&amp;#x27;ll be hard to explain the 10+ year gap&lt;br&gt;16 years gapmaxxer here, would you hire me?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862208&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Every nation has 10% unemployable retards. What to do with them?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;send them into the meatgrinder&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;employ them for the least possible payment&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;give them fake jobs&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;giver them life long gibs payed by everyone else&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A nation can do any of these without problems. BUT: If you open your borders and let the 10% retards of the entire third world in, you can not give them gibs anymore or you risk financial collapse. Especially if you destroy your own industry and energy security. The meatgrinder is then the only viable solution. Prepare for a war.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>stock market: allocation and frequency — 9 replies — 36.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61862099</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61862099?lm=1771278653</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 21:50:53 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;stock market: allocation and frequency&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61862099'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 9 • Updated: 2026-02-16 21:50 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Am I insane foe wanting to invest in 50 different comapnies and 3 ETFs? Am I overdoing it? Or should i just choose sector ETFs instead of companies to reduce my list.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Also how often should I invest per year to reduce overall commission costs? Quarterly? Is there a way on IBKR to place a basket order so I only pay for one trade across multiple stocks?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862142&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;50 is too much, portfolio theory says around 20-30 before it&amp;#x27;s not worth it and I would lean towards the smaller number&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862144&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862099&lt;br&gt;In general it&amp;#x27;s better to bet on something broader than something more specific. As long as the sector grows you&amp;#x27;ll grow but a company can easily fail even if the product or the sector is wanted. When I was younger I invested in Nikola because I thought I would be hedging against Tesla. Turns out the company was a mess and people don&amp;#x27;t care that they&amp;#x27;re sucked dry by Elon. I still believe EVs will be more important for long haul and business use.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862220&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862144&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I invested in Nikola because I thought I would be hedging against Tesla. Turns out the company was a mess and people don&amp;#x27;t care that they&amp;#x27;re sucked dry by Elon&lt;br&gt;you thought the ceo who would go on to lead tsla to a 20x was sucking they company dry so instead you put your money into an obvious scam whose CEO would go on to be arrested for securities and wire fraud? Where do you do your research, the daily show???&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862273&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Translation: &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;PLEASE GOD STOP DUMPING MICROSOFT AHHHHHHHH&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862287&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862142&lt;br&gt;Why?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862313&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862099&lt;br&gt;https://investcalc.github.io/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862329&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862220&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;you thought the ceo who would go on to lead tsla to a 20x was sucking they company dry&lt;br&gt;No stop trying to twist the words on my screen. Elon is milking his customer base and its obvious and apparent to everyone. I thought people would notice that and move to a better car manufacturer. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;whose CEO would go on to be arrested for securities and wire fraud?&lt;br&gt;Hindsight is 20/20&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Where do you do your research, the daily show???&lt;br&gt;I invested long before any of the scandals came to be and the focus on long haul makes sense for as long as we don&amp;#x27;t have a sufficient hydrogen infrastructure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862353&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862099&lt;br&gt;Can he take one picture where he doesn&amp;#x27;t look like a slimeball piece of shit? Just one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862425&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862287&lt;br&gt;MPT claims you can only diversify away idiosyncratic (company specific) risk, and at some point you have so many different companies and exposure to so many different sectors that adding another company doesn&amp;#x27;t reduce risk by much if at all. I think markowitz or sharpe has a mathematical proof on it out there somewhere. Apparently they say that number is around 20-30&lt;br&gt;I say lean towards less because you have to take into consideration transaction costs and time and energy spent reorganizing your portfolio and tracking your positions as well. If you&amp;#x27;re just an average person and not a portfolio manager getting paid you&amp;#x27;re probably just fine with 12-15&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>So... is this "le AI will take your jerb!" just a lame FUD to make people (men, really) focus on becoming electricians,… — 23 replies — 33.1/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860974</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860974?lm=1771276619</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 21:16:59 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;So... is this &amp;quot;le AI will take your jerb!&amp;quot; just a lame FUD to make people (men, really) focus on becoming electricians,…&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860974'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 23 • Updated: 2026-02-16 21:16 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;So... is this &amp;quot;le AI will take your jerb!&amp;quot; just a lame FUD to make people (men, really) focus on becoming electricians, plumbers,or construction workers out of fear of being unemployed in the future? Society is running out of people interested on being blue collars, after all&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860984&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No it&amp;#x27;s just overselling shit on levels you&amp;#x27;ve never even dreamed were possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860993&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;every narrative is always fake and gay, just do the opposite of what jews say&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861009&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860974&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;just a lame FUD to make people (men, really) focus on becoming electricians,&lt;br&gt;It is FUD meant to oversell the technology and justify spending.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;It can destroy the world&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;It will take all the jobs&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;It is the most powerful and terrible thing ever&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;And this is because you must give us your money&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861012&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860974&lt;br&gt;That&amp;#x27;s why you have illegal immigrants doing it for half the cost.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;But don&amp;#x27;t worry, in a few years there will be waymo robot fleets that you can hire to do plumbing for 20$&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861030&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860974&lt;br&gt;I don’t know &lt;br&gt;But what I do know is if a Jew is saying it, then it’s a lie.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861182&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861009&lt;br&gt;I was imagining white hetero guys being strategically denied jobs by roasties as well, jews want women in position of power doing bullshit white collar jobs while men have to clean the toilets for a living. Men get no respect from women anymore, stay demoralized and depressed, while these &amp;quot;successful&amp;quot; women that have breakfast and brunchs every hour in the office aim for nepo jewish babies and give them childrenses. But yeah it&amp;#x27;s also about selling smoke, make profits from retards. What a circus the West has become, oh boy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861239&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861012&lt;br&gt;By plumbing, do you mean service my wife?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861575&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861239&lt;br&gt;No, that job will never be taken from the illegals&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861608&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860974&lt;br&gt;Not at all.&lt;br&gt;I am using AI to do basically all my work these days.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;claude spit out a RACI matrix in confluence markdown language for my new program.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;gemeni draw me a pyramid with 3 sections labeled such and such&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;chatgpt how do I even do my job?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;claude draw me a flow chart in mermaid format that is as follows&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is not a meme. AI can replace almost any white collar job right now if it is trained and focused on that role. Give it a couple years and they&amp;#x27;ll be good enough to just replace you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861611&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860974&lt;br&gt;the point is to demoralize people during a time when it&amp;#x27;s easier than ever to build stuff and take control of things&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861623&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;its powerful if you&amp;#x27;re a sigma male. the issue is you still need a network to push things + capital to make the numbers go up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861626&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860974&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;electricians, plumbers, contractors &lt;br&gt;Making a significant portion of their revenues from white-collar clients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861670&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860974&lt;br&gt;For all the &amp;quot;AI taking all the jobs&amp;quot; yap, I still get up every day and go to work, so guess it&amp;#x27;s BS&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861687&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861670&lt;br&gt;this essentially, I don&amp;#x27;t know anyone IRL who has told me &amp;quot;i lost my job because of AI, fugg&amp;quot; that&amp;#x27;s why I tell is just FUD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861691&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860974&lt;br&gt;I hope it takes my job. Cause I hate my job.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861737&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861687&lt;br&gt;most people still don&amp;#x27;t know how to harness it. think about how long it took for companies to even get half decent websites.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861756&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860974&lt;br&gt;It’s literal Indian scammers (tech CEOs) trying to pump their bags before they dump on retail and the gravy train comes to an end. LLMs are a dead end&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861803&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861009&lt;br&gt;How do you explain the mass layoffs then if it&amp;#x27;s all just made up hype? I see people on LinkedIn that have been unemployed for over a year complaining about AI taking their positions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861865&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Humans don&amp;#x27;t have the capacity to evaluate things in order, it&amp;#x27;s either on or off. People fantasize about having to survive in the post-apocalyptic world after most of humanity has been wiped out but can&amp;#x27;t fathom the same end result happening slowly after years and decades. The same thing is true about AI&amp;#x27;s effect on the job market. People can only think about AI either being shit and irrelevant or so advanced it makes their job obsolete. The reality is that AI will slowly but surely get integrated into most jobs, just like all technology is. Think about social media, the internet, computers, phones, calculators, etc. They have all become part of business and they have all changed the job market in unpredictable ways. We thought social media and the internet would connect us and bring countless benefits, the reality is that we are more divided, hateful, and exploited. The only guarantee is wages wont increase to keep pace with productivity and workers will suffer. Technology always has and always will benefit the business owners and harms the workers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;TLDR: you will still have to work, you will get less money, and there is nothing you can do about it because technology is the enemy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861983&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861803&lt;br&gt;either lies or bots, what else my friend? Don&amp;#x27;t tell me you trust (((linkedin))) or the media, lol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861991&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860974&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s demoralisation posting. Anyone who visits alternative media like 4chan must be forcibly blackpilled and distracted&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862255&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861803&lt;br&gt;the gay AI toys make finding a new job harder because lazy piece of shit HR people (same as before) use LLMs to spew out tons of pipeline posting job descriptions now. free and simple LLM tools did change that.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The economy was shit before and still mostly shit now. Inflation is down and markets are up slightly even after offsetting the inflation we do have, but salaries, bonuses, raises, hiring are NOT keeping up with the profit management is taking in. They&amp;#x27;re going to fuck over the middle forever to punish the orange man as long as they can, that&amp;#x27;s my secret non-/pol/, only /biz/ opinion&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862259&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;jokes on them&lt;br&gt;i&amp;#x27;m a jobless neet in my mid 20s&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Privacy Coins — 37 replies — 32.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61849447</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61849447?lm=1771274955</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 20:49:15 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Privacy Coins&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61849447'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 37 • Updated: 2026-02-16 20:49 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whether you like it or not, BTC is dying. Which way anons?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849481&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gold and silver.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849898&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849447&lt;br&gt;XMR as always. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849481&lt;br&gt;Acceptable but unusable for internet transactions and too easily stolen. Also makes smaller or spontaneous transactions harder unless the governments were to issue gold coins again and that would be bearish.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849958&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849447&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;BTC is a pedo coin&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;most used currency for CP is not however&lt;br&gt;quit the infighting, monegro.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61852712&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849958&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850046&lt;br&gt;The OP pic is interesting no matter how you slice it.. I think it calls into question the legitimacy of monegro. Who knows what else is in the &amp;quot;files.&amp;quot; Im not against monergro per se, but I was browsing the XMR general thread and I am not happy with what I saw over there. They are incredibly hostile to anyone non-monegro.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The lack of engagement here also bothers me, as that means that there are no alternatives other than a few eth based ones like the aztec one&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850071&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851550&lt;br&gt;Esptein aside, BTC has severe scalability issues&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;picrelated stolen from the monegro thread, i dont have any other memes on this pc&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854671&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61852712&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The OP pic is interesting no matter how you slice it.&lt;br&gt;Imagine letting demons and satanists control your life so much that you conspire against the letter M. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;They are incredibly hostile to anyone non-monegro.&lt;br&gt;No, we just despise you nerva shills. You&amp;#x27;re just &amp;#x27;asking questions&amp;#x27; but can&amp;#x27;t name a single one that hasn&amp;#x27;t been refuted multiple times. Then you cry about reddit as if that matters to 4chan. And then you just all seem to bring up, out of nowhere and completely unrelated of course, the solution which is an unmaintained jeetcoin with a ring size less than 1/3 of Monero&amp;#x27;s ring size and none of the development Monero received since 2018. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;as that means that there are no alternatives&lt;br&gt;Correct. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;a few eth based ones like the aztec one&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850071&lt;br&gt;ETH is PoS and a L2 will never be as good as a L1.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854812&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;/thread&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855004&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854671&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;ETH is PoS and a L2 will never be as good as a L1.&lt;br&gt;PoS is better that PoW. Something like what Chia has going on is arguably better for decentralization. Don&amp;#x27;t know what you mean by &amp;quot;never as good as L1&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855021&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855004&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;pos better than pow&lt;br&gt;The rest of your arguments are moot, because you start with a probably wrong premise&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855046&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855004&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Chia&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855184&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855021&lt;br&gt;Proof of asic is retarded.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855046&lt;br&gt;No such thing as a storage asic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855597&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849447&lt;br&gt;BTC is more alive than ever, most especially now with BTCFi narrative spreading like wild fire&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855672&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Proof of asic is retarded&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s at least as retarded as proof of space/memory&lt;br&gt;https://github.com/libbitcoin/libbitcoin-system/wiki/Proof-of-Memory-Fa%C3%A7ade&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855855&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849447&lt;br&gt;is monero the only non-jew coin out there?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855859&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;monero is the only actual privacy coin btw, all other coins are backdoored that&amp;#x27;s why nobody use them&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855868&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854671&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Imagine letting demons and satanists control your life so much that you conspire against the letter M.&lt;br&gt;Imagine ignoring it so hard that people like epstein are allowed to exist and eat your next door neighbors children while they backdoor BTC and then promote it. Fuck off.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;No, we just despise you nerva shills. You&amp;#x27;re just &amp;#x27;asking questions&amp;#x27; but can&amp;#x27;t name a single one that hasn&amp;#x27;t been refuted multiple times. Then you cry about reddit as if that matters to 4chan. And then you just all seem to bring up, out of nowhere and completely unrelated of course, the solution which is an unmaintained jeetcoin with a ring size less than 1/3 of Monero&amp;#x27;s ring size and none of the development Monero received since 2018.&lt;br&gt;What the fuck is nerva? and why am I a shill? What questions did I ask that even have a &amp;quot;refutation?&amp;quot; Reddit? &lt;br&gt;Nigger, what the actual fuck are you even talking about? Did you forget your meds? Im going to report your post as spam because none of what you said makes sense.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;picrelated.jpg&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854812&lt;br&gt;The line breaks being inconsistent is the same as all three 6&amp;#x27;s not being in upright position, for the two nuts for the tubal cain facebook logo not matching &amp;quot;Exactly.&amp;quot; If you&amp;#x27;re going to be a schizo, try to get on schizo levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855898&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Privacy coins&lt;br&gt;Why not Zcash?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855919&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855898&lt;br&gt;Several reasons, actually:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Centralized distribution from early dev-taxes to the founders (these taxes are still baked in but go to a slightly-less centralized committee now.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Privacy can be disabled at the protocol level because miners can reject the shielded pool. There is no fix to this because it would require removing the transparent pool entirely which would make Zcash delisted from all exchanges that it intentionally cripples its privacy for.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Mining hashrate is cornered, Zcash is 60% mined by a singe pool at any given time, and the 20% pool is the one that blocks the shielded pool.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Founder outright said they work with DC and will make Zcash private but not so private it could be used for crime.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855926&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849447&lt;br&gt;US Dollars ticker $&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856365&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855898&lt;br&gt;mossad coin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856605&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The line breaks being inconsistent is the same as all three 6&amp;#x27;s not being in upright position, for the two nuts for the tubal cain facebook logo not matching &amp;quot;Exactly.&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;No, it&amp;#x27;s not similar at all. The arches of the M are completely different.&lt;br&gt;The chrome symbol is the divine king symbol and matches exactly, and you can see far more similarities between the tubal Cain and facebook logos.&lt;br&gt;This meme sucks, the discord you got it from sucks, your ability to evaluate schizo levels suck, and you suck.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856661&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856605&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;unironically puts himself in a position that makes him look like he works for the very societies listed in infograph by explaining symbols further&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;t. mossad devil worshipper who sucks mason dick&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;only furthers the stereotype that monegro may be untrustworthy&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;claims i got my low quality infograph from discord&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Nigger i dont use discord&lt;br&gt;kek, the low quality bait and switch tactic always works on self proclaimed smart people&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856710&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849481&lt;br&gt;basedo!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856781&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;hurr durr i tricked you&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;a REAL schizo wouldn&amp;#x27;t know THAT much&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;i also don&amp;#x27;t know what t. means&lt;br&gt;I think we&amp;#x27;re done here&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857609&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849898&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;ve had thousands in BTC stolen via address poisoning, but my gold and silver are safe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858772&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856781&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;i also don&amp;#x27;t know what t. means&lt;br&gt;you have to be 18 to post here anon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858821&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858772&lt;br&gt;I remember when I turned 18 and my parents took me aside and told me that the abbreviated form of &amp;quot;regards&amp;quot; in finnish was a 4chan meme&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859002&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849447&lt;br&gt;Soon enough (this year) everything on ETH will be privacy enabled by ZAMA&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860206&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855868&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Imagine ignoring it so hard that people like epstein are allowed to exist and eat your next door neighbors children while they backdoor BTC and then promote it. Fuck off.&lt;br&gt;Why would I care about BTC when Monero exists? Why are you trying to make this about BTC in the first place when I clearly spoke about the claims you made about XMR? &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Im going to report your post as spam because none of what you said makes sense.&lt;br&gt;You claim that you were browsing the general but you haven&amp;#x27;t seen the main topic of the last few generals? Just admit that you&amp;#x27;re wrong. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857609&lt;br&gt;Gold can&amp;#x27;t be stolen? I&amp;#x27;d say it&amp;#x27;s far easier to pick a lock than the attack you fell victim to, if the user is somewhat attentive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861627&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860206&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Why would I care about BTC when Monero exists? Why are you trying to make this about BTC in the first place when I clearly spoke about the claims you made about XMR? &lt;br&gt;epstein files show he not only met with moot from 4chan, but also conspired to start /pol/, and had his hands in the israeli team that began to work on bitcoins code. XMR is also in said infographic due to masonic smybols, and has bots on their board. Thats why I created this general after finding the schizo infographic, neither BTC nor XMR can be trusted.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;You claim that you were browsing the general but you haven&amp;#x27;t seen the main topic of the last few generals? Just admit that you&amp;#x27;re wrong. &lt;br&gt;I hate talking to retarded bots. Admit that Im wrong about what exactly? that your entire thread glows to high heaven or that you &amp;quot;main topic&amp;quot; is non existant across the first 3 maxed out posts of general info? &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;bot continues to talk about how its far more unlikely for anons BTC to be stolen via address poisoning than for someone to pick his locks and steal his gold. Bots are coded by jeets, transfolk, and der jude, none of which are qualified to write bots.&lt;br&gt;How unfortunate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861669&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861627&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;epstein files show he not only met with moot from 4chan, but also conspired to start /pol/, and had his hands in the israeli team that began to work on bitcoins code.&lt;br&gt;Ok? I&amp;#x27;m here for XMR considering this thread is about privacy coins and picrel features XMR prominently in the middle. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;XMR is also in said infographic due to masonic smybols,&lt;br&gt;Back to hating the letter M? &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;and has bots on their board.&lt;br&gt;Wrong, nervajeet&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;after finding the schizo infographic,&lt;br&gt;In the Monero general, mind you&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;neither BTC nor XMR can be trusted.&lt;br&gt;Where&amp;#x27;s the problem in the code?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I hate talking to retarded bots.&lt;br&gt;Preferable to jeets on discord&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Admit that Im wrong about what exactly?&lt;br&gt;About Monero. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;that your entire thread glows to high heaven&lt;br&gt;Because we don&amp;#x27;t tolerate jeetcoins? lol&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;that you &amp;quot;main topic&amp;quot; is non existant across the first 3 maxed out posts of general info?&lt;br&gt;Are you seriously claiming that nerva wasn&amp;#x27;t mentioned at all in the last three generals? It&amp;#x27;s been mentioned by name over 100 times in the current general and it&amp;#x27;s not the first one to feature this irrelevant jeetcoin.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Bots are coded by jeets,&lt;br&gt;Says someone defending the literal jeetcoin, how ironic. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Show me the flaw you see in Monero&amp;#x27;s code.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861976&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HOLY SHIT GUYS OP IS A FREEMASON&lt;br&gt;HE EVEN HAS 2 MASONIC MS IN HIS ID&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862096&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861976&lt;br&gt;Is that like a double agent kinda deal or did he get promoted?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862129&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849481&lt;br&gt;aggressively low IQ take on the left&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>The US is in recession — 70 replies — 30.8/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61857490</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61857490?lm=1771270949</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 19:42:29 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;The US is in recession&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61857490'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 70 • Updated: 2026-02-16 19:42 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US is in recession&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857499&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White collar recession comes before regular recession 100% of the time. We&amp;#x27;ve been in a white collar recession since 2020.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857500&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;Always was, its depression for over a year now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857508&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;GDP is growing, recession is fake.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nothing ever happens. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stop putting your vibes and feelings into your job search, learn to get better skills and be more marketable to employers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;McDonalds is always hiring&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858397&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857499&lt;br&gt;Except 2022 had a labour shortage&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858404&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858383&lt;br&gt;https://fred.stlouisfed.org/series/CIVPART&lt;br&gt;Also I do not think they count gig workers as unemployed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858449&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858383&lt;br&gt;If you don&amp;#x27;t apply for one job a month, you&amp;#x27;re not unemployed. If you have a masters degree and you work at McDonald&amp;#x27;s, you&amp;#x27;re not unemployed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858696&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;I voted for this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858910&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857805&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Disrupted the international order from which the US greatly benefitted and everyone else benefited from the US even more&lt;br&gt;fuck off retard. did you forget&lt;br&gt;-single handedly carrying NATO&lt;br&gt;-protecting international shipping lanes&lt;br&gt;-being the global leader in innovation and tech&lt;br&gt;-only genuine believer and de facto practitioner of promoting human rights&lt;br&gt;? fuck you euronigger canacuck spic or whatever you are. we&amp;#x27;re allowed to take care of ourselves for once.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859778&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858910&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Wow america number one in everything when it created and proliferated a working order&lt;br&gt;Yeah no shit he already said that&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859785&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858023&lt;br&gt;Either Mossad agent or photoshopped picture&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859951&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857805&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;international order&lt;br&gt;jesus christ turn off the television. US economy (and western economy) is in tatters precisely because of the &amp;quot;international order&amp;quot; ie ZOG. They flood your country with cheap violent labor to suppress wages and sow division, they inflate away your wealth by constantly printing to pay the interest on government borrowing for GIBS for your replacements and zog wars. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How the fuck do you reach the conclusion that America needs an &amp;quot;international order&amp;quot; to function when it&amp;#x27;s downfall has correlated perfectly to its kowtowing to international interests. America is almost entirely self-sufficient and has plenty of skilled workers. It doesn&amp;#x27;t need an international order, it needs a financial sector that isn&amp;#x27;t destroying the country for its own benefit and it needs to get rid of the millions of useless eaters in your country. Get America back up to 70%+ White, fix your money printing problem, deal with the israel problem in your government, and the economy will take care of itself. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s just nuts to me that people talk about the economy without mentioning the giant rotting elephant in the room which is the trillions that gets siphoned from productive workers to various kike interests. The K-shaped economy isn&amp;#x27;t an accident it&amp;#x27;s deliberate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859958&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;DEI moneysinks getting destroyed&lt;br&gt;Sucks to suck. Go be a negro in Negrovia or something&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859986&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;Isn&amp;#x27;t it good for the US economy if everyone is losing their jobs to AI?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860143&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858383&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;go to jobcentre &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;get offerd the a streetsweeper&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;I din&amp;#x27;t waste 6 years of my life getting a master&amp;#x27;s to sweep puke and shit of the sidewalk&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;well if you don&amp;#x27;t want to work than you can&amp;#x27;t be unemployed, so no benefits for you&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;Call me Broomy-Mcbroomster guvna&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860535&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860143&lt;br&gt;I wish I got benefits, I&amp;#x27;ve been unemployed in Poland for 7 years now and I&amp;#x27;ve gotten a grand total of $0 in benefits&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860619&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859951&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Get America back up to 70%+ White, fix your money printing problem, deal with the israel problem in your government, and the economy will take care of itself.&lt;br&gt;anything else while we have the magic wand out sir?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860705&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859951&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;How the fuck do you reach the conclusion that America needs an &amp;quot;international order&amp;quot; to function when it&amp;#x27;s downfall has correlated perfectly to its kowtowing to international interests&lt;br&gt;What international interests? The US has been profiting off the international order since Breton Woods. Its rise as a superpower correlates to the dollar’s international dominance. It’s the opposite of what you’re describing.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;America is almost entirely self-sufficient&lt;br&gt;It is completely dependent on foreign pharmaceuticals and various input goods for manufacturing. It has virtually no domestic source of lithium, cobalt, graphite or REMs. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;the problem is international Jewry and this will be rectified when the us becomes an autarky &lt;br&gt;Why? &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rotting elephant in the room is a declining dollar, obscene debt, and an overinflated market + made up statistics. None of this gets better by fucking up international trade.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860719&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857750&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;US being in a recession isn&amp;#x27;t about Trump.&lt;br&gt;Yes he&amp;#x27;s a fucking retarded boomer brained moron, but US has been doomed to hit this point sooner or later ever since they decided to crank the money printers on permanently after 2008 and doomed the entire West to be stuck in a slow death limbo.&lt;br&gt;Everyone has basically just been waiting for the big one for years now and we&amp;#x27;re getting closer and closer to it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860738&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859951&lt;br&gt;You have no idea how the dollar system works and it shows. What&amp;#x27;s happening to the United States right now is irreversible&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860813&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860719&lt;br&gt;Printing after 2008 happened because 2008 happened, which happened because republicans deregulated finance. You&amp;#x27;re right, it&amp;#x27;s not about Trump, it&amp;#x27;s about half the country being fucking retarded hicks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860867&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860813&lt;br&gt;Republicans like Raegan deregulated finance, that’s true (though some of that was put into motion by Jimmy Carter). That said, it’s impossible to talk about 2008 without recognizing that Clinton is the one who repealed the Glass-Steagall act and let insurance banking merge with commercial banking. Pretty much every president for the 30 years leading up to 2008 did something to enable it or make it worse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860880&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860867&lt;br&gt;I forgot that Clinton was also the one that made derivatives immune to regulation. He really fucked up finance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860916&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857825&lt;br&gt;Holy shit this is the most retarded post I have ever read on /biz/, why are you on a finance board??&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860980&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860880&lt;br&gt;Clinton also forced banks to give mortgages to people with bad credit scores and low income&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861063&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857508&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;GDP was never meant to measure the health of the economy. Simon Kuznets advised against using it for that purpose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861445&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860705&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;It has virtually no domestic source of lithium, cobalt, graphite or REMs. &lt;br&gt;There are actually fucking tons of sources, but none of them are developed because US companies exported the environmental cost of mining them to &amp;quot;dEvElOpInG&amp;quot; nations for cheaper labor/materials and most of the mines shut down because they couldn&amp;#x27;t compete. There are ludicrous amounts of these materials just sitting there in the US.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US could be self-sufficient (example: fracking boom was because oil price had gotten to the point where domestic supply was economically viable again - in less than a decade the US had more oil than it could even use, because the oil was already in the ground, just not being extracted), but the profit motive won&amp;#x27;t allow self-sufficiency to persist if it&amp;#x27;s cheaper to import.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861531&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861445&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;”we are almost entirely self-sufficient”&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;”ok we currently have no infrastructure to mine these resources”&lt;br&gt;Yes, exactly. We are totally dependent on foreign suppliers and as of right now we do not have a domestic source for these things. My point stands and yours is wrong. Coping about how we COULD have these things eventually doesn’t matter. Like it or not, the US is not self-sufficient, and it isn’t close. We import tremendous amounts of goods. Don’t even bother looking into pharmaceuticals because it will just depress you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861694&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857750&lt;br&gt;We&amp;#x27;ve been in a recession since 2023. This isn&amp;#x27;t glorphf&amp;#x27;s fault or joepedo. Our economy is fake and gay made up of jewish daycare bullshit jobs. Soon it will all unravel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861711&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861531&lt;br&gt;Don&amp;#x27;t get your panties in a bunch, all I took issue with was saying &amp;quot;virtually no domestic source.&amp;quot; Some people in these discussions act like SEA is the only place in the world that has minerals.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A water source is still there even if nobody builds a well. Since you seem to get that, you were probably looking for the phrase &amp;quot;domestic SUPPLY.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861724&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857805&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oh no, its over, the Europeans and Anglos are mad we voted a republican again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861729&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858084&lt;br&gt;The fantasy is better than the reality&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861769&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857805&lt;br&gt;We should be bombing Mexico.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861811&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861711&lt;br&gt;No I wasn’t. I don’t feel like explaining it to you so I’ll just let AI do it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>there are people buying BTC at $67k expecting it to miraculously recover and moon to $300k+. — 28 replies — 20.4/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860893</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860893?lm=1771274174</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 20:36:14 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;there are people buying BTC at $67k expecting it to miraculously recover and moon to $300k+.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860893'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 28 • Updated: 2026-02-16 20:36 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;there are people buying BTC at $67k expecting it to miraculously recover and moon to $300k+. what is society doing to help these mentally ill people&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860896&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860893&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;what is society doing&lt;br&gt;collapsing expeditiously&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860897&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;idk why they do this but i will gladly buy their bags at 20-30K when they lose hope&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860925&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860893&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;there are people buying BTC at $5k expecting it to miraculously recover and moon to $100k+. what is society doing to help these mentally ill people&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;how you sound right now &lt;br&gt;Buy the Dip, Always Bank on the Bigger Fool&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860927&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860925&lt;br&gt;at 67K we are not at the dip, sorry&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860933&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m buying at $30k later this year and selling at $150k in 2029.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860934&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860893&lt;br&gt;people have given up on traditional means of success because basic things like owning the shelter over your head are out of reach for them. so they resort to risky financial behavior because they think that&amp;#x27;s the only way for them to really get ahead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860938&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860893&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;ll buy back at $8k once Saylor has capitulated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860972&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860933&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I&amp;#x27;m buying at a level that will never happen to sell at a price at only half the next ATH&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860981&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860893&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;expecting it to miraculously recover and moon to $300k+&lt;br&gt;uuuuh yes? retardo froggo. Not anytime soon, but yes in many years&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860988&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;bitcoin is an easy 3x from here, dude&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860990&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860893&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;we could be at the bottom now&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861000&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860927&lt;br&gt;Nigger we are -50% this is the bottom. The pumps are weaker but the dumps are too. Your brain is like a retarded child’s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861002&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860925&lt;br&gt;Except 100k had been tagged. The hype is done, the meme target was reached now what&amp;#x27;s left to keep this thing up long term is fundamentals&lt;br&gt;Oh wait&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861013&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860893&lt;br&gt;His name&amp;#x27;s Michael.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861023&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861000&lt;br&gt;this&lt;br&gt;bobotards are really expecting a -80% capitulation just like mumutards were expecting a 6x ATH from the last one&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861052&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861002&lt;br&gt;the meme target has always been bitcoin to $1,000,000&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861054&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860893&lt;br&gt;I expect it to fall a little further but I buy every week&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861058&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860893&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;There are people buying Bitcoin over $1 expect it to go to $100&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;What is wrong with these people&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Idk man&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861067&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;not buying until saylor capitulates&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861094&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861013&lt;br&gt;kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861100&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Moot spoke with Epstein via email&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Epstein got /pol/ created&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;flooding of BTC threads on /pol/ and /g/&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;/biz/ later created as crypto containment board&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;emails implicate Epstein on creating and /or getting BTC funded to extract wealth from lower class individuals.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bonus - Epstein asked by rich Elite friends if BTC worth is &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;anything via email.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;lol no” -Epstein&lt;br&gt;l&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861191&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861100&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;everything was made by Epstein because he emailed someone vaguely related to X &lt;br&gt;shalom&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861195&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861052&lt;br&gt;No, that was the fundamental long term target if BTC would be widely adopted. As a payment method it&amp;#x27;s even less adopted now than 10 years ago, the fundamental case is dead and buried. 100k it is sorry buddy, and it will never go to 100k again&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861199&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860938&lt;br&gt;It has to stay at $8k for 3 years for Strategy to be forced to sell some.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861243&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861199&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862007&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860934&lt;br&gt;people with that attitude are not going to be rewarded with gains. btc is basically guaranteed to crash imo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862021&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860893&lt;br&gt;because after over a decade people just can&amp;#x27;t seem to understand it takes a year for btc to fully crash after an ATH.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862065&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860893&lt;br&gt;No they don&amp;#x27;t. People bought at obvious support levels like 60k and sold at 72k for a free 20%. Meanwhile you&amp;#x27;re stuck holding USD which is constantly losing purchase power.&lt;br&gt;You are insecure and mad because buyers stop it from crashing further.&lt;br&gt;You are not a real bobo, you are a bull troon who wants to time the bottom which is why you deserve to get sidelined.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>&gt;Saylor will be liquida—ACK! — 38 replies — 16.6/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858109</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858109?lm=1771270893</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 19:41:33 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;&amp;gt;Saylor will be liquida—ACK!&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858109'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 38 • Updated: 2026-02-16 19:41 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;Saylor will be liquida—ACK!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858119&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;So we have to short squeeze bitcoin until 8k? &lt;br&gt;Noted&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858128&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Challenge accepted&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858135&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858109&lt;br&gt;Hostile takeovers will take place long before that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858216&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858109&lt;br&gt;Hes not going to sell&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858224&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858178&lt;br&gt;why does it matter if he&amp;#x27;s down 7 billion? the debt isn&amp;#x27;t due... seriously plz explain to me why it matters and why he can&amp;#x27;t just wait for the inevitable recovery?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858229&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858224&lt;br&gt;Explain how he repays creditors without diluting shareholders (baggies) to zero, if Bitcorn stays supressed for any significant period.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858234&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858229&lt;br&gt;the argument is that buttcorns stay at $8k for years? is that right?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858301&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858109&lt;br&gt;Im pretty sure a bank will call the loans long before it hits $8k because what the fuck would liquidating $6 billion of BTC do to the price even at todays levels?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858224&lt;br&gt;the banks will call in their loans if the collateral loses value long before $8k. retards like you dont understand that the bid/ask price is meaningless when you are trying to liquidate 715,000 btc. and that selling this in a short period of time would destroy order books and crash the market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858314&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858234&lt;br&gt;It doesn&amp;#x27;t need to, the stock is alreaady crashing because everyone knows he can;t keep up this scam for much longer. Even if the government is turning a blind eye now to his ponzi scheme.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858315&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Let&amp;#x27;s go 7.9k BTC!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858325&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858109&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;if Bitcoin falls to $8k, we have so much Bitcoin we could sell like you wouldn&amp;#x27;t even believe&lt;br&gt;Really confidence inspiring.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858370&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858128&lt;br&gt;CZ will either win or give us the greatest discount in history while he simultaneously send the whole crypto market to the brink of extinction&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858405&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858109&lt;br&gt;Btc to 7.9k confirmed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858418&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858109&lt;br&gt;So what happens when it drops to $7900?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858439&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858109&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858452&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858109&lt;br&gt;Anyone want to speculate what MSTR share price would be at BTC $8K …kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858499&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858418&lt;br&gt;He just refinances with a finger snap. ezpz.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858501&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Don&amp;#x27;t they have to make payments on that debt though, which will draw down assets further&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858608&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858301&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; bank loans&lt;br&gt;Where did you even get this information from? Afaik he has only take one bank loan from SVB which was paid back a long time ago.&lt;br&gt;His debt comes from convertible notes which won&amp;#x27;t mature before the next cycle (not in this bear market unless it&amp;#x27;s a multi year bear).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; selling this in a short period of time would destroy order books&lt;br&gt;He would never sell on the open markets. He can sell it to OTC services which will be able to finance whatever amount he has to sell.&lt;br&gt;Some 2011 whale sold 80k BTCs to Galaxy Digital when BTC was trading at 110k.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858619&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This jew is a ponzi scam artist and crypto lards only support him because they think he is doing the work of finding greater fools which is what they need for their own bags to go up&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859185&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858171&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;price dumps to $8k in effort to liquidate saylor&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;unsuccessful&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;those sellers don&amp;#x27;t buy back in at giga-generational wealth creating dips&lt;br&gt;sounds like bitcoin ain&amp;#x27;t the one&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859214&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858501&lt;br&gt;bro they just refinance and roll it forward, its simple&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859218&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858171&lt;br&gt;Whales know it doesn&amp;#x27;t even have to go that low. Keeping it at 30-40k for a few years could be sufficient.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859228&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858234&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;$8k&lt;br&gt;Check MSTR&amp;#x27;s price action when bitcoin is around $70k right now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859235&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858178&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;lowering your DCA is le bad&lt;br&gt;Okay retard&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859963&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859228&lt;br&gt;what does that have to do with Strategy&amp;#x27;s obligation to sell BTC?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;did you even read the thread?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860237&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858501&lt;br&gt;lol no, their convertible notes have a 0% coupon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860245&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The jeet brain can&amp;#x27;t comprehend Strategy&amp;#x27;s business model.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860247&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858109&lt;br&gt;ChatGPT says ther total liabilities are actually 15BN as of q3 2025 filings, but that still gives them a 60BN net asset position. I guess they&amp;#x27;re actually in a pretty safe position in terms of debt/margin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860391&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858152&lt;br&gt;Too many other players with too much skin in the game for them to do this. Pension funds, corpos and governments are tied to bitcoin now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860465&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860237&lt;br&gt;What about the coupé notes?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861801&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858109&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;ll be buying at $7999 then&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861808&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858178&lt;br&gt;Wow big deal. just refinance at a lower rate&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>SAY IT /BIZ/ ETHEREUM = PROGRAMMABLE MONEY — 9 replies — 15.3/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860962</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860962?lm=1771277000</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 21:23:20 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;SAY IT /BIZ/ ETHEREUM = PROGRAMMABLE MONEY&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860962'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 9 • Updated: 2026-02-16 21:23 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;SAY IT /BIZ/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;ETHEREUM = PROGRAMMABLE MONEY&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860982&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860962&lt;br&gt;ultrasound chads can&amp;#x27;t stop winning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861322&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860962&lt;br&gt;lol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861377&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860962&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;PROGRAMMABLE MONEY&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;There is no use case for this in the real world&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;B-B-BUT-&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;No&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861389&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860962&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;$87M&lt;br&gt;Wow it&amp;#x27;s literally nothing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862015&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860962&lt;br&gt;Not going back to that 25 dollar swap fee scam chain. Also the eth team could just fork the entire project whenever they feel like it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862198&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860962&lt;br&gt;You would think that these harvard cunts are smart enough to buy the real asset instead of the etf.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862246&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860962&lt;br&gt;eth will never deliver on what they&amp;#x27;ve promised. its been over 10 years we&amp;#x27;ve been hearing that smart contracts will be the future of business and finance. all we&amp;#x27;ve got was&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;cryptokitties&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;NFTs&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;USDT money laundering&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;shitcoin casino&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;ICOs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862286&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860962&lt;br&gt;ETH is the future of finance and I&amp;#x27;m tired of pretending it isn&amp;#x27;t&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862299&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860962&lt;br&gt;all the stablecoins use ethereum so there will be demand for that and 1500-2000 is probably bottom territory&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>