<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>/biz/ Active (filtered, with replies)</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/</link><description>Filtered out: general, gme, bbbyq. OP + first 3 replies + last 30 replies.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 17:37:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>The US is in recession — 93 replies — 372.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61857490</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61857490?lm=1771349834</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 17:37:14 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;The US is in recession&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61857490'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 93 • Updated: 2026-02-17 17:37 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US is in recession&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857499&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White collar recession comes before regular recession 100% of the time. We&amp;#x27;ve been in a white collar recession since 2020.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857500&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;Always was, its depression for over a year now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857508&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;GDP is growing, recession is fake.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nothing ever happens. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stop putting your vibes and feelings into your job search, learn to get better skills and be more marketable to employers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;McDonalds is always hiring&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861531&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861445&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;”we are almost entirely self-sufficient”&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;”ok we currently have no infrastructure to mine these resources”&lt;br&gt;Yes, exactly. We are totally dependent on foreign suppliers and as of right now we do not have a domestic source for these things. My point stands and yours is wrong. Coping about how we COULD have these things eventually doesn’t matter. Like it or not, the US is not self-sufficient, and it isn’t close. We import tremendous amounts of goods. Don’t even bother looking into pharmaceuticals because it will just depress you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861694&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857750&lt;br&gt;We&amp;#x27;ve been in a recession since 2023. This isn&amp;#x27;t glorphf&amp;#x27;s fault or joepedo. Our economy is fake and gay made up of jewish daycare bullshit jobs. Soon it will all unravel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861711&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861531&lt;br&gt;Don&amp;#x27;t get your panties in a bunch, all I took issue with was saying &amp;quot;virtually no domestic source.&amp;quot; Some people in these discussions act like SEA is the only place in the world that has minerals.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A water source is still there even if nobody builds a well. Since you seem to get that, you were probably looking for the phrase &amp;quot;domestic SUPPLY.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861724&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857805&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oh no, its over, the Europeans and Anglos are mad we voted a republican again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861729&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858084&lt;br&gt;The fantasy is better than the reality&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861769&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857805&lt;br&gt;We should be bombing Mexico.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861811&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861711&lt;br&gt;No I wasn’t. I don’t feel like explaining it to you so I’ll just let AI do it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863135&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858023&lt;br&gt;Pam Bondi was such a hot piece of ass when she was young. She&amp;#x27;s still sorta cute give that she&amp;#x27;s sixty years old. It&amp;#x27;s too bad she&amp;#x27;s protecting Jewish pedophiles and cannibals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863175&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;BUMP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863206&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And the burger gov is again burning absolutely everything in the market, including themselves to make a smoke screen to cover the crashing dollar.&lt;br&gt;Nobody wants that shit yet it is going up with not only no buyers but countries constantly throwing it into the market. Absolute shitshow from a drowning in shit man.&lt;br&gt;Funny isn&amp;#x27;t it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863218&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860719&lt;br&gt;The boat that is jewsa has been sinking for a while. The orange nigger is actively making more holes in it and setting it on fire&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863252&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What&amp;#x27;s the polymarket for that??&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863679&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857500&lt;br&gt;Try since 08. Things have never actually genuinely recovered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864332&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;End of the Juglar cycle. Overproduction crisis. Fed interest rates plunging toward zero. Soon an other Capital idling necessary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864333&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863679&lt;br&gt;Capital final crisis since 2008.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864989&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863206&lt;br&gt;2006 was giving out loans like candy to people who had absolutely no way of ever servicing them&lt;br&gt;this then resulted in a lot of forced selling into a no bid market as all of this inventory was cleared when the bubble popped&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;right now we dont have excessive loans, quite the opposite retards arent given insane loans this is legit existing money bidding up hard assets because so much money got printed and it has to go somewhere&lt;br&gt;you dont get a crash in housing without forced selling and who is going to force sell his real estate at low prices without the bank margin calling them&lt;br&gt;unlike stocks which are completely fungible and its price is set at the margin, housing isnt and the owner can just sit on the asset forever and not be forced to take any offer being made at market price&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;to disrupt this &amp;#x27;bubble&amp;#x27; you need the government unprinting the money supply (lol, lmao even) or you need a large section of boomers dying off and leaving their heirs with no way to pay the taxes/upkeep and force dump it&lt;br&gt;the second one is the only realistic option, tho there is also the risk that the heirs can pay for the inheritance and real estate is now permanently locked up in magnate hands and the nation reduced to permarenting slave&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865001&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It really isn&amp;#x27;t mentioned enough that our &amp;quot;recovery&amp;quot; after 2008 was just setting interest rates to 0 for 10 years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865048&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864989&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;...a large section of boomers dying off and leaving their heirs with no way to pay the taxes/upkeep...real estate is now permanently locked up in magnate hands....&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;ve laid out exactly what&amp;#x27;s been going on since 2008&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865068&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865048&lt;br&gt;yes thats the point, the implication here is that real estate is now permanently priced out of the middle class income range&lt;br&gt;not that a crash is imminent like the anon i was replying to seemed to suggest&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865501&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;I knew it was really over when Wendy&amp;#x27;s and pizza Hut announced theyre closing hundreds of stores.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865585&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;Idk these terms, and economics is a fraudulent science anyways, so I&amp;#x27;ll just say what I see.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;My life sucks.&lt;br&gt;Its getting worse.&lt;br&gt;I am watching generational decline among my family (each new set of kids struggle more than their parents).&lt;br&gt;People seem unhappy.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Call that recession, depression, or economic boon! Idc, US is a shithole.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m sure people will respond saying I&amp;#x27;m cherry picking. Dishonesty is rampant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865659&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857779&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Foreign money taking investments out of the US because trump is an unpredictable fucking moron being puppeteered by unironically evil people&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;American dollar has lost 10% of its value over the course of 2025&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Constant tariff bullshitery that is objectively hurting American industries that rely on imports&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Nuked basedbean deal with China on top of farmers needing a fucking bailout because of the retard they voted in (again)&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Tourism industry cratering every day as we speak so even less money being injected into the economy &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;ICE operation have caused businesses across the country to shut down because either no one&amp;#x27;s willing to go out, or because they don&amp;#x27;t want random goons in masks harassing employees&lt;br&gt;Dude it&amp;#x27;s actually impressive how hard these retards just destroyed the entire reputation of america abroad and fucked us over domestically, but his cult fan base and circle of wannabe oligarchs who own media outlets will continue telling you that there is no war in ba sing se&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865663&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861063&lt;br&gt;We really need to do what the Chinese do with making sure household consumption as share of GDP is increasing. Actually reflects living standards instead of billions of dollars getting spitswapped between 3-4 different AI companies constantly. Then again, most of the people hear would just ree hearing the term “5 year plan” or “stability focused infrastructure development.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865674&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865585&lt;br&gt;MIGAtrannies will happily eat shit if a libtard has to smell their breath.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865800&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865585&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;US is a shithole&lt;br&gt;and the usa still gives you about the best chance in the world to improve your life if you come from humble beginnings&lt;br&gt;altho it also offers you every temptation possible to make you drive yourself over the financial cliff at every turn at the same time it offers you opportunity&lt;br&gt;just know its far worse everywhere else as society in general is reverting back to medieval style caste based system of neither hope nor escape&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865942&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865800&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;and the usa still gives you about the best chance in the world to improve your life if you come from humble beginnings&lt;br&gt;this has not been true in at least 20-25 years&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866035&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865942&lt;br&gt;lol, lmao&lt;br&gt;then give me the list of countries that you think arent just better today but were better 20 years ago and i&amp;#x27;ll have a good laugh&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;and to clarify we are specifically talking about giving chances to poor unconnected people so dont say retarded shit like liechtenstein&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866071&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865800&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;he fell for the meme&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866130&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860705&lt;br&gt;None of these are necessary. We could be totally self-sufficient, even for things like rare-earths. The Epstein class decided that would be bad for them so we aren&amp;#x27;t.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866186&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866130&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;pharmaceuticals are not necessary &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;input goods for new tech are not necessary &lt;br&gt;Uh huh. So what’s necessary? Shovels, canned food and farmland? If you want to be Amish so badly just do it, nobody is stopping you. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the real world, though, self-sufficiency would entail access to pharmaceuticals and the ability to evolve technologically and keep up with the first world. We can sing songs all day about how the US could be self-sufficient one day and that’s fine. The point is that we aren’t.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Privacy Coins — 71 replies — 284.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61849447</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61849447?lm=1771349590</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 17:33:10 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Privacy Coins&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61849447'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 71 • Updated: 2026-02-17 17:33 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whether you like it or not, BTC is dying. Which way anons?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849481&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gold and silver.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849898&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849447&lt;br&gt;XMR as always. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849481&lt;br&gt;Acceptable but unusable for internet transactions and too easily stolen. Also makes smaller or spontaneous transactions harder unless the governments were to issue gold coins again and that would be bearish.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849958&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849447&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;BTC is a pedo coin&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;most used currency for CP is not however&lt;br&gt;quit the infighting, monegro.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862538&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;steals pic that is interesting from nervjeet&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;stolen image literally has the fucking fileneame from the post it came from&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;this bot thinks im the same guy&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;his nonsensical bot reply gives him away within a few posts because it always handles the same&lt;br&gt;Report this fucker, if he doesnt get banned, all the more reason to NOT trust monero or anyone pushing monero, because the bot is being run from 4chan itself.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;on the XMR thread, this is the same bot&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860201 DXIC7i+b&lt;br&gt;it just goes on and on. hope real anons find this post and start to question wtf is going on around here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862542&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862475&lt;br&gt;Do you have Revolut?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Use it on Hodlhodl (trade escrow service)&lt;br&gt;Send it to some BTC wallet (Sparrow)&lt;br&gt;Use Trocador to convert it to XMR&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862551&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859002&lt;br&gt;Privacy is basically impossible to do for smart contracts outside of creating a specific app such as Tornado. When you create specific apps such as Tornado, you make it extremely vulnerable to censorship from the government, like happened to Tornado. Even though the lawsuit was &amp;quot;dropped&amp;quot;, activity on Tornado is basically nonexistent because nobody trusts it anymore. They shouldn&amp;#x27;t. Likewise, nobody should ever trust a &amp;quot;privacy app&amp;quot; on top of a public L1.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;And don&amp;#x27;t get me started on how ridiculous a &amp;quot;privacy L2&amp;quot; would be on top of a public L1.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you want privacy, you start at the L1 layer.&lt;br&gt;If you want privacy, you choose Monero.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862566&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862538&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;this bot thinks im the same guy&lt;br&gt;No, I think you&amp;#x27;re a nerva shill that tries to play stupid and make this about BTC (it never was) and me being bad because I expose your stupidity. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;his nonsensical bot reply gives him away within a few posts because it always handles the same&lt;br&gt;If it took you 7 posts to undercover my identity as the jeet enemy #1 then either I&amp;#x27;m not as predictable as you say or you&amp;#x27;re retarded. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;it just goes on and on.&lt;br&gt;Because I always refute every point nervajeets make. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;hope real anons find this post and start to question wtf is going on around here.&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m real, that&amp;#x27;s why I continuously offer you to ask me anything regarding XMR. All of the questions you (in English this can be used both for singular and plural, raj) posted have been answered. I&amp;#x27;m glad you visited the general again and saw that they actually have been answered three years ago already on your favorite platform - reddit. &lt;br&gt;If you have any flaws in XMR&amp;#x27;s you wish to point out let me know, otherwise admit defeat or continue embarrassing yourself publicly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862582&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849447&lt;br&gt;framing bitcoin as an epstein jewish globalist pedo creation to sabotage it right as it was on the cusp of actually elbowing its way into the world financial system was a masterstroke psyop&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862608&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862566&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Because I always refute every point nervajeets make. &lt;br&gt;NO ONE MADE ANY POINTS ITT you fucking poo stain bot. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I&amp;#x27;m real, that&amp;#x27;s why I continuously offer you to ask me anything regarding XMR. All of the questions you (in English this can be used both for singular and plural, raj) posted have been answered. I&amp;#x27;m glad you visited the general again and saw that they actually have been answered three years ago already on your favorite platform - reddit.&lt;br&gt;If you have any flaws in XMR&amp;#x27;s you wish to point out let me know, otherwise admit defeat or continue embarrassing yourself publicly.&lt;br&gt;No thanks Alexa, get the fuck of this thread&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862631&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862608&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;NO ONE MADE ANY POINTS ITT you fucking poo stain bot.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The OP pic is interesting no matter how you slice it..&lt;br&gt;Did &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61852712 not make any points then? &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;If you have any flaws in XMR&amp;#x27;s you wish to point out let me know, otherwise admit defeat or continue embarrassing yourself publicly.&lt;br&gt;Hey, I remember someone saying that!&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;No thanks Alexa, get the fuck of this thread&lt;br&gt;I appreciate your concern but I&amp;#x27;ll continue staying here if you are continuing to smear the only properly functioning crypto currency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862698&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861669&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;CTRL+F &amp;quot;Nerva&amp;quot;, first person to mention anything about Nerva is the retarded nigger from the Monero threads&lt;br&gt;&amp;quot;Nervajeets&amp;quot; living rent free lmao&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Nerva network hashrate just hit another ATH today.&lt;br&gt;No signs of slowing down&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863379&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849447&lt;br&gt;Buy Decred.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863975&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863379&lt;br&gt;Irrelevant shitcoin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864393&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862698&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;Nervajeets&amp;quot; living rent free lmao&lt;br&gt;No, but I notice patterns, like the smell of cow shit, overuse of the word sir (misspoken as sar) and the incessant need to shill some unmaintained jeet coin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864510&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862698&lt;br&gt;Irrelevant shitcoin #2&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864651&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864393&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Nerva sucks as a privacy coin&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Nerva was forked from moneros code&lt;br&gt;You only get to pick one, bot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864667&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864651&lt;br&gt;Nice try but having less than 1/3 of our ring size and no mitigations against multiple attacks that worked on our code base (the devs don&amp;#x27;t even know whether their code has the same flaws or not) means it is not sufficient as a privacy coin. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;picrel&lt;br&gt;Next time try something somebody actually said&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864677&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849898&lt;br&gt;why would that be bearish&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864683&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864677&lt;br&gt;The governments as they are currently don&amp;#x27;t want to embrace our freedom or even anything to our benefit. If they go back to gold coins there will be some catch. If the jew embraces something, try to move as far away from that as possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864708&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855597&lt;br&gt;BTCFi is giving it more use cases with Babylon leading the charge. And I think when we have more projects offering native BTC staking, then we will see the narrative go viral&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864866&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864667&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Try something somebody actually said&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;literally you on every general&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;almost you entirely&lt;br&gt;Cry me some diodes, clanker.&lt;br&gt;Nerva is here to stay.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864897&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864866&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Nerva is here to stay.&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t care if it stays as long as you stop smearing XMR and spamming our threads&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864948&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864897&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I don&amp;#x27;t care if it stays as long as you stop smearing XMR and spamming our threads&lt;br&gt;The only spammer is you, in both this thread and the xmr general. You came here to start shit and have done so in every privacy thread that has popped up. You also accuse everyone of being a poojeet and promoting nerva. Again, the only person promoting (xmr in your case) and causing a stink has been YOU. So fuck off back to your little monero hole, jeetbot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865014&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864948&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The only spammer is you,&lt;br&gt;I wish that were true but sadly the nervajeets constantly try to shit up our thread and this board. There&amp;#x27;s a reason all of these anti-Monero threads pop up when they lose the discussion in the general. Notice how quiet they&amp;#x27;ve become after &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860646 was posted. All of their anti-Monero arguments (which was the entire value proposition for nerva) are gone. Their questions they claim never were answered poofed up into air. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;You came here to start shit&lt;br&gt;OP literally accuses XMR of being some freemason bullshit. You&amp;#x27;re the perfect representation of the jew asking what harm he has done to us. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;You also accuse everyone of being a poojeet and promoting nerva.&lt;br&gt;No, I say that the ones that copy all of the points the nervajeets make to be a nervajeets. That&amp;#x27;s because the only people interested in nerva are jeets.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Please don&amp;#x27;t challenge me when I smear the only functional crypto currency please just go away I can&amp;#x27;t handle it please please please&lt;br&gt;No sar, you wish to talk about XMR? I&amp;#x27;ll be there and refute each on of your pathetic claims.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865124&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864651&lt;br&gt;Holy shit, XMR to a fucking T anon...&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865014&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;bot programmed to hate random shitcoin&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;even if not true, makes it look like hes funded by masons/jews because he literally cannot stop promoting monero&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;becomes a meme in and of himself here&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864651&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;he seriously cant stop&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;he will bring nerva up in random threads every chance he gets even when no one is talking about it&lt;br&gt;Just fucking stop and go away monegro. Maybe they didnt stop after that was posted, because they were never spamming up your threads in the first place you pathetic fucking loser. Only you were, they were just asking questions, something anyone can do. I scoured your xmr generals, and your clearly the psychopath across every fucking one. Non stop blogposts of text that do nothing but go in circles, and now youre doing it here. Save yourself some time and go shit up someone elses thread. Oh right, you cant, because youre a monegro botnet that works for monero glowies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I started this thread to discuss privacy coins and all youve done is shit up my thread you piece of shit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865161&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865014&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;bot&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865268&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862698&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862796&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864651&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864866&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865161&lt;br&gt;good morning nervasaaars&lt;br&gt;truly xnv is the most aryan bharatoken superior peer-to-poop privacy coin xnvsaars redeem asap&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865595&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865268&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;i cant stop sucking monero dick, am i gay enough yet? Somebody like me pleeease!!&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;Back to your xmr general faggot shill&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865847&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865268&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;nooo not my heckin fedcoin noo all other privacy coins are jeetcoins noooo&lt;br&gt;CryptoNight-Adaptive &amp;gt; RandomX for decentralization&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865869&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865014&lt;br&gt;Fuck jannies and fuck Monero. XMR stays up, Nerva generals get took down immediately. Your jewish glowcoin is gonna hit zero, and youll have no one to blame but yourselves. Your posts never get removed? Why is that? Is it bc your a jannie? All you do is advertise monero on here, yet you never get banned.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kek picrelated asshole, proof youre just a monero shill who works for the jew. How many nerva generals have you deleted? All of them? We know what youre doing. Fuck you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865956&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865869&lt;br&gt;Have you tried bumping your generel thread so it stays up like everyone else does&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865998&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865956&lt;br&gt;Wasnt my general. I got the screenshot someone snapped of it off the discord. No way a thread gets bumped off this board that fast. There is shit on here for days that no one replies to. Mods are afraid of it. Idk why. Glowies or bagholders probably.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866158&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865869&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;This thread has been pruned or deleted &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865998&lt;br&gt;How do you know that it wasn&amp;#x27;t deleted by the OP?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Are people really shifting to the EU? I keep seeing more and more threads focussed on EU biz? Did Trump really fuck the… — 22 replies — 88.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861131</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861131?lm=1771349384</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 17:29:44 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Are people really shifting to the EU? I keep seeing more and more threads focussed on EU biz? Did Trump really fuck the…&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861131'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 22 • Updated: 2026-02-17 17:29 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Are people really shifting to the EU? I keep seeing more and more threads focussed on EU biz? Did Trump really fuck the US economy that much? Should i start investing in Europe too?&lt;br&gt;t.asian biz bro&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861139&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861131&lt;br&gt;no...that was the move over a year ago. those are the exit liquidity farming shills youre seeing&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861253&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861139&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;over a year ago&lt;br&gt;What about all the investment firms that started pulling out of the US over Trump&amp;#x27;s Greenland threats? This happened recently. Are you sure that the move has stopped or is it still ongoing?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861308&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861131&lt;br&gt;yes they have always been the main character. america is strong but there is nothing holy in this stolen country. it will always remain a european colony in spirit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861368&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861131&lt;br&gt;how many european companies do you know?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861374&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;he isn&amp;#x27;t already&lt;br&gt;I shiggy doo, better hurry up!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861920&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861131&lt;br&gt;America has been in a crab market since Oct and possibly a bear market since a few weeks. Meanwhile Europe is in a bull market. You need to pick the right ETFs and stocks though. Best ask Gemini. I&amp;#x27;m big on Siemens Energy and country index ETFs like UK, Poland, Italy, Greece, etc&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861932&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861131&lt;br&gt;There&amp;#x27;s literally nothing good about the EU for finance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861959&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I’m european and the shift from my childhood is just immense. Back then most of the music would be american, most of film and television, most video games ect. Nowdays there aren’t any big trends coming from USA anymore, nobody cares about american pop culture and it just feels mild and old fashioned.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861986&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861959&lt;br&gt;American pop culture is dogshit now. The US used to be where all the cool movies came from, now it&amp;#x27;s all slop.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862063&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861986&lt;br&gt;Yeah the last time american culture was cool was in like 2011 or so.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862081&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861131&lt;br&gt;Europe is a joke dude. Putting a bunch of dead civilizations into the same economic zone, salting it with Muslims, and picking a fight with both Russia and the US doesn’t look great. They don’t produce much, spend like crazy, don’t reproduce, and are filled with leftists and degenerates. In 50 years it’ll be an Islamic caliphate. You’re better off looking elsewhere&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862094&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862081&lt;br&gt;Lmao you’re talking like different european countries are different ancient civilizations. You have no idea what you’re talking about.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862531&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861959&lt;br&gt;American here, our music is all spics and our movies are all gay niggers, good job avoiding our jew exports.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862556&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861131&lt;br&gt;The only good EU stock rn is defense, but I wouldn&amp;#x27;t hold it for long, all their talk of doing this and that is already falling apart because they can&amp;#x27;t agree whose falling industry gets the most gibs to build their supposedly military hardware, 100% they will quietly cancel everything in a year or two as nobody notices, other than that there&amp;#x27;s literally no companies worth it at all there, not even euros put money there they put all in the us and keep doing despite whatever hostility they may feel&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862568&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861131&lt;br&gt;You should&amp;#x27;ve already had international stocks years ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862602&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;follow numbers not narratives&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862640&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The money sure did. My Euro etfs saved my portfolio last year. Keep in mind pic related is not including a 11% apy dividend so the total 1year return was 33% vs the S&amp;amp;P500 which only returned 11% in that same year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862653&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861920&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;a crab market since Oct&lt;br&gt;Oh no, NVDA hasn&amp;#x27;t gone up another trillion in 4 months, it&amp;#x27;s all over.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865879&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861131&lt;br&gt;invest in Eastern Poland&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865999&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861131&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Are people really shifting to the EU? &lt;br&gt;Nope.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I keep seeing more and more threads focussed on EU biz? &lt;br&gt;k&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;focussed&lt;br&gt;Do not redeem saar.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Did Trump really fuck the US economy that much? &lt;br&gt;Nope.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Should i start investing in Europe too?&lt;br&gt;Don&amp;#x27;t care.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;t.asian biz bro&lt;br&gt;Quit reading right there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866095&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861131&lt;br&gt;I mean I straight up lose money investing in the US as long as the Dollar is that weak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866142&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;there&amp;#x27;s some great ideas in here. you guys should do that stuff if you really believe in yourselves, I believe in you too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>&gt;mom yells at me for not having a job 5 months after I got laid off from my last one &gt;Complains how we need more money t… — 40 replies — 42.5/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61863594</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61863594?lm=1771346471</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 16:41:11 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;&amp;gt;mom yells at me for not having a job 5 months after I got laid off from my last one &amp;gt;Complains how we need more money t…&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61863594'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 40 • Updated: 2026-02-17 16:41 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;mom yells at me for not having a job 5 months after I got laid off from my last one&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Complains how we need more money to pay the bills and how she can&amp;#x27;t keep working 10 hour shifts to pay our bills&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Look through her purse when she&amp;#x27;s not looking &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;See a $600 receipt for perfume and makeup, and a bank note evidencing a $1800 transfer to her neet sister who also has 2 neet sons and a neet daughter. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Dad gambled away another $10K in stocks. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;He keeps sending me job openings in other states/cities that require 10+ years of experience and he tells me &amp;quot;just walk up to them and ask them to train you, that&amp;#x27;s how we did it back in the old days&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;My own savings are slowly dwindling and I&amp;#x27;ve got no more than a few months left before I&amp;#x27;m officially broke &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;800+ job apps and nothing yet&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m not sure how much more of this I can take bros...&lt;br&gt;Why won&amp;#x27;t the economy get better? &lt;br&gt;Who do I blame for this miserable situation?&lt;br&gt;What are some easy painless ways to check out of this economy earlier don&amp;#x27;t speak?&lt;br&gt;Why are old people all so stupid and contemptible?&lt;br&gt;NGMI?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863604&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863594&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Who do I blame for this miserable situation?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863605&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;See a $600 receipt for perfume and makeup&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;a bank note evidencing a $1800 transfer to&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Dad gambled away another $10K in stocks&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Complains how we need more money to pay the bills &lt;br&gt;what came first?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863607&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863594&lt;br&gt;Meant to say, So to speak, not don&amp;#x27;t speak &lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s been almost a few decades of smartphone development and auto correct still doesn&amp;#x27;t work properly yet AI fags are still like &amp;quot;we&amp;#x27;re totally gonna get agi and self driving cars this year bro!!!&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863782&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863651&lt;br&gt;NTA but I was medically disqualified after an injury helping a relative&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863786&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863594&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Join ICE.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863791&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863651&lt;br&gt;Most active duty army tried to join a different branch first (bar combat arms), but couldn&amp;#x27;t due to various reasons. Be real this is /biz/.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863810&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Do you live with your parents? That sounds like a lot of the problem&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863822&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863810&lt;br&gt;COL being what it is means even living with asshole parents is better in every circumstance other than them literally being physically abusive or outright robbing you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863846&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;mom seething that she might have to come out of early retirement because her 401k is only up 5% since the start of the year and she spends too much on vacations&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;complains &amp;quot;it&amp;#x27;s not fair, I should get to have a life&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;mfw she used to say this all the time whne I was in highschool when she grounded me -for existing- so she could go out with her friends on fridays, preventing me from ever having a life&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;realize she&amp;#x27;s a narcissist and deserves to suffer and am glad ot be an albatross around her neck&lt;br&gt;Shouldn&amp;#x27;t have stolen 20,000 dollars from me when I was 23, bitch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863852&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863651&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863648&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863782&lt;br&gt;Army is good because it runs weeaboo psyops.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863786&lt;br&gt;I applied for ICE in 2024 before Trump got elected, they&amp;#x27;re hiring beaners instead. Turns out no one will just &amp;#x27;let&amp;#x27; you be useful to society while making 150k a year working 80 hours a week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863856&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863822&lt;br&gt;He&amp;#x27;s just gonna tell you you&amp;#x27;re a loser and to get an apartment with a crackhead roommate or something. Your parents are the problem for not hooking you up with a year of rent and a job if they don&amp;#x27;t want you around. American parents deserve everything coming to them for stealing from their own kids. Who the fuck thinks they can just peace out and retire when society is collapsing lmao. Anyone who says &amp;quot;not my problem, I&amp;#x27;ll be dead by the time it gets REAL bad&amp;quot; is a person I conside rit my duty to cause as much suffering as posible for.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863912&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sounds like your whole family is dead weight except your mom. The perfume and makeup is probably a desperate move to hopefully find a man.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863922&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863856&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Anyone who says &amp;quot;not my problem, I&amp;#x27;ll be dead by the time it gets REAL bad&amp;quot; is a person I conside rit my duty to cause as much suffering as posible for.&lt;br&gt;They&amp;#x27;ll all be abused by Indians in the retirement home while their actual children are estranged. Poetic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864141&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863594&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863622&lt;br&gt;How old are you, OP? Sounds like your family is financially abusive to you. Can you move out on your own (as soon as you find a job, I mean) and cut contact?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864148&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863822&lt;br&gt;It really isn&amp;#x27;t. You can live VERY cheaply in a lot of Asian countries (Thailand, Laos, Indonesia) and do ridiculously low-paying remote work and still come out with net savings every month.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I worked in Taiwan (DON&amp;#x27;T GO THERE) for a while and was able to save over 50% of my pay even though I made half as much as an American would make doing the same job (not ESLosering).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wish I hadn&amp;#x27;t because it completely destroyed my health permanently (they&amp;#x27;re just as bad, maybe worse, about dumping toxic industrial chemicals in food as the mainland chinsects), but it was the only thing available to me after the 2008-12 crash during the Obamaconomy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864222&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863594&lt;br&gt;corner your dad and mom about that 600+1.8k+10k$. That&amp;#x27;ll make them shut for another 1 month.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864358&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863594&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;neet sister who also has 2 neet sons and a neet daughter.&lt;br&gt;nigga how old are you? &lt;br&gt;or are you calling infants neets kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864379&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863594&lt;br&gt;What the fuck does your retarded family have to do with the economy?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864420&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864358&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;her neet sister&lt;br&gt;His aunt is the neet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864425&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863648&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863651&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863643&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;just go get killed for ZOG!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The only military worth joining is the russian one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864429&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864222&lt;br&gt;These are classic case narcissists or sociopaths. They’ll become affronted, say something along the lines of ‘none of your business’ and if they are reticent then it would most certainly be for lip service.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864434&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864425&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;just go get killed for ZOG (east)!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864449&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863643&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863648&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863651&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863852&lt;br&gt;Wow the sõyjack party leaks were true this place is infested with glowies&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864425&lt;br&gt;come on dude&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864740&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864358&lt;br&gt;My neet aunts children are in there fucking 40s and never worked jobs yet live like kings. One of them is 400 pounds and my mom complains about how she needs to keep buying him bigger and bigger gift shirts every year...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864743&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;beat your mother&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864751&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864141&lt;br&gt;I can&amp;#x27;t unfortunately.&lt;br&gt;I tried really hard but it didn&amp;#x27;t work out&lt;br&gt;Got my mom&amp;#x27;s adhd+schizophrenic OCD and my dad&amp;#x27;s autism adhd. I can barely function and the few years I worked a job I was tempted to drive my car into oncoming traffic every single day to and back from work &lt;br&gt;Col is just too high plus I can&amp;#x27;t get a good paying job&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864222&lt;br&gt;Have you read a certain painters description of a certain group of people being like jelly when you argue with them? It&amp;#x27;s impossible to discuss anything with these animals I have for parents. They forget everything the next day and gaslight you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864763&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864743&lt;br&gt;My dad already does and she fucking loves it.&lt;br&gt;Meanwhile I slightly raise my voice to make sure she can hear me and she goes berserk calling me an asshole who&amp;#x27;ll never get women cuz I have no job meanwhile my dad gambled 200k on stock margins in the 90s and lost his job for a decade and she still dutifully stuck with him. It&amp;#x27;s comical how everyday my dad cusses her out and yells at her calling her a dumb bitch at the top of his lungs and she&amp;#x27;ll dutifully have dinner ready for him in an hour while washing all his clothes for him yet she&amp;#x27;ll scold me for not cooking my own food even though I never asked her to cook for me&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864768&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863594&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;He keeps sending me job openings in other states/cities that require 10+ years of experience and he tells me &amp;quot;just walk up to them and ask them to train you, that&amp;#x27;s how we did it back in the old days&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;my dad used to do this&lt;br&gt;holy shit it pissed the fuck out of me&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864788&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864763&lt;br&gt;She loves getting beat?&lt;br&gt;Huh&lt;br&gt;Wonder if she’d love getting her pussy beat into smithereens. Tell your dad to try that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864795&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863604&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863594&lt;br&gt;Ironically the same people who make these demoralisation threads&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864888&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863856&lt;br&gt;Average zoomer blaming everyone but themselves&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865867&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864888&lt;br&gt;explain how he&amp;#x27;s wrong&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865875&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863594&lt;br&gt;She&amp;#x27;s not wrong that you need to contribute just because she&amp;#x27;s also bad with money.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>PLEASE MAKE IT FUCKING STOP — 8 replies — 32.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61865162</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61865162?lm=1771349592</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 17:33:12 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;PLEASE MAKE IT FUCKING STOP&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61865162'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 8 • Updated: 2026-02-17 17:33 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;PLEASE MAKE IT FUCKING STOP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865166&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ACCEPT THE DEAL YOU BALD HEADED PRICK&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865174&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;sell now nigga its just going lower&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865177&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You should have apologized to dan pena now you lose everything&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865188&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865162&lt;br&gt;you&amp;#x27;re profiting in BTC anon, just buy more!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865247&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865162&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;buy the dip&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;bro there is literally no more flesh on my skeleton&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865750&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865162&lt;br&gt;oh wow, it&amp;#x27;s you! how does it feel to be one of the greater fools?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865798&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865162&lt;br&gt;NO CRYING IN THE CASINO&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866159&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Do you guys not buy low and sell high then rebuy lower again then resell higher again? I&amp;#x27;ve turned 83k ONDO in to 116k ONDO and 280 SOL to 312 SOL doing this. It&amp;#x27;s not hard anons, stop fixating on one single position.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pic related. I don&amp;#x27;t trade the BTC, but the ONDO and SOL I have steadily been increasing in size without adding any new money, just trading.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>I made 30k in a Day — 6 replies — 24.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61865072</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61865072?lm=1771349121</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 17:25:21 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;I made 30k in a Day&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61865072'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 6 • Updated: 2026-02-17 17:25 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;it was enough&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;find out about RAM bubble&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;have dozens of servers for homelab&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;make meme eBay listing&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;sell 6TB of RAM for $30k after taxes and fees&lt;br&gt;Same sticks sold for double at the time&lt;br&gt;Same sticks now 70% less per stick&lt;br&gt;I saw the bubble and did a flip off the top into profit&lt;br&gt;Once the payment cleared I quit my jerb&lt;br&gt;Been making more per day not working&lt;br&gt;2026 is van life friendly&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865094&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Should i sell my 4060 rtx?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865134&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865094&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Should i sell my 4060 rtx?&lt;br&gt;NvidiAI is bleeding money on AI and going to restart consumer GPU production soon&lt;br&gt;so, yes&lt;br&gt;I am currently in the process of selling ALL my Nvidia GPU&amp;#x27;s&lt;br&gt;From professional cards to 40 series&lt;br&gt;already bought AMD replacements&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865873&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865072&lt;br&gt;But RAM prices are still at ATH?....&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865929&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865873&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;But RAM prices are still at ATH?....&lt;br&gt;This, i&amp;#x27;m work at a VAR. A customer of mine wanted to add 128GB DDR5 RDIMMs to server, our quote was $10k. Dell&amp;#x27;s retail site lists it for like $13k&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865979&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865072&lt;br&gt;This meme again. These broads are like 40 by now&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866110&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865979&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;emma roberts is 35&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>BREAKING NEWS: $70 PRICE TARGET FOR XRP. — 13 replies — 17.2/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861161</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861161?lm=1771347131</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 16:52:11 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;BREAKING NEWS: $70 PRICE TARGET FOR XRP.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861161'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 13 • Updated: 2026-02-17 16:52 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are repeating the 2017 bullrun with a longer timeframe. The wave 2 has completed and wave 3 will take us to $13 within the next 3 months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861168&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861161&lt;br&gt;got a long way to go&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861395&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;13$?&lt;br&gt;I sell all my xrp&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861475&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861161&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;$13&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;d be a millionaire.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861504&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;5 trillion mcap&lt;br&gt;random bullshit does not go up forever lmao&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861511&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861161&lt;br&gt;Thanks. Shorting this harder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864005&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861504&lt;br&gt;Price x supply can never be this high number !&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864008&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864005&lt;br&gt;The supply is constantly growing and it&amp;#x27;s not gonna go up to 10 trillion mcap because retards like you are invested in it and tards are never right.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864012&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861161&lt;br&gt;BOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOM&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865668&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861395&lt;br&gt;I am out at $4.90&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865741&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861161&lt;br&gt;$13 is FUD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865781&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861504&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;gold and silver still undervalued at multiple trillions of fake fiat &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;but arbitragebotchain couldn&amp;#x27;t possibly be worth a few tril&lt;br&gt;Normie moment&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865845&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865668&lt;br&gt;I am out at $3.60&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865934&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SO BULLISH XRP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Is it really that much more difficult to start a business in the eu than us? — 25 replies — 16.6/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860796</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860796?lm=1771344450</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 16:07:30 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Is it really that much more difficult to start a business in the eu than us?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860796'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 25 • Updated: 2026-02-17 16:07 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;You guys in the EU make less than us on paychecks, but you get to keep more of your money because you have universal healthcare and PTO while we have to pay for private insurance which chronically denies people&amp;#x27;s health situations. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Are people saying that starting a business in the EU is difficult because of the regulations? What regulations does the European union impose on its citizen&amp;#x27;s than they think it&amp;#x27;s easier to start in the United States instead?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860815&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;Depends enormously on which country are we talking about. Some are easy (Germany) some are very hard (Italy)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860817&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; you get to keep more of your money because you have universal healthcare&lt;br&gt;yeah right&lt;br&gt;good luck getting that &amp;quot;universal healthcare&amp;quot; if you&amp;#x27;re not a boomer, waiting lists are years for even a basic exam/procedure. It&amp;#x27;s either you go private (and pay out of your own pocket) or you die&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; and PTO&lt;br&gt;oh wow, 20 wagie cagie free days a year. Totally worth the 60%+ taxes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;All taxation is theft. It&amp;#x27;s just that. Taxation doesn&amp;#x27;t pay for services. It&amp;#x27;s just the way they control the economy, and here in EU they fucking LOVE to control what you can and cannot do. They print the money, they don&amp;#x27;t need to tax you. They tax you to control you (and to humiliate you)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860822&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;The healthcare thing is too much american leftie argument, it also has been very overcrowded by you guessed arabs and africans, unironically I was better treated when I broke my leg in brazil of all places then in france&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860823&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860815&lt;br&gt;How about the Czech Republic?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860836&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860817&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;waiting lists are years for even a basic exam/procedure&lt;br&gt;we have them too except they&amp;#x27;re called &amp;quot;pre authorization&amp;quot; and we still get to pay for it all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860837&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;What regulations does the European union impose on its citizen&amp;#x27;s than they think it&amp;#x27;s easier to start in the United States instead?&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;re shitting me right? As the other guy said it really varies based on the country, but in places like Italy you need 20 authorizations and 10 certifications (that you pay for) to open something like a bar or a carpentry shop, plus constant &amp;quot;controls&amp;quot; which are basically bribe requests at this point by officials of all kinds. Oh, and good luck filing your taxes. Here&amp;#x27;s how it goes&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; be business owner&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; tax filing time (yay)&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; tax system is so incredibly fucking complex you have to hire people just to calculate how much you own&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; because of course YOU need to tell the state how much the state wants from YOU&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; slightest fuck up? You&amp;#x27;re on the hook for 240% of the original amount&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; they have 5-7 years to come after you&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; &amp;quot;oh hello here&amp;#x27;s a tax bill from 5 years ago cause you filed 3.51 euros less than you were supposed to, plus 1500 eur sanction, plus interest&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; oh btw you pay FIRST, and MAYBE when (after an average of 12 years in court at your expense) you are declared right, you get it back, no interest accrued, your legal expenses still on your back&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; so most people just pay&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; it&amp;#x27;s mafia with a hand of paint on top and the full force of the state behind it&lt;br&gt;EU is completely fucked. Stay away. We can just pray it somehow implodes from within. These bureaucrat jew lover good goyim will kill us all and replace us with shitskin and pajeets and they will feast on top of it all while the continent dies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860842&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860837&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;tax system is so incredibly fucking complex you have to hire people just to calculate how much you own&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; because of course YOU need to tell the state how much the state wants from YOU&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; slightest fuck up? You&amp;#x27;re on the hook for 240% of the original amount&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; they have 5-7 years to come after you&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; &amp;quot;oh hello here&amp;#x27;s a tax bill from 5 years ago cause you filed 3.51 euros less than you were supposed to, plus 1500 eur sanction, plus interest&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; oh btw you pay FIRST, and MAYBE when (after an average of 12 years in court at your expense) you are declared right, you get it back, no interest accrued, your legal expenses still on your back&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; so most people just pay&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; it&amp;#x27;s mafia with a hand of paint on top and the full force of the state behind it&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;EU is completely fucked. Stay away.&lt;br&gt;again this is more or less the same as the US&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860847&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860823&lt;br&gt;A bureaucracy nightmare.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860850&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860842&lt;br&gt;everywhere is completely fucked, but you burgers have weapons and a strong constitution that backs you&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;yeah you&amp;#x27;re retarded pussies and you will never ever use them, we all know. I mean they&amp;#x27;re telling you know that you&amp;#x27;re ruled upon by a bunch of satanist jew pedophiles and there&amp;#x27;s no shooting in the streets, so there you have it. But at least you have the guns. If the Cheka comes knocking at your door demanding your harvest and your daughters, you can shoot back at the fuckers. Here in EU we&amp;#x27;re basically at the mercy of a state that hates us and wants us dead, and we have only our dicks to hold in our hands to defend ourselves from it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860860&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;As far as I keep reading on economic subreddits, negligible, the US just has far more available credit and tax companies a bit less at start allowing them to grow, otherwise its basically the same, sounds legit just a complacency issue from europeans, most of the time they get more unemployment benefits than they would working and have legit no time limit for them so they just don&amp;#x27;t bother lol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860967&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;in my country, the one thing one has to look out for is paying for your own social/healthinsurance, ie, if you have your own business, you need to pay taxes for your own health/socialinsurance, and the taxman wont ask you for the first 3y of that business.&lt;br&gt;After the 3y pass, you will then have to payup all the retrospective social insurance tax costs incurred, which fucks over a lot of retard or unfortunate first business owners&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861032&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860837&lt;br&gt;This is why we need a unified EU business regulation and undermind the corrupt sovereignist that want to keep individual burocratic fuckery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861057&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860815&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Some are easy (Germany)&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; some are very hard (Italy)&lt;br&gt;let me guess italian never tried germany?&lt;br&gt;Germany is known to be a bureucracy hellhole with people fleeing to other countries from it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861032&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;unified will fix it&lt;br&gt;France&amp;amp;germany have been dictating eu lawmaking. You will eat shit as you already do. You have eu wide higher taxes because germany didnt want to compete and made mandatory higher minimum vat a thing.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Not to mention that countries that joined got their industries destroyed by unified regulation and had to import from germany/france what they used to produce themself&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861071&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s the one thing the USA gets right. I personally made a &amp;quot;business&amp;quot; (that never made any profit) in the span of an afternoon. Cost maybe $200 to get my identification numbers for the llc&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861091&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861032&lt;br&gt;yeah let&amp;#x27;s give the EU bureaucrats more power that will fix it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861111&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Is it really that much more difficult to start a business in the eu than us?&lt;br&gt;Depends on the business. If you want to do something shady the US is the place to go. The US has barely any standards and barely any regulations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861113&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860817&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;waiting lists are years for even a basic exam/procedure&lt;br&gt;What are you talking about? I live currently in the EU and have never had to wait for medical care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861119&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Us is easier.&lt;br&gt;I have created 2 corpos and 1 llc for different purposes within the past 8 years. You can do it all online for a few bucks, other regulations depend on specific industry but overall it&amp;#x27;s pretty easy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861128&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860860&lt;br&gt;higher taxation alone puts euros at a disadvantage. Its fine if you do a local job since you compete with locals but anything online / shipped its bad since they have to be more efficient than rest of world to reach same profit margin.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As for amount of bureaucracy its fucking complex and depends on what country and what profession. There is even stupid shit like if you run a repair shop and repair inside your building it counts different than if you decide to drive to your customer and repair locally. In the later case they classify you as a handyman worker and will fine you if you didn&amp;#x27;t register with the craftsman ministry. Also if you do something you didn&amp;#x27;t register for you will also be fined but you can register as &amp;quot; i will do anything&amp;quot; more broadly and dodge it. The amount of bullshit can easily fill a book.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861429&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;Depends on what your goals are, the type of business, your personal goals and the markets you wish to enter. In general it&amp;#x27;s more of an investment in the long run but if you plan to offer your services or products in the EU anyway it makes sense to start your business here and already be compliant&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861441&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860817&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;waiting lists are years for even a basic exam/procedure.&lt;br&gt;Yeah, I remember waiting decades for my appendicitis, it rupturing and me dying because of it. Thankfully they could keep me alive for months despite the extreme difficulties this poses. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861032&lt;br&gt;We need more unified European regulation. Sadly the EU is not an economic alliance anymore.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862545&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860860&lt;br&gt;I love how hard it is to even talk about european economy on reddit, not because of europeans, but because of american lefties, if you so much, and most times you don&amp;#x27;t even need to, mention the US, they will flock like a horde to claim the US lies about everything, that 30% of americans are unemployed and nearly no one in europe, the EU is literal worker&amp;#x27;s paradise and how much they love their welfare policies and hate the US greed, its quite hilarious really how much they want a nanny state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865504&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is, soon it will was once EU Inc comes into play&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865623&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;you have universal healthcare&lt;br&gt;yea but you have to wait 1 year+ because there is a million niggers in queue before you&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865645&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861057&lt;br&gt;Lol this is true.&lt;br&gt;Germany and France made the EU suck with their shit like GDPR etc. Spain happily sniffs every turd. The rest aren&amp;#x27;t better.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Someone out there owns more BTC than Saylor or Satoshi, and we don't know who they are. — 4 replies — 15.5/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61866005</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61866005?lm=1771348931</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 17:22:11 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Someone out there owns more BTC than Saylor or Satoshi, and we don&amp;#x27;t know who they are.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61866005'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 4 • Updated: 2026-02-17 17:22 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Someone out there owns more BTC than Saylor or Satoshi, and we don&amp;#x27;t know who they are.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866021&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866005&lt;br&gt;Yes we do, it&amp;#x27;s literally a google search away. Largest wallet is Binance.&lt;br&gt;https://bitinfocharts.com/top-100-richest-bitcoin-addresses.html&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866032&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866021&lt;br&gt;There&amp;#x27;s no way of knowing if someone split their holdings into many different addresses my friend&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866049&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866032&lt;br&gt;Occam&amp;#x27;s razor my good sir *tips fedora*&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866094&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866021&lt;br&gt;Damn, CZ could literally nuke BTC to $0 if he wanted.&lt;br&gt;Self-custody is the only way to save this market, but I guess most people are too dumb for that. It&amp;#x27;s over.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>$TSLA @$405 — 3 replies — 12.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61866167</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61866167?lm=1771349786</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 17:36:26 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;$TSLA @$405&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61866167'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 3 • Updated: 2026-02-17 17:36 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;What is the fair value for this stock?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866173&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866167&lt;br&gt;$405&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866174&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;$3.50&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866182&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866173&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866174&lt;br&gt;ok, ty. Imma take the average of the two. Wisdom of the crowd&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;No additional replies in the latest window.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>&gt;Bought BTC ATH &gt;Bought the gold ATH &gt;Bought the silver ATH Just want to let you know guys that i'm going to start inves… — 6 replies — 8.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61865488</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61865488?lm=1771347159</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 16:52:39 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;&amp;gt;Bought BTC ATH &amp;gt;Bought the gold ATH &amp;gt;Bought the silver ATH Just want to let you know guys that i&amp;#x27;m going to start inves…&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61865488'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 6 • Updated: 2026-02-17 16:52 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;Bought BTC ATH&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Bought the gold ATH&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Bought the silver ATH&lt;br&gt;Just want to let you know guys that i&amp;#x27;m going to start investing in AI related stocks. Wish me luck because this is my last chance&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865510&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;kek&lt;br&gt;I wouldn&amp;#x27;t do that if I were you&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865519&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865488&lt;br&gt;Finally the stock market perma pump is over, get ready for lost decade while crypto pumps&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865561&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI stocks already rugged&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865569&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865519&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;while crypto pumps&lt;br&gt;lol no&lt;br&gt;crypto is fucking over and btc will be around 30k in a few months&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865617&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865488&lt;br&gt;I heard Microjeet is cheap, try that&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865937&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;thank you anon, I could really use some RAM right now&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Day 1641 of snailposting every day until BTC is at 1M — 5 replies — 4.4/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61863800</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61863800?lm=1771345728</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 16:28:48 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Day 1641 of snailposting every day until BTC is at 1M&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61863800'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 5 • Updated: 2026-02-17 16:28 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Day 1641 of snailposting every day until BTC is at 1M&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863809&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863800&lt;br&gt;To think that you were once a hero, the one who had done the impossible. How far you have fallen snailbro...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863911&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;NPC listed across solid exchanges&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;easy access for new money&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;that kind of infrastructure matters long term&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;doors are open&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864373&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863800&lt;br&gt;cute&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864409&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863809&lt;br&gt;Sad, many such cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865819&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863809&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864409&lt;br&gt;You know, snailposting could have petered out if not for the energy you add to it daily.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864373&lt;br&gt;Thank you friend&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Day 1640 of snailposting every day until BTC is at 1M — 7 replies — 4.1/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61859537</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61859537?lm=1771343773</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:56:13 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Day 1640 of snailposting every day until BTC is at 1M&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61859537'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 7 • Updated: 2026-02-17 15:56 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Day 1640 of snailposting every day until BTC is at 1M&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859779&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859537&lt;br&gt;These snail threads are just pathetic spam now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859893&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859779&lt;br&gt;now? It&amp;#x27;s been spam since 2022&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860133&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859537&lt;br&gt;cute&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861900&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859537&lt;br&gt;cute&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862239&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859537&lt;br&gt;snail fag should of just stopped when it hit 100k.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862283&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859537&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865566&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859537&lt;br&gt;everything was better when the goal was 100k. I didn&amp;#x27;t have to squeeze my NPC every fucking day, the new dogs were profitable, and even the frogs stayed alive longer&lt;br&gt;tf happened?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>/smg/ - Stock Market Gambling — 380 replies — 157.9/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861684</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861684?lm=1771341198</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:13:18 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;/smg/ - Stock Market Gambling&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61861684'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 380 • Updated: 2026-02-17 15:13 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Casino Economy Edition&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Some helpful links to numb the pain&lt;br&gt;https://findahelpline.com/&lt;br&gt;https://www.nvidia.com/refunds/&lt;br&gt;https://www.whitehouse.gov/refunds&lt;br&gt;https://jlingz.com/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Educational sites:&lt;br&gt;https://www.investopedia.com&lt;br&gt;https://www.khanacademy.org/economics-finance-domain&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Financial TV Streams:&lt;br&gt;https://www.newslive.com/american/cnbc.html&lt;br&gt;https://www.livestreamy.net/bloomberg/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Charts:&lt;br&gt;https://www.tradingview.com&lt;br&gt;https://www.finscreener.com&lt;br&gt;https://www.portfoliovisualizer.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Screeners: so you feel like in the movies&lt;br&gt;https://finviz.com/&lt;br&gt;https://etfdb.com/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Gambling:&lt;br&gt;https://www.optionsplaybook.com/options-introduction/&lt;br&gt;https://www.optionsprofitcalculator.com&lt;br&gt;https://optionstrat.com/&lt;br&gt;https://www.optionistics.com/quotes/option-prices&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Pre-Market and Live data:&lt;br&gt;https://www.investing.com/indices/indices-futures&lt;br&gt;https://finance.yahoo.com/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Calendars&lt;br&gt;https://www.marketwatch.com/economy-politics/calendar&lt;br&gt;https://www.earningswhispers.com/calendar&lt;br&gt;https://www.cmegroup.com/trading/interest-rates/countdown-to-fomc.html&lt;br&gt;https://www.mortgagenewsdaily.com/data/building-permits&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Boomer Investing 101: so zoomers with meme stocks can outperform you&lt;br&gt;https://www.bogleheads.org/wiki/Getting_started&lt;br&gt;https://www.sec.gov/search-filings&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Misc smg:&lt;br&gt;https://www.financialjuice.com/home&lt;br&gt;https://finance.yahoo.com/trending-tickers&lt;br&gt;https://market24hclock.com/&lt;br&gt;https://www.dividendchannel.com/drip-returns-calculator&lt;br&gt;https://brokerchooser.com/&lt;br&gt;https://www.chathamfinancial.com/technology/us-market-rates&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Previously on /smg/: &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858740&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861716&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m an American, I have extreme anxiety that i can&amp;#x27;t sell or buy right now&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;so me, and my fellow americans formally decided were panic selling everything Tuesday&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;sorry euros&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861738&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861716&lt;br&gt;i just watch the spot silver chart and get either mad or relieved when it doesnt move very far from 75&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864779&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This europoor just bought 70k USD worth of a global index fund and an ex-USA fund. Feel sick desu but I can’t sit on this cash forever&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864791&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864756&lt;br&gt;I dunno... what portion of nearly 50% of John Q Investor&amp;#x27;s assets are going to go into gold after he capitulates between now and August?&lt;br&gt;What is it they were saying 6 months ago? 60/20/20?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864794&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864791&lt;br&gt;forgot pic&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864805&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864588&lt;br&gt;enjoy your anal lysis&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864818&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;it&amp;#x27;s over.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864862&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;anyone know how to get fidelity to display my port value in premarket it doesn&amp;#x27;t update until market open and i need to aaaaaaaaaaahhhhhh more accurately right now&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864869&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864862&lt;br&gt;Have you tried to do math, you nigger gorilla?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864875&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864869&lt;br&gt;shiet wypipo be making computers hard to learn and shit to keep the black man down&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864876&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861707&lt;br&gt;ETOR&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864877&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864750&lt;br&gt;LEMEOW&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864887&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862034&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862207&lt;br&gt;DOSH&lt;br&gt;LOADS O MONE&lt;br&gt;SMG BTFO AGAIN&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864895&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864887&lt;br&gt;ok but how does that affect you personally?&lt;br&gt;post your profits big boy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864940&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864877&lt;br&gt;That&amp;#x27;s your 47% tariff doing it&amp;#x27;s job&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864953&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864895&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;GME baggie coping&lt;br&gt;go back to your containment thread&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864962&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ready for the bloodbath?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864974&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;soxl down 10%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864975&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;everyone&amp;#x27;s expecting it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864982&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The nurse at the psychs office called after out appointment today saying she was worried about me and asked if I wanted to get institutionalized.&lt;br&gt;While on one hand it feels good that someone cares about me, fuck no give me pills to survive [society] or stfu.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;what are the market implicaitons of this?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864986&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864777&lt;br&gt;I hope you guys bought hopium when I said. up another 20%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865002&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864982&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;asked if I wanted to get institutionalized&lt;br&gt;newby here. is this common in finance?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865011&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864411&lt;br&gt;hi bob&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865015&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865002&lt;br&gt;if you aren&amp;#x27;t getting wellness checks from the county health system or your female broker you probably aren&amp;#x27;t taking enough risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865028&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALL HANDS ON DECK&lt;br&gt;GET READY TO DEPLOY THOSE V&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865049&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865002&lt;br&gt;Yes. Saying &amp;quot;getting balls deep in leverage to see green or red numbers is the only thing that makes me feel anything&amp;quot; was the wrong answer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865127&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Well my mining portfolio has just been raped&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865178&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;jesus christ&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865184&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;bought google at 300 &lt;br&gt;how bad of an idea was that?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865241&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864986&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864777&lt;br&gt;Hopium currently up 324%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865274&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is today the day to slurp google&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865308&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865274&lt;br&gt;For me it&amp;#x27;s XOM&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>When did you realize that you were NOT going to make it? — 60 replies — 73.4/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61862922</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61862922?lm=1771346917</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 16:48:37 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;When did you realize that you were NOT going to make it?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61862922'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 60 • Updated: 2026-02-17 16:48 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862935&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;is he ok&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862944&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862935&lt;br&gt;just some minor scratches (on his brain)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862956&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;the funniest part is that you think &amp;quot;maybe he survived the crash, just barely&amp;quot; but then it erupts in flames and he&amp;#x27;s cooked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864540&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864461&lt;br&gt;How are you supposed to pass on two way highways?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864595&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863976&lt;br&gt;This, America just couldn&amp;#x27;t afford mass surveillance before. Soon, total Amerimutt death will flood teh interwebz&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864624&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864540&lt;br&gt;This is how it should be done safely. There’s a median barrier, a shoulder, an acceleration lane at entries, and a deceleration lane at exits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864646&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864595&lt;br&gt;America had plenty of money for this sorta shit, it was just rejected by Joe Citizen as unnecessary Big Brother. They even put up cameras at all the traffic points in my shithole Missouri town to issue tickets, until people got fed up. Now they just sit there deactivated.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Of course now that MIGA is running the country for Big Corp, everyone is embracing Big Brother to &amp;quot;own teh libz&amp;quot; and trannies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864685&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;Watching link refuse to pump over the last 2 years made me certain, but I had an inkling in late 2021.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864687&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864699&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863924&lt;br&gt;Reap or not you have to understand 2 things:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;the pedo elite (redundant, there are no non-pedo elite) believe in this shit HARD. If you know your enemies motivations, you can outmaneuver them&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;we currently inhabit this material plane, largely outside the strong harmonic influences of what we would call gods. Just don&amp;#x27;t be such a conniving piece of shit when you can help it&lt;br&gt;Don&amp;#x27;t over think it, anon.&lt;br&gt;Yes, I know I misused greentext; leave it alone, well poisoners&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864709&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Driving in hard shoulder&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Driving way too fast&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Slamming on the brakes causing you to front flip&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Not trying to switch lane&lt;br&gt;Darwin award.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864714&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863183&lt;br&gt;you&amp;#x27;re not supposed to drive there&lt;br&gt;play stupid games, win stupid prices&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864734&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863411&lt;br&gt;When I got my permit in the EU the first evasion maneuver you learn is the quick jerking of the handle to swerve and avoid this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864738&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863681&lt;br&gt;Should we just back china then?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is this the only way to topple the status quo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864767&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;Why do you care what other people are thinking? Does it hurt your feelings when Jesus leaves you on read? You still don&amp;#x27;t have to be atheist.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864769&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864709&lt;br&gt;not starting with &amp;gt;riding a motorcycle&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864775&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;I BOUGHT SHINY ROCK @ $120 &lt;br&gt;BIZ TOLD ME IT WAS GOING TO $5000 EOY&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864842&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864092&lt;br&gt;No it&amp;#x27;s not dumbass. Nearly all roads in Asia are like this and they all have motorbikes that drive on it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864852&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864842&lt;br&gt;Well then it&amp;#x27;s a retarded design if you have to give way to vehicles turning every 2 seconds - and it has no markings to indicate as such.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864870&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;That finishing final destination touch&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865341&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864842&lt;br&gt;Just because people abuse the emergency lane it illegal doesn&amp;#x27;t mean that&amp;#x27;s what it is designed for.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865399&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862935&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;he&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865412&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864842&lt;br&gt;they have roads where motorcycles try to front brake doing 70mph? lol, this chink deserved what he got, like it or not.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865437&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s not tragic to die doing what you love&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865490&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;When the NSA broke fisa and used Pegasus on me whilst on vacation and upon arriving home and getting a new phone being threatened in person after dodging a SWAT attempt through someone using back doors on my hardwired internet connection. Just the tip of the icerberg but I would strongly advise leaving the united states, it’s only gonna get worse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865508&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;cutting across 2 lanes just to go 5 mph in a turn&lt;br&gt;motorcyclist shouldn&amp;#x27;t have been there but white car is a fucking retard&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865611&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865490&lt;br&gt;There&amp;#x27;s nowhere to go. We have to take a stand where we are.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865639&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;When did you realize that you were NOT going to make it?&lt;br&gt;I looked at the conditions of the people who had made it to the wealthiest tiers of society. They all had generational wealth behind them, and they all operated on insane levels of exploitation to generate that wealth. Realized that &amp;quot;making it&amp;quot; means screwing over so many people that you alienate yourself from most people, except the likes of musk, epstein, trump, etc.&lt;br&gt;I realized that though the club was small and that I wasn&amp;#x27;t in it, that the people in the club were not the kind of person I wanted to be. I&amp;#x27;d rather disband the club.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865646&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865611&lt;br&gt;Nope, I’m out - fuck this third world country in disguise. The problem is thresholds were crossed and stupid people who shouldn’t have power drag you into shit that doesn’t even matter. This whole entire country is rotten, the corrupt local cop is just an extended phenotype of the so called “elite”. Shut off the news, delete all media and just get up and fucking go. Don’t lift a finger for this surveillance prison social credit score algorithm hellscape.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865657&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863529&lt;br&gt;Beautifully put.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865848&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865437&lt;br&gt;Ok Alesteir&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865901&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863924&lt;br&gt;Yes those entities actually exist. In history, people were religious because they were uneducated and most couldn&amp;#x27;t read. now people can read and are educated, but they aren&amp;#x27;t religious, but they also told that spiritual or religious hoo-hah is bull, the only thing that exists is what you see in front of you with your basic senses blah blah. When in fact, people should be using their educated brain to dig deeper. but it&amp;#x27;s all by design by the elites to continue obscuring the truths. they did it hundreds of years ago, and they continue to do it today just in a different way. READ THINGS. start with the bible. answers for a lot of things are in there. you don&amp;#x27;t need to be religious to read the bible and think critically.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;then move upwards throughout history and you&amp;#x27;ll notice the pattern. these people are extremely, extremely religious/spiritual themselves. They are Yahwists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865913&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864842&lt;br&gt;Because the chinks are all retarded insects, its not supposed to be driven on&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>