<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>/biz/ Active (filtered, with replies)</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/</link><description>Filtered out: general, gme, bbbyq. OP + first 3 replies + last 30 replies.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 11:19:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Fake and Gay Economy — 84 replies — 333.8/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61871520</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61871520?lm=1771758280</guid><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 11:04:40 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Fake and Gay Economy&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61871520'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 84 • Updated: 2026-02-22 11:04 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;When will this gay as economy finally collapse and how can i profit from it?&lt;br&gt;Its ridiculous the woman at our workplace contribute nothing to the company and make more money than i do&lt;br&gt;Its infuriating we just had a bunch of lay offs and we lost some of oir best workers but somehow a bunch of HR shits who do nothing all day still work here&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871530&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HR is a necessary function, chud&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871569&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871530&lt;br&gt;For what?&lt;br&gt;Genuinely why do we need it to this extent?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61871755&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871569&lt;br&gt;Protect the corp from lawsuits&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882397&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873944&lt;br&gt;Really? Hm ok&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878449&lt;br&gt;I dont quite get how you see this? You say not cheating is loser tier?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882408&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;know a fat art hoe with an Art History degree&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;before she began selling pics of her huge tits online and streaming herself playing videogames, she was working remotely in Operations (HR) at an office&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I got a liberal arts degree in pre-law, aiming to be a lawyer&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;constantly see dopey bitches get accepted to their law schools of choice, I was not and no one would hire me to paralegal or legal assistant roles either despite demonstrating superior knowledge of the law, only roasties&lt;br&gt;I wouldn&amp;#x27;t mind the fake and gay, if it wasn&amp;#x27;t explicitly directed towards fucking over as many men as possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882442&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873611&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;fake&lt;br&gt;rooted in make-believe&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;gay&lt;br&gt;You are a faggot if you believe it, or even want to believe it&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For example, space is fake and gay. It&amp;#x27;s fake because it&amp;#x27;s built around unfalsifiable, circular reasoning &amp;quot;science&amp;quot; with no anchor to the real world. It&amp;#x27;s gay because you are a spiritual homosexual if you think Star Trek is something to aspire to. Thus, space is fake and gay.&lt;br&gt;Nukes are fake and gay because the bombs do not exist and cannot exist (fake), and gay because thinking you live in a world where you are scared a jew can push a button and wipe out a city is inherently pathetic and homosexual. &lt;br&gt;The modern workplace is fake and gay, because the work isn&amp;#x27;t actual work it&amp;#x27;s role-play daycare for adults. And it&amp;#x27;s gay because it&amp;#x27;s a system that empowers women above all, turning all males into low T cucks instead of productive men who build real shit with their hands and have real accomplishments. They make you pretend to work then pay you with fake money conjured out of thin air by jews running the banks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882487&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871569&lt;br&gt;because the line need to go UP even if you burn half of the World for it, that&amp;#x27;s modern capitalism&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882495&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871931&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882506&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873181&lt;br&gt;underrated&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882519&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871937&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;HR is a reflection of fake and gay legal system.&lt;br&gt;I run my own business and thats why i&amp;#x27;d never want to hire anyone.&lt;br&gt;I can&amp;#x27;t wait until AI and robots become advanced enough that i can just have robots as my employees that help me with my tasks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882601&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882495&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t get it. It doesn&amp;#x27;t make me mad but I don&amp;#x27;t understand what are they saying and why. It&amp;#x27;s just some retards flailing.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In fact this type of dance could be performed by Chris Chan and it would not look out of place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882608&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882495&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882869&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871530&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871569&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871755&lt;br&gt;Our HR manager is the local cum dumpster. Even I&amp;#x27;ve dumped my nerdy incel load in her pussy a few times.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883066&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879023&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;If they didn&amp;#x27;t provide value they wouldn&amp;#x27;t be there.&lt;br&gt;75% or more of white collar work literally does nothing, roasties or not.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883243&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;Did they fire itty bitty titties &amp;amp; a bob?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883399&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;When there is an alternative for the money and people to pour over into.&lt;br&gt;Fagmerica&amp;#x27;s slow decline relies on everywhere else being shittier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883616&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;HR while i&amp;#x27;m anxious, waiting for them to communicate their decision about hiring me, being unemployed and thinking about suicide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883644&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882495&lt;br&gt;you know, society almost always makes you think you desire gen z boss and a mini, but fuck that, i&amp;#x27;m gonna say it, loud and proud: i&amp;#x27;m more akin to have a relationship with secret product and a trench, i dont know if its about my selfsteem, i would like to be enough for gen z boss and a mini. Maybe what i need is 5&amp;#x27;3 and an attitude.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883760&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883243&lt;br&gt;They got promoted to Chief Diversity, Equity &amp;amp; Inclusion Officer&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883781&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883644&lt;br&gt;You meant to say inclined. You are more inclined. Akin means &amp;quot;similar to&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883784&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882869&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;incel&lt;br&gt;Im so confused as to what that term means, involuntarily celibate? But its not being celibate if your literally having sex. Such a weird term clearly carrying different meaning. What is the point of using a term that literally has no definition to its meaning, you might aswell speak in baby noises at this point.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884146&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;guys, ALL we have to do is called women like this ugly chopped shit to their face as much as possible and they will lose all motivation to live&lt;br&gt;they are SO fragile in that regard.&lt;br&gt;next time you are walking down the street and see some bitch like this just start yelling “YOURE UGLY”&lt;br&gt;they will spend the next week and a half minimum making reddit posts about it and getting their SSRI prescription upped.&lt;br&gt;don’t ever engage with any ideas or thoughts they have. just pick apart their appearance. you look like a fridge and a stick insect at the same time. your fake dyed hair sucks. you have clown makeup on, you must have learned how to do makeup at the circus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884272&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883066&lt;br&gt;So you&amp;#x27;re saying ceo&amp;#x27;s willingly burn 75% of their money for fun?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884291&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884272&lt;br&gt;he&amp;#x27;s saying the ceo is a fucking retard&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884297&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871520&lt;br&gt;I want to shove my cock deep into the first one from behind. Just lift the skirt and blast the pussy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884717&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883784&lt;br&gt;Yes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884737&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61871569&lt;br&gt;Without HR you could complete the work, banter and build a genuine camaraderie with your common co-worker, but we cant have unions, and its better if you&amp;#x27;re all divided and conquered, here&amp;#x27;s a harpy to make your life hell&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884742&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873193&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872087&lt;br&gt;These niggers actually get it. All problems flow downstream from jews controlling the issuance of your (since 1913) fake and gay fiat debt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885902&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873611&lt;br&gt;You must be over 18 to use this site&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886326&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882442&lt;br&gt;Yeah this kind of mega über schizos who believe in fe and no nuke use this phrase holy shit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886329&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882442&lt;br&gt;And yes the idea of space is falsifiable you absolute schizo. Satellites wouldn&amp;#x27;t even work without it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886359&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883784&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Such a weird term clearly carrying different meaning. What is the point of using a term that literally has no definition to its meaning&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s just people overusing words or ideas to oblivion, where they lose all context. It&amp;#x27;s like the worst insult was being called gay way back, then it was subverted (actually gay is cool), then it became retarded, then it got subverted (actually retarded is cool because you&amp;#x27;re not trying), then it become autistic, then it became subverted (actually it&amp;#x27;s interesting to be autistic), now it&amp;#x27;s random baby talk by gen alpha (mog, cortisol spike, chopped, unc, lil bro, frame, aura farming, 67, incel, cuk). Now it&amp;#x27;s being subverted by people overusing the terms even if they don&amp;#x27;t apply to anyone or anything in the context at all. Someone not having sex for a week = incel. Someone having a slightly embarrassing moment (cortisol spike), someone better looking walking past (mogged), doing something that&amp;#x27;s barely good (aura farming), having a strong presence even if it&amp;#x27;s completely autistic and retarded (frame). Or like when old people started wearing skateboard shirts having no clue what it was, or everyone and their dog wearing an off white shirt. People make shit gay eventually, it&amp;#x27;s a universal law.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886363&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;work office job (engineer) with way too many women and diversity hire niggers and Indians who do nothing all day&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;get new (white) South African Vice President&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;calls us all together&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;in his funny accent tells us he’s an engineer and knows the business and there will be changes&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;tells us he will cut 20% of the workforce soon&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;everyone is shit scared and the normie femoids start climbing over each other trying to save their useless asses&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;office girlies start spreading rumours about everyone and everything in desperate attempt to make themselves look better&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;don’t give a fuck, I’m a technician and actually make money for the company unlike them&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Vice President just observes the shit show and never comments on anything while he feels out the office&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;come in one Monday&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;literally all blacks are gone&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;all except the actual useful Indians are gone&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;he culled every single female that we all knew had jewish make believe adult daycare jobs&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;only kept the old hag secretaries that actually do a great job&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kek, based white nigger. Turns out all it takes is some third world coloniser to clean this woke shit up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>TICK TOCK WAGIE — 14 replies — 15.6/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61884227</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61884227?lm=1771755953</guid><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 10:25:53 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;TICK TOCK WAGIE&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61884227'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 14 • Updated: 2026-02-22 10:25 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;MONDAY WILL BE HERE BEFORE YOU KNOW IT!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884234&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;bezos will laugh at me for 30 years until I retire and am too old to enjoy it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884271&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;ve not worked in two years now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884444&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884227&lt;br&gt;total wagie death. &lt;br&gt;retired at 28.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884609&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NOW THE PARTY DON&amp;#x27;T START TILL I WALK IN&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885590&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Don&amp;#x27;t forget to set you alarm and back up alarms tonight, wagie. cannot have you being late for the 06:00 standup&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885594&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884227&lt;br&gt;foh nigga you keep offering VTO&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885608&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885590&lt;br&gt;Winter storm, no one will be in the office, faggot!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885622&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884227&lt;br&gt;that&amp;#x27;s ok Jeff, i have become desensitized to waging&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885626&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885608&lt;br&gt;Acts of god will be docked from your pay&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885888&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884227&lt;br&gt;Joke&amp;#x27;s on you Archon, cause I got fired. Can&amp;#x27;t own my soul if I starve myself to death on purpose now can you? Who can take my Monday mornings from me when I can&amp;#x27;t even afford a calender? Jeff Bozos.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885921&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Monday is my day off though, Jeff.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886102&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884227&lt;br&gt;your 48-hour trial of living is nearly over, wagie. the weekly humiliation ritual about to kick off once again&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886324&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884227&lt;br&gt;Wagies, don&amp;#x27;t forget to pack your little plastic lunch container and bring a snack&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886327&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stay strong, wagies. That 2% annual raise is definitely coming this time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>the US is in recession — 63 replies — 14.3/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61869320</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61869320?lm=1771743344</guid><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 06:55:44 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;the US is in recession&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61869320'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 63 • Updated: 2026-02-22 06:55 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;the US is in recession&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869343&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869320&lt;br&gt;doomed fag nation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869350&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Adjust by population&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869389&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bump&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876391&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870855&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870872&lt;br&gt;Yeah we should be like Obama and just accept that jobs will never return. It takes time to improve things so don&amp;#x27;t ever try, silly goy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876412&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;the cope itt is crazy. it hurts to watch a once-great nation falling apart in denial.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876435&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China will take over as world superpower&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876558&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870808&lt;br&gt;this is like those 5&amp;#x27;11&amp;quot; vs 6&amp;#x27; memes &lt;br&gt;holy shit, they cannot be serious&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876562&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870808&lt;br&gt;How bad is it if this is the good news damn&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61876847&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869320&lt;br&gt;I have talked to retarded job hogs proud of being exploited. Seriously you can&amp;#x27;t ask for a raise and give me one of your jobs? Then you mock me for failing to get a job? You are hogging 2 jobs. If you didn&amp;#x27;t work 2 jobs there would be room for unemployed people to have jobs too. Boomer X fuckers still don&amp;#x27;t get it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877134&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870808&lt;br&gt;I hope you’re trolling&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877277&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869343&lt;br&gt;as long as wagies keep waging, it aint doomed nigga&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877309&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869320&lt;br&gt;People are working two or more jobs and you call this recession? Fucking hilarious&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877311&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61876310&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61876213&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;SING UP FOR&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;like places are just a great volunteer association and not a rigorous shittest from hr.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877894&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869507&lt;br&gt;There are 7 days a week anon. If you consider a 40 hour week a full time job, then an 80 hour week is two full time jobs. That&amp;#x27;s under 12 hours a day, every day. Plus commutes to the two jobs, you are out of home 13 to 14 hours. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61876213&lt;br&gt;99% larpers, 1% get caught after on-boarding period&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61876139&lt;br&gt;Other than fast food, I doubt people who work 80 hour weeks even have time to spend their money on bullshit. They probably just shower and collapse to bed at the end of the day. My bet is that they are paying a mortgage or have an incapacitated spouse or parent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61877899&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;if the US is in recession, why did Doordash just have it&amp;#x27;s biggest ever jump in orders?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878363&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869517&lt;br&gt;I cant imagine working more than 50 hours a week, tf is wrong with americans? Working 70 hours a week to buy an oilguzzler to commute to work? Living in the sterile suburbs? Tossing a coin everytime a negro passes you on the street? What is even the point of all that?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878371&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872563&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880061&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877899&lt;br&gt;People can&amp;#x27;t afford cars, and there&amp;#x27;s a decline in driver&amp;#x27;s license applications. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;And Increased senior population demand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880092&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878363&lt;br&gt;to enrich uncle sam at the small cost of every waking minute of your life&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880116&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878363&lt;br&gt;I work 100+ hours plus just to not get evicted by my corporate landlord. My rent is $4,000 a month. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boomers here opose affordable housing because it&amp;#x27;s gonna hurt their home values. But fuck me I guess.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880131&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878363&lt;br&gt;Forgot screenshot&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880323&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869320&lt;br&gt;What a perfect moment for the Democrats to rule against receiving free money from the rest of the world because we are all pinky friends and we all love each other&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880329&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870808&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Pro Trump post in a fag infested board&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anon...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880446&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880323&lt;br&gt;Explain?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882513&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880131&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;d just kill myself. I don&amp;#x27;t see you wagies as human.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883379&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869320&lt;br&gt;All this effort to pay off loans from jews.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883410&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878363&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I cant imagine working more than 0 hours a week&lt;br&gt;ftfy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883424&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61870808&lt;br&gt;A lot of business is booming better than this. There&amp;#x27;s been a 300% increase of day cares in Minnesota. Golden age baby&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883429&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883410&lt;br&gt;holy based&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883432&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869507&lt;br&gt;it&amp;#x27;s fake, just like all boomerfag retards bragging about having worked 2 jobs in their 20s to get ahead. they always leave out that it was 2 part time jobs or something that maybe equaled 50 hours a week total.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884208&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872300&lt;br&gt;how did you do the 2 hard days of the week, energy drinks?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884252&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869507&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;it&amp;#x27;s impossible to do two full time jobs and there&amp;#x27;s no way you can convince me otherwise.&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;re right. It&amp;#x27;s impossible. That&amp;#x27;s why I quit.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;wake up at 6am to show up at Job 1 at 7am.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;be off by 3:30pm, start driving to Job 2&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;5:00pm to 1:00am&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Drive home and go to bed immediately &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Sleep from 2:00am to 6:00am&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;repeat &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;technically never had a weekends off since Job 2 required me to work weekends, I would only get two nights off during the week&lt;br&gt;I did this for 7 months. Money wasn&amp;#x27;t worth it. Just settled on living below my means, but at least I was debt free after it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886021&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877894&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>BTC dumping? Don’t care. It’s temporary. — 77 replies — 10.8/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61869212</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61869212?lm=1771733546</guid><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 04:12:26 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;BTC dumping? Don’t care. It’s temporary.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61869212'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 77 • Updated: 2026-02-22 04:12 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;If it drops, I buy more. If it goes sideways, I accumulate. If it pumps, I chill. I’m earning yield and stacking long term. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Short term volatility doesn’t change the plan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869234&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869212&lt;br&gt;Crypto and BTC is dead retard &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Everyone knows about it by now&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869237&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869212&lt;br&gt;The niggercattle aren&amp;#x27;t going to pump your epsteincoin bags.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869244&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869212&lt;br&gt;Pixel tranny cope.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878072&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877979&lt;br&gt;Is it another centralized shit?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878078&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869212&lt;br&gt;Welcum bro&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878113&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61872347&lt;br&gt;It’s got maybe one more bull run left in it, but $150K is never happening. Ethereum is already at the &amp;quot;no new ATHs ever again&amp;quot; stage. Crypto is dead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878176&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869234&lt;br&gt;newfag alert&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878183&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61873082&lt;br&gt;you are genuinely retarded, keep making them stronger with your rocks but in the end it won&amp;#x27;t matter&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878193&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878176&lt;br&gt;Yeah and beanie babies as an asset class will come roaring back any day now. Enjoy holding your digital bags.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878207&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878193&lt;br&gt;Not exactly accurate there&amp;#x27;s a few beanie babies still fetching over a million right now anon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878212&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877711&lt;br&gt;FUD only&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878223&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878207&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;fetching&lt;br&gt;Why are they all the same price if they&amp;#x27;re an appreciating asset?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878248&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878207&lt;br&gt;Just because you ask for a price doesn&amp;#x27;t mean you&amp;#x27;ll get it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878256&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877979&lt;br&gt;No. You never share private keys. BTC is locked in a Bitcoin script where spending still requires the staker’s signature. If the platform disappears like I said, the timelock path lets you withdraw using Bitcoin only.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878321&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877722&lt;br&gt;sure anon. why? tech, users, or just hoping for a pump?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878324&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878207&lt;br&gt;Can we make money here? I&amp;#x27;m so tired of negative PNL&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878330&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878248&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s losers trade&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878331&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869212&lt;br&gt;I own a lil bit of btc and eth myself (3% of my entire portfolio) but I would unironically love to see the entire crypto market going to 0. You bitcoin maxi retards need to wake up. Your 5k stack of crypto wont magically 100x in the next 5-10 years and make you rich lol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878347&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878072&lt;br&gt;Nah. I’ve already explained it a bunch. DYOR anon. Either let BTC sleep or look into native, self custody setups and pick what fits you kek.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878349&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869514&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;the elites&lt;br&gt;There are many kinds of elites that compete against each other. Many of them want strategic reserves of BTC to trade with. BTC will never die.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878352&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878331&lt;br&gt;What&amp;#x27;s wrong with btc maxis&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878368&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877734&lt;br&gt;Damn! Taxi drivers don’t call tops and bottoms, they just repeat headlines. Stick to your plan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878374&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878078&lt;br&gt;Not my crowd. Stay poor, anon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878376&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869212&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I&amp;#x27;ve tricked myself with a berg-word for any situation!&lt;br&gt;good for you anon? what do you want me to do with this information?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878386&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869360&lt;br&gt;And yet comex+cme can evaporate 10 trillion in market cap in three days. Going to take one from the xrp schizos and say mcap doesn&amp;#x27;t mean anything. Still hold actual metals and not paper derivatives though...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879258&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878113&lt;br&gt;If crypto is dead, why is the onchain activity, stablecoins, and L2 growth still there? Price isn’t the whole story.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880618&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878349&lt;br&gt;Someone gets it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882946&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878376&lt;br&gt;It depends on you anon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882959&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869212&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is Polkadot decoupling from Bitcoin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883795&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61877290&lt;br&gt;Based. We’ve all seen how “temporarily custodial” ends. NGMI if you outsource sovereignty and then act surprised when it rug-pulls itself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883846&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878331&lt;br&gt;the problem with btc is it used to be the gambling outlet than we got kalshi, polymarket, all the sports gambling. no one cares about up down anymore, theres 100000 different things to gamble on. they&amp;#x27;re sucking up all the crypto money. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;god damn tho those 7.10 kalshi stock options. how about build something instead of try to piggy back someone else?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883859&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869212&lt;br&gt;Who thinks ANY crypto is worth it....in 2026!?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Not old stuff then, what NEW crypto will be 100 or 1000 times on Monday, faggots?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885711&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882959&lt;br&gt;it just hasn’t dumped yet. wait for BTC to sneeze and we’ll see how independent it really is&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Why do people on this board whine piss and moan about having six-figs? — 50 replies — 10.7/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61883830</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61883830?lm=1771742435</guid><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 06:40:35 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Why do people on this board whine piss and moan about having six-figs?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61883830'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 50 • Updated: 2026-02-22 06:40 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Do any of you realize how unbelievably lucky you are compared against most in even 1st-world countries? Your average person is tens of thousands in credit card debt and struggling to pay off their klarna these days. Even worse, they&amp;#x27;re a few months behind on their mortgage and about to lose their house.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meanwhile, your lot go &amp;quot;WAAAAAA WOE IS ME I&amp;#x27;M ONLY WORTH $475K AT 23 YEARS OLD I&amp;#x27;LL NEVER BE RICH!!!!!&amp;quot; Even if you&amp;#x27;re larping, I mean fuck you don&amp;#x27;t&amp;#x27; realize how spoiled rotten and ridiculous you sound, you&amp;#x27;re not even funny nor cute when you whine like that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883852&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883830&lt;br&gt;yea but crypto went down&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883873&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883830&lt;br&gt;because im still a wageslave you retarded cockgargling faggot&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883874&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883830&lt;br&gt;There are no 1st world countries anymore. It goes:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Switzerland, Northern Italy, Poland, and everybody else&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884587&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883830&lt;br&gt;Yeah but the jews&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884630&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I used to have a crypto portfolio worth $300k and now I have a negative NW. I would do anything to go back in time and put it all in boomer ETFs. I might not be able to quit working but life would exponentially easier. I fucked up badly and I know it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884639&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883830&lt;br&gt;100k and below is loser class. &lt;br&gt;150k is middle class.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884645&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is getting the first 100k really the point when your wealth starts to snowball higher? I forget where I heard that opinion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884650&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884645&lt;br&gt;100k. Maybe back then. &lt;br&gt;It is probably 1m now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884652&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883830&lt;br&gt;Because 6 figs is nothing and still incel tier, I want to be chad rich tier and never have to work again&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884658&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884652&lt;br&gt;Come join us in the neet thread&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884755&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883830&lt;br&gt;Nigga I aint free until I can be free from the cage forever&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884765&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884755&lt;br&gt;You are kinda free if you are in the top 10% ig. They are the group still spending in usa.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884780&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883830&lt;br&gt;Another day another poorfag trying to drag me into his crab bucket.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;FUCK OFF YOU PIECE OF SHIT LOSER STOP TRYING TO MAKE EVERYONE SUFFER WITH YOU&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884789&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884780&lt;br&gt;He isn’t wrong. American median household income is 60k.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885028&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883830&lt;br&gt;Six figs isnt enough to retire. Anyways Im at very low 6 figs one slight dump in stocks and Im back to 5 figure hell.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I want out of the wagecage and its not luck when the average person in the US probably buys fast food 10 times a week, goes out to a restuarant once a week at $200 per visit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885045&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;it called being tongue-and-cheek you stupid fucking retarded fucking nigger&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885049&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885045&lt;br&gt;oops meet to say tongue in cheek but whatever&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885051&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884789&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;median household income&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;household&lt;br&gt;Kek they try so hard to giving a realistic number. Show me median individual income, emphasis on median. Don&amp;#x27;t feed me &amp;quot;average&amp;quot; which is easily skewed upwards.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;you live in a nation of 100 people&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;1 person makes $1b&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;99 people make $10k&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;average houshold size is 10 people&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;median individual income $10k&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;median household income $100k&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;average individual income ~$10m&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;average household income ~$100m&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885310&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885051&lt;br&gt;by your own math median is just as misleading as mean&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885331&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883830&lt;br&gt;500k is nothing. If you have this, congrats. You can spend your entire net worth and buy a decent house. Now what? &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;There has to be more than this, op. People who are &amp;quot;doing well&amp;quot; should be able to actually make a change in this world, yet they can barely afford to buy a house. The system is broken&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885340&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885331&lt;br&gt;Back in muh day we just gathered sticks of wood and nailed cardboard&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885350&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883830&lt;br&gt;The majority of people in first world countries are boomers, they own multiple houses, have had multiple wives, multiple kids, multiple cars, multiple pension plans. I literally have nothing in comparison.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885360&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885350&lt;br&gt;Dont go there just stay where you are. When they send their drones china will just hack them and make them crash. And thats how the white cookie crumbles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885501&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885310&lt;br&gt;But far more accurate to reality than the supposed reality they try to paint. In both median individual and household income the amounts are more accurate than average while median individual income bears the most accuracy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885512&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m about to enter 6 figure hell next week, what am i in for?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885530&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883830&lt;br&gt;My 300k is literally nothing&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885562&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885512&lt;br&gt;5 figure hell after trump&amp;#x27;s tariff tirade&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885855&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883830&lt;br&gt;Lucky? I&amp;#x27;m a fucking wage slave. Having 600k usd means fuck all when houses cost 2 million AUD in Sydney and I&amp;#x27;m 30 years old. I don&amp;#x27;t want to work the rest of my life (I won&amp;#x27;t anyway as AI is about to take me out)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885862&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885512&lt;br&gt;Depends on your age and savings rate&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885873&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883830&lt;br&gt;Nope. Not good enough.&lt;br&gt;Sense of accomplishment is relative. We want to go up in life, not down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885878&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883830&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s good that I was born when and where I was. It is a good thing. I greatly appreciate being born on a scaffold.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885983&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885051&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;what is law of large numbers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885987&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885331&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;muh house&lt;br&gt;Kys retard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Is it even possible to make it by opening a traditional business anymore? — 20 replies — 7.1/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61881439</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61881439?lm=1771748989</guid><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 08:29:49 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Is it even possible to make it by opening a traditional business anymore?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61881439'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 20 • Updated: 2026-02-22 08:29 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Read subject &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is it even possible? Not only do you have to jump through a million regulations and fees just to get started, you&amp;#x27;re also competing against trillion dollar mega corps who can and will undercut you because they employ ten thousand indians and illegals who work for pennies. Even traditional blue collar jobs like plumbers and HVAC are all slowly coagulating into one single corporate entity (in my area), and basically every single mom and pop store was killed during COVID. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It seems like the only way you can actually achieve anything is to basically trick angle investors into giving your bullshit tech start-up a ton of money or getting really lucky and have an app you make be bought out by a megacorp so they can rape your customers to death.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pic unrelated&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881446&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881439&lt;br&gt;Step 1: get a girlfriend&lt;br&gt;Step 2: have her start an ASMR channel on YouTube&lt;br&gt;Step 3: have her start a merchandise line on shopify&lt;br&gt;There.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881567&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881446&lt;br&gt;the pretty girl ASMR youtuber to OF is so undefeated.. Ive been watching ASMR for 8 years and the amount of hot ASMR girls that build a quick following and launch OF is high.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881609&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881446&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Step 1: get a girlfriend&lt;br&gt;Do you have anything more realistic that I can accomplish?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881624&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881609&lt;br&gt;Become a trans vtuber. Work on your feminine voice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882459&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881439&lt;br&gt;Even trillion dollar companies can&amp;#x27;t do everything. The amount of bureaucracy involved to manage such a large entity is limiting in its own ways.&lt;br&gt;You have to find a niche that isn&amp;#x27;t currently being served in your market and then create a business for that.&lt;br&gt;For example: nobody is making catgirl gfs right now, it&amp;#x27;s a completely untapped market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882478&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Corporations can now grow indefinetly due to advancement&amp;#x27;s in economic planning. It used to be theyd crash and burn after they got to a certain size.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882584&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881624&lt;br&gt;This, also after few years of HRT start OF, get cosmetic surgeries to look like a bimbo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882649&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m not sure which is a worse feeling. The frustration of losing a bunch of games for dumb reasons or the anxiety of not wanting to fuck up a good winning streak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883247&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881439&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s possible, but made very difficult by design. Can&amp;#x27;t have too many people escaping the wage cage.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Everything is over regulated, because it means only mega corps have the resources to deal with the BS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883254&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881439&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;a million regulations and fees just to get started&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;there are fees and regulations but they&amp;#x27;re not impossible to navigate, just look at how retardedness and drunkeness of the average trades small business owner.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;but you&amp;#x27;re right about consolidation and private equity ownership. there&amp;#x27;s no way around this, other than killing PE jews or the people who sell out to PE.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883298&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881446&lt;br&gt;I did a similar thing with my wife&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;have gf&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;she films herself having sex with guys in college while we were long distance&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;both of us have cuckold fetish&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;whenever she visits me we usually set aside time for threesomes with guys we meet online and sex clubs&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;eventually get married, start onlyfans where we film it all but blur the faces&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;make around $8000 a month &lt;br&gt;not a traditional business model as OP says however&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883454&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883298&lt;br&gt;disgusting freak. why marry at this point?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883460&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883454&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s bait anon. No one has a GF here on 4chin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884102&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881624&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882584&lt;br&gt;kill yourselves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884346&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881439&lt;br&gt;Welcome to the patent system!&lt;br&gt;* invent something new under the sun&lt;br&gt;* spend a few thousand dollars with a patent attorney to protect your invention in an airtight manner&lt;br&gt;* sue the shit out of anyone who infringes&lt;br&gt;* make outsized profits on everything you sell&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I vaguely remember being told by one of my patent law professors during law school that over 80% of profits in the U.S. are tied to intellectual property, i.e., patents and copyrights. Commodity goods just aren&amp;#x27;t profitable when you have to compete by selling as close to zero margin as you can get, and make it up on volume.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A company called Rare Breed is doing that right now in the field of &amp;quot;forced reset trigger systems&amp;quot; for firearms. Their projections are that they will make mid-eight figures of profit annually if they are the sole source. Note &amp;quot;profit&amp;quot; not &amp;quot;revenue&amp;quot;. Manufacturing costs on each of their units is probably around $50, and they&amp;#x27;re selling them for $500 each.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The difficulty: lots of infringers, including one batshit insane asshole from Arizona, and one kid who designed a free one that anyone can 3D print at home. (And in all fairness, the kid put it out on free 3D printing websites before several of Rare Breed&amp;#x27;s patents issued, but after they were filed, so he arguably wasn&amp;#x27;t even infringing at the time.) They&amp;#x27;ve got something like seventeen lawsuits going right now, IIRC, and some of the defendants are trying to get their cases consolidated into a single trial because of the expense.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884359&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s like getting into the in-game market in an MMO that&amp;#x27;s been around for 20 years, it&amp;#x27;s completely futile&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884385&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881624&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882584&lt;br&gt;picrelated&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884627&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Of course it is. Where do you think all these giant houses come from? There&amp;#x27;s tons of well-off business owners all throughout your city, state, country.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886156&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884627&lt;br&gt;Most of whom got started a couple of generations ago. Then they set up legislative roadblocks to make it impossible for new competitors to spring up.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;My state requires a 1000 hour training certificate before someone can cut hair. As a result, a large percentage of those who do it are guys who were stuck in prison and learned their trade in the prison barbershop, because it was free for them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886164&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884627&lt;br&gt;Oh, I forgot about the used car lots. Used to be that anyone could set up as a used car dealer. Then the big stealerships started getting outcompeted, with one big driver (heh) being because the independents would stay open on Sundays while the stealerships were closed. So the stealerships lobbied the legislature to prohibit used car lots from being open on Sundays.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lots more similar stories in various businesses. Funeral parlors are heavily regulated (the excuse being &amp;quot;they can dispose of bodies in their crematoriums, so we have to regulate and license that profession&amp;quot;), and so on and so on.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;FFS in NYC Mamdani just asked for &amp;quot;volunteer snow shovelers&amp;quot; and demanded that they register with &amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;The City&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;#x27; by showing two forms of ID plus their Social Security card.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>LINK is over — 16 replies — 7.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61883208</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61883208?lm=1771750940</guid><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 09:02:20 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;LINK is over&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61883208'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 16 • Updated: 2026-02-22 09:02 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;What will you do when LINK hits $1?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883225&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883208&lt;br&gt;It probably won’t hit $1 but actually worse in that it’ll slowwwwly draw down over the next few years to 5-ish with every pop met with a violent drawback sell off&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883228&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whenever I see AI art I’m always baffled by how boring/unfunny/literal most these guys internal world is.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883259&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883228&lt;br&gt;i quite like this piece&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;but the chainholders should be barefoot&lt;br&gt;and some should be flagellating with their chains&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883269&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883208&lt;br&gt;buy a lot and then sell when it moons to $4&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883278&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883208&lt;br&gt;Apready accepted it&amp;#x27;s over...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883330&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883208&lt;br&gt;go to the temple of time to take LINK from $7 to $16&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884041&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883208&lt;br&gt;Smile and laugh at the baggies who were so vicious they tried to con others into holding and were willing to sell all values they have to back a play that is actual fucking rent seeking with no other purpose&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884289&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883208&lt;br&gt;If it&amp;#x27;s over then why are you still here 24/7 trying to get people to sell?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884311&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884289&lt;br&gt;because wagmi anon, i want you to succeed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884558&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883228&lt;br&gt;its literally how brown people think; moreover they&amp;#x27;re self-centered npc&amp;#x27;s with a very rigid, fatalistic and cynical worldview. its impossible for them to entertain responsibility and consequence. guys like adem lost so much izzat he is self-damned to an eternity to izzat pickle, such is life for the brownie. absolutely grim.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884574&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884289&lt;br&gt;please don&amp;#x27;t sell, ok? please&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886149&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884289&lt;br&gt;Because, it&amp;#x27;s not enough to merely win; others must lose. I want to watch the souls of the damned suffer in sorrow. I wish to revel in their anguish.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886194&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;how much is 1 times 1000?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886201&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884289&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61886149&lt;br&gt;Also, on further introspection, I don&amp;#x27;t want you to sell. I want you to grab tighter to your bag in desperation, hoping for a turn around. A turn around that never comes. I want you to hold as you are devoured by a black hole of sub $1 prices. Your entire existence is only to waste your life holding a bag of LINK as it further deteriorates in price, and observers like myself watch with glee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886206&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883225&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;it’ll slowwwwly draw down over the next few years to 5-ish&lt;br&gt;Why would it take so long? Bear market just got started and it&amp;#x27;s $8. It&amp;#x27;ll be five dollars again within a few months, maybe as long as towards the end of the year at best.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886212&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61886206&lt;br&gt;Bear market started a lot longer ago than you think&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>insider here, again. — 20 replies — 4.9/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61879263</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61879263?lm=1771744638</guid><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 07:17:18 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;insider here, again.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61879263'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 20 • Updated: 2026-02-22 07:17 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;i hope you bought BBBY-WT BBBY-WARRANTS&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879648&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I have a few thousand of these along with shares what am I in for&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879767&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879648&lt;br&gt;getting dumped on by OP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879836&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879767&lt;br&gt;Due to my current occupation, I am prohibited from holding stocks, options, or similar investments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879895&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This you?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879921&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879767&lt;br&gt;idk I mean bed bath was once a huge American retail darling...the historic overstock chart is super schizo/presently quite low...these warrants are trading like a shitcoin which is funny...I also don&amp;#x27;t dislike lemonis. He&amp;#x27;s a media player and if you actually listened to some of his shit there does seem to be an interesting intersection between blockchain capabilities and homeownership etc...not financial advice of course just a variety of things I was peeking at when researching&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879944&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879263&lt;br&gt;no&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61879999&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879836&lt;br&gt;What is your current occupation anon? Nothing revealing but in general etc...the exercise price of the warrants is $15...trading currently at less than a dollar it seems like a confusing deal...at this point if one likes the company wouldn&amp;#x27;t shares be the move? I did some modeling around warrant prices if the shares price goes to xyz and that is very interesting...also speaking of interesting what&amp;#x27;s the deal with the alleged cusip similarity to the old bbbyq shares?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880091&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879999&lt;br&gt;Financial system. I am not asking you to hold those warrants until they are exercised. I am asking you to hold them and sell the warrants when we can realize a substantial profit. Nice quads.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881477&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880091&lt;br&gt;Interesting. Wouldn&amp;#x27;t trading the warrants implicitly come with a short term capital gains tax insofar as its impossible to hold them over a year at this point? Would have to be some pretty fair gains to offset that 40% hit...anyways doesn&amp;#x27;t the warrants increasing in price also imply that the shares have gone up in price as well? I ran some informal modeling estimates using black scholes with iv, roughly .65 years to expiry and this is what I came up with: 15.5 bbby share price = 4.50ish warrant price...25 share price/12ish warrant price...60 share price/45ish warrant price...100 share price/85ish warrant price...200 share price 185ish warrant price...I make no claim as to the veracity of these numbers, just for fun. Anyways what do you see happening to the bbby stock price for these warrants to be worthwhile? Am I thinking on the right track in general?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881670&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879263&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881753&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879999&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881477&lt;br&gt;note the digis&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881916&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879263&lt;br&gt;Buy these if you want, but remember, these warrants are not related to the canceled BBBYQ/DK-Butterfly, reguardless of what the BBBYQ schizos say.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881980&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881916&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;nobody tell him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882152&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61879263&lt;br&gt;I hold a few&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882389&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;why are americans starting to invest more into VT?&lt;br&gt;isn&amp;#x27;t america the greatest country on earth?&lt;br&gt;for me it has always been VOO&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882429&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;look at NPC holder distribution&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;there&amp;#x27;s no big dumps&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;base still present&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;conviction quietly intact&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884950&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880091&lt;br&gt;So you&amp;#x27;re allowed to buy warrants, won&amp;#x27;t your employer know you bought them?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885366&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get ready everyone. I don&amp;#x27;t think they will be able to kick the can after this sneeze. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885357&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886042&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;what about BBBYQ? i lost all my money. the little i&amp;#x27;ve earned since then i&amp;#x27;ve spent on equipment that will make me a self-made millionaire thanks to my own intellect and blood sweat and tears and not thanks to ryan cohen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886054&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61886042&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>2026 is THE year of the Link token. You'll see. Check 'em. — 28 replies — 4.5/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61882840</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61882840?lm=1771736852</guid><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 05:07:32 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;2026 is THE year of the Link token. You&amp;#x27;ll see. Check &amp;#x27;em.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61882840'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 28 • Updated: 2026-02-22 05:07 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;2026 is THE year of the Link token. &lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;ll see. Check &amp;#x27;em.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882854&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882840&lt;br&gt;Great year for Sergey. Horrible year for baggies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882857&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882840&lt;br&gt;you have nothing to check, not even dubs, you will fail&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882865&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Uh, I&amp;#x27;ma put my cat on the keyboard. Meow meow meow, meow, meow meow. Meow meow. Meow meow? Meow. (Financially speaking)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882879&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882840&lt;br&gt;CHECKED!!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882894&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;fantastic work everyone, link will be $1k eoy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882895&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s over for us, it was always over for us&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882898&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;digits and Stink goes to zero&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882908&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882840&lt;br&gt;Link is dead. Wake the fuck up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883848&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why is the link community so low energy now&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883854&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882908&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882898&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882895&lt;br&gt;Check this shit nigger&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883860&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883854&lt;br&gt;Low energy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883861&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883854&lt;br&gt;checked&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883890&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;2026 is the YEAR&lt;br&gt;That link reaches AOT of $10.99&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884002&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882840&lt;br&gt;Sergey in Spanish is:&lt;br&gt;Ser = is&lt;br&gt;Gey = Gay&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;His name is &amp;quot;is gay&amp;quot; in Spanish&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884010&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882840&lt;br&gt;I thought he solved oracles problems, but now it looks more like a temporary bandaid. I sold all my link and Oracle stock.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884032&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882840&lt;br&gt;Link has no value and is already over priced. It is just rent seeking and fee insertion jewry with zero other utility. Like no hate or anything but this isn&amp;#x27;t even exaggeration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884132&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;digits and link is $100 eoyt 2026&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884172&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884132&lt;br&gt;You are low energy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884202&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882840&lt;br&gt;linkies are THE cuckolds of crypto xD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884230&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882840&lt;br&gt;Zero digits in this thread. SAD!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884400&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884230&lt;br&gt;How is that even possible?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884841&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883854&lt;br&gt;how embarrassing&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884942&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;$500 EOY CHECKEM&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885073&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;$10,000 EOY. Check em niggers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885105&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;$20 in April, digits confirm&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885130&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882840&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;whitnessed&lt;br&gt;$120 eoq&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885795&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is known&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885804&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885795&lt;br&gt;I hate these niggers so much. Every financial opinion piece they spew out is complete dog shit on crypto. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;...And for that reason goy, BUY BITCOIN! Just because!&amp;quot; &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;And PLEASE pay for a subscription to our stock picks!&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;Everytime. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;They made retards generational baggies the last run.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Bro just give me 50 stocks to shotgun I will literally build a balanced portfolio of all your posts ITT. — 70 replies — 4.4/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61874540</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61874540?lm=1771701690</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 19:21:30 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Bro just give me 50 stocks to shotgun I will literally build a balanced portfolio of all your posts ITT.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61874540'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 70 • Updated: 2026-02-21 19:21 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bro just give me 50 stocks to shotgun I will literally build a balanced portfolio of all your posts ITT. Dont repost tickers. Trips I&amp;#x27;ll buy 5x the amount. This is a financial experiment, not a shill thread. /biz/ should outperform the market. No cryptos. Go&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874568&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I dont own many individual stocks here are the ones i have:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;GLEN SHELL MDT DHR ISRG RHM BRK.B RR. FCX IYAA NOV GOOG YAR IFX ROK LGEN boeing VOW SNPS TSLA AMBA SNPS SYM RKLB AVAV OUST CRCL&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874578&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874540&lt;br&gt;uhm, Accenture&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61874612&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874578&lt;br&gt;looks good!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881768&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878135&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;sun is in front of the clouds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881844&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881768&lt;br&gt;You are right; I was too busy ogling curvy Amelia and thinking of saving the white race and sending pajeets back to notice&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881982&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881844&lt;br&gt;if only she was real&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882019&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881271&lt;br&gt;Im here, I&amp;#x27;m busy this weekend . I am 100% building the portfolio&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882026&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;we have great and balanced suggestions I just need to compile it. I will vacuum the trash value stocks. Just need to compile and weight. and like I said I didn&amp;#x27;t want to buy today because of a high possibility of weekend shenanigans&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882029&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882026&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I will vacuum the trash value stocks&lt;br&gt; I&amp;#x27;ll include falling knives I mean but with appropriate size&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882149&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61874540&lt;br&gt;ARMP (Armata Pharmaceuticals)&lt;br&gt;You’re welcome&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882160&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WPM and TTWO. For the latter it now looks bad, but wait when Gta6 hits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882255&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BMXI&lt;br&gt;OMQS&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882490&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882026&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882029&lt;br&gt;AI can do this in like 8 seconds, just paste the whole thread and tell it what to do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882730&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882490&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882735&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882730&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882736&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882735&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882740&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882736&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882747&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882740&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;pick abroad index fund TO AVOID slop&lt;br&gt;Costanza&lt;br&gt;Anon can’t into getting the most out of a Jewish LLM&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882767&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882740&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882736&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882735&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882730&lt;br&gt;You are an incredibly incompetent person.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;TICKER | SHARES | TOTAL DOLLAR COST&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AEM | 6 | $901. (≈6×150.38)&lt;br&gt;AMBA | 8 | $903. (≈8×112.94)&lt;br&gt;AMZN | 4 | $840. (≈4×210.11)&lt;br&gt;AVAV | 3 | $793.89&lt;br&gt;BA | 4 | $928.12&lt;br&gt;BIPC | 23 | $950.59&lt;br&gt;CDE | 40 | $985.2&lt;br&gt;CLSK | 102 | $984.3&lt;br&gt;CODA | 73 | $982.02&lt;br&gt;COST | 1 | $985.27&lt;br&gt;CRCL | 15 | $945.3&lt;br&gt;DAVE | 5 | $882.55&lt;br&gt;DHR | 4 | $838.0&lt;br&gt;FCX | 15 | $965.1&lt;br&gt;GD | 2 | $702.84&lt;br&gt;HIMS | 63 | $985. + (~63×15.63)&lt;br&gt;HPQ | 53 | $985.03&lt;br&gt;HOOD | 12 | $913.32&lt;br&gt;IBM | 3 | $771.48&lt;br&gt;INTC | 22 | $970.42&lt;br&gt;ISRG | 1 | $504.05&lt;br&gt;JNJ | 4 | $969.96&lt;br&gt;LUCK | 8 | $903.52 (≈8×112.94) — used DUOL price as proxy (Duolingo)&lt;br&gt;MARATHON (MARA) | 123 | $980.31&lt;br&gt;MSFT | 2 | $794.46&lt;br&gt;MTD | 10 | $968.6&lt;br&gt;NOV | 48 | $978.72&lt;br&gt;OUST | 52 | $968.24&lt;br&gt;PESI | 73 | $979.66&lt;br&gt;RKLB | 20 | $962.6&lt;br&gt;ROK | 2 | $797.58&lt;br&gt;SNPS | 2 | $879.88&lt;br&gt;SYM | 18 | ~$968.31 (≈18×53.795)&lt;br&gt;TCGL | 7 | ~$984.71* — assumed ~$140.67 price (not quoted)&lt;br&gt;TTD | 39 | $978.9&lt;br&gt;TTWO | 4 | $798.88&lt;br&gt;UPST | 33 | $966.57&lt;br&gt;WMT | 8 | $983.92&lt;br&gt;WPM | 6 | $902.28&lt;br&gt;XLE | 13 | ~$988.51* — assumed ~$75.96 price (typical)&lt;br&gt;XOM | 6 | $883.68&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882771&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882767&lt;br&gt;First was ChatGPT.&lt;br&gt;Grok took way longer but here is what I ended up with using Grok.&lt;br&gt;ACN | 5 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;AEM | 4 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;AMBA | 14 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;AMZN | 5 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;ARMP | 113 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;AU | 9 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;AVAV | 4 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;BIPC | 21 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;BMXI | 39411 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;BRK.B | 2 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;CDE | 40 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;CLSK | 102 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;COST | 1 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;CRCL | 16 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;DLR | 6 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;DNN | 243 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;EPOL | 26 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;EUAD | 21 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;FCX | 15 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;FIG | 38 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;FLOT | 19 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;GD | 3 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;GOOG | 3 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;HIMS | 62 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;HOOD | 13 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;HP | 28 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;IGV | 12 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;INVZ | 1048 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;JD | 36 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;MARA | 124 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;MRVL | 12 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;NAK | 752 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;NOV | 48 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;OUST | 53 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;PESI | 73 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;RGLD | 3 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;RHM | 861 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;RR | 377 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;SHEL | 12 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;SNPS | 2 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;SYM | 18 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;TEM | 17 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;TTD | 39 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;VGSH | 17 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;WDAY | 7 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;WDEF | 28 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;WMT | 8 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;WPM | 7 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;XLU | 21 | 985.27&lt;br&gt;XYZ | 19 | 985.27&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882776&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882771&lt;br&gt;~$50k to replicate this. I could easily do it, but I won&amp;#x27;t. If $50k is less than 10% of your portfolio and you&amp;#x27;re a crazed degenerate Yolo gambler maybe give it a try. Report back results yearly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882780&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882771&lt;br&gt;EUAD and WDEF are redundant so don&amp;#x27;t buy both.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882784&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882767&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882771&lt;br&gt;COST is the highest priced stock per share.&lt;br&gt;Idiocracy was prophecy.&lt;br&gt;Gaze upon your future.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882960&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882771 (and others)&lt;br&gt;I appreciate the effort but ChatGPT and grok are dumber than midwits.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882735&lt;br&gt;I can literally tell this is gemini because of its recommendations&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;compare what i hold in my 2nd post to its baseline recommendations&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I bought some of those because gemini recommends it and I foresee normies getting their stock picks from googles ai mode&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882969&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;anyone who has extensively toyed with muh ai for finance and stock picks has come across this&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;here&amp;#x27;s why stock X is currently a &amp;quot;bottom-blasted&amp;quot; value pick: (3 bullet points, not x but y)&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;open chart&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;stock has just spent 12 weeks hitting new ATHs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882997&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;anyway it doesnt need to really pick anything, just allocate sanely&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883121&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882969&lt;br&gt;Grok is the only AI that gave me decent advice on investment s. But Gemini, chatgpt and even Claude opus were terrible. You should always do your own research with stonks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883654&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883121&lt;br&gt;post the good grokpicks they can be included&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883658&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;or your own preferably this is the biz portfolio after all,. just channel what first comes to mind like a schizo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883675&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882776&lt;br&gt;have you never heard of a paper account? Nigga.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883693&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Can you make a trading 212 pie from this my retarded ass can copy? My skillset is engineering and plowing Asian girls not this shit. I’ll just put a 500 in for fun.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884110&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883121&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883654&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;bro just give me 50 stocks&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;actually I&amp;#x27;m gonna just buy what I already bought and what Gemeni told me to&lt;br&gt;What a fag. At least make a fake paper portfolio of 50 of the stocks we gave you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884222&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884110&lt;br&gt;learn to read teh thread moron&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>If you're retired right now in the US, how much do you live on per month? — 9 replies — 3.5/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61885522</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61885522?lm=1771750000</guid><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 08:46:40 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;If you&amp;#x27;re retired right now in the US, how much do you live on per month?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61885522'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 9 • Updated: 2026-02-22 08:46 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;#x27;re retired right now in the US, how much do you live on per month?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885525&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All ponzis are dead&lt;br&gt;If you are over 50 kill yourself or you will be killed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885543&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885525&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;kill yourself or you&amp;#x27;ll DIE&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885550&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885543&lt;br&gt;Die on your own terms. That option is gone latest in July when the global sovereign bond ponzi hits the continental ice shelf&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885643&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885543&lt;br&gt;Kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886090&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885522&lt;br&gt;60k&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886095&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885522&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m not retired, but I do eat 2x double cheeseburger&amp;#x27;s with the Mcapp for the BOGOF1D sale so that&amp;#x27;s $4.76 for lunch and then I go home to my parents house after work and eat a protein bar I got off Amazon for $1.12 through the subscribe and save program. I&amp;#x27;ll game and goon basically for free and I pay no rent so monthly costs are basically $200 a month after factoring in taxes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886155&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61886095&lt;br&gt;by double cheeseburgers do you mean mcdoubles, i thought those were 1 dollar each&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886184&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885522&lt;br&gt;40k, plus occasionally I&amp;#x27;ll splurge a few times a year and buy a new car or trade up my yacht.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886189&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61886155&lt;br&gt;They have double cheese as well. McDouble is two patties but only one slice of cheese.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>i don't know if he was tasked to destroy bitcoin's prospects as an actual currency alternative but he seems eerily power… — 2 replies — 3.4/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61886338</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61886338?lm=1771757052</guid><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 10:44:12 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;i don&amp;#x27;t know if he was tasked to destroy bitcoin&amp;#x27;s prospects as an actual currency alternative but he seems eerily power…&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61886338'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 2 • Updated: 2026-02-22 10:44 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;i don&amp;#x27;t know if he was tasked to destroy bitcoin&amp;#x27;s prospects as an actual currency alternative but he seems eerily powerful and has devoted his whole existence to propping up BTC valuation so I&amp;#x27;m happy to be on his bandwagon even if he&amp;#x27;s shady as all hell&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886341&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He&amp;#x27;s just a stereotypical bubbleboy. His company lost like 99% of its value during the dotcom crash&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886342&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;there is no second best Laura&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;No additional replies in the latest window.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>I thought that by 2026 XRP would be $500 and BTC would be $1.75 million, and I'd be living the dream — 10 replies — 3.1/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61881191</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61881191?lm=1771747547</guid><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 08:05:47 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;I thought that by 2026 XRP would be $500 and BTC would be $1.75 million, and I&amp;#x27;d be living the dream&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61881191'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 10 • Updated: 2026-02-22 08:05 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;I thought that by 2026 XRP would be $500 and BTC would be $1.75 million, and I&amp;#x27;d be living the dream&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881201&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881191&lt;br&gt;When did you form that thought?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881223&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881201&lt;br&gt;Feb 2021&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881248&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;That&amp;#x27;s exactly what I say (living the dream) when customers ask how I am at my retail cashier job&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881340&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881223&lt;br&gt;Your XRP assumption was acceptable but man you were way too optimistic about BTC. Start thinking in longer time frames and you&amp;#x27;ll likely have more success&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882589&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m livin the dream baby :)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883958&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881191&lt;br&gt;Same here, anon. Instead, I’m here stacking sats and planning to park it in a Bitcoin trustless vault for passive income, keep the keys, stay sovereign, let it grow while I just live my life.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dream’s still alive, just playing the long game.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883966&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881191&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;XRP would be $500&lt;br&gt;BOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOM&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884282&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881191&lt;br&gt;What was your DCA for each?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884577&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881191&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I&amp;#x27;M A BAG HOLDER&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;A BAG HODLER&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;NOW YOU KNOW&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;IS YOUR (ORDER) TO GO?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886123&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881191&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;XRP&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bullish&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>BREAKING NEWS: RIPPLE INSIDERS SPECULATE POSITIVE PRICE ACTION FOR THE XRP CHART IN TWO WEEKS — 9 replies — 2.8/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61884214</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61884214?lm=1771747485</guid><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 08:04:45 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;BREAKING NEWS: RIPPLE INSIDERS SPECULATE POSITIVE PRICE ACTION FOR THE XRP CHART IN TWO WEEKS&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61884214'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 9 • Updated: 2026-02-22 08:04 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is **massive** news, a Ripple riddler has speculated allegedly an insider elon musk new world reserve currency tesla and trump global reserve finance new digital currency&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884250&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Upwards of $4?! I&amp;#x27;d be a hundred-thousandaire!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884276&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;never go full retard&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884518&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;https://link-flip.alwaysbeshipp.ing/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884693&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884214&lt;br&gt;classic bart, eth and btc will finish this bear flag in a few days and BOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOM! 50c!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884806&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pic related is since the Trump pump. XRP is the only one to keep its gains, has outperformed any other asset as a new issuance ETF based product, and as opposed to link which just tries to insert rent seeking, increases efficiencies and kills frictions actually putting the token at the heart of every part of its business, etc. Cope nigger. Also, it is corny to put a picture of yourself expressing to characterize a post/OP.&lt;br&gt;See:&lt;br&gt;https://ripple.com/insights/institutional-defi-on-xrpl-scaling-real-world-finance-with-xrp-at-the-core/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884813&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884806&lt;br&gt;OP disregard the pic comment. I copied the text because you fags are equivalently flooding and forgot to delete it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884854&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884214&lt;br&gt;2 more weeks! BOOM!!!!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886121&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOOOOOOOM&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>IQ test. Don't fail it — 11 replies — 2.7/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61878164</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61878164?lm=1771744605</guid><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 07:16:45 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;IQ test. Don&amp;#x27;t fail it&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61878164'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 11 • Updated: 2026-02-22 07:16 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;IQ test. Don&amp;#x27;t fail it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61878192&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878164&lt;br&gt;what test?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882316&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878164&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61882337&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Not buying your bags&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885177&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61882337&lt;br&gt;If &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;pic related &lt;br&gt;happens, this habbening will make this coin&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;100x&lt;br&gt;and start &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;the antiapocalyptical bullrush&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885182&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61878164&lt;br&gt;fill me in op. i cant miss another opportunity&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885198&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885182&lt;br&gt;Every opportunity is a pullback.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885205&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885198&lt;br&gt;are we in a pullback right now? or did it pass?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885254&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sorry what’s the use case for trump coin other than the gay dinner?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885272&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885254&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s another way for boomers to give Trump more money. He needs your money. Don&amp;#x27;t be stingy or greedy. Give him your money.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886043&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;it&amp;#x27;s gonna be so good bros. Easiest 2x of 2026&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886052&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885272&lt;br&gt;Boomers still don&amp;#x27;t get crypto. Their loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>