<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>/biz/ Active (filtered, with replies)</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/</link><description>Filtered out: general, gme, bbbyq. OP + first 3 replies + last 30 replies.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 18:10:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CRYPTO IS DEAD — 36 replies — 144.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61880718</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61880718?lm=1771869553</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 17:59:13 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;CRYPTO IS DEAD&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61880718'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 36 • Updated: 2026-02-23 17:59 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Crypto is dead. So I&amp;#x27;m looking into buying again, maybe lump sum maybe DCA. What do you think, anons? Some think that the bear market is just starting so maybe it&amp;#x27;s better to wait... but idk, the sentiment seems rather depressed already. Anyone else also accumulating rn or ar you waiting for october? Alts or BTC?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880730&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;rn&lt;br&gt;Tiktok negrobabble gets your thread filtered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61880848&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880730&lt;br&gt;You answered tho?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881053&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880718&lt;br&gt;all other macro bottoms took several months of crabbing before the markets went up again, we havent done that yet&lt;br&gt;probably better to wait it out and only deploy capital when its clear the trend has shifted&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;like last macro bottom in late 2022, if you waited till conformation you bought at 18k instead of 16k, a marginal difference&lt;br&gt;i&amp;#x27;ll assume that nobody actually nabbed the 60k bottom here for how short it was&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61881505&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880718&lt;br&gt;I voted for this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883131&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881187&lt;br&gt;That&amp;#x27;s not true, pic related is the covid dip. You had a total of 5 days at 5k, then it started a pretty steep recovery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883135&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881266&lt;br&gt;Pretty much this, except things will probably turn suddenly when CLARITY passes in a month or 2&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883290&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880718&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883374&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883135&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Polity is going to make my bag go line up&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;BUY MY BAG NOW&lt;br&gt;no&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883380&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;btc behaves like a more volatile leveraged spy. I thought the whole idea is crypto being a hedge against fiat and being decentralized. now american companies like mstr and blackrock own huge chunks and the whole crypto movement depends on american regulations. I dont own crypto and I never will. Everyone still being heavily into crypto at this moment must be desperate as fuck otherwise I dont get it. Last 5 years btc couldnt even outperform the s&amp;amp;p lol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883384&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883380&lt;br&gt;Everyone being into ponzi asset, including every single ponzi paper in the spx is desperate &lt;br&gt;You can&amp;#x27;t print yourself out of a demographic deflation. Your advertising is futile&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883390&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880718&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Polkadot crypto&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;https://www.figment.io/insights/polkadots-dynamic-allocation-pool-dap-an-evolution-in-issuance-and-staking/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883398&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883390&lt;br&gt;Go advertise somewhere else freak jeet/chink&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883516&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883290&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;buy my stockbags and metalbags&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;don&amp;#x27;t you dare buy decentralized currencies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883562&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880718&lt;br&gt;Wait, its going lower. Experts think 40k is the bottom&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883576&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883398&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Im Korean not Indian&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883624&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883576&lt;br&gt;What&amp;#x27;s the difference?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883631&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;cryptoniggers still DCAing into crypto in the midst of crypto winter&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;completely ignoring asset classes that have momentum like AI, space tech, precious metals, energy, etc.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The definition of insanity is doing the same thing over and over again and expecting different results.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883636&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883631&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;buy my bags at ath&lt;br&gt;No thank you&lt;br&gt;I always made the most money when faggots like yourself tell me crypto is dead and chase assets hitting multi decade highs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883645&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883636&lt;br&gt;Everything that&amp;#x27;s been doing well, and that means not crypto, will keep doing very well until May. Then we get bust and people will rotate into treasuries and cash, ready to buy the next bottom. Watch and learn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883665&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883645&lt;br&gt;So I should buy the tippy top and sell in about 2 months? Are you fucking retarded?&lt;br&gt;Yeah I don&amp;#x27;t play chicken with assets, I DCA when there&amp;#x27;s fear and I sell when there&amp;#x27;s greed.&lt;br&gt;Once again, not buying your bags, nigger.&lt;br&gt;Sold my silver @103 as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883782&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883631&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;like AI&lt;br&gt;buying ai here is about the most retarded investment strategy possible&lt;br&gt;ai credit is cracking all over the place and the mag 7 are going to spend 90% of their revenue on capex this year&lt;br&gt;who is left to incinerate trillions of dollars now, we are about to hit the minsky moment on the ai build out&lt;br&gt;considering the regular economy isnt doing too badly might not even be bad for other assets as the retarded overspend on infrastructure build out is curtailed&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;and also this isnt even touching on the rather hard physical limits that even if they keep exponentially building more datacenters there doesnt exist the electricity surplus to actually turn the things on&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883866&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The value of a company is based on its ability to split its profits between its owners, aka shareholders.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What is the value of Bitcoin based on?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61883974&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880718&lt;br&gt;Brics, Banks and Billionaires only buying one thing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884007&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883866&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The value of a company is based on its ability to split its profits between its owners, aka shareholders.&lt;br&gt;lol.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884025&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880718&lt;br&gt;Did crypto ever have life in the first place? When you consider the (((forces))) at play behind normalizing CBDCs and tokenization of everything - the entire crypto concept becomes just another homosexual ponzi used to control people, track their purchases, and control their rates in order to reward the good goyim, and punish the bad. Unbacked digital tokens on a screen never had any value to begin with. Some people still think the jew.s. dollar has value even though it is literally unbacked and printable monopoly game board paper. It&amp;#x27;s &amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;VALUE&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot; comes from the jew.s. AIPAC government forcing its usage through tyranny and semitic organizations like the FED. Unbacked paper that the state prints could never be an actual wealth instrument, just fake currency for a fake economy in a fake two-party &amp;quot;&amp;quot;democratic&amp;quot;&amp;quot; nation. Press S to spit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885137&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61883631&lt;br&gt;What if I am doing the same thing that always worked and expecting the same result too? Buying assets that &amp;quot;have momentum&amp;quot; is just a different way to say you&amp;#x27;re buying tops, it&amp;#x27;s a retarded strategy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886530&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880718&lt;br&gt;If you didn&amp;#x27;t make it in 2021 or 2017 you are ngmi&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crypto needs a major flush out reset or its cooked for good this time. I have never been more bearish for the future of crypto.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888075&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880718&lt;br&gt;If you are buying alts at this point then you are foolish and deserve to die poor. Go all in on BTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888148&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881059&lt;br&gt;Alts saw no bull run desu, BTC on the other hand pump over 5X. Its a smart choice to go for BTC in case this will happen again. I see a lot of anons are into staking now and that&amp;#x27;s a good sign for long term holding&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889468&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here&amp;#x27;s the chart of the tulip bubble. Hope it helps you bros out. Unfortunately, unlike tulips which grow on solar power and have their own solar cells, your Bitsteins need electricity too, which of course is not distributed. Have fun!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891527&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888148&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Alts saw no bull run desu, BTC on the other hand pump over 5X. Its a smart choice to go for BTC in case this will happen again.&lt;br&gt;Logic?&lt;br&gt;What if next time alts get a run and btc doesn&amp;#x27;t?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891540&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61881059&lt;br&gt;This&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;But the bottom might not be in so just take it slow and DCA. BTC takes the escallater up and the elevator down so there&amp;#x27;s always time to accumulate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891605&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61880718&lt;br&gt;I voted for this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Buy Gold ASAP and stay away from Silver. — 25 replies — 100.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890123</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890123?lm=1771869508</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 17:58:28 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Buy Gold ASAP and stay away from Silver.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890123'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 25 • Updated: 2026-02-23 17:58 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gold will skyrocket when Trump bombs Iran.&lt;br&gt;Kikes and Glowies advertising the silver scam.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890127&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890123&lt;br&gt;Begone jew&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890130&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890123&lt;br&gt;You must be a zogbot trying to keep the goyim away from holding silver which is an essential component of milspec electronics, batteries, radars, primary explosives and so on. There&amp;#x27;s approximately 500 ounces of silver in every tomahawk cruise missile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890139&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890123&lt;br&gt;There are 90 tonnes of silver in a blackhawk tank you filthy jew!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890143&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890127&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890130&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Silver has no real value because it can be corroded.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;There&amp;#x27;s no central bank around the world who buys silver. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KKKXVTZAk9s&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890147&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890127&lt;br&gt;Love this execution tool that killed the criminal Jew. Christianity is a Jewish psyop&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890156&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890147&lt;br&gt;Another jew&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890159&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890147&lt;br&gt;Its the real world™, everything is a jewish psyop.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890169&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890147&lt;br&gt;best post&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890273&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890143&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;There&amp;#x27;s no central bank around the world who buys silver.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890280&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890273&lt;br&gt;All of that metal that should be used for electronics, stored in vaults because jews are retarded dwarven larping faggots.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890289&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890273&lt;br&gt;those are chicken eggs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890290&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890123&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;buy the generational top&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890293&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890290&lt;br&gt;the return to normal of the gen top.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890304&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890273&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;There&amp;#x27;s no central bank around the world who buys silver.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is how Gold is stored in Russia.&lt;br&gt;I hope you understand the difference.&lt;br&gt;Silver is a shitty common metal that can be easily found.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890403&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890273&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;pallets &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;No way this is actually Russian&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890408&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They are both going to go up this year. Gold because it has always been a hedge against geo-political instability and de-dollarisation, and silver because it is so obviously being suppressed and is running out of supply in March. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m in gold personally as it&amp;#x27;s less volatile, I don&amp;#x27;t want to deal with the stress of silver.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890455&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Please buy chinks and ivans same asset re-leveraged ponzi bag to make line go up so the collateral doesnt devalue&lt;br&gt;niet. Russia is going to lose 75% of its population, china likely up to 90%. Enjoy the cannibalism&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890470&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890123&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890581&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;OP destroyed in one image&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890792&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890143&lt;br&gt;retard&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890810&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890143&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;because it can be corroded&lt;br&gt;That&amp;#x27;s just wrong. Silver doesn&amp;#x27;t corrode.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890911&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890810&lt;br&gt;it can if it remain for a very long time (at least few centuries) in seawater. Silver is chalcophile while gold is siderophile (like all platinum group metals). Silver doesn&amp;#x27;t react much to anything, but still more than gold, who react to nothing but aqua regia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890992&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890911&lt;br&gt;all seawater does is darken silver with tarnish. it is easily cleaned&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891160&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890169&lt;br&gt;I wonder what you think this chart means. It&amp;#x27;s well established that only evangelical Christians recognize the Jews as being responsible for the execution of the Messiah&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891602&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wait so precious metals is just a bunch of mentally ill people calling each other jews?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>European funds for an american — 18 replies — 72.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890472</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890472?lm=1771869678</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 18:01:18 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;European funds for an american&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890472'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 18 • Updated: 2026-02-23 18:01 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;I want to put 20% of my account in foreign, but not all foreign is created equal. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I predicted the rise in the polish economy. It&amp;#x27;s very simple, a homogenous white country free from communism is always going to become rich. A diverse country full of communists like Canada and South Africa is going to get worse and worse. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I also predicted that the real-estate market in Croatia would sky rocket due to whites fleeing countries like the UK. I was right. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;So.... are there any good mutual/index funds that target the white regions of Europe, that an American can invest in? Is there a Balkans fund? A Baltic fund? Norway/Finland fund (not Sweden or Denmark)? I do not want to invest in the UK, France, Germany, or Spain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890485&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;finland&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;white&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890499&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;please buy my bag&lt;br&gt;nein. Death to every communist, that includes every single member of a political party, everyone over 50, every bureaucrat and every single subsidized &amp;quot;private&amp;quot; which in europe is every company.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890518&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No fucking way those numbers on finland are right. I live in Helsinki and it’s like 25% brown.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890524&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890472&lt;br&gt;You are correct about Poland but everybody knew and knows about Poland but nobody wants to talk about why they&amp;#x27;ve been the hottest economy in Europe for 15 years (white and Christian).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anyway. You&amp;#x27;ve never heard of EPOL?&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;ve owned the Polish index tracker ETFs for 8 years and it has done nicely.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Otherwise, Baltics do have stock markets but they are Frontier markets (this is below emerging markets) and you basically can&amp;#x27;t buy them if you&amp;#x27;re not in the country.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Norway invests in U.S. stocks. So does Sweden and their banks. Hottest Swedish bank stock is 100% invested in NYSE traded companies. So it&amp;#x27;s circular. If you invest in European banks or Norway you&amp;#x27;re actually buying U.S. stocks with extra steps. EPOL is heavily weighted towards Polish banks and you guessed it - they all hold U.S. company stocks.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;European Bank customers are just a source of capital to invest in the New York Stock Exchange. And I&amp;#x27;m an insider so I know.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you want an actual good EU based investment buy WDEF. European defense spending will be hot for 15 years. Otherwise buy Spotify and the upcoming revolut IPO.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890543&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890524&lt;br&gt;Any funds for manufacturing from the regions I mentioned in the OP, or medical services?&lt;br&gt;Medical services will always be the last to go even under socialism since Europeans will bankrupt their country with debt before they let a hospital go bankrupt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890855&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890543&lt;br&gt;You clearly don&amp;#x27;t understand the region. You&amp;#x27;re way out of your depth and element. I&amp;#x27;m sorry but it would take me hours to explain this to you.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;t. American in Latvia who knows Poland pretty well (dated a Polish chick and been there many times).&lt;br&gt;You assume Eastern Europe has the economic model of America or Germany, just poorer and white. You&amp;#x27;re way off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890868&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890472&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;France &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;85%&lt;br&gt;lmaoooo&lt;br&gt;this is the 1972 census?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890982&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890524&lt;br&gt;This map is from 10 or 15 years ago, it&amp;#x27;s actually changing rapidly now. Im from a small town and back then i haven&amp;#x27;t ever saw any foreign looking face apart from an occasional gypsy. Now we have filipino, indian, and central asian &amp;quot;guest&amp;quot; workers coming here to the middle of nowhere.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890989&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890868&lt;br&gt;France is pretty much 100% white outside of Paris and the south&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891003&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890989&lt;br&gt;not at all. Even the smallest, most remote villages are chokefull of shitskins. There isn&amp;#x27;t a single STREET in the countryside not populated with at least 2-3 shitskins/niggers.&lt;br&gt;I know becuz i live in one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891134&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890472&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;a homogenous white country free from communism&lt;br&gt;not Sweden&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891154&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890855&lt;br&gt;I have friends who moved to Croatia. Reason? White flight from the UK. Highly productive middle class white people pouring out of one area and into another, means good things for one economy and bad things for the other. It&amp;#x27;s no different than watching the small cities that surround Akron, Cleveland, Chicago, Detroit, Oakland, Baltimore, etc... All get richer and richer and have better and better economies due to all of the whites in those cities pouring out into the surrounding areas. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You say it&amp;#x27;s not that simple, yet I&amp;#x27;ve told people this will happen and for 30 years, I&amp;#x27;ve been right. I watched the real estate market in Croatia skyrocket into the stratosphere. I&amp;#x27;ve also made a lot of money on real-estate outside of Cleveland and Akron just by investing in the white flight destinations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891164&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890868&lt;br&gt;This is in fact, old data. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891134&lt;br&gt;Yes. That&amp;#x27;s why I said funds that invest in Norway and Finland, but not Denmark and Sweden. I know Finland isn&amp;#x27;t really Nordic but they&amp;#x27;re next door.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891236&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891154&lt;br&gt;That&amp;#x27;s fine but from the average person&amp;#x27;s perspective you can&amp;#x27;t understand the bigger economic picture and appreciate the vast differences in market size and capital flows.&lt;br&gt;Life for average people may be more or less similar in Croatia and England but the English stock exchange is in another universe compared to these small economies.&lt;br&gt;As I said, I&amp;#x27;m an American living in Latvia. My life is better in Latvia. I&amp;#x27;m just a normal guy. The top 1% and .01% would see things quite differently. Where does one park $100,000,000 in the Baltics?&lt;br&gt;Answer: you don&amp;#x27;t. And downstream from that is YOU don&amp;#x27;t get to invest $50,000 in an Estonia market ETF either. These are frontier markets not even as developed as Brazil or India.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891243&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891003&lt;br&gt;Euskadi&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891374&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891236&lt;br&gt;I think real-estate, and downstream from that medical services, are pretty simple by and large because they&amp;#x27;re mostly just a matter of predicting the migration patterns of middle class white people, while avoiding the political behavior of lumpenprole voters. At a bare minimum investing in medical services and realestate are a safe bet in any communist free white flight destination. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Question then becomes, what financial products are available to me that resemble that in any way. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;There&amp;#x27;s a fund called NHCBHFFT that invests in real estate in estonia, for example.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891396&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890472&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I do not want to invest in the UK&lt;br&gt;FTSE100 has been outperforming the S&amp;amp;P500 for a while now but okay&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891622&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891396&lt;br&gt;I want a stock that will perform well long term, the UK, like Canada and South Africa, has not future unless it claws it&amp;#x27;s way back from Weimar conditions. The massive white flight that has already taken place and has been accelerating, looks exactly how things looked for Detroit, Chicago, Oakland, Baltimore, etc... &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ghettofication is an economy killer. Because people ignore it and it makes people irrational, that is the area an investor can exploit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>theyre STILL buying this — 22 replies — 61.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889884</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889884?lm=1771868943</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 17:49:03 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;theyre STILL buying this&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889884'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 22 • Updated: 2026-02-23 17:49 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;theyre STILL buying this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889888&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;un &lt;br&gt;fucking &lt;br&gt;believable&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889891&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;this is the biggest crime and scam EVER HOW THE FUCK IS IT AT 240 HOW DO THEY KEEP DOING THIS&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 1MIN CANDLE ON SPOT IS 400K$ VOLUME AND ON PERPS ITS FUCKING 10M$&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889892&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;how CAN IT BE PROFITABLE who the FUCK BUYS THIS???????????????&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889894&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;first it goes from FUCKING 180 TO FUCKING 320 and it STILL WONT DIE!!!!!!!!!!!!!!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I CANNOT BELIEVE THIS PIECE OF MOSSAD SHIT&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889895&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889892&lt;br&gt;Israel spambots&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889899&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889895&lt;br&gt;its FUCKING UNBELIEVABLE how the fuck can this work. the only way is by controlling the CEX its binance and mossad together&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889904&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HOW THE FUCK IS THIS PIECE OF SHIT THE SAME PRICE AS FUKCKING YESTERIAIYDIYDYAIDYADYAI I FUCKING HATE YOU MOOSSAD NIGGERSIFJSOIHFJSOGJISGAEPJIRG UFUICCKOYU&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889906&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AND IM THE ONLY NIGGER ON THE INTERNET WHO NOTICES IT BECAUSE EVERYTHING IS SO FAKE AND GAY NOW THAT LITERALLY NOBODY REALIZES THE CRIMETHEFT GOING ON ON THIS FUCKING PIECE OF SHIT&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;FOR 4 &lt;br&gt;FUCKING&lt;br&gt;MONTHS&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;FOUR!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889910&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;un FUCKING BELIEVABLE theyre gonna FUCKIG PUMP IT 20% AGAIN AAAAAAAGOAEGOAUGOAUGOAEGJOAIJGOAJIGOAI&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889919&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;fucking unbelivable&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;who has infinite funds? HOW can this be profitable? HOW?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;they instalong with $10M then they start selling it for 2 days&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;SOMEHOW NOBODY sells&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;NOBODY sells it down&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;WHO THE FUCK KEEPS BUYING IT?????????????&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;biggest fucking crypto crime happening before every nigger&amp;#x27;s eyes. literally un fucking believable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889927&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UN FUCKING BELIEVABLEFUAOGFIAEGAGEATJAET4JWPY4JEWPRJEPRHJERHEK&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890004&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889899&lt;br&gt;u think so?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890005&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889919&lt;br&gt;the jews did 10/10&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890079&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890004&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890005&lt;br&gt;yeah fucking jews. still shorting it to 0&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890210&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889884&lt;br&gt;Step aside moneroboi, Vitalik himself converted all his ETH for ZEC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890218&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890210&lt;br&gt;Kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891335&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;un fuckingbelievable&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891486&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UN FUCKING BELIEVASBLUE&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;EVERYTHING AT THE BOTTOM OF ITS RANGE AND SOEHOW THIS FUCKING PIECE OF SHIT IS STILL AT 240&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2 FUCKING 40&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891502&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;thye LITERALLY ALWAYS KNOW WHAT THE MARKETS ARE GONNA DO A DAY IN ADVANCE HOW CAN THEY KEEP FUCKING DOING THIS FOR 4 MONTHS MAN&lt;br&gt;4 FUCKING MOPNTHS&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891514&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EVERYTHIGN LITERALLY EVERYTHING IS IN THIS RANGE EXCEPT THIS FKCCKIGSTOUSTHOUSUGSYGOUSGR4USR4UEI OHUDRHIDRHODRHIPIOITHPIREYEEYE5YE5YE5RYHEU5YUYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYY6RU6UU66666666666&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891523&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;howthe fUCK CAN THESE NIGGERS GET AWAY WITH THIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIS&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891533&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;who the FUCK DOESNT DUMPTHEIR FUCKING ZTRASH WHILE EVERYTHING DUMPS its BEYONDFYUCKING BELIEVABLE&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>I don't think BTC is how Satoshi described Bitcoin to be in 2008/9. — 8 replies — 32.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890488</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890488?lm=1771870074</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 18:07:54 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t think BTC is how Satoshi described Bitcoin to be in 2008/9.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890488'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 8 • Updated: 2026-02-23 18:07 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890544&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;you can&amp;#x27;t read c++&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890560&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890488&lt;br&gt;satoshi was kind of retarded about scaling, remember he actually envisioned that people were grinding hashes on their home CPU and be competitive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890570&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890488&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I don&amp;#x27;t think BTC is how Satoshi described Bitcoin to be in 2008/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was created as an alternative back then. A decentralized tool that cannot be sanctioned taxed or stolen by governments.&lt;br&gt;Until the Governments stepped in and convinced the people to start mining it and shorting it for them. Small miners were replaced by big corporations and venture capitals.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kikes are gifted. They always find ways to destroy good ideas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890647&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890488&lt;br&gt;Bitcoin doesn&amp;#x27;t even work that way, only difficulty scales not transaction rate. The fact the supposed creator would say something completely wrong about it shows it wasn&amp;#x27;t actually created by a single person but an organization consisting of individuals with varying levels of understanding of how it works&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890651&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890544&lt;br&gt;Don&amp;#x27;t need to unc, I have claude&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890835&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890651&lt;br&gt;claude will tell you that nothing has fundamentally changed &lt;br&gt;aside from the P2P hardfork and code cleanup&lt;br&gt;you probably don&amp;#x27;t even know that a 0.8 can still participate in the network &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890570&lt;br&gt;you don&amp;#x27;t even know what &amp;quot;decentralization&amp;quot; means, astroturf jew&lt;br&gt;you are blockchain illiterate&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890882&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890560&lt;br&gt;This, Bitcoin has evolved to becoming a kwh futures market backstopping the grid with 0 chance of a 51% attack. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890647&lt;br&gt;Even Hal Finney suggested Bitcoin banks to address scaling, but everyone has their own opinions and hybrid models. &lt;br&gt;What&amp;#x27;s more interesting than outdated blocksize drama is the op_return drama. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;There&amp;#x27;s a little civil war going on how big the op_return data field should be and what should be allowed in it. &lt;br&gt;Tether started on BTC only and now utilizes a few different chains &lt;br&gt;There are a bunch of projects arguing how much data should be allowed to be inscribed into the op_return field that is causing arguments in the community. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is because some op_return data is just garbage, but it has to be validated. &lt;br&gt;On the other hand some data in that field will open up a great deal of security for these projects to reference. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;So OP is a fag, but there are still arguments on how this project is going develop.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891661&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oh my, this thread attracted a lot of copers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Is this biz approved? — 8 replies — 29.6/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890765</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890765?lm=1771869270</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 17:54:30 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Is this biz approved?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61890765'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 8 • Updated: 2026-02-23 17:54 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;Making myself stand out in the freezing cold and pouring rain when I&amp;#x27;m too tired to study so I know how it feels to be homeless if I fail&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Should she instead play a violent pvp video game then take a nap to know how it feels to hurt evil people in a game and then be asleep for a really long time?&lt;br&gt;Should she instead message a random anonymous man through an encrypted messaging app and send him a couple hours worth of pics, videos and video calls doing whatever he requests of her so she knows how it feels to have an OF and be a camgirl?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890875&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890765&lt;br&gt;Women and social media were such a mistake, holy fucking shit why would anyone make a video like this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890903&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She should suck my dick behind a dumpster while I finger her asshole until I cum in her throat to know how it will feel to be a $20 street hooker when she NGMI&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890927&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890765&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;making myself listen to a woman talk for one entire minute when I&amp;#x27;m tired of looking at charts so I know how it feels to work for a female middle manager if I don&amp;#x27;t make it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890931&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890765&lt;br&gt;that particular approach seems retarded for sure.&lt;br&gt;but in general it&amp;#x27;s a good idea to think about what you want out of life, think about how you can reach it, and then simply work through that plan.&lt;br&gt;otherwise you end up aimlessly dicking around never really getting anywhere. look at how many cryptoshitters sat through their rise and peak all the way to the bottom again, because they didn&amp;#x27;t even have any clear goals for what target they want to hit.&lt;br&gt;it was always just &amp;quot;even more would be even nicer&amp;quot; and then &amp;quot;well, at least back to the prior ATH!&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890875&lt;br&gt;also this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890941&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890765&lt;br&gt;Being a woman in 2026 is so easy, simps will always elevate you, society revolves the legal system around you, and if all else fails you can do OnlyFans. The only requirement in life for a woman is not to be fat but even then there&amp;#x27;s a niche degenerate market for fat women.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891118&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890765&lt;br&gt;I knew it would be an indian.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891418&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891118&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891567&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891418&lt;br&gt;The Indian looks so masculine holy fuck&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>I just bought some LINK tokens. — 7 replies — 28.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891507</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891507?lm=1771869569</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 17:59:29 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;I just bought some LINK tokens.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891507'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 7 • Updated: 2026-02-23 17:59 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;I just bought some LINK tokens.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891546&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891507&lt;br&gt;ygmi&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891559&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891507&lt;br&gt;retard, it&amp;#x27;s going to $2&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891571&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891559&lt;br&gt;I think I&amp;#x27;m gonna be buying some each month this year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891575&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891507&lt;br&gt;interesting. do you waste your money often? is this a .. sexual fetish of yours?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891581&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891559&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m thinking $4 but yeah buying now isn&amp;#x27;t a good idea&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891593&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891507&lt;br&gt;Same. It feels like stealing at those prices.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891606&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891575&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;do you waste your money often?&lt;br&gt;I am a gay muslim actually.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>&gt;FIRE &gt;saving &gt;"options are gambling" &gt;savings account` &gt;HYSA &gt;properties &gt;real estate &gt;bonds &gt;dividend ETFs &gt;"branching… — 5 replies — 20.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891613</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891613?lm=1771870137</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 18:08:57 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;&amp;gt;FIRE &amp;gt;saving &amp;gt;&amp;quot;options are gambling&amp;quot; &amp;gt;savings account` &amp;gt;HYSA &amp;gt;properties &amp;gt;real estate &amp;gt;bonds &amp;gt;dividend ETFs &amp;gt;&amp;quot;branching…&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891613'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 5 • Updated: 2026-02-23 18:08 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;FIRE&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;saving&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;options are gambling&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;savings account`&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;HYSA&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;properties&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;real estate&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;bonds&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;dividend ETFs&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;branching out into other sectors&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;diversification&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Europe&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;The AI bubble&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;mortgage&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891626&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;So true oomfie&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891629&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;sucking cock&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891650&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891613&lt;br&gt;fuck i forgot a few obvious ones&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;stop loss&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;trailing stop loss&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;stop gain&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;time in the market beats timing the market&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891658&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891650&lt;br&gt;Ehhhmmmm last one&amp;#x27;s right doe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891672&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891613&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;K-shaped economy &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Immigration is good for the economy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Tether about to flip ETH — 4 replies — 16.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891508</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891508?lm=1771869669</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 18:01:09 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Tether about to flip ETH&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891508'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 4 • Updated: 2026-02-23 18:01 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tether about to flip ETH&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891513&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;crypto is dead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891538&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891513&lt;br&gt;Always was.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891611&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891513&lt;br&gt;Tether is also crypto, retard&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891620&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891611&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;custodial centralized stablecoin is heckin crypto&lt;br&gt;lol.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>trump in case you read this — 2 replies — 8.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891512</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891512?lm=1771869480</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 17:58:00 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;trump in case you read this&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61891512'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 2 • Updated: 2026-02-23 17:58 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;FUCK YOU UGLY FAT TRANNY !! I HOPE YOU GET SCARIFIED TO MOLOCH YOU FUCKING DICK SUCKER !!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891569&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891512&lt;br&gt;I voted for this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891598&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61891569&lt;br&gt;yes, but did you thank him yet?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;No additional replies in the latest window.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Financial independence / retire early — 38 replies — 152.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61884958</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61884958?lm=1771869427</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 17:57:07 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Financial independence / retire early&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61884958'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 38 • Updated: 2026-02-23 17:57 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;How&amp;#x27;s FIRE going for you, anons?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884964&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884958&lt;br&gt;Well I&amp;#x27;m looking into LCOL countries I can retire to because waiting until I&amp;#x27;m a multi millionaire in the states is not viable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884966&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884958&lt;br&gt;Just need a 7x then I&amp;#x27;m good. Already have rope if ready if I don&amp;#x27;t reach the goal in 5 years&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884967&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884958&lt;br&gt;i have about 3m networth but haven&amp;#x27;t quit my job yet. making too much money but want to quit real bad. i took a 4 day weekend recently and got bored because i have no life and hobbies because my job dominates my life and i have no energy left over to develop my personal life after work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884986&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884958&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m just living off NEETbux+savings. It doesn&amp;#x27;t completely cover rent, so once my savings are gone I&amp;#x27;m going to just KYS myself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884996&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884974&lt;br&gt;Interesting. I never thought of Japan as having a low cost of living. And I&amp;#x27;ve heard Thailand is not as cheap as it was.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61884999&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884976&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884986&lt;br&gt;I listened to a Grant Cardone video on YouTube about pulling IRA retirement money into self-directed fund then you can use it to buy real estate without getting the penalty but you have to go big and do multi-dwelling unit or else IRS flags you. I&amp;#x27;m too chicken shit to try it (yet) but if you&amp;#x27;re going to an hero anyway fuck it try it&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;pull life retirement savings&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;buy 10 unit apartment building&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;give self job fixing toilets&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;collect rent from tenants &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;profit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885003&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ok maybe a 3 unit building&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885030&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884999&lt;br&gt;You literally cannot fix the toilets yourself. Under IRC §4975 you are considered a &amp;quot;disqualified&amp;quot; person. Basically you can own it but you can never touch it. Very gay way to &amp;#x27;own&amp;#x27; something.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885054&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;way ahead of schedule.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Full time job income (104K + 11K in retirement)&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Cost of living 32K&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Fully owned apartment(450K)&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;308K in liquidish assets&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;90K in retirement&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;2K coming in every month from passive revenue from a side business (vidya gaems)&lt;br&gt;In 7-8 years i will probably reach full FIRE. But i&amp;#x27;m releasing new products this year. If i can have similar success i will probably just Barista FIRE living the gamedev dream.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885059&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884967&lt;br&gt;Dude, just quit. You&amp;#x27;ll probably decompress after a month or two, then you can re-evaluate. If you decide you need to work, then you can just go apply to some jobs. Maybe you&amp;#x27;ll decide you want to work in a library or something stupid like that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885062&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885030&lt;br&gt;that fucking sucks what is Cardone talking about then?&lt;br&gt;retirement money is just going to the bank then when I starve to death. maybe that was their plan all along. &lt;br&gt;take the 10% penalty + taxes ? now it&amp;#x27;s a duplex maybe in a cold flyover state&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885102&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just had my 2nd kid.&lt;br&gt;Already gave up and accepted that I&amp;#x27;ll be waging til I die.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885131&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884958&lt;br&gt;Pretty good despite the recent market drawdown. I stopped working 9 months ago and moved to a luxury condo in Thailand. Expenses are relatively low but I&amp;#x27;m still paying my mortgage and car note in America. I get a little bit of income from trading options and renting out my house to my younger sister. I&amp;#x27;m financially set for the rest of my life but I&amp;#x27;m still figuring out what I want to do as far as family, kids, etc.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885135&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885062&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885030&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884986&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;ok I found this. instead of self directed IRA to have to roll it into a business startup&lt;br&gt;so don&amp;#x27;t an hero yet &lt;br&gt;or put me down as your beneficiary first&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;https://www.bankrate.com/loans/small-business/what-are-robs/#:~:text=Key%20takeaways,penalties%20are%20associated%20with%20ROBS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885141&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884967&lt;br&gt;Nigger. Based on the 4% rule you can draw about 120k yearly off investments and statistically never run out of money. Wife and I retired early w/ Lite Fire. No debt. Last year our gross income was $55,000. We bought and sold a RV, Saw the Grand Canyon, Zion, Bryce Canyon, Rushmore. Took a 21 day cruise from west coast through Panama Canal, Cruised out of Florida for 3 weeks and hung out in Fort Lauderdale for 2. Did 2 more week in the Caribbean. Have a 20 day transatlantic cruise from NYC to Sicily booked with stops in 9 ports in April. Tons of midweek short trips seeing cool shit. Leaving work is an adjustment definitely but I have never been happier. See the world, meet people, always with an eye to relocation. Picrel is heading into Cartagena Columbia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885152&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884967&lt;br&gt;I was just like you before I decided to walk away. I call it &amp;quot;golden handcuffs&amp;quot; when a job pays so well that it makes you feel obligated to keep going even though you don&amp;#x27;t need the money. Your job feels like your identity but I promise you&amp;#x27;ll forget about it after you quit and find new hobbies and a gf.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887260&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884974&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884996&lt;br&gt;Japan is not a lcol area. Its cheaper compared to the west but not Thailand/Vietnam cheap. My plan is to live 90 days visa free there a year and live frugally elsewhere for the rest of the year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887270&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884958&lt;br&gt;Closing in on luxury fat FIRE thanks to gold/silver/oil/uranium. Fuck crypto.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887292&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t want to retire early, cuz id probably just be doing the same thing without getting paid for it, but i have enough money to be comfortable for now&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887302&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I am starting to realize the whole game plan of FIRE is just giving me reason to wake up in the morning, something to look forward to. I dont think I will really be that much happier once I achieve my dream of semi financial freedom.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887313&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887292&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;id probably just be doing the same thing without getting paid for it&lt;br&gt;Your job is your hobby? Congrats. What do you do?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887338&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s not really going.&lt;br&gt;Would take me getting my inheritance and buying the bottom of the next global market crash and riding the recovery wave with everything I can throw in during it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887601&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;uhh im 38. been retired since 32. probably unretiring soon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887625&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887313&lt;br&gt;gay prostitute&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890044&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887302&lt;br&gt;frugality is like a game, to see how little i can spend each month&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890071&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885054&lt;br&gt;what&amp;#x27;s your side business anon? reseller?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890085&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;is 1.5M too little to retire?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I round tripped 8 figs being greedy&lt;br&gt;its all i have left&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890089&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890085&lt;br&gt;depends where you live&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890151&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885102&lt;br&gt;My #2 is 4 months old now. Thanks to the fire-induced frugality I was able to reduce my hours for half a year by 10 hours a week which was priceless in itself. Will probably also wage forever but probably only 20 hours or so per week.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884958&lt;br&gt;We managed to pay off the house @32. other than that I only have 15k cash and 50k in the MSCI. &lt;br&gt;The plan was to retire @40 but unrealistic unless I win the lottery ( and I don&amp;#x27;t even play)&lt;br&gt;So yes full fire is impossible right now, but on the plus side: we need less than 2k/ month for a very comfortable life. &lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m converting a part of the house to a rental flat atm which should bring another 600 per month and allow for tax deductions.&lt;br&gt;After installing solar this year my electricity bill should drop from 110 to 40 per month. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;So all in all we can have a cozy lifestyle for an acceptable trade off in lifetime. &lt;br&gt;Wife would like to work 20 hours/week in 10 years or so, I should be able to fully switch to do freelance consultant work in my niche ( or not. Her meager wage combined with the surplus of the next 10 years should easily pay for everything and give the kids a nice tailwind) &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m putting 180 bucks/month per kind into an ETF which should become a nice 150k downpayment (infl.adj.) when they turn 27&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890181&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Never gonna happen on my income. Millennials are fucked out of retirement. At least I own all my shit and have actual children and a loyal wife.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890213&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I dont know what number to stop at..&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891226&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61884968&lt;br&gt;Balkan and Baltic countries are cheap and super white. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fuck off if you&amp;#x27;re not white though. They&amp;#x27;re the most racist countries and that&amp;#x27;s what makes them awesome.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891591&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885054&lt;br&gt;What games?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>KASPA — 37 replies — 55.7/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61885700</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61885700?lm=1771867851</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 17:30:51 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;KASPA&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61885700'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 37 • Updated: 2026-02-23 17:30 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;were gonna be so rich when Kaspa kicks off this season, rolling dubs for prime Jewess pussy that I will purchase with a few dozen Kaspa&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885703&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885700&lt;br&gt;kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885758&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rolling for kaspa jewssy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885760&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885700&lt;br&gt;Scamcoin that does nothing&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61885997&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;rollan&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886010&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;honestly i can live with that&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886492&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885766&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;fair launch no pre-mine&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;implying&lt;br&gt;I like KAS but the chain history is serious FUD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886517&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885700&lt;br&gt;Rolling for Yentapie&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61886691&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roll&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887123&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61886492&lt;br&gt;This is debunked 2021 FUD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887138&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885700&lt;br&gt;6 7 maybe 0 if Im drunk&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887379&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885700&lt;br&gt;0&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887403&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885700&lt;br&gt;9&amp;gt;7 whatever&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887409&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885700&lt;br&gt;i would fuck 9&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887450&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The all look dysgenic and possibly inbred, what&amp;#x27;s wrong with them?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887454&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887450&lt;br&gt;They&amp;#x27;re all Jewish&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887455&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885700&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;when Kaspa kicks off this season&lt;br&gt;which is when exactly?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887465&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887455&lt;br&gt;When all of retail have been completely rinsed and sold their bags. This week or next week&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887589&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885700&lt;br&gt;roll&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887591&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887589&lt;br&gt;LUCKYYY!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887799&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887123&lt;br&gt;Not according to Yonotan, who&amp;#x27;s answer is&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Kaspa full nodes verify only recent history, because the goal of Consensus is to reach Agreement, not to print a medal of historical aesthetic integrity that satisfies the aesthetic tastes of cryptographers with no tangible integrity value to speak of.&lt;br&gt;TL;DR stop noticing&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887812&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887799&lt;br&gt;So who got 52% and reorganised blocks then? Which wallets?&lt;br&gt;Dumb fag&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;TL;DR: block chains are vulnerable to 51% attacks Jeetish FUD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887838&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887812&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;why worry about something that isn&amp;#x27;t going to happen?&lt;br&gt;Fact is, there is no full chain history and the implications of that are still unknown. Maybe it&amp;#x27;s nothing, maybe it&amp;#x27;s going to be devastating in the future. We just don&amp;#x27;t know&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887853&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Honestly I like this shit. And I made money on it last year buying in hard at 5 cents and holding until 12 cents. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The tech is good - it’s magic to watch hard wallet confirmations happen instantly. The chart still looks painful though, but I’m actively considering starting to acquire again. It’s a spiffy first party wallet to be honest. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Any word on level 2 shit?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887873&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887799&lt;br&gt;Yonatan here, this is misleading.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kaspa supports archival nodes and pruned nodes. Bitcoin, Ethereum and most modern Blockchain also prune.&lt;br&gt;So this is not unique to Kaspa.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The most important distinction you need to realise is that pruning old block data does NOT mean skipping consensus verification. Nodes still validate consensus, enforce rules and track UTXO state. They just don&amp;#x27;t keep every ancient block at once.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61887902&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61887873&lt;br&gt;As we&amp;#x27;ve established, Mr Sompolinsky, it&amp;#x27;s not that the old blocks weren&amp;#x27;t kept; they were lost. And a great deal of work has been done to recover what has been lost, but not all of it has been recovered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888092&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If anyone of you are lurking, it’s quite clear /biz/ is JIDF headquarters. They think their jewish humor doesn’t glow. Death to Judaism and all of its followers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888189&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What do you guys think about Xelis?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888282&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885700&lt;br&gt;7 and maybe 0 if she’s a squirter&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888292&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885700&lt;br&gt;Rolan&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888770&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885700&lt;br&gt;9 is the only one I&amp;#x27;d have sex with.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889128&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885700&lt;br&gt;7 and 9, that&amp;#x27;s it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891242&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885700&lt;br&gt;shalom goyim&lt;br&gt;roll for 7,0 and dubs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891402&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61885700&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;ll take anything at this point...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>WHAT IS HAPPENING — 37 replies — 17.7/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61888550</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61888550?lm=1771862735</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 16:05:35 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;WHAT IS HAPPENING&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61888550'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 37 • Updated: 2026-02-23 16:05 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHAT IS HAPPENING&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888557&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888550&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;he still thinks being saylors exit liquidity is a smart hold&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888558&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bitcoin is going to zero, for real this time&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888570&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;is something happening in iran?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888644&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888570&lt;br&gt;Hot Muslim sex&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888664&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888570&lt;br&gt;mexico ol’ donnie trumpie is doing more distractions. el mencho is a cia mexican american plant&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888679&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;G A P E D &lt;br&gt;A&lt;br&gt;P&lt;br&gt;E&lt;br&gt;D&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888720&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maybe you should have got real money instead instead of 1s and 0s&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888727&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Finally... the real bottom...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888738&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;linkbtc needs to go down at any cost&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888756&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;WHAT IS HAPPENING&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Took a screenshot for you, fren. Your BitCorns are going to zero, fren. You fell for the digital casino scam for the zillionth time, fren.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888805&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888720&lt;br&gt;You don&amp;#x27;t understand&lt;br&gt;Bitcoin allows you to securely transfer ledger space associated with your wallet, to someone else&amp;#x27;s wallet&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888814&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888756&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;late sunday&lt;br&gt;chinks are dumping again&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888818&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888814&lt;br&gt;le chings aren&amp;#x27;t even awake yet you ree-ree&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888821&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888814&lt;br&gt;binance piss snake dump on the weekend during low liquidity&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888852&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888550&lt;br&gt;Going to Zero as we&amp;#x27;ve told you.&lt;br&gt;Then it will go to 750k and will go up forever 5-15% a year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888863&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;bitpoop status: GAPED + RAPED&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61888979&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888550&lt;br&gt;Trump hit the blockchain with the Discombobulator&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889033&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hope it goes to zero soon. This ponzi has lasted way too long.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889152&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889033&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;ponzi&lt;br&gt;You don&amp;#x27;t even know what that word means you dumb gook jeet&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889159&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889152&lt;br&gt;It is a ponzi&lt;br&gt;Bitcoin generates no revenue, produces nothing, has no unique properties that can&amp;#x27;t be perfectly cloned.&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s a fungible collectible, by definition&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889195&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888570&lt;br&gt;Based on supply and personnel movements they were definitely planning a full on invasion this week, but the interview with Huckabee might have ruined it. Now a lot of middle eastern allies are coming out of the woodwork opposing an invasion. Personally I think they will still go through with it today or tomorrow&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889201&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889159&lt;br&gt;But enough about gold.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889202&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889159&lt;br&gt;Even if true, still wouldn&amp;#x27;t make it a ponzi, brainlet&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889204&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889159&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;i use words i dont understand to describe things i dont like&lt;br&gt;good luck, anon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889245&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889201&lt;br&gt;Gold is an element of the universe, by definition it has unique properties &lt;br&gt;Bitcoin can be perfectly cloned in like 15 minutes, the reason the clone would be worth zero is because humans would think that other humans don&amp;#x27;t value it&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As far as what makes Bitcoin a ponzi, it&amp;#x27;s zerosum, there&amp;#x27;s no revenue, earnings, or use cases, yet people talk it up like it&amp;#x27;s an investment, because they know the price only goes up if new suckers get in.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889248&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889245&lt;br&gt;At this price I don&amp;#x27;t think whales even care if price goes up, they just need exit liquidity on the way down&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889250&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888550&lt;br&gt;I voted for this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889259&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888550&lt;br&gt;I also voted for this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889272&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888550&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;fkn 0&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;micro second&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;VR00M&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889327&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889245&lt;br&gt;Bitcoin is the relationship of currently existing btc miners running a shared protocol. You cant replicate that quickly. There has to be a huge amount of decentralized effort, it is in its nature to slowly emerge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889332&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888550&lt;br&gt;i wanted this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890940&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888550&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;NOONE KNOWS&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;CULTURES DON&amp;#x27;T EXIST&lt;br&gt;THE MASSES ABANDONED CILIZATION&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;PRESIDENTS BEING KILLED&lt;br&gt;PEOPLE BEING KILLED EN MASS&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;EVERYBODY IS RETARDED OR IMBECILE FAGGOT&lt;br&gt;EVERYBODY BELONGS TO SATANIC SECTS&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;EVERYBODY CAN BE KILLED WITH A LITERAL STONE IN HAND. THEY DON&amp;#x27;T EVEN KNOW HOW TO LIVE&lt;br&gt;ALL PEOPLE ARE FAKE!!!!&lt;br&gt;THEY SAY THIS CULTURE THAT CULTURE&lt;br&gt;ALL PEOPLE WHO SAID THEY BELONG TO SOME NATIONALITY CULTURAL NONSENSE COULD BE PROSECUTED!!!!! THEY PROBABLY WILL BE PROSECUTED ONLY MATTER OF TIME&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890959&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61888550&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m sorry retard, the Liquidity Leprechaun has spoken has your 01 memeshit is now worthless. Goodbye (no refunds).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>I sold. 4600 Stinkies, 14.8 ETH. thanks for nothing — 17 replies — 11.7/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889893</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889893?lm=1771865024</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 16:43:44 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;I sold. 4600 Stinkies, 14.8 ETH. thanks for nothing&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889893'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 17 • Updated: 2026-02-23 16:43 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;I sold. 4600 Stinkies, 14.8 ETH. thanks for nothing&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889901&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You are a traitor&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889903&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889893&lt;br&gt;ee sold?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889911&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889893&lt;br&gt;kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889912&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889893&lt;br&gt;Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889925&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889903&lt;br&gt;Literally this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889930&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889925&lt;br&gt;refinance where OP?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889939&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OP set us free&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889961&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889939&lt;br&gt;kek this guy :D &lt;br&gt;reallife wojak&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889983&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I CANT FEEEEEEEEL&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;THE WAY I DID BEFORE&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;TIME WONT HEAAAALL&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;THIS DAMAGE ANYMORE&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889985&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889983&lt;br&gt;You were the only real trader left. We all were waiting for you to sell and now we pump it unitl you fomo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889988&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889983&lt;br&gt;nigger big jew banks predicting 10k btc in tumor weeks™ and u selled?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889994&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889983&lt;br&gt;didnt see those jewtube spams here in the past 4 days about how fucking over for beetkoin and it will never go back up ever again? maybe even negative values in dollars? :D&lt;br&gt;always buy the retard 10iq nigger fud, dont capitulate it!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890002&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889985&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889988&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889994&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I lied. I sold my highest cost basis ETH buys (4.3 ETH total). I have a nice 10k realized loss hole for 2026, but I still think ETH and link make me whole by end of year. I’m expecting a false flag or full scale war with strike on Iran, millions of deaths. So I wanted to pull some out, contemplating selling some more but maybe we get a little fakeout pump. Im hoping to slurp some more if we get one less capitulation, if It runs and I miss out, I still got an ok bag. Also stay frosty for a grid down scenario. Best of luck anons&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890009&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890002&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890397&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890002&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I’m expecting a false flag or full scale war with strike on Iran, millions of deaths&lt;br&gt;wow such market asymmetric information and expectation, you are truly ahead of the curve am i rite lmao&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891057&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890002&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890009&lt;br&gt;He didnt solded?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891165&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889893&lt;br&gt;Puuump it. Thanks anon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Link vs XRP — 21 replies — 11.6/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889600</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889600?lm=1771863737</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 16:22:17 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Link vs XRP&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61889600'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 21 • Updated: 2026-02-23 16:22 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;When will the gap close? Link came within a hair of flipping xrp in January ‘21. We all know that Link is everything Xrp fraudulently claims to be so it makes sense that this chart should flip soon enough. Will it be gradual or violent? Will it flip because xrp crashes or because Link moons? &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most importantly where are some places you can use Link as collateral to borrow Xrp to take full advantage of the trade of the century?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889606&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m so tired.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889622&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889600&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889606&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889620&lt;br&gt;Link is scam&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Buy XRP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889634&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889606&lt;br&gt;Xrp is like chainlink if all the nightmares came true: no use case, no revenue, an ipo that formally cuts token holders out of the picture etc.. and we need over a 10x to reach their market cap. This fact always gives me energy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889799&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889634&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889823&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889600&lt;br&gt;It won&amp;#x27;t. Even RLUSD will pass link&amp;#x27;s marketcap in a matter of a few months.You invested poorly in a project with the only purpose of jewishly injecting fees for literally no reason and assuming people will allow you to entrench in core services. It is a bad financial and moral investment&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889827&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889634&lt;br&gt;XRP had no ICO. Link sells to retail at every pump and drains operator rewards it claimed it wouldn&amp;#x27;t. Link has literally zero use case outside arbitrary jewish rent seeking crypto toll boothing. It solves no problem and has no use outside ADDING frictions. XRP from Ripple alone has: &lt;br&gt;https://ripple.com/insights/institutional-defi-on-xrpl-scaling-real-world-finance-with-xrp-at-the-core/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61889841&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889600&lt;br&gt;not gonna happen, jews will reward retard boomers once again, they are the golden generation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890083&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889600&lt;br&gt;strongly believe 2026-2027, hopefully you&amp;#x27;re ready. won&amp;#x27;t be instant, but still swift. cant believe there are anons who actually think like this &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889827, i hope they dont disappear and comment a little longer so we can have fun with them. chainlink wont be the only crypto that will flip xrp either&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890125&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;xrp&lt;br&gt;BOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOM&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890250&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889827&lt;br&gt;always funny to see them gloating with their &amp;quot;MPT&amp;quot; and permissioned dex when literally all of that has been absolute standard and normal for the rest of crypto&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;XRP retards are even saying wrapped assets on their chain is something novel like lmao&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890307&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889600&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;We all know that Link is everything Xrp fraudulently claims to be&lt;br&gt;Since when did sergoy claim link was a bridge currency? &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The bigger issue you&amp;#x27;ll have saying it&amp;#x27;s &amp;quot;everything&amp;quot; XRP claims to be&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Is it a security or not? &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Which honestly give me an idea, which maybe will settle things in the USA. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Holding this piece of shit token + writing the previous statement out made me realize, we can probably class action chainlink and find out legally. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Is security or not? &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Has it or has it not been advertised as one?&lt;br&gt;Might be able to recover these -50% bags and get the SEC involved to settle things. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;No more waiting on the pool to open. No more cope on clarity act. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anyone willing to get this started?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890390&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;What AI thinks&lt;br&gt;Argument That LINK Is a Security&lt;br&gt;Under the Howey test (SEC v. W.J. Howey Co.), an asset is a security if there is:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;An investment of money&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;In a common enterprise&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;With a reasonable expectation of profit&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Derived from the efforts of others&lt;br&gt;LINK can arguably meet all four elements:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Investment of money: &lt;br&gt;People buy LINK with capital.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Common enterprise: &lt;br&gt;The value of LINK rises and falls with the success of the Chainlink ecosystem.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Expectation of profit: &lt;br&gt;Many buyers hold LINK expecting price appreciation, not immediate utility use.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Efforts of others: &lt;br&gt;The value of LINK depends significantly on the continued development, partnerships, and ecosystem growth driven by Chainlink Labs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additionally, the original token distribution helped fund development, which resembles capital formation typical of securities offerings.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thoughts anons? Is this class actionable?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890519&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889823&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889827&lt;br&gt;Oh hey I remember this deranged plebbit shitbag peddling cripple marketing material unironically&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;if you make fun of me or my fat jew goblin xrp shitcoin youre a LITERAL &amp;quot;pharisee&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;youre LITERALLY &amp;quot;abstracting&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;mirroring&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;xrp is LITERALLY a force of objective good guys, for real&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;xrp is gonna LITERALLY save the banks FROM usury &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I LITERALLY have no idea how swift fees work on a basic level and all of my hopium relies on my failure to comprehend this&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;muh LITERAL saudi prince&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890539&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biepum is in this very thread, seething at the standard.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;All and every progress regarding the &amp;#x27;&amp;#x27;flippening&amp;#x27;&amp;#x27; that they have been praying for can be found here&lt;br&gt;https://link-flip.alwaysbeshipp.ing/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;RLUSD will sooner overtake chainlinks mcap than chainlink xrp&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890828&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889600&lt;br&gt;It will be violent, and partly due to xrp crashing, but in no small part due to link pumping. Its going to happen after Clarity act + full staking release and neet nodes. So 2050 at this rate&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890840&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890828&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;dude, le clarity&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;le full staking&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;le neet nodes&lt;br&gt;never happening, sweetie&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890870&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889600&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889606&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889620&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889622&lt;br&gt;the only usecase any of these has is XLM; because africans are still trading phone minutes as currency and XLM is a reasonable replacement&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;XRP and LINK are complete LARPs that nobody even trusts&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;and i don&amp;#x27;t even give a shit about giving africans currency. but its literally the only thing your larp does in the physical world&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61890891&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61890390&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;common enterprise&lt;br&gt;You bought a product, not a share. Everything you just wrote proves this is a speculation and not an investment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891011&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889827&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;https://ripple.com/insights/institutional-defi-on-xrpl-scaling-real-world-finance-with-xrp-at-the-core/&lt;br&gt;You keep posting same article like its some kind of mic drop moment. As if linking it over and over suddenly turns it into undeniable proof. It doesn’t lol Youre taking a CEOs words at face value because you think hes personally invested in making you rich. Thats not how this works. CEOs promote their companies and his job is to literally sell you XRP.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61891035&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889600&lt;br&gt;Thanks spammy.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61889620&lt;br&gt;/thread&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>