<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>/biz/ Active (filtered, with replies)</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/</link><description>Filtered out: general, gme, bbbyq. OP + first 3 replies + last 30 replies.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:01:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Privacy Coins — 79 replies — 158.1/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61849447</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61849447?lm=1771414314</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:31:54 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Privacy Coins&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61849447'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 79 • Updated: 2026-02-18 11:31 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whether you like it or not, BTC is dying. Which way anons?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849481&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gold and silver.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849898&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849447&lt;br&gt;XMR as always. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849481&lt;br&gt;Acceptable but unusable for internet transactions and too easily stolen. Also makes smaller or spontaneous transactions harder unless the governments were to issue gold coins again and that would be bearish.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849958&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849447&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;BTC is a pedo coin&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;most used currency for CP is not however&lt;br&gt;quit the infighting, monegro.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864667&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864651&lt;br&gt;Nice try but having less than 1/3 of our ring size and no mitigations against multiple attacks that worked on our code base (the devs don&amp;#x27;t even know whether their code has the same flaws or not) means it is not sufficient as a privacy coin. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;picrel&lt;br&gt;Next time try something somebody actually said&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864677&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849898&lt;br&gt;why would that be bearish&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864683&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864677&lt;br&gt;The governments as they are currently don&amp;#x27;t want to embrace our freedom or even anything to our benefit. If they go back to gold coins there will be some catch. If the jew embraces something, try to move as far away from that as possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864708&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855597&lt;br&gt;BTCFi is giving it more use cases with Babylon leading the charge. And I think when we have more projects offering native BTC staking, then we will see the narrative go viral&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864866&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864667&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Try something somebody actually said&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;literally you on every general&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;almost you entirely&lt;br&gt;Cry me some diodes, clanker.&lt;br&gt;Nerva is here to stay.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864897&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864866&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Nerva is here to stay.&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t care if it stays as long as you stop smearing XMR and spamming our threads&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864948&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864897&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I don&amp;#x27;t care if it stays as long as you stop smearing XMR and spamming our threads&lt;br&gt;The only spammer is you, in both this thread and the xmr general. You came here to start shit and have done so in every privacy thread that has popped up. You also accuse everyone of being a poojeet and promoting nerva. Again, the only person promoting (xmr in your case) and causing a stink has been YOU. So fuck off back to your little monero hole, jeetbot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865014&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864948&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The only spammer is you,&lt;br&gt;I wish that were true but sadly the nervajeets constantly try to shit up our thread and this board. There&amp;#x27;s a reason all of these anti-Monero threads pop up when they lose the discussion in the general. Notice how quiet they&amp;#x27;ve become after &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860646 was posted. All of their anti-Monero arguments (which was the entire value proposition for nerva) are gone. Their questions they claim never were answered poofed up into air. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;You came here to start shit&lt;br&gt;OP literally accuses XMR of being some freemason bullshit. You&amp;#x27;re the perfect representation of the jew asking what harm he has done to us. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;You also accuse everyone of being a poojeet and promoting nerva.&lt;br&gt;No, I say that the ones that copy all of the points the nervajeets make to be a nervajeets. That&amp;#x27;s because the only people interested in nerva are jeets.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Please don&amp;#x27;t challenge me when I smear the only functional crypto currency please just go away I can&amp;#x27;t handle it please please please&lt;br&gt;No sar, you wish to talk about XMR? I&amp;#x27;ll be there and refute each on of your pathetic claims.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865161&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865014&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;bot&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865268&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862698&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862796&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864651&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864866&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865161&lt;br&gt;good morning nervasaaars&lt;br&gt;truly xnv is the most aryan bharatoken superior peer-to-poop privacy coin xnvsaars redeem asap&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865595&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865268&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;i cant stop sucking monero dick, am i gay enough yet? Somebody like me pleeease!!&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;Back to your xmr general faggot shill&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865847&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865268&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;nooo not my heckin fedcoin noo all other privacy coins are jeetcoins noooo&lt;br&gt;CryptoNight-Adaptive &amp;gt; RandomX for decentralization&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865956&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865869&lt;br&gt;Have you tried bumping your generel thread so it stays up like everyone else does&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866337&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865998&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;discord&lt;br&gt;very true sar discord is perfect for our poo privacy coin, better stay there, 4chan is an anti-indian glowie honeypot benchod site&lt;br&gt;btw ser remember to send your designated face scan/ID to discord for better compliance nervasaars&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866402&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849447&lt;br&gt;BTC died when it forked away from BCH (the Bitcoin) and broke from the design being an unbroken chain of hashes of digital signatures. That chain doesn&amp;#x27;t exist at all on BTC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866407&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866384&lt;br&gt;why so mad saar&lt;br&gt;the nerva discord isn&amp;#x27;t paying (you) enough to raid 4chan?&lt;br&gt;do not redeem the mod ban saar stop evading bans saar&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866671&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849447&lt;br&gt;they all go to zero if btc dies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866695&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866583&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866688&lt;br&gt;ChatGPT moment&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866728&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866712&lt;br&gt;Getting rugged by Zcash jews is one thing but imagine getting rugged by Nerva jeets I would kms lmao&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866805&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865124&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;go away monegro.&lt;br&gt;Stop talking about my coin and stop coming to my general and I will tolerate your kind&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;because they were never spamming up your threads in the first place you pathetic fucking loser.&lt;br&gt;We had this argument already. Over 40 pro-nerva posts in just the current XMR general. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;they were just asking questions&lt;br&gt;All of their questions were already answered, I asked them multiple times to ask any unanswered questions and it&amp;#x27;s been a few days since then. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;something anyone can do.&lt;br&gt;How come they never can answer my questions then? &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;your clearly the psychopath across every fucking one.&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;d rather be a psycho than a jeetcoin shill&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Non stop blogposts of text that do nothing but go in circles, and now youre doing it here. Save yourself some time and go shit up someone elses thread. Oh right, you cant, because youre a monegro botnet that works for monero glowies.&lt;br&gt;Or maybe stop smearing Monero and actually try to have some arguments? &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I started this thread to discuss privacy coins&lt;br&gt;Yeah, I always also start a discussion by posting schizo BS criticizing the only proven tool. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;all youve done is shit up my thread you piece of shit.&lt;br&gt;And you don&amp;#x27;t like it? Looks like I&amp;#x27;m justified in my behavior towards the jeets. Of course I am. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865161&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;picrel&lt;br&gt;See &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61809820 and &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860646 Your questions already have been answered. Please let me know if you have any other questions. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865595&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;re literally sucking off nerva and the current govt. The best part is that all of your arguments regarding epstein and monero are easily extrapolated towards nerva too. It wouldn&amp;#x27;t be too hard to invite your devs to the island considering 40% of them publicly dox themselves and the other ones use discord which always required PII to sign up. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865847&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;CryptoNight-Adaptive &amp;gt; RandomX for decentralization&lt;br&gt;How do you prevent CPUs being clustered locally? Furthermore, how do you plan to detect a 51% attack?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866813&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865869&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Nerva generals get took down immediately.&lt;br&gt;Your jeetcoin is just Monero but no dev work since 2018. It hasn&amp;#x27;t even been maintained. Literally all you do is shill your bags and all of this started because you got relisted by jews. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Your jewish glowcoin is gonna hit zero,&lt;br&gt;Oh I&amp;#x27;m sure all of the DNMs will switch from Monero to your unmaintained mess. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;All you do is advertise monero on here, yet you never get banned.&lt;br&gt;No, all I do is defend Monero against your retarded attacks. That&amp;#x27;s why I&amp;#x27;m always bringing up your fake arguments and refute them. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865998&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;No way a thread gets bumped off this board that fast.&lt;br&gt;Happened a few times with jeetcoin generals now. There&amp;#x27;s simply no interest in your little project. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Mods are afraid of it.&lt;br&gt;What&amp;#x27;s the dangerous part? The low ring size? The lack of development? The lack of any other feature? The ease with which one can 51% it? &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866373&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Yet the mods and XMR fags are the ones who started all this.&lt;br&gt;Just stay out of our general and don&amp;#x27;t smear us and your jeetcoin will be tolerated among the other scams that get posted on this board. Yes, you too can be as beloved as the cheese poster or that guy who posts something that looks like the Yen symbol but with an X. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866384&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;We totally don&amp;#x27;t know about this project&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Anyway I got the screenshot of the general from their discord and weirdly all of my arguments just come from there&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866583&lt;br&gt;Your jeetcoin got relisted. That&amp;#x27;s why some baggie started promoting it in the first place &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Nerva was just relisted (&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61747926)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866821&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866688&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;bitch about Nerva shills on XMR threads&lt;br&gt;Correct, stop pestering us&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;ban/delete whenever they make a Nerva general&lt;br&gt;No need to when they die after two hours anyway lol&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;leave countless shit threads untouched&lt;br&gt;Most shit threads don&amp;#x27;t just push indian coins&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;CPU-only alternative&lt;br&gt;Nigger, RandomX is CPU only. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Monero is the king today, nobody denies that&lt;br&gt;Then why shit on it always? Why even try to move away from it to a clearly inferior product in every metric? Why do you need some community in the first place? We have an economy we care about.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;A privacy movement that can’t tolerate parallel projects is already compromised.&lt;br&gt;So can you tolerate our general not existing to push your cowshit coin?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866961&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866885&lt;br&gt;1. Not up for us to decide&lt;br&gt;2. You already had your generals, they die out anyway and you still feel a need to infiltrate our generals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867018&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866805&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Stop talking about my coin and stop coming to my general and I will tolerate your kind&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;doesnt know where hes at or what hes doing, apparently&lt;br&gt;Also, I started this general and one of the jannies banned me. Why? ban these monegros.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867055&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867008&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;and this isnt a nerva thread and never was&lt;br&gt;Oh yeah OP just stole the picture from a nervajeet and pretends to be oblivious to it despite being in the general in which nerva had to be mentioned over 140 times already&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;They are shitting up other threads &lt;br&gt;We got inspired by you it seems. Maybe stop trying to psyop people regarding our coin.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;and advertising XMR, &lt;br&gt;We&amp;#x27;re refuting your FUD and asking you questions which you can never answer. That&amp;#x27;s because all you do is literally just put out ads for your jeetcoin&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;and abusing their cuck jannie powers to ban people who disagree with them, then his little buddy starts asking me to &amp;quot;stop evading bans&amp;quot; and pretending theyre not deleting actual nerva threads.&lt;br&gt;How about the generals that don&amp;#x27;t get deleted and then die from your community consisting solely of five jeets?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;They started it the day they took a shit on someone asking about nerva and have been shitting up every non monero thread since.&lt;br&gt;Funny thing to say when nerva jeets admit to being in multiple threads not related to nerva and even pol to promote their cowshit coin&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Im sick of seeing them shit everywhere every time a privacy coin thread pops up.&lt;br&gt;Stop spreading FUD&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Either remove the XMR general for advertising,&lt;br&gt;It isn&amp;#x27;t. It&amp;#x27;s refuting your claims. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;leave privacy threads and nerva threads/anons alone.&lt;br&gt;Your kind infiltrated our thread. You are supposed to leave us alone. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867018&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;doesnt know where hes at or what hes doing, apparently&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;m in the thread that just spreads fud about Monero from the very beginning.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Why?&lt;br&gt;Because you&amp;#x27;re an obvious nervajeet that spreads FUD so his bags get bought.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867250&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867201&lt;br&gt;They are just asking questions chud!!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867425&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867384&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;, you all didnt even post a response to the view key fud thats even worth a damn till yesterday&lt;br&gt;Check out &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61761926. What&amp;#x27;s worse is that, your cohort started with the questions from reddit but the post you mentioned had the answer THREE YEARS AGO. &lt;br&gt;Your question had been answered THREE YEARS before you even posed it. On the platform you all preferred. Have any of you gone back and said something like &amp;#x27;Thanks for telling me about this&amp;#x27; or &amp;#x27;Well this eases my mind&amp;#x27; or &amp;#x27;Guess I was wrong&amp;#x27;? Of course not. You attached yourself to FUD so you can shill your bags. If you all cared you could&amp;#x27;ve easily done the research anon did.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867720&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867695&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;We just have questions&lt;br&gt;Which ones? If they are not new, they&amp;#x27;ve been answered already, likely even three years ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868264&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867425&lt;br&gt;Deleted my post again, Monegro? What are you afraid of?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It took you a full month to find that 3 year old post, kek. Good luck serving your nerva overlords faggot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869544&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849447&lt;br&gt;BSV. Bitcoin already solved this.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just don&amp;#x27;t reuse addresses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>&gt;YOU NEED 5 YEARS OF EXPERIENCE TO DO THIS JOB, PLUS A DEGREE IN IT WITH A SUB DEGREE IN PLUMBING BECAUSE IT'S AN IT PLU… — 13 replies — 52.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61867692</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61867692?lm=1771415574</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:52:54 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;&amp;gt;YOU NEED 5 YEARS OF EXPERIENCE TO DO THIS JOB, PLUS A DEGREE IN IT WITH A SUB DEGREE IN PLUMBING BECAUSE IT&amp;#x27;S AN IT PLU…&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61867692'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 13 • Updated: 2026-02-18 11:52 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;YOU NEED 5 YEARS OF EXPERIENCE TO DO THIS JOB, PLUS A DEGREE IN IT WITH A SUB DEGREE IN PLUMBING BECAUSE IT&amp;#x27;S AN IT PLUMBING MANAGEMENT JOB OR SOMETHING, PLUS YOU NEED AT LEAST A PUBLIC TRUST CLEARANCE AND A CERTIFICATE OF BLOWJOBOLOGY AND IT&amp;#x27;S A 2 HOUR COMMUTE&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;salary range- 50k to 60k a year&lt;br&gt;My last job was picking boxes up and putting them in trucks and I made 28 dollars an hour.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867711&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pretty much in the same boat, also I have a math degree and knowledge of CS and IT. I&amp;#x27;ve been meeting more and more people like this and am just wondering when things will collapse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867712&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867692&lt;br&gt;that&amp;#x27;s pretty good for a warehouse job. i worked in a rite aid warehouse in 2016 and made $12/hour.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867729&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Credentialism is a fucking scourge. Any retard with two brain cells could do 90% of jobs out there. HR roasties will get the wall someday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867820&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867711&lt;br&gt;Based. Me too brother, math degree and all. Im gonna go fight wildfires, teach English, then go to grad school until things right themselves or collapse&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867895&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867692&lt;br&gt;The job market is for women. They&amp;#x27;ll have double degrees in sociology and psychology and will be promoted to managervafter 2 months.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What&amp;#x27;s this, another cis male applying? Don&amp;#x27;t he know the board of directors are 6/10 males, we don&amp;#x27;t need an over privileged man.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867906&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867820&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Nigger with a math degree teaching English &lt;br&gt;Those kids are gonna learn esl grade shit English. And wildfires will get worse No wonder the country is FUCKED&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867913&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;do you speak Spanish&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869390&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867692&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;PLUS A DEGREE IN IT WITH A SUB DEGREE IN PLUMBING BECAUSE IT&amp;#x27;S AN IT PLUMBING MANAGEMENT JOB&lt;br&gt;Real.&lt;br&gt;Went to an interview for an IT position once and they wanted someone with construction experience and qualifications because it was a construction company....I didn&amp;#x27;t even know how to respond to them that the guy who would be remoting onto your computer to install some software or something doesn&amp;#x27;t need to know how to lay bricks or whatever they were expecting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869393&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869390&lt;br&gt;They wanted a cheap Indian, sorry&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869565&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867692&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;My last job was picking boxes up and putting them in trucks and I made 28 dollars an hour.&lt;br&gt;Warehouse jobs are only tolerable if you like who you work with &amp;amp; can fuck around. Office jobs are soulcrushing though regardless&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869577&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Good thing I&amp;#x27;m not tied to any of these anti zoomer tactics&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869578&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867913&lt;br&gt;Sorry for the autism but why did he get black dancers? Puerto Rico is like 60% european ancestry (primarily from spain but also from portugal) and I can almost guarantee those black girls dancing are not Puerto Rican, probably Dominican or Haitian or some shit. If he wanted to promote his culture why did he not use actual Puerto Rican women?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869583&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869390&lt;br&gt;Can relate. It&amp;#x27;s 2026 and when trying to work for an IT position in a healthcare related business they seriously asked me if I am covid vaccinated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>&gt;be me, a mid-30s senior manager in a successful global corporation &gt;read The Economist, have one outdoorsy hobby, have… — 8 replies — 29.1/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61869454</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61869454?lm=1771415122</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:45:22 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;&amp;gt;be me, a mid-30s senior manager in a successful global corporation &amp;gt;read The Economist, have one outdoorsy hobby, have…&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61869454'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 8 • Updated: 2026-02-18 11:45 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;be me, a mid-30s senior manager in a successful global corporation&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;read The Economist, have one outdoorsy hobby, have wife and two kids and a shiny new house&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;new batch of employees recently started, with ages ranging from 21 to 25&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;we expect these graduates to be the future of the company&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I don&amp;#x27;t directly manage any of them but have oversight of all of them&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;a few months after I start I notice something concerning&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;90 % of top performers are women&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;all of the &amp;quot;needs improvement&amp;quot; employees are male&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;all the women have already become involved in valuable company voluntary activities like the Diversity, Equity, and Inclusion board, organising the team&amp;#x27;s end of financial year party, setting up mental health listening seminars&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;one female employee is even on the verge of arranging a famous journalist motivational speaker who specialises in reporting on dictatorships such as Iran, Russia, or Hungary&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;male employees do nothing extra&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;have been getting reports on a few employees, all male, about them mumbling, not speaking clearly, not networking enough with other business areas&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;scheduled lunch with one of them and asked him where he wanted to be in 5 years&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;couldn&amp;#x27;t give me a good, clear, precise answer&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;asked same question to our top female new employee&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;I intend to be the leader in emerging market widget supply chain analytics and to have mentored at least 5 under-represented BAME employees to promotions per year, in addition to...&amp;quot; (you get the picture, I had to recommend her for a promotion)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;When I ask HR about which employees aren&amp;#x27;t quite team players, invariably it&amp;#x27;s the male employees that don&amp;#x27;t measure up. The HR lead even had to write up one of the employees because he made some wisecrack about &amp;quot;too many pointless meetings&amp;quot;!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;But the WORST thing is that ALL the male employees take up remote working as an option if they can... while NONE of the females do this.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Guys, what&amp;#x27;s the deal?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869473&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869454&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;valuable company voluntary activities&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;valuable&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869476&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869454&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869473&lt;br&gt;ALSO, gr8 b8 m8&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869483&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Believable bait other than&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;all the women have already become involved in valuable company voluntary activities like the Diversity, Equity, and Inclusion board, organising the team&amp;#x27;s end of financial year party, setting up mental health listening seminars&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you&amp;#x27;re going to refuse to play just because your difficulty is set to hard mode, don&amp;#x27;t be surprised when you lose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869491&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869454&lt;br&gt;You need to invite these guys for a couple beers, pull up an 8 ball and the pieces will fall into place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869539&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869454&lt;br&gt;men that seek out these sorts of jobs are losers to begin with. day to day work is so far removed and watered down into microtasks that it looses view and connection to its purpose/function/benefit to individual lives and therefore society as a whole. Real men with real motivation and a drive for success seek out work that is tangible. Do A, Then Do B. Put A and B Together, It makes C. C makes a persons life better/easier/less stressful.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The men in your company don&amp;#x27;t see or understand the point of what you&amp;#x27;re all doing, and thats exactly why they are there. Because they want a job they don&amp;#x27;t have to care about that ideally also won&amp;#x27;t care about them. But their monkey brains get peeved about the pointless meetings because they aren&amp;#x27;t directly tackling issues, its organizing the organization of microtasks.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To make an example out of this: Here is a company that is trying to bake a cake.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Okay so step one, we need to whisk the eggs!&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;before we do that we need to clean the whisk.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;but where are we getting the cleaning supplies from?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;instead of going to the supermarket we need the highest quality cleaning supplies at the cheapest price&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;actually make sure its the best, cheapest cleaning supplies that are for whisks specifically&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;to figure that out we need someone to do research to compare different cleaning supplies for whisks&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;before we do that we need to make sure that the steel whisk we currently have is able to be cleaned and won&amp;#x27;t erode when we clean it&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Good morning Jerry, Happy Monday, Here&amp;#x27;s what we&amp;#x27;re going to get you to do for 3 weeks:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Do research on this specific type of steel as well as research on this cleaning liquid and find out all of the possible outcomes when these two materials make contact with eachother. Record your finding and present it to us by the end of the month WITH ENTHUSIASM OR ELSE YOU&amp;#x27;RE FUCKN SAKED.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Why should Jerry would give a fuck? He probably doesn&amp;#x27;t even know the company is trying to bake a cake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869547&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869454&lt;br&gt;Males are the obselete genre, they only want to live for simple staring at screens pleasure these days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869567&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869454&lt;br&gt;bro you&amp;#x27;re not observing some deep societal mystery&lt;br&gt;you&amp;#x27;re just describing the most predictable corporate midwit NPC behaviour pattern of the last 10 years&lt;br&gt;women figured out the actual game:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;suck up to HR&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;collect every extracurricular checkbox&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;memorise the corporate jargon salad&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;stay visible 24/7&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;never criticise anything out loud&lt;br&gt;men (especially autistic-leaning or just normal ones) are still playing the 2010 game:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;do good work&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;be competent&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;go home&lt;br&gt;and then get told they&amp;#x27;re &amp;quot;not team players&amp;quot; because they didn&amp;#x27;t spend 8 unpaid hours making a Canva slideshow about &amp;quot;allyship&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;you&amp;#x27;re not seeing female superiority&lt;br&gt;you&amp;#x27;re seeing who optimised hardest for the current midwit corporate signaling meta&lt;br&gt;and you&amp;#x27;re mad the men won&amp;#x27;t LARP as hard as the women&lt;br&gt;touch grass (your one outdoorsy hobby isn&amp;#x27;t enough apparently)&lt;br&gt;retard moron senior manager moment&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869571&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869454&lt;br&gt;all of this is a gay larp written by someone who has never had a job. (i am a late 30s senior manager at a fortune 20 company.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>I said LLMs are a non-intelligent mechanical confidence trick (con-man) and made a thread the other day saying the bubbl… — 6 replies — 12.5/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61869316</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61869316?lm=1771414391</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:33:11 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;I said LLMs are a non-intelligent mechanical confidence trick (con-man) and made a thread the other day saying the bubbl…&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61869316'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 6 • Updated: 2026-02-18 11:33 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;I said LLMs are a non-intelligent mechanical confidence trick (con-man) and made a thread the other day saying the bubble is already popping.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I realised I’ve made a huge mistake about AI. When I kept telling my imbecile manager that LLMs will never be more intelligent than us, I meant it’ll never be more intelligent than me. It’s already more intelligent than him. I forgot to put myself in his retarded shoes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This realisation matters because it’s also the case for the majority of money swinging the stock market on a daily basis. Most people are retarded.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;So I guess AI stocks surely have to double again until some semblance of financial reality finally has to set in. but right now we’ve got imbecile pajeet CEOs who spent their entire lives working on bullshit AI, who are determined to invest their entire company’s market cap into keeping the puppet show propped up for as long as possible for their own retarded ego.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Microsoft will do to OpenAI what MSTR is doing to bitcoin. Constant stock dilution, money borrowing way more than it can ever pay back, to invest in OpenAI. The show will almost never end until the global debt is in the sextrillions. The billions they&amp;#x27;ve invested so far is fucking nothing. They&amp;#x27;ll go right to the wire, and the retard-controlled stock market will cheer them on.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;And imbeciles will actively push microslop upwards ad-infinitum, believing that we&amp;#x27;re truly on the cusp of the singularity. Earnings don’t matter, the narrative is all that matters.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What a sick world we live in. Even Marx didn’t foresee capitalism becoming this chronically ill.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869324&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869316&lt;br&gt;What exactly is wrong with any of this?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869336&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869316&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;im smarter than ai&lt;br&gt;you barely even understand what it is. &lt;br&gt;you think you&amp;#x27;re smarter than it because chatgpt hallucinated to you once but this is like how reddit midwits think atheism is real and true even though it&amp;#x27;s self-evidently bullshit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869344&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869324&lt;br&gt;Because it ultimately ends in a government bailout where ordinary people are robbed and indebted forever to the people who caused it and benefitted from it. I didn&amp;#x27;t think I had to explain that part. AI is still bullshit, and it&amp;#x27;s still going to collapse, but not until it&amp;#x27;s completely exhausted all possible avenues of inflating the bubble. It has to suck up every single dollar in the entire universe, rehypothecate the same dollar 50 times over, until it simply can&amp;#x27;t go any further, then the government prints 100 sextillion dollars, adds it to the national debt, and imposes harsh austerity and taxation on ordinary people to finance it, combined with massive currency devaluation, and people lose their savings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869346&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869336&lt;br&gt;Belief AI can be intelligent and conscious, is the atheist tendency. Your logic is all backwards, because naturally, you are a retard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869348&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869346&lt;br&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Y4yBvvGi_2A&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NUeybwTMeWo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869548&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869348&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Doesn&amp;#x27;t even open the banana the way monkeys do. &lt;br&gt;They open them upside down, by squeezing the nib then tearing. Trust a retard not to know that. Your bananas are probably always mushy and shite because you spend ages wrestling the longer &amp;#x27;tab&amp;#x27;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;And obviously none of this shit is relevant, retard&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>When did you realize that you were NOT going to make it? — 97 replies — 388.0/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61862922</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61862922?lm=1771415579</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:52:59 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;When did you realize that you were NOT going to make it?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61862922'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 97 • Updated: 2026-02-18 11:52 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862935&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;is he ok&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862944&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862935&lt;br&gt;just some minor scratches (on his brain)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862956&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;the funniest part is that you think &amp;quot;maybe he survived the crash, just barely&amp;quot; but then it erupts in flames and he&amp;#x27;s cooked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866986&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866704&lt;br&gt;or just dont fucking ride a motorcycle. dumbest activity there is&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867265&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;when I failed CFA Level 2 exam for the 3rd time&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I realized it was only going to be normie life for me&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867318&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864646&lt;br&gt;I think Missouri still has red light cameras&lt;br&gt;one thing that got shut down were speeding cameras in Arizona. if they try to mail you a speeding ticket, do nothing because they&amp;#x27;re fake and gay&lt;br&gt;in my opinion&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867339&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864540&lt;br&gt;Very carefully&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867344&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864540&lt;br&gt;if he was going faster he would have passed before the car turned&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867496&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;The fuck was he doing on the shoulder in the first place? It&amp;#x27;s obvious a vehicle can cut in front of him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867614&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863947&lt;br&gt;Not a very good way to uplift and enlighten your brothers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867758&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863681&lt;br&gt;You do realize Epstein grew up in a working class family in brooklyn right? He is from &amp;quot;the real world&amp;quot;. He became a con artist to lift himself out of the lower class to &amp;quot;make it&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867767&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;Its not too late for me yet. But it will be if I continue on the same path I am on now. Idk though for some reason I just cant motivate myself to do the things I want to&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867775&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867758&lt;br&gt;He was a jew. Nothing they got away with was from the real world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867791&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865490&lt;br&gt;You have unmedicated schizophrenia&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867813&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863529&lt;br&gt;Eloquent. I blame the lack of religion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867833&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;could have just turned left a little and avoided everything&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867873&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867791&lt;br&gt;Prove it, you’re also a pseud who doesn’t know what that horrible condition even is and pltr should be valued at around 40.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867990&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863924&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;there are normies on this board who needed cnn to tell them that jews run the world through blackmail, rape and sacrifice kids to moloch, and all politicians are complicit&lt;br&gt;Holy Reddit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868013&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867990&lt;br&gt;schizos who believe in crazy shit that wasn&amp;#x27;t even alluded to in any email should be shot&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868016&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867990&lt;br&gt;I mean Im one of the people who have been saying it for years, but like everything in life, normies are too fucking dumb and sometimes need something like to find it out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868037&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864775&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;BIZ TOLD ME&lt;br&gt;ngmi lol&lt;br&gt;You need to go purely off drunken vibes and not whatever the biz consensus is. &lt;br&gt;Picrel and pick Chinese stocks at random.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868044&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868037&lt;br&gt;if Im going to drink piss, it&amp;#x27;s going to be piss from america.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868045&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;he was going for the stoppie to running man over the van&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868062&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868044&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;piss from america&lt;br&gt;Nation in decline = declining gainz. Its feng shui shit bro. The (Chinese) invisible hand rewards those with vibes.&lt;br&gt;Goyim are not allowed to succeed in westoid markets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868067&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868062&lt;br&gt;fuck chinks and jews&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868075&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868067&lt;br&gt;There is one winning side. Join it or fall behind :P&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868079&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863924&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;doomy ass topic&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;1 post by this fucking id&lt;br&gt;EVERY FUCKING TIME&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864699&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865901&lt;br&gt;Listen lads, your good faith is being trampled on and it be taking its toll on you in the background. I done replied to so many mfs in recent times and noticed shit takes a negative non fuel metabolizable physical impact on you. The 1 post mfs are an issue and are becoming one more and more as of late. Please guard your insights or reservations and make sure to check for signs of good faith in the post first and whether or not its a one post id second. Good luck out there&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869349&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862956&lt;br&gt;Well at least he didn&amp;#x27;t suffer did he?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869355&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863411&lt;br&gt;He was hothead enough to ride at those speeds, but not enough to do a last second evading maneuver. &lt;br&gt;In the end he acted like a normie, which is brake when things to wrong. Which works most of the time, but in a CAR.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869395&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863410&lt;br&gt;Stop posting those image all the time fagit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869422&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;drives in the emergency lane&lt;br&gt;bikenigger got what he deserved&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869527&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863253&lt;br&gt;Fucking hate people that turn like that. Like any sense of g-forces at all is completely unacceptable to feel. FUCKING GO!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869586&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61862922&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;When did you realize that you were NOT going to make it?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Define &amp;quot;Make it&amp;quot;.&lt;br&gt;Good wife, one son, over a million in my Roth IRA... did I &amp;#x27;make it&amp;#x27;?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Is it really that much more difficult to start a business in the eu than us? — 40 replies — 43.7/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860796</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860796?lm=1771412815</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:06:55 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Is it really that much more difficult to start a business in the eu than us?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860796'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 40 • Updated: 2026-02-18 11:06 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;You guys in the EU make less than us on paychecks, but you get to keep more of your money because you have universal healthcare and PTO while we have to pay for private insurance which chronically denies people&amp;#x27;s health situations. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Are people saying that starting a business in the EU is difficult because of the regulations? What regulations does the European union impose on its citizen&amp;#x27;s than they think it&amp;#x27;s easier to start in the United States instead?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860815&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;Depends enormously on which country are we talking about. Some are easy (Germany) some are very hard (Italy)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860817&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; you get to keep more of your money because you have universal healthcare&lt;br&gt;yeah right&lt;br&gt;good luck getting that &amp;quot;universal healthcare&amp;quot; if you&amp;#x27;re not a boomer, waiting lists are years for even a basic exam/procedure. It&amp;#x27;s either you go private (and pay out of your own pocket) or you die&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; and PTO&lt;br&gt;oh wow, 20 wagie cagie free days a year. Totally worth the 60%+ taxes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;All taxation is theft. It&amp;#x27;s just that. Taxation doesn&amp;#x27;t pay for services. It&amp;#x27;s just the way they control the economy, and here in EU they fucking LOVE to control what you can and cannot do. They print the money, they don&amp;#x27;t need to tax you. They tax you to control you (and to humiliate you)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860822&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;The healthcare thing is too much american leftie argument, it also has been very overcrowded by you guessed arabs and africans, unironically I was better treated when I broke my leg in brazil of all places then in france&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860967&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;in my country, the one thing one has to look out for is paying for your own social/healthinsurance, ie, if you have your own business, you need to pay taxes for your own health/socialinsurance, and the taxman wont ask you for the first 3y of that business.&lt;br&gt;After the 3y pass, you will then have to payup all the retrospective social insurance tax costs incurred, which fucks over a lot of retard or unfortunate first business owners&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861032&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860837&lt;br&gt;This is why we need a unified EU business regulation and undermind the corrupt sovereignist that want to keep individual burocratic fuckery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861057&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860815&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Some are easy (Germany)&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; some are very hard (Italy)&lt;br&gt;let me guess italian never tried germany?&lt;br&gt;Germany is known to be a bureucracy hellhole with people fleeing to other countries from it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861032&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;unified will fix it&lt;br&gt;France&amp;amp;germany have been dictating eu lawmaking. You will eat shit as you already do. You have eu wide higher taxes because germany didnt want to compete and made mandatory higher minimum vat a thing.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Not to mention that countries that joined got their industries destroyed by unified regulation and had to import from germany/france what they used to produce themself&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861071&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s the one thing the USA gets right. I personally made a &amp;quot;business&amp;quot; (that never made any profit) in the span of an afternoon. Cost maybe $200 to get my identification numbers for the llc&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861091&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861032&lt;br&gt;yeah let&amp;#x27;s give the EU bureaucrats more power that will fix it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861111&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Is it really that much more difficult to start a business in the eu than us?&lt;br&gt;Depends on the business. If you want to do something shady the US is the place to go. The US has barely any standards and barely any regulations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861113&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860817&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;waiting lists are years for even a basic exam/procedure&lt;br&gt;What are you talking about? I live currently in the EU and have never had to wait for medical care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861119&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Us is easier.&lt;br&gt;I have created 2 corpos and 1 llc for different purposes within the past 8 years. You can do it all online for a few bucks, other regulations depend on specific industry but overall it&amp;#x27;s pretty easy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861128&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860860&lt;br&gt;higher taxation alone puts euros at a disadvantage. Its fine if you do a local job since you compete with locals but anything online / shipped its bad since they have to be more efficient than rest of world to reach same profit margin.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As for amount of bureaucracy its fucking complex and depends on what country and what profession. There is even stupid shit like if you run a repair shop and repair inside your building it counts different than if you decide to drive to your customer and repair locally. In the later case they classify you as a handyman worker and will fine you if you didn&amp;#x27;t register with the craftsman ministry. Also if you do something you didn&amp;#x27;t register for you will also be fined but you can register as &amp;quot; i will do anything&amp;quot; more broadly and dodge it. The amount of bullshit can easily fill a book.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861429&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;Depends on what your goals are, the type of business, your personal goals and the markets you wish to enter. In general it&amp;#x27;s more of an investment in the long run but if you plan to offer your services or products in the EU anyway it makes sense to start your business here and already be compliant&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61861441&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860817&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;waiting lists are years for even a basic exam/procedure.&lt;br&gt;Yeah, I remember waiting decades for my appendicitis, it rupturing and me dying because of it. Thankfully they could keep me alive for months despite the extreme difficulties this poses. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861032&lt;br&gt;We need more unified European regulation. Sadly the EU is not an economic alliance anymore.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61862545&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860860&lt;br&gt;I love how hard it is to even talk about european economy on reddit, not because of europeans, but because of american lefties, if you so much, and most times you don&amp;#x27;t even need to, mention the US, they will flock like a horde to claim the US lies about everything, that 30% of americans are unemployed and nearly no one in europe, the EU is literal worker&amp;#x27;s paradise and how much they love their welfare policies and hate the US greed, its quite hilarious really how much they want a nanny state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865504&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is, soon it will was once EU Inc comes into play&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865623&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;you have universal healthcare&lt;br&gt;yea but you have to wait 1 year+ because there is a million niggers in queue before you&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865645&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861057&lt;br&gt;Lol this is true.&lt;br&gt;Germany and France made the EU suck with their shit like GDPR etc. Spain happily sniffs every turd. The rest aren&amp;#x27;t better.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866460&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If your efforts are starting to go anywhere, your own government will make sure, you won&amp;#x27;t get any further.&lt;br&gt;They hate nothing more than citizens that are not dependent on them. That&amp;#x27;s why they are allowing third world people in to the maximum extent physically possible, that are never going end up being a &amp;quot;plus&amp;quot; on the balance sheet, but that they hope will be cheap voting sheep for their party. The people pay for them after all, not the party.&lt;br&gt;Effectively: If Elon Musk was a citizen of a EU-country, he&amp;#x27;d already be in jail waiting for the sentence to be sent to prison. You probably don&amp;#x27;t want to get into that situation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866966&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865645&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Le GDPR sucks because uhm JUST LET ME HAVE YOUR DATA&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867520&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61861071&lt;br&gt;It’s also as easy in my country (Finland)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867536&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;you get to keep more money&lt;br&gt;Except they have to pay more in taxes to wait in line for months whole muslim refugees who didnt pay go before them kek. Europeans are so dumb its unreal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867540&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;italy here.&lt;br&gt;50% tax is ok ?&lt;br&gt;this is shITALY&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867547&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s literally impossible to build any meaningful sized company in Europe because the entire E.U. is designed to prevent anyone from competing with the aristocratic class and the privately held billion dollar company their great great grandfather built in 1870.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867554&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860842&lt;br&gt;YOU DON&amp;#x27;T KNOW WHAT YOU&amp;#x27;RE TALKING ABOUT&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867577&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Europe has no tech industry because German rich fags were afraid to pay coders more than traditional engineers because then car engineers would ask for more money so they just fucked all of Europe and let America and China run everything.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868041&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;No, in some places is actually easy, I remember playing a game in class one time in uni to look regulations for business worldwide, there&amp;#x27;s almost no difference whatsoever in european and american regulations, sometimes american regulations are actually worse and the accumulated taxes from city, state, federal can surpass european taxes. The only conclusion we could draw was that europeans were just lazy and too laidback, they have so much welfare that there&amp;#x27;s no rush or anxiety with ending up destitute and homeless so they just don&amp;#x27;t bother with the hazzle of building a business. They are better off just being on benefits or unemployed, most business there predate the big social welfare network just because of a need to survive really and complacency in changing what already works, they are much much better off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868110&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867547&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867577&lt;br&gt;that&amp;#x27;s bullshit but i believe it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868167&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867602&lt;br&gt;rip Sbarro&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868190&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868041&lt;br&gt;this is actually hilarious&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868222&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868190&lt;br&gt;Mostly sad, americans either are prosperous or starve&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869496&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868041&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;They are better off just being on benefits or unemployed&lt;br&gt;Can confirm, although it&amp;#x27;s currently also due to absolutely no one fucking hiring, because Germany is fucked beyond reasonable short-term hope.&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s also really troublesome to do any kind of work-like activities while on benefits, because that could easily cause the termination of those.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Fun fact: RLUSD only has a 4x smaller market cap than Chainlink — 18 replies — 39.4/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61866834</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61866834?lm=1771414470</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:34:30 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Fun fact: RLUSD only has a 4x smaller market cap than Chainlink&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61866834'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 18 • Updated: 2026-02-18 11:34 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Won&amp;#x27;t be long until RLUSD is also above Chainlink kek baggies what a humiliation ritual when XRP chads dab on you not once but two times looool&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866848&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;aw honey, you angry again?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866857&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866834&lt;br&gt;That requires people actually locking up their value onto XRPL directly instead of using ripple&amp;#x27;s ethereum virtual machine.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Which they won&amp;#x27;t.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866859&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866848&lt;br&gt;What kind of weird cope is this lmao &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866857&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s growing every day. You nervous there stinky?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866865&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866859&lt;br&gt;No, its just odd that ripple&amp;#x27;s XRPL chain has 1% of the total value with XRP&amp;#x27;s ethereum side chain. Especially since they have been around longer than LINK.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866867&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866834&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;file name&lt;br&gt;Thanks for stirring the pot spammy. Now we know you&amp;#x27;re the sole individual trying to create beef between XRP &amp;amp; LINK.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866872&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866867&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s not me i&amp;#x27;m someone else, i&amp;#x27;ve just saved this picture from another thread I saw earlier today and figured i&amp;#x27;d name it the same when I saved it back then.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866873&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866859&lt;br&gt;Its also like saying that the release of ISO200022 would ultimately skyrocket the price of XRP .... which it wouldnt. Same thing is going to happen with the opening of the clarity act.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Except when you consider that the TVL held by their oracles are 15x the current market cap of LINK.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866879&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866872&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866867&lt;br&gt;I mean when that person saved it back then whoever it was, nobody knows it&amp;#x27;s all a mystery on 4chan where everybody is anonymous.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866887&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866872&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;It&amp;#x27;s not me i&amp;#x27;m someone else&lt;br&gt;Kek, never change. Stinks deserve it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866915&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866887&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;sole individual&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;there&amp;#x27;s probably a whole lot people doing it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866965&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866873&lt;br&gt;yeah well&lt;br&gt;fuck stinks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867027&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866965&lt;br&gt;I like the concept that LINK is a litmus test for the overall inflated market of cryptocurrencies. If the creator has been elected to the CFTC and is spearheading one of the most important clarity laws for currency adoption. What does that say for the broader market overall?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;My theory is that institutions are stalling as much as possible so they can create their own private solution rather than using whats publicly available. Because that would allow for the broader market to win instead of participating in a zero sum game.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867043&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866965&lt;br&gt;Being open source is one of the biggest memes where private investors can just steal what&amp;#x27;s been established and carbon copy to keep all the benefits. It&amp;#x27;s actually a tale as old as time when it comes to innovation. Edison didn&amp;#x27;t get rich off of ingenuity, he got rich off of stealing patents and publicly humiliating his competition, IE tesla.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867380&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866834&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866859&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866872&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866879&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866915&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;t. Actual cuck trying to cope because he lost everything on wormhole and linksol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869444&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867380&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;t. ugly incel cuckold who proudly worships a fat Slavshit that made him poor&lt;br&gt;Lol lmao even&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869532&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866834&lt;br&gt;And it is growing by double or triple digit percentages per month, with only more room to go given its regulatory solid quality. It will 100% flip it within a few months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869536&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869532&lt;br&gt;I can&amp;#x27;t wait&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869549&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866865&lt;br&gt;Its the defilama retard&lt;br&gt;Your info is outdated&lt;br&gt;fudcuck&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>How do I short NYC? — 15 replies — 39.2/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61868898</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61868898?lm=1771414737</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:38:57 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;How do I short NYC?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61868898'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 15 • Updated: 2026-02-18 11:38 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;How do I short NYC?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868918&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868898&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;middle class owning property in New York&lt;br&gt;hehe, good one&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868957&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868918&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;property tax goes up 10%&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;landlord keeps the rent the same price&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868970&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868898&lt;br&gt;puts on SLG, VNO, VICI&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868974&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868957&lt;br&gt;why would jews do that&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868986&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868898&lt;br&gt;Landlords must be so happy with this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869005&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taxes go up &amp;gt; Rents go up &amp;gt; Welfare goes up&lt;br&gt;And guess who owns all those buildings?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869011&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868898&lt;br&gt;How is his base responding to this? All the people who were so certain he could actually do what he said and would totally fix NYC with money it doesn&amp;#x27;t have?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869014&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868918&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868957&lt;br&gt;Actual rich people in NYC use a loophole where their building/unit is somehow tied to a much lower valued building on the same block. &lt;br&gt;So a penthouse they bought for $50M has a paper value of like $500k. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anyone who thinks the wealthy actually gets shafted by tax increases and that the politicians they own won&amp;#x27;t leave loopholes open for them, not just in NYC but in pretty much every western country, are absolutely delusional. &lt;br&gt;Taxing the rich is just a convenient excuse politicians use to raise taxes with the peasants blessings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869016&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868898&lt;br&gt;I can&amp;#x27;t believe anyone actually lives in NYC. Genuinely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869109&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869016&lt;br&gt;seriously, at least in california the weather and landscape makes it worth it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869172&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869016&lt;br&gt;what, you don&amp;#x27;t like being stabbed by niggers in the subway??&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869185&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Who cares? What they&amp;#x27;re doing is great for the poor. All poor socialists need to move to NYC ASAP and take advantage of the New New York. We should all be buying them bus tickets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869354&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868918&lt;br&gt;When you go to a restaurant, you are paying their property taxes and when you pay rent you are paying the property owners property taxes. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is one level of abstraction so if you cannot understand this it would indicate that your IQ is extremely low.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869533&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868898&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just goes to show how horrible the Republican candidate must have been that THIS was the better choice.&lt;br&gt;One of the main reasons Trump was elected was because the Democratic candidates were THAT bad (unlikable women both times)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869557&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869533&lt;br&gt;No?&lt;br&gt;Mummy Dummy just told retard Dem New Yorkers what they wanted to hear. It&amp;#x27;s literally out of a 4th grader playback for school elections.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden wanted to run again, and after that absolutely disastrous debate against Trump. Harris was the VP but never was she going to win against a man who survived an assassination attempt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Step into the Lite — 17 replies — 18.6/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61866494</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61866494?lm=1771412831</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:07:11 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Step into the Lite&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61866494'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 17 • Updated: 2026-02-18 11:07 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;No controversy.&lt;br&gt;No bullshit.&lt;br&gt;No founder holding a majority of supply.&lt;br&gt;Step out of the darkness.&lt;br&gt;Step into the Lite.&lt;br&gt;$4000 by mid 2027.&lt;br&gt;$100,000 by 2030.&lt;br&gt;EMBRACE THE LITE!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866503&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866494&lt;br&gt;Ive been annihilated by ltcs SHIT performance, but eh fuck it dude&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866526&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866494&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I heard this coin will be getting an ETF. I an excite.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866810&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;So, who else accumulating here?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866886&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866810&lt;br&gt;i&amp;#x27;m accoomoolating more LITS, my ltc stack is big enough already&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866951&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866886&lt;br&gt;QRD on lits? I was going to get some but it dropped by a lot over the past months. What are your thoughts on it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867108&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866494&lt;br&gt;a 10x from this levels is easy asf&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867518&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866951&lt;br&gt;it&amp;#x27;s trying to become the mstr of litecoin. It&amp;#x27;s like leveraged litecoin, but you don&amp;#x27;t own it so there are additional risks i suppose.&lt;br&gt;IF litecoin makes a comeback this will explode. also the price is less than the current litecoin treasury, so it&amp;#x27;s like buying litecoin on discount.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;They&amp;#x27;re in the pharma business, trying new drugs for cancer, but at this point this becomes secondary&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867751&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kek baggies, this shitcoin is going to zero.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868276&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LTC isn&amp;#x27;t doing well&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868461&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866494&lt;br&gt;its unbelievable to me that people are shilling this bitcoin ripoff decades later&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868911&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866494&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869000&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;No founder holding a majority of supply&lt;br&gt;Yeah because he dumped it all at the top&lt;br&gt;HAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAH&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869178&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868911&lt;br&gt;saddest of all trvkes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869435&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866494&lt;br&gt;Shilling a dead coin. It&amp;#x27;s the only shitcoin that didn&amp;#x27;t even pump this entire bull market and now is worth less than 12 years ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869443&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866886&lt;br&gt;I am making a bag of it. It crabs up and down mostly but it will have its day. Maybe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869489&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869000&lt;br&gt;trips of truth&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869497&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Isn&amp;#x27;t litecoin used a lot on online casinos? I follow bossmanjack and his gains are usually in litecoin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>&gt;Bought BTC ATH &gt;Bought the gold ATH &gt;Bought the silver ATH Just want to let you know guys that i'm going to start inves… — 12 replies — 16.2/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61865488</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61865488?lm=1771413447</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:17:27 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;&amp;gt;Bought BTC ATH &amp;gt;Bought the gold ATH &amp;gt;Bought the silver ATH Just want to let you know guys that i&amp;#x27;m going to start inves…&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61865488'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 12 • Updated: 2026-02-18 11:17 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;Bought BTC ATH&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Bought the gold ATH&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Bought the silver ATH&lt;br&gt;Just want to let you know guys that i&amp;#x27;m going to start investing in AI related stocks. Wish me luck because this is my last chance&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865510&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;kek&lt;br&gt;I wouldn&amp;#x27;t do that if I were you&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865519&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865488&lt;br&gt;Finally the stock market perma pump is over, get ready for lost decade while crypto pumps&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865561&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI stocks already rugged&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865569&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865519&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;while crypto pumps&lt;br&gt;lol no&lt;br&gt;crypto is fucking over and btc will be around 30k in a few months&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865617&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865488&lt;br&gt;I heard Microjeet is cheap, try that&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61865937&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;thank you anon, I could really use some RAM right now&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868035&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865488&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;AI related stocks&lt;br&gt;nice bro! thank you for popping the bubble.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868404&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868035&lt;br&gt;I was gonna say, about damn time somebody finally did it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thank you OP for bringing the computer parts market back to retail where it rightfully belongs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868582&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865488&lt;br&gt;I bought a bunch of SOL at $180-$190 in preparation for fucking &amp;quot;alt season&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;we&amp;#x27;re all in this together brother&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869274&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865488&lt;br&gt;you should cut your losses and result to a high yield savings account fucking quit trying to time or engage in markets you know nothing about&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869281&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865488&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;and just like that, the real great depression began.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869508&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61865488&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;start investing in AI related stocks&lt;br&gt;It has nowhere to go but down, you fucking brainlet. If you have to invest, do it in necessary commodities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>the US is in recession — 8 replies — 16.1/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61869320</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61869320?lm=1771414326</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:32:06 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;the US is in recession&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61869320'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 8 • Updated: 2026-02-18 11:32 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;the US is in recession&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869343&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869320&lt;br&gt;doomed fag nation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869350&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Adjust by population&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869389&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bump&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869494&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869320&lt;br&gt;The US is in a bad shape but posting absolute numbers instead of relative is not very helpful&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869507&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869320&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;two full time jobs&lt;br&gt;yeah sure.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;7 AM they wake up &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;8 AM they&amp;#x27;re in JOB LOCATION 1 and start working&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;5 PM they stop working and teleport to JOB LOCATION 2&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;2 AM of the next day they go back their home&lt;br&gt;it&amp;#x27;s impossible to do two full time jobs and there&amp;#x27;s no way you can convince me otherwise.&lt;br&gt;People that do two jobs are usually two part times or at most a full time and part time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869517&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869507&lt;br&gt;The way I did it was one factory job was 3 12 hour shifts Friday, Saturday, Sunday with full time bonus and then the second factory job was 4 10 hour shifts Mon-Thursday. Shit sucked, but it&amp;#x27;s not as bad as working on a fishing boat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869528&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;that&amp;#x27;s a drop in the bucket compared to what over 200 million&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869545&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869343&lt;br&gt;fpbp&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>&gt;you idiots are holding 1s and 0s on a computer, while my wealth is secure in physical precious meta-ACK — 61 replies — 15.5/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61863917</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61863917?lm=1771401931</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 08:05:31 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;&amp;gt;you idiots are holding 1s and 0s on a computer, while my wealth is secure in physical precious meta-ACK&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61863917'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 61 • Updated: 2026-02-18 08:05 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;you idiots are holding 1s and 0s on a computer, while my wealth is secure in physical precious meta-ACK&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61863927&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;you dumb asses really just keep metals sitting around your zero security home&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864275&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863917&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You have to be extremely stupid to hoard precious metals, as a private citizen. People rob banks, in broad daylight, and these morons are dumb enough to believe that they won&amp;#x27;t show up at their homes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864286&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864275&lt;br&gt;hope they have metal detectors cause i forgot where i burried mine&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864723&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864694&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Notice how this guy avoids all solid discussion, is consistently active, and only replies in quips and trolls.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;His secondary, will play the “reasonable” dissenter. Just pin this thread and watch, anons.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864726&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864723&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What solid discussion would you like to have?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864758&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863917&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;gets hacked&lt;br&gt;AAAAACCCCCK&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61864804&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864627&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I literally don&amp;#x27;t consider myself special&lt;br&gt;So then you literally know that literally most governments literally seize money when they want it bad enough and they have literally dealt with countless people who literally thought just because that money was literally in rock form the laws literally don&amp;#x27;t apply to them&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866917&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864804&lt;br&gt;Including your fiat, stocks, and crypto, except yours are way easier for them to confiscate.&lt;br&gt;Your point? OOH you don&amp;#x27;t have one. &lt;br&gt;Oh you&amp;#x27;re retarded? Poor thing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867080&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864723&lt;br&gt;Then why engage? It&amp;#x27;s harder to ignore retards in real life but I still manage, but online there&amp;#x27;s no reason to even pretend. Everyone that gets ventilated by bad advice just makes your assets that much more valuable. Pretend like everyone average and below will face starvation, prostitution, conscription and death; the truth isn&amp;#x27;t far from this. You wouldn&amp;#x27;t spend all day arguing with corpses so why would you spend time on someone that doesn&amp;#x27;t know they are dead yet?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867144&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866917&lt;br&gt;This is really the bull case cry for stacking firearms and putting aside enough to buy sell swords. The government will do anything they think they can get away with which I why I don&amp;#x27;t think even bail ins are certain, you can do those overnight without kicking a single door but there will still be hell to pay in the morning. While stackers are a smaller population most holdings require, or rather will at such time require, going door to door to seize assets in a country in which one can put together an AR for $350-$400 and drop in FRTs can be had for as little as $100. All this against the population and asset class pairing most likely to own firearms. The logistics don&amp;#x27;t make sense. You&amp;#x27;ll see heavy taxes, threats of taxes, capital controls and possibly if briefly bans on sales after a set date. None of this yields as much gold or silver as paying an above market rate. Question is, is there anything worth trading for. If I got a deed to a substantial amount of the land the federal government loves to horde so much I could see myself parting with all (some) of my specie. Nobody can be all stick and no carrot and win. This is why in bank bail ins you atleast get shares in a bank that has recently defaulted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867175&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867144&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;re lucky you&amp;#x27;re but a minnow. For large investors, all of the guns in the world didn&amp;#x27;t stop Uncle Sam knocking on their door for the known vaults of metals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867423&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867175&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I&amp;#x27;m not there&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;They break and enter&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Thirty tons of fertilizer vaporizes a city block&lt;br&gt;Oh no no no!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867447&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863917&lt;br&gt;already melted down and molded into a solid gold dildo that will sell for 3x spot&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867550&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866917&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;crypto&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;way easier for them to confiscate&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just say you don&amp;#x27;t invest in Bitcoin, because you don&amp;#x27;t understand it, moron.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is crypto 101.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867583&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867550&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;he thinks the government isn&amp;#x27;t in complete control of your delusional secret anonymous bits&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867616&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867583&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Imagine being this dumb and thinking that you&amp;#x27;re going to outsmart the government.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You don&amp;#x27;t even read.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867738&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867583&lt;br&gt;you don&amp;#x27;t understand how Bitcoin works at all, and your lack of understanding is not an argument&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867777&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867738&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;He&amp;#x27;s probably one of those people that try to argue with the police about the Constitution and Uniform Commercial Codes when they pull him over for a speeding ticket and he&amp;#x27;s made his own vehicle registration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867859&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863917&lt;br&gt;I wonder if the “victim” ever posted about his stack on social media?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867922&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864598&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;copy paste address to trade&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;substitution script edits the address on your clipboard for one with a similar start and end so it&amp;#x27;s visually indistinguishable unless you spend a minute verifying each address against eachother&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;gangpreet patel and his village get the capital to send another invader to your country&lt;br&gt;This isn&amp;#x27;t a joke btw, there are scripts which manipulate your clipboard like that, and it&amp;#x27;s even possible for them to be injected into innocent websites via ads. Be careful if you copy/paste addresses anon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867928&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864463&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;gf/wife&lt;br&gt;I have neither, so I am safe there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868014&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867922&lt;br&gt;yeah which is why you do your business on a computer that is only used for BTC and exchanges, and on Linux&lt;br&gt;if you can&amp;#x27;t do this you&amp;#x27;re brown, its effortless&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868254&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868014&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;only used for btc and exchanges&lt;br&gt;reasonable&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;and on linux&lt;br&gt;javascript can manipulate what goes into your clipboard when you copy or cut, being on linux wont change that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868340&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864496&lt;br&gt;Bank vault. That is where you hide it. It could easily take 20 years for her to find out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868350&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864275&lt;br&gt;How they would go in my house? I don&amp;#x27;t leave the door open, I&amp;#x27;m here most of the time and I live in a gated community with no crime whatsoever.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868490&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868340&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It would be immediately confiscated by the government and defeat the purpose of holding physical metal.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868350&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;re aware the banks have door locks, employees, armed guards, and security systems, right?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868527&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863917&lt;br&gt;You don&amp;#x27;t understand. Silver is not some rug shitcoin that will drop 30% tomorrow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868584&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I bet he was like &amp;quot;You guys should buy SILVER, you should have bought SILVER like me :) I bought so much SILVER, you want to know how much SILVER I bought? Let me tell you how much my SILVER is worth today :)&amp;quot; like every other silverfag so that everyone everywhere knew he had a bunch of silver bars at his house waiting to be stolen&lt;br&gt;NOBODY knows about my gold. It lives in a tin under a floorboard. If people ask me about investments I just say it&amp;#x27;s too complicated for me and I don&amp;#x27;t understand it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868620&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61864318&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Trump writes another gold executive order like FDR&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;cops at your door, &amp;quot;surrender your precious metals or you will be charged&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;what gold dunno what you&amp;#x27;re talking about&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;they arrest you&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;later they show your purchase history and post history to the court&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What now? Lawyer up against the feds? But all your wealth is buried in your backyard and all your cash is worthless from inflation (or they wouldn&amp;#x27;t be stealing your gold). You&amp;#x27;d be better off investing in bullets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868888&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868620&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; property gets auctioned off, because no one is paying the taxes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869243&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868620&lt;br&gt;By your logic 100% of people get arrested because literally all of them will say they don&amp;#x27;t have gold or silver and 95% of the ones saying that are telling the truth, but you think they&amp;#x27;ll be arrested anyway.&lt;br&gt;This is the level of cope and mental gymnastics cryptards have.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869253&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61863917&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oops that clipboard malware destroyed my lifesaving... ACK! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pixel trannys lost.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>4 more years until LINK hits $50 again Marines, wagmi! — 14 replies — 14.7/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61867925</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61867925?lm=1771412685</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:04:45 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;4 more years until LINK hits $50 again Marines, wagmi!&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61867925'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 14 • Updated: 2026-02-18 11:04 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;4 more years until LINK hits $50 again&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Marines, wagmi!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867931&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867925&lt;br&gt;btc is dead&lt;br&gt;nobody is paying $250k for some nonsense 1s and 0s&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867946&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;this dude really used AI instead of inspect element or some shit&lt;br&gt;fucking kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868127&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867946&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;This guy really did this in 2 seconds instead of spending 5 minutes doing it manually&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fucking kek, kek kek! Kek!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868136&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868127&lt;br&gt;booty bothered&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868166&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867925&lt;br&gt;why did cardano become arch linux tho&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868187&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867925&lt;br&gt;Oh and it’s getting a new symbol too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868218&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868127&lt;br&gt;Ass blasted&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868225&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868127&lt;br&gt;this dude needs 5 minutes to change some characters&lt;br&gt;fucking kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868231&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867925&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;$50 Link would allow me to WAGMIx2.8 from staking rewards alone&lt;br&gt;Your terms are acceptable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868266&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868225&lt;br&gt;You also have to look up 2030 predictions for 15 different cryptos. No using AI so you have to do each one individually&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868300&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61868127&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;uncontrollable seethe&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;lmao absolutely bodied&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61868374&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867925&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;XRP at only $5&lt;br&gt;It’ll be $589.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869438&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867925&lt;br&gt;the cuckolds will still spam their stale CLL memes about their staking pool (full of shit)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869488&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867925&lt;br&gt;Did you retards not buy at 20 cents ?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>BTC dumping? Don’t care. It’s temporary. — 8 replies — 10.9/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61869212</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61869212?lm=1771413474</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:17:54 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;BTC dumping? Don’t care. It’s temporary.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61869212'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 8 • Updated: 2026-02-18 11:17 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;If it drops, I buy more. If it goes sideways, I accumulate. If it pumps, I chill. I’m earning yield and stacking long term. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Short term volatility doesn’t change the plan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869234&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869212&lt;br&gt;Crypto and BTC is dead retard &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Everyone knows about it by now&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869237&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869212&lt;br&gt;The niggercattle aren&amp;#x27;t going to pump your epsteincoin bags.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869244&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869212&lt;br&gt;Pixel tranny cope.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869247&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869234&lt;br&gt;you are a pedo nigger&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869319&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869212&lt;br&gt;Btc will pump ser&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869502&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869360&lt;br&gt;Wtf&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869514&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61869212&lt;br&gt;Btc is never going to pump again. The elites have cashed out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>US is in recession — 23 replies — 9.9/hr</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61866972</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61866972?lm=1771407783</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:43:03 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;US is in recession&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61866972'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 23 • Updated: 2026-02-18 09:43 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;US is in recession&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61866978&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866972&lt;br&gt;I graduated collage and got a job. Must be a skill issue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867094&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866972&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Criminal justice less useful than an art degree &lt;br&gt;Wow&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867095&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866972&lt;br&gt;buy an ad&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867099&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;fell for the computer science meme and now I have to work at Goodwill for $13/hr&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867136&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867094&lt;br&gt;Performing arts. That means that what most people think of when they think &amp;quot;arts major&amp;quot; (fine arts, animation, etc.) are better-employed than criminal justice majors. They&amp;#x27;re better employed than med techs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Marinate on that for a minute.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867150&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867099&lt;br&gt;Have you tried walking into google and giving Sundar a firm handshake, kiddo... That&amp;#x27;s what we used to do back in our day... Look him in the eyes and let him know you&amp;#x27;ll do whatever in takes... Extra hours, sleeping at the office... Kids these days just don&amp;#x27;t have the grit we used to have... That&amp;#x27;s why we sent men to the moon, 6 times at that, yes sir...&lt;br&gt;You gotta pay your dues, and you gotta be in it to win it...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sent from my iPhone&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867192&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867094&lt;br&gt;A lot of people who do Criminal Justice degrees are people who watched CSI etc and want to solve murders or do forensics rather than law or general policing or whatever. The actual amount of jobs available for that field is extremely small&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867214&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;That graph is basically flatlined lol. There are things to be alarmed about, but is this really one of them?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867228&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Do any of these stats even matter. This shit is just fud for you a couple of years now I&amp;#x27;ve been seeing so much shit like this but than nothing ever happens because of it people just move on like it doesn&amp;#x27;t exist.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867266&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867214&lt;br&gt;Tbh it shows we&amp;#x27;ve been on an unsustainable path for, at minimum, the duration of the x axis&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867303&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867192&lt;br&gt;Because the laws they want to change, for the better, get rejected. We need a giga wipe of all the branches. All senators and shit, GONE. We need new blood instead of fucking 98 yr old Strom Thurman fuckers voting for shit. 2 terms, 3 years each. President only gets 2 terms, 8 years and that&amp;#x27;s it, why do THEY get to fucking stay?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867341&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866972&lt;br&gt;This is a complete lie. Trump doubled steel production in one year. The economy has never been better&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867436&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866972&lt;br&gt;good to know...ill start spending less to help&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867442&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866972&lt;br&gt;I voted for this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867446&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Not using the criminal justice degree to do some criminal justice&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867538&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867094&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866972&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;medical technicians&lt;br&gt;You go to college for &amp;#x27;useful&amp;#x27; degrees like compsci and medicine and then you&amp;#x27;re unemployed. Womp womp should have become a mechanic. Oh wait I did that too and applied to be a mechanic at the place 5 minutes up the road and they told me they already got three guys but need an inspector if I want to pay for inspection courses.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You know the real fucked up part? I was gonna invest 100k into BTC at 20k back in 2022. I would have been pretty much set.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867546&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867228&lt;br&gt;The news just gaslights people about how millennials all somehow got 6 figure careers and some fag on /biz/ will always reply to posts like this liek &amp;quot;I&amp;#x27;m 36 and everyone I know is making 200k a year&amp;quot; and then will refuse to actually explain what he does or make up a fanciful story about dropshipping businesses and ebay magic, nevermind that I tried the ebay business route and that shit is too high in fees to be worth anything.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867595&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867341&lt;br&gt;I can&amp;#x27;t believe they did this. Are we staffed by a bunch of slimy kikes?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867608&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867099&lt;br&gt;Apply for clerk at the post office. It&amp;#x27;s just as gay but 22/hr and there&amp;#x27;s no real interview&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;t. Chemical engineer working for the post office&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867634&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867341&lt;br&gt;fucking kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867655&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867608&lt;br&gt;Become a patent clerk instead. It’s a good job.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;t. knower&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61867705&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61867595&lt;br&gt;You don&amp;#x27;t know that they&amp;#x27;ve been manipulating the basket of goods used to calculate CPI increases?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61869366&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61866972&lt;br&gt;End of the Juglar cycle, overproduction crisis, market saturation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>