<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>/biz/ Active (no generals, context, ticker-first, exploding)</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/</link><description>OP + first 3 replies + last 30 replies. Ticker threads boosted. Exploding threads flagged.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 16:02:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>[TICKER | EXPLODING 562.3/hr] /BBBYQ/ - Bath Barron Edition — 229 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61803438</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61803438?lm=1771256260</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:37:40 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;/BBBYQ/ - Bath Barron Edition&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61803438'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 229 • Updated: 2026-02-16 15:37 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;BBBYQ&lt;br&gt;TOKENS.COM&lt;br&gt;TZERO&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;WAGMI&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61803541&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WAGMI&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61803630&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Look at them go!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61804731&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;pp, if i don&amp;#x27;t get anything for my canceled shares, i&amp;#x27;m going to find you and kick you in the balls&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856432&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855697&lt;br&gt;I dont care&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857014&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hallo?&lt;br&gt;When BBBY return? &lt;br&gt;I dont care&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857266&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857014&lt;br&gt;BBBY is trading now. BBBYQ was canceled, and no longer exists. If you had BBBYQ when it was canceled you lost that investment, it can never be returned. Anyone who says BBBYQ is coming back is a scammer or mentally ill.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857313&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855287&lt;br&gt;What mental illnesses are you diagnosed with?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857321&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857266&lt;br&gt;I dont care of loss my Money.&lt;br&gt;I dont read your shit post.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857369&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;where we&amp;#x27;re you when your shares we&amp;#x27;re cancel?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;me I&amp;#x27;m at house&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;wife come home and say &amp;quot;no bbq sauce&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;it does not matter&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;sauce is not the main for me to eat&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;she ask if I&amp;#x27;m eat without, I say yes&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I&amp;#x27;m love it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857512&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857369&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Michael Goldbergenstein say from iPhone&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;share are cancel&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;No&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857528&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857512&lt;br&gt;Yes, share are cancel. Shorts are also cancel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857530&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853518&lt;br&gt;BBBY and gme sagas have been incredibly illuminating for me&lt;br&gt;I always thought that it is at least *possible* for rational actors to creatively misunderstand evidence disproving legacy conspiracies like flat earth&lt;br&gt;but for meme stocks it&amp;#x27;s all completely dry corporate and legal documents explicitly formulated in such a way that there&amp;#x27;s nothing to misunderstand&lt;br&gt;meme stocks gave me a new understanding of the strength of people&amp;#x27;s delusion&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857546&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857528&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857530&lt;br&gt;What do you guys think about DK-Butterfly&amp;#x27;s CUSIP matching the new BBBY warrants?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What do you guys think about GME needing to recognize a loss on a security they never sold?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What do you guys think about Gustavo Arnal being murdered in cold blood for helping RC?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What do you guys think about there being no final decree yet?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I bet you have a lot to say about it on a Sunday morning don&amp;#x27;t you?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857565&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857313&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;There is zero counterargument.&lt;br&gt;I am sorry. But there is no answer to the CUSIP Conundrum. What else am I to believe other than the thesis that CH11 for BBBYQ would end in a transaction. We now have evidence that this transaction took place. You just don&amp;#x27;t like that I harp on it and won&amp;#x27;t let it go. &lt;br&gt;You are just a grumpy wumpy seethy weethy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857577&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857546&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;What do you guys think about DK-Butterfly&amp;#x27;s CUSIP matching the new BBBY warrants?&lt;br&gt;This is quite intriguing indeed! By my best calculations, it appears that BBBYQ shell has reverse merged with BBBY. This is the only way possible the warrants would use the wrong CUSIP. &lt;br&gt;This would be like filing your taxes and you suddenly misusing the wrong social security number when filling out the paperwork. The bankers that help underwrite these securities are not guessing and using the wrong CUSIP. When the investment bankers helped in creating these warrants for distribution, at that very moment the controlling interest of BBBY was BBBYQ. It&amp;#x27;s 100% proven fact. It&amp;#x27;s a fact because we can literally check the CUSIPs right here right now. We can also go into Bed Bath and Beyond stores right here and now. We also know what a Butterfly transaction is. It&amp;#x27;s exactly what happened in this CH11. There is still much more to come!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857602&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857565&lt;br&gt;There is an answer, you just refuse to accept it because of your mental illness. Anyone who held BBBYQ at cancelation will never get anything for it, that was a 100% loss that is unrecoverable. &lt;br&gt;There are also some that know this, yet try to tie the old BBBYQ to the warrants in order to pump and dump them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857791&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;mental illness&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857968&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857602&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;There is an answer&lt;br&gt;What is the answer? You sure do a lot of seething about some pretty basic logic here. I am doing, with 100% Grade-A proven facts that A + B = C and you are having a meltdown about it. You have three options:&lt;br&gt;1 - State the obvious. Reverse merger already happened. Towelkings win. &lt;br&gt;2 - State a logical explanation why the wrong CUSIP is being used on warrants in the context that we&amp;#x27;ve been postulating for YEARS that this restructuring ends in a transaction. The evidence supports our thesis.&lt;br&gt;3 - Be a grumpy wumpy seethy weethy. &lt;br&gt;Those are your only options, and no, being a seethy does not solve the CUSIP Conundrum. If you can&amp;#x27;t solve the conundrum then that means we have our Cusip Confirmation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858165&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857968&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;CUSIP Conundrum&lt;br&gt;There is no Conundrum, the CUSIP of BBBYQ no longer exists as it was canceled.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858182&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ken griffin LOL&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858188&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858182&lt;br&gt;KEN GRIFFIN &lt;br&gt;LOL&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858201&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858182&lt;br&gt;KG is down 97.5% on GME? Damn, shoulda been long lol.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858219&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;hahahahaha can&amp;#x27;t believe mentally ill bagholders who lost all of their money still here. they lost their money because someone on the internet told them to buy a dead company stock. how about i tell you to suck my dick. would you do it? BBBYQ = dead company, dead stock, bankrupt. BBBY = new company. if you are too stupid to understand this, there&amp;#x27;s no light for you, keep coping until 2100, no refunds. you shouldn&amp;#x27;t have gambled your hard earned money. if this continues, i&amp;#x27;ll start threads about my roulette losses and demand that casino pay me back, because casinos ASSIP-6 starts with the number hit on roulette. KEK baggies. you guys are literally living in the dream world. reading your cope on reddit and here, gives me schadenfreude.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858250&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858219&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;rage posting about a stock he doesn&amp;#x27;t own&lt;br&gt;but why?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858863&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858250&lt;br&gt;empathy for fellow man maybe?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858996&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858219&lt;br&gt;The money will be refunded x1000 at least maybe twice that. You can&amp;#x27;t argue with the value it brings. That&amp;#x27;s just math.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859061&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858250&lt;br&gt;They are very empathetic anon. Please give up and stop nooticing. Please, it&amp;#x27;s for your own good. We care about your sanity and safety. Plz&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859101&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858219&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;uses reddit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859650&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857266&lt;br&gt;The chapter 11 judge stated himself that class 9 recovery is possible&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859915&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858996&lt;br&gt;HERTZ 5% &lt;br&gt;BBBYQ 1000%?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859947&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nigga, take a bath and put your money in something actually worthwhile like LINK&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860655&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859947&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Nigga, take a bath&lt;br&gt;no you&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860846&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BED BATH AND BEYOOOOOOONDD.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pedo hedgies on ledgies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>[TICKER | EXPLODING 240.0/hr] Thread 61857490 — 60 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61857490</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61857490?lm=1771257626</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 16:00:26 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Thread 61857490&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61857490'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 60 • Updated: 2026-02-16 16:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US is in recession&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857499&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White collar recession comes before regular recession 100% of the time. We&amp;#x27;ve been in a white collar recession since 2020.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857500&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;Always was, its depression for over a year now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857508&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;GDP is growing, recession is fake.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nothing ever happens. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stop putting your vibes and feelings into your job search, learn to get better skills and be more marketable to employers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;McDonalds is always hiring&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858034&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857812&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;pretending there was a point and that you weren&amp;#x27;t just being called out for being retarded (you are)&lt;br&gt;No wonder you&amp;#x27;re unemployed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858084&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858023&lt;br&gt;She&amp;#x27;s pretty cute for a 60 year old, I can&amp;#x27;t help but fantasize her wearing black lingerie doing unspeakable things whenever I see her at a congressional hearing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858131&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;and have you even said thank you ONCE, anon?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858335&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857779&lt;br&gt;Destroyed trust in america, which is the #1 prerequisite for any economic activity&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858342&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857508&lt;br&gt;by this logic, if 1 person earned 100% of GDP but it was high enough, there would be no recession&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858343&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857840&lt;br&gt;Now if only they could put a leash on their trannies and the war-kikes it wouldn&amp;#x27;t have come to this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858364&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;Who gets to decide when the Second Great Depression is under way?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858366&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857808&lt;br&gt;lol, lmao even.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858379&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857824&lt;br&gt;Not only did you pick a commodity (hint: it&amp;#x27;s derived from the word common), you&amp;#x27;re not even right about it because oil companies agree Vlvenezuelan oil is not profitable&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858383&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Weakest year for job creation since the Great Recession&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Almost as many layoffs as during 2020&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How the fuck is unemployment only at 4.3%?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858397&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857499&lt;br&gt;Except 2022 had a labour shortage&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858404&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858383&lt;br&gt;https://fred.stlouisfed.org/series/CIVPART&lt;br&gt;Also I do not think they count gig workers as unemployed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858449&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858383&lt;br&gt;If you don&amp;#x27;t apply for one job a month, you&amp;#x27;re not unemployed. If you have a masters degree and you work at McDonald&amp;#x27;s, you&amp;#x27;re not unemployed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858696&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;I voted for this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858910&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857805&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Disrupted the international order from which the US greatly benefitted and everyone else benefited from the US even more&lt;br&gt;fuck off retard. did you forget&lt;br&gt;-single handedly carrying NATO&lt;br&gt;-protecting international shipping lanes&lt;br&gt;-being the global leader in innovation and tech&lt;br&gt;-only genuine believer and de facto practitioner of promoting human rights&lt;br&gt;? fuck you euronigger canacuck spic or whatever you are. we&amp;#x27;re allowed to take care of ourselves for once.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859778&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858910&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Wow america number one in everything when it created and proliferated a working order&lt;br&gt;Yeah no shit he already said that&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859785&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858023&lt;br&gt;Either Mossad agent or photoshopped picture&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859951&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857805&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;international order&lt;br&gt;jesus christ turn off the television. US economy (and western economy) is in tatters precisely because of the &amp;quot;international order&amp;quot; ie ZOG. They flood your country with cheap violent labor to suppress wages and sow division, they inflate away your wealth by constantly printing to pay the interest on government borrowing for GIBS for your replacements and zog wars. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How the fuck do you reach the conclusion that America needs an &amp;quot;international order&amp;quot; to function when it&amp;#x27;s downfall has correlated perfectly to its kowtowing to international interests. America is almost entirely self-sufficient and has plenty of skilled workers. It doesn&amp;#x27;t need an international order, it needs a financial sector that isn&amp;#x27;t destroying the country for its own benefit and it needs to get rid of the millions of useless eaters in your country. Get America back up to 70%+ White, fix your money printing problem, deal with the israel problem in your government, and the economy will take care of itself. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s just nuts to me that people talk about the economy without mentioning the giant rotting elephant in the room which is the trillions that gets siphoned from productive workers to various kike interests. The K-shaped economy isn&amp;#x27;t an accident it&amp;#x27;s deliberate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859958&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;DEI moneysinks getting destroyed&lt;br&gt;Sucks to suck. Go be a negro in Negrovia or something&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859986&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857490&lt;br&gt;Isn&amp;#x27;t it good for the US economy if everyone is losing their jobs to AI?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860143&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858383&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;go to jobcentre &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;get offerd the a streetsweeper&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;I din&amp;#x27;t waste 6 years of my life getting a master&amp;#x27;s to sweep puke and shit of the sidewalk&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;well if you don&amp;#x27;t want to work than you can&amp;#x27;t be unemployed, so no benefits for you&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;Call me Broomy-Mcbroomster guvna&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860535&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860143&lt;br&gt;I wish I got benefits, I&amp;#x27;ve been unemployed in Poland for 7 years now and I&amp;#x27;ve gotten a grand total of $0 in benefits&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860619&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859951&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Get America back up to 70%+ White, fix your money printing problem, deal with the israel problem in your government, and the economy will take care of itself.&lt;br&gt;anything else while we have the magic wand out sir?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860705&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859951&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;How the fuck do you reach the conclusion that America needs an &amp;quot;international order&amp;quot; to function when it&amp;#x27;s downfall has correlated perfectly to its kowtowing to international interests&lt;br&gt;What international interests? The US has been profiting off the international order since Breton Woods. Its rise as a superpower correlates to the dollar’s international dominance. It’s the opposite of what you’re describing.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;America is almost entirely self-sufficient&lt;br&gt;It is completely dependent on foreign pharmaceuticals and various input goods for manufacturing. It has virtually no domestic source of lithium, cobalt, graphite or REMs. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;the problem is international Jewry and this will be rectified when the us becomes an autarky &lt;br&gt;Why? &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rotting elephant in the room is a declining dollar, obscene debt, and an overinflated market + made up statistics. None of this gets better by fucking up international trade.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860719&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857750&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;US being in a recession isn&amp;#x27;t about Trump.&lt;br&gt;Yes he&amp;#x27;s a fucking retarded boomer brained moron, but US has been doomed to hit this point sooner or later ever since they decided to crank the money printers on permanently after 2008 and doomed the entire West to be stuck in a slow death limbo.&lt;br&gt;Everyone has basically just been waiting for the big one for years now and we&amp;#x27;re getting closer and closer to it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860738&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859951&lt;br&gt;You have no idea how the dollar system works and it shows. What&amp;#x27;s happening to the United States right now is irreversible&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860813&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860719&lt;br&gt;Printing after 2008 happened because 2008 happened, which happened because republicans deregulated finance. You&amp;#x27;re right, it&amp;#x27;s not about Trump, it&amp;#x27;s about half the country being fucking retarded hicks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860867&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860813&lt;br&gt;Republicans like Raegan deregulated finance, that’s true (though some of that was put into motion by Jimmy Carter). That said, it’s impossible to talk about 2008 without recognizing that Clinton is the one who repealed the Glass-Steagall act and let insurance banking merge with commercial banking. Pretty much every president for the 30 years leading up to 2008 did something to enable it or make it worse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860880&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860867&lt;br&gt;I forgot that Clinton was also the one that made derivatives immune to regulation. He really fucked up finance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860916&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857825&lt;br&gt;Holy shit this is the most retarded post I have ever read on /biz/, why are you on a finance board??&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>[TICKER | EXPLODING 30.7/hr] Is it really that much more difficult to start a business in the eu than us? — 10 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860796</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860796?lm=1771256555</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:42:35 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Is it really that much more difficult to start a business in the eu than us?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860796'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 10 • Updated: 2026-02-16 15:42 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;You guys in the EU make less than us on paychecks, but you get to keep more of your money because you have universal healthcare and PTO while we have to pay for private insurance which chronically denies people&amp;#x27;s health situations. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Are people saying that starting a business in the EU is difficult because of the regulations? What regulations does the European union impose on its citizen&amp;#x27;s than they think it&amp;#x27;s easier to start in the United States instead?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860815&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;Depends enormously on which country are we talking about. Some are easy (Germany) some are very hard (Italy)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860817&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; you get to keep more of your money because you have universal healthcare&lt;br&gt;yeah right&lt;br&gt;good luck getting that &amp;quot;universal healthcare&amp;quot; if you&amp;#x27;re not a boomer, waiting lists are years for even a basic exam/procedure. It&amp;#x27;s either you go private (and pay out of your own pocket) or you die&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; and PTO&lt;br&gt;oh wow, 20 wagie cagie free days a year. Totally worth the 60%+ taxes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;All taxation is theft. It&amp;#x27;s just that. Taxation doesn&amp;#x27;t pay for services. It&amp;#x27;s just the way they control the economy, and here in EU they fucking LOVE to control what you can and cannot do. They print the money, they don&amp;#x27;t need to tax you. They tax you to control you (and to humiliate you)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860822&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;The healthcare thing is too much american leftie argument, it also has been very overcrowded by you guessed arabs and africans, unironically I was better treated when I broke my leg in brazil of all places then in france&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860823&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860815&lt;br&gt;How about the Czech Republic?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860836&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860817&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;waiting lists are years for even a basic exam/procedure&lt;br&gt;we have them too except they&amp;#x27;re called &amp;quot;pre authorization&amp;quot; and we still get to pay for it all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860837&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;What regulations does the European union impose on its citizen&amp;#x27;s than they think it&amp;#x27;s easier to start in the United States instead?&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;re shitting me right? As the other guy said it really varies based on the country, but in places like Italy you need 20 authorizations and 10 certifications (that you pay for) to open something like a bar or a carpentry shop, plus constant &amp;quot;controls&amp;quot; which are basically bribe requests at this point by officials of all kinds. Oh, and good luck filing your taxes. Here&amp;#x27;s how it goes&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; be business owner&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; tax filing time (yay)&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; tax system is so incredibly fucking complex you have to hire people just to calculate how much you own&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; because of course YOU need to tell the state how much the state wants from YOU&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; slightest fuck up? You&amp;#x27;re on the hook for 240% of the original amount&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; they have 5-7 years to come after you&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; &amp;quot;oh hello here&amp;#x27;s a tax bill from 5 years ago cause you filed 3.51 euros less than you were supposed to, plus 1500 eur sanction, plus interest&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; oh btw you pay FIRST, and MAYBE when (after an average of 12 years in court at your expense) you are declared right, you get it back, no interest accrued, your legal expenses still on your back&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; so most people just pay&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; it&amp;#x27;s mafia with a hand of paint on top and the full force of the state behind it&lt;br&gt;EU is completely fucked. Stay away. We can just pray it somehow implodes from within. These bureaucrat jew lover good goyim will kill us all and replace us with shitskin and pajeets and they will feast on top of it all while the continent dies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860842&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860837&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;tax system is so incredibly fucking complex you have to hire people just to calculate how much you own&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; because of course YOU need to tell the state how much the state wants from YOU&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; slightest fuck up? You&amp;#x27;re on the hook for 240% of the original amount&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; they have 5-7 years to come after you&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; &amp;quot;oh hello here&amp;#x27;s a tax bill from 5 years ago cause you filed 3.51 euros less than you were supposed to, plus 1500 eur sanction, plus interest&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; oh btw you pay FIRST, and MAYBE when (after an average of 12 years in court at your expense) you are declared right, you get it back, no interest accrued, your legal expenses still on your back&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; so most people just pay&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; it&amp;#x27;s mafia with a hand of paint on top and the full force of the state behind it&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;EU is completely fucked. Stay away.&lt;br&gt;again this is more or less the same as the US&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860847&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860823&lt;br&gt;A bureaucracy nightmare.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860850&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860842&lt;br&gt;everywhere is completely fucked, but you burgers have weapons and a strong constitution that backs you&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;yeah you&amp;#x27;re retarded pussies and you will never ever use them, we all know. I mean they&amp;#x27;re telling you know that you&amp;#x27;re ruled upon by a bunch of satanist jew pedophiles and there&amp;#x27;s no shooting in the streets, so there you have it. But at least you have the guns. If the Cheka comes knocking at your door demanding your harvest and your daughters, you can shoot back at the fuckers. Here in EU we&amp;#x27;re basically at the mercy of a state that hates us and wants us dead, and we have only our dicks to hold in our hands to defend ourselves from it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860860&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860796&lt;br&gt;As far as I keep reading on economic subreddits, negligible, the US just has far more available credit and tax companies a bit less at start allowing them to grow, otherwise its basically the same, sounds legit just a complacency issue from europeans, most of the time they get more unemployment benefits than they would working and have legit no time limit for them so they just don&amp;#x27;t bother lol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>[TICKER | EXPLODING 28.0/hr] BOOOOOOOOOOM — 7 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860799</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860799?lm=1771257267</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:54:27 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;BOOOOOOOOOOM&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860799'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 7 • Updated: 2026-02-16 15:54 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Imagine not buying XRP right now.&lt;br&gt;Institutions are waiting for the clarity act to pass so that they announce their XRP holdings.&lt;br&gt;This is your last chance before the train lefts off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860806&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860799&lt;br&gt;BOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOM&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860862&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860799&lt;br&gt;BOOM, LINKLETS IN SHAMBLES!!!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860868&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This has been known for like 5 years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860872&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOOOOOOOOOOM&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;BULLISH XRP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860875&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;wait until its 25 cents eoy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860876&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860799&lt;br&gt;It literally says in the image token not needed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860899&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860799&lt;br&gt;Kek baggies. How is rect city this time of year ?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>[TICKER | EXPLODING 8.0/hr] Thread 61860893 — 2 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860893</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860893?lm=1771257159</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:52:39 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Thread 61860893&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61860893'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 2 • Updated: 2026-02-16 15:52 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;there are people buying BTC at $67k expecting it to miraculously recover and moon to $300k+. what is society doing to help these mentally ill people&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860896&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860893&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;what is society doing&lt;br&gt;collapsing expeditiously&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860897&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;idk why they do this but i will gladly buy their bags at 20-30K when they lose hope&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;No additional replies in the latest window.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>[TICKER | 828.0/hr] /GME/ - Settle in for Comfy (Long) Weekend Edition — 365 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61853052</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61853052?lm=1771256139</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:35:39 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;/GME/ - Settle in for Comfy (Long) Weekend Edition&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61853052'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 365 • Updated: 2026-02-16 15:35 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;Basic Information&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;gme.cac site redacted due to aids&lt;br&gt;https://finra-markets.morningstar.com/MarketData/EquityOptions/detail.jsp?query=14%3A0P000002CH&lt;br&gt;https://gmetimeline.com (up to 2021)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Daily reminder&lt;br&gt;s[Kek Melvies]bzilp4&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Mandatory study time&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The Everything Short&lt;br&gt;reddit.com/mgucv2&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;^watch-along&lt;br&gt;youtu.be/AaalT8rn9lc&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Naked Short Selling and Systemic Risk&lt;br&gt;youtu.be/FCiL4v7_z9E&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Failure to deliver&lt;br&gt;youtu.be/I0WXg5T3cBE&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;GameStop Investor Site&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;SEC 10-K Annual report FY24 &amp;amp; &amp;#x27;25 Proxy Statement&lt;br&gt;news.gamestop.com/annual-meeting/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;What will happen if Citadel becomes insolvent?&lt;br&gt;DTCC with 60T USD, will pay as the final boss with FDIC as the insurance&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Real-Time Trades&lt;br&gt;https://www.nasdaq.com/market-activity/stocks/GME/latest-real-time-trades&lt;br&gt;https://eresearch.fidelity.com/eresearch/gotoBL/fidelityTopOrders.jhtml&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Current Trade Halts + Short Restrictions&lt;br&gt;nasdaqtrader.com/Trader.aspx?id=TradeHalts&lt;br&gt;nyse.com/markets/nyse-arca/notices&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;All other news/DDs/etc&lt;br&gt;en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Stag_hunt&lt;br&gt;https://prospect.org/power/how-the-gamestop-hustle-worked&lt;br&gt;https://computershared.net/?bot=drsbot&lt;br&gt;DRS Guide:&lt;br&gt;reddit.com/ptvaka&lt;br&gt;Avoid DSPP (more information under legacy links):&lt;br&gt;sec.gov/about/reports-publications/investor-publications/holding-your-securities-get-the-facts&lt;br&gt;HF/broker class action lawsuit evidence:&lt;br&gt;storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.flsd.590042/gov.uscourts.flsd.590042.416.0.pdf&lt;br&gt;SEC GME/meme stocks report:&lt;br&gt;sec.gov/files/staff-report-equity-options-market-struction-conditions-early-2021.pdf&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;DD Compilation:&lt;br&gt;reddit.com/mnss65&lt;br&gt;Quarterly Movements, Equity Total Return Swaps, DOOMPs, ITM CALLs, Short Interest, and Futures Roll Periods:&lt;br&gt;reddit.com/pb22oj&lt;br&gt;Cellar Boxing:&lt;br&gt;reddit.com/pmj9yk&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Temporary alliance with reddit and Jaws to take down other sharks, we can go back to hating each other later&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;reddit DDs don&amp;#x27;t take them for fact use your brain&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Check your broker and clearing house to ensure you&amp;#x27;re not rugpulled&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last time on /GME/: &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61847072&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As always:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;sneed hedgies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853060&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853052&lt;br&gt;Still comfy waitin&amp;#x27; and holdin&amp;#x27;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Summary&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;GameStop Info&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Complete corporate revamp by Ryan Cohen&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Debt free with positive increases and reductions (see ER); $8.8 B cash and cash equivalents on hand + high inventory&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;DRS &amp;amp; Computershare&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;~67.0 million shares of ~448.0: 15% total held by Dec 5, 2025&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;~66.7/~447.7: 15% 9/5, ~68.1/~447.3: 15% 6/5, ~69.5/~447.08: 16% 3/19&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;~71.0/~446.8: 16% Dec 4, 2024&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;~72.8/~426.5: 17% 9/4, ~74.6/~351: 21% 6/5&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;~75.3 of ~305 25% by Mar 20, 2024,&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;~75.4 by Nov 30 2023, ~75.4 8/31, ~76.6 6/1, ~76.0 3/22 Vs Cede &amp;amp; Co&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Previously 71.8 (17.95) M shares DRS&amp;#x27;d by Oct 29, 2022, 71.3 by 7/30,&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;12.7 of ~77 by 4/30, 8.9 by 1/29&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;and 5.2 by Oct 30 2021&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unfuddable&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Shorts never closed and there exists more fakes than real shares&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;#x27;MOASS&amp;#x27; is a matter of time&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Further information can found by reading the OP or DYOR!&lt;br&gt;Reply to this pasta for any confusion.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;WGAMI!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other news/reminders:&lt;br&gt;Wednesday RRP: 1.048B, 6P = 0.175B per (roughly)&lt;br&gt;Thursday RRP: 2.844B, 10P = 0.2844B per&lt;br&gt;Friday RRP: 0.377B, 3P = 0.126B per (roughly)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investor site links to SEC for old filings, FAQ for warrants exp [Oct 30 2026]&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;4-for-1 Stock Split Form of stock dividend (Rec: Jul 18, 2022; Dist. 21st AH)&lt;br&gt;^2022-07-06 8-K&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Q3 25 8-K/10-Q&lt;br&gt;^2025-12-09&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Proxy Statement: Stock given in comp issued as RSUs that vest in quarterly increments over 4 years.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;798 pg SEC doc confessions of FIs/MMs/HFs/DCEs/Swaps Counterparties etc on short selling transparency&lt;br&gt;sec.gov/comments/s7-11-23/s71123-typec.pdf&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;100 page comparison DD&lt;br&gt;https://pdfhost.io/v/05TEEk3U6_MOV_GME_Comparison_Doc&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Legacy links&lt;br&gt;wallet.gamestop.com&lt;br&gt;nft.gamestop.com&lt;br&gt;www.gmedd.com/report-model (Nov 2021)&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Use archives&lt;br&gt;Avoid DSPP:&lt;br&gt;reddit.com/r/DRSyourGME/comments/12pfm9s/&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;GME shorted percentage of float as of Jan 15th, 2021: 226.42%&lt;br&gt;www.rosenlegal.com/media/casestudy/2289_Robinhood%20-%20Initial%20Complaint%20-%20Market%20Manipulation%204835-8623-1514%20v.2.pdf&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please don&amp;#x27;t feed spammers and sliders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853135&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s been five years bro. How long you gonna keep posting this?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853136&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853135&lt;br&gt;Im here until I see more jews cry on tv&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860135&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860126&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; if its not really changing hands in any significant way.&lt;br&gt;You understood everything, that how jewjitsu work&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860137&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860129&lt;br&gt;update! its at 1P (quadrillion but why P) market cap&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860145&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860137&lt;br&gt;P is for Peta in metric terms aka quadrillion&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860226&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859729&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860294&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853372&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859833&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860252&lt;br&gt;Good.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860336&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860294&lt;br&gt;hell yesss wagmi&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860365&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859916&lt;br&gt;Jesus Christ that guy is certifiably insane. Someone post the pictures. &lt;br&gt;It’s also interesting that he is saying the exact same thing as the bbby spammers in these threads, so the bbby poster is either buttfag himself or they are all posting from some kind of script&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860374&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860252&lt;br&gt;check out the website and socials on the left&lt;br&gt;https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/gamestopcoin-net/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860398&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;market closed&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;still have to work today&lt;br&gt;these are the worst days&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860404&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GameStop has acquired RoaringKitty&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860497&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860398&lt;br&gt;They really are.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860498&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860252&lt;br&gt;vindicated, but at what cost&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860526&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anyone see barking puppy&amp;#x27;s video yesterday? I can&amp;#x27;t help but suspect that MOASS is about to start soon. LIkely being caused by the Yen Carry trade unwind. I can&amp;#x27;t help but get the feeling we are being warned ahead of time before Kitty&amp;#x27;s Return. I&amp;#x27;m pretty sure the whole movie plot he walked about why an analogy for BBBYQ as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860532&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859729&lt;br&gt;Swaps reporting was halted almost immediately after the sneeze. The reports that were supposed to come that fall never did. It&amp;#x27;s been almost 5 years, everyone has been flying blind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860540&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860365&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Someone post the pictures.&lt;br&gt;Isn&amp;#x27;t he also Canadian?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860581&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860540&lt;br&gt;That is clearly an eskimo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860586&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Started learning dutch this week, post wagmi I swear I&amp;#x27;ll strive to get fluent. Wagmi first or fluent first, guess we&amp;#x27;ll see.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860604&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860586&lt;br&gt;kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860697&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860540&lt;br&gt;They are all Canadian. Anyone who has turned out to be a grifter/liar/bad actor in this whole debacle has been Canadian. &lt;br&gt;I suspect this is really just a conduit for city of London/ Vatican interests. Something about Canada makes it a hotbed for off the books ops. &lt;br&gt;Bbby nonsense is being pushed by state actors&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860716&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860604&lt;br&gt;yeah kek dutchies :/&lt;br&gt;still rather take that hit than live rest of my life in swe tho. wagmi anyways.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860735&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860697&lt;br&gt;Makes sense. They work in shifts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860739&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860252&lt;br&gt;tracing the fuck out of bitcoin, what the fuck is this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860740&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860526&lt;br&gt;hype fatigue shill is still being a gaylord I see&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860767&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860604&lt;br&gt;Are there market makers / hedge funds over there just sitting on unrealized gains? Is this supposed to convince retail citizens to go back to savings accounts, 401k&amp;#x27;s, shit like that?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860820&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860697&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; Canadian&lt;br&gt;https://x.com/GabeZZOZZ/status/2022963819383836818&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860835&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860697&lt;br&gt;They really don’t want AA involved in that for reasons&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860839&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860820&lt;br&gt;That guy is hilarious&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>[TICKER | 114.1/hr] Thread 61858975 — 60 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858975</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858975?lm=1771255833</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:30:33 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Thread 61858975&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858975'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 60 • Updated: 2026-02-16 15:30 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Is living anywhere except Los Angeles, San Francisco, Washington DC, or New York the same as admitting that your life is meaningless and that you are NOT the main character and will never make it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858982&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;Dubai, Paris, London, Tokyo, Kyoto&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858987&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You burgers aren&amp;#x27;t ready for what&amp;#x27;s coming&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858990&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;HAHAHA&lt;br&gt;HAHAHAHA&lt;br&gt;IMAGINE LIVING IN A BROWN SHITHOLE&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859281&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859001&lt;br&gt;This is true only if you&amp;#x27;re extremely rich, and every year its advantage over elsewhere declines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859295&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859032&lt;br&gt;No one who says LA is nice lives in the actual city&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859299&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859122&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;only 20%&lt;br&gt;The national average was 12.5% in 2020.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859303&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859279&lt;br&gt;What city anon?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859311&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;san fran&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;dc&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The only cities worth living in are NYC, Miami, and LA. Saying anything else is pure cope.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859314&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859303&lt;br&gt;Boise, Idaho. I have lived all over the United States, including in several supposedly very &amp;quot;trendy&amp;quot; cities according to faggots like OP, and nothing comes remotely close to Boise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859319&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859279&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Walk through skid row right now&lt;br&gt;Good boy, you memorized the name of the worst street in Los Angeles. Wonder how many people know the name of your city. Skid Row is 45 minutes away from me btw, that&amp;#x27;s how large this city is.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859324&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OP and &amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858982 are correct for the most part. Most people ITT seem to be falling for /pol/ memes, are scared, or it’s sour grapes, but if you actually want to have upward economic mobility, living in a major metro area is almost necessary. Certainly makes it so much easier. &lt;br&gt;I know it’s cliche but it’s true that your network is everything. And the best place to build a good network and have the best economic opportunities is in a major city. &lt;br&gt;I grew up poor as fuck in central valley CA (209 represent) but moved to SF after college and I now have a 8 figure networth and an incredible career. That would not have happened if I lived anywhere else.&lt;br&gt;Haters will say it’s false&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859347&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;There are retards that honestly believe this and get stabbed by an AIDS infected needle waiting for a bus that&amp;#x27;s 45 minutes late. Meanwhile I work an easy job here in Tennessee and dump everything into investments and have a higher networth with a better quality of life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859355&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;All of these cities are NPC central dude. The objective in life is to live as far away from bug men as possible, in peace, and with a lot of land. You are insane to want to live in these places&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859373&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859314&lt;br&gt;Sounds comfy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859400&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859021&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;you can&amp;#x27;t even swim in the water after it rains.&lt;br&gt;Why?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859407&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859314&lt;br&gt;Dude shut the fuck up, next thing you know youll be flooded with 869848584 billion brown californians. Ops doing you a favor, dont end up like us (colorado)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859450&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858987&lt;br&gt;what&amp;#x27;s coming?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;hard to imagine how you &amp;quot;make it&amp;quot; blowing all your money on taxes, rent, parking, and getting nickle and dimed 1000x other ways&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859453&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859001&lt;br&gt;i took an uber ride through SF a bit ago to go to a tiki bar. there&amp;#x27;s millionaires bathing in wealth mixed in with fent zombies and literal bottles of piss and shit just scattered along the street. it&amp;#x27;s a very fucked place&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859461&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859314&lt;br&gt;Come visit Creston BC sometime &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1488&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859463&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859043&lt;br&gt;Gays really aren&amp;#x27;t that bad. Just let them pack fudge in peace and enjoy the nice weather and unparalleled upward mobility opportunities that san fran has to offer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859468&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859319&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;45 minutes away in LA&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oh so it&amp;#x27;s 5 miles away?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;LA is filled with tards. I guess the weather is nice. I bet that guy you&amp;#x27;re replying to lives in Boise, Idaho though. The nicest city in America by far.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859470&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859400&lt;br&gt;All of the runoff concentrates into drainages that dump directly into the ocean. It doesn&amp;#x27;t rain often so months of garbage, human shit, needles collect in the street and dump directly into the ocean.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;https://www.pacificsurf.com/surfing-after-it-rains/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;A few of the things you could get are ear infections, sinus infections, pink eye, the flu,gastroenteritis, MRSA, Hepatitis, and Staph.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860590&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;d consider living there after you threw all the non-Whites out. Otherwise, I&amp;#x27;d visit it but not stay there permanently.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860659&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Assuming you’ve made it, what are the benefits of living in these cities when job opportunities are no longer a factor&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860666&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;No. You can also live in a remote cabin in Alaska. At least until your old crew calls you out of retirement for one last job.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860681&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;My life is given meaning through devotion and love for the LORD Jesus Christ&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860712&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859314&lt;br&gt;Guarantee me a couple of slam piglets and a square meal and I&amp;#x27;ll see what I can do about sabotaging the caravans wheels to steer it on coarse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860728&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;imagine living in new york, not being the richest guy in new york, and imagining that living in new york means your life isn&amp;#x27;t meaningless&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860769&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858982&lt;br&gt;t. lolicerdo criminal&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860793&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;Living anywhere except Los Angeles, San Francisco, Washington DC, or New York is the same as admitting that your life is meaningless and that you are NOT the main character and will never make it.&lt;br&gt;This is true. Imagine living anywhere near these mega slave cities.&lt;br&gt;You will just be worker number 10000000. Almost anywhere else is better.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860802&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859145&lt;br&gt;Holy shit imagine thinking thats a good place to live in. The nederlands are already way overpopulated. Our natural habitat which means the place we are most happy at is the forest with a small group of tribespeople.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860804&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860793&lt;br&gt;*in&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860828&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858975&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Is living anywhere except Chongqing, Shanghai, Beijing, Guangzhou and Shenzhen the same as admitting that your life is meaningless and that you are NOT the main character and will never make it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>[TICKER | 71.6/hr] GERMANY TO END BURGERGELD PROGRAMS — 61 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858970</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858970?lm=1771254658</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:10:58 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;GERMANY TO END BURGERGELD PROGRAMS&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858970'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 61 • Updated: 2026-02-16 15:10 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;WILL BE REPLACED WITH A STRICTER PROGRAM IF YOU REFUSE WORK. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEXT STOP, PRIVATIZED HEALTHCARE.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858974&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Uh oh, Europeans actually have to work for a living now? Aw shucks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858980&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858974&lt;br&gt;They will soon legalize 12 hour work days much like Argentina has done. Even contributing 5% of their GDP to NATO has ultimately bankrupted them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859007&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858970&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wait you could get NEETbux in Germany this whole time by simply “refusing to work”? WTF&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859975&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858980&lt;br&gt;and they&amp;#x27;ll also patch any loopholes that allow you to exit the normgroid plantation. A forced update, if you will. As gay and retarded as the ones in google chrome.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Netherlands to introduce unrealized capital gains tax of 36% on crypto and stocks. &lt;br&gt;They&amp;#x27;re obsessed with squeezing more out of the human trash who &amp;quot;deals in the real world&amp;quot;. Only the goyim/golem who &amp;quot;deal in the real world&amp;quot; have anything real to steal i.e. not just jewish toilet paper squares that you can print for free aka monopolybuxx. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Note how all these privacy raping, freedom limiting, mind raping, leash tightening decisions are occurring in parallel in every government in the world. Just a coincidence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859979&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859007&lt;br&gt;wageslavery is rape with extra steps. You&amp;#x27;re used by another man for his goals, like a cocksleeve. No, the extra steps don&amp;#x27;t make it more consensual you stupid little nigger.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859984&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859082&lt;br&gt;not now because they&amp;#x27;re still useful to the elites. For now. The elites want to tighten their control over the native normalfags and to do that you replace the poorfags with desperate shitskins who are willing to work those shitty jobs for peanuts and even if some shitskins refuse to work you just dump them in a fancy neighborhood where they proceed to fuck n stab everyone and remove them from their properties and even if the natives somehow manage to avoid getting raped n gaped by the nignogs and abduls you have another trick up your sleeve: you print a mountain of jewish toilet paper squares, you rape the economy and steal all their assets and force them out&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860147&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is the german man the most cucked living thing in the entire universe?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;lets millions of male invaders from the worst and most violent nations in&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;feeds them, gives them money, cares for them, nurtures them &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;the feral wildlings go totally apeshit. They fuck, rape and kill german women. They steal, rob, betray, scam and swindling the last penny out of the german man‘s pocket&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;germany can’t get rid of the invasion.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;they breed worse than rabbits&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;like an invasive species, they soon take over the entire host nation&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;year after year, the government raises taxes to finance the costs of this invasion.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;the country will slowly transform into an absolute shithole &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;leftist politicians protect these foreign orc invaders and discredit every critic&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Like a good little tame and castrated beta cuck, the german man does absolutely nothing against this&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How can a single creature be this cucked?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860177&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860147&lt;br&gt;all of this applies to america which is below 40% white&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860191&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Germnanys real current issue is that they might run out of Gas and then its lights out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860401&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858970&lt;br&gt;still easy to get around that.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;go to job center appointment smelling like smegma and piss&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;send half assed CV to places that hire&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;nobody will hire you anyway&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;if they invite you to some interview just pretend to be officer doofy tier retarded&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;continue getting NEETbucks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860422&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859979&lt;br&gt;Shouldn&amp;#x27;t you be updating your resume instead of wasting time on 4chan? It&amp;#x27;ll be hard to explain the 10+ year gap in employment to interviewers, but I&amp;#x27;m sure you&amp;#x27;ll come up with something.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860441&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860422&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;It&amp;#x27;ll be hard to explain the 10+ year gap &lt;br&gt;a 10+ year gap is good and makes you unemployable.&lt;br&gt;also talk really slow like a retard and pretend not to know more complicated words. like just play an idiot. you will never have to wagecuck again and can collect neetbux freely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860446&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860441&lt;br&gt;Why are you on this board if you aim to live in poverty?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860499&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860422&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;the super sewious big boy wageslave loses his shit on 4chan&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;the post wasn&amp;#x27;t even directed at him &lt;br&gt;lol lmao even&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860527&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860446&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;hurr durr the only way to make money is by sucking a jews dick&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860538&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860527&lt;br&gt;wageslaves are so traumatized by wageslavery and interviewing that they&amp;#x27;re spreading their defeatism everywhere they go as a shitty coping mechanism. You know that they&amp;#x27;re forcing goyim to humiliate themselves with 5-10 round interviews nowadays? Insane.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860550&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860538&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;wagecuck&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;hypergamble to a few million&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;live in poverty on welfare&lt;br&gt;Not great options. I choose to wagecuck.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860567&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860527&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;You just can&amp;#x27;t have a business, ok????&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860591&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860550&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;it&amp;#x27;s either the whip or picking cotton&lt;br&gt;That false dichotomy is sure proof of wageslave brainrot. I don&amp;#x27;t blame you, though. The whole system is rigged against you from birth and every aspect of your human nature is weaponized against you by the very thing you&amp;#x27;re meant to worship as a social animal, i.e. society.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860601&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858970&lt;br&gt;They just gave away all our money to Ausländers and now that the social systems are running dry they are simply getting rid of them kek.&lt;br&gt;Nothing they do will fix this. Humanity is doomed.&lt;br&gt;Accelerationism is the only way.&lt;br&gt;Let the third world starve and divert fund into AI datacenters.&lt;br&gt;The wolf will chew its own leg off to survive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860612&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860601&lt;br&gt;third world is the biggest net exporter of food to the point frenchoids were crying it would kill their overpriced artistical wine or something, they aint starving bro&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860626&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860591&lt;br&gt;Sorry chief, I find the idea of opening a business to be enticing but I don’t see any sort of moat I could pursue with it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860651&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858970&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858974&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860660&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860612&lt;br&gt;Africa imports a lot of food&lt;br&gt;And France was rightfully complaining that imposing huge restrictions on European agriculture while signing free trade agreements with countries having little restrictions is retarded&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860678&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859446&lt;br&gt;a 10% reduction? kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860682&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860422&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;10 year gap&lt;br&gt;I tell them it is due to the government forcing employers to lower standards to hire the affirmative action subhumans. They never call me back, because they are off giving useless lazy meritless and sometime convict affirmative action subhumans jobs. &lt;br&gt;Enjoy paying to taxes to niggers, spics, and cunts that hate you, just in the vain hopes they one day stop calling you a racist and sexist. Get back to work wagie... the whole economy rests on you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860686&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860191&lt;br&gt;Gas?!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860707&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860422&lt;br&gt;kek, they won&amp;#x27;t work at all, german economy will implode and as merz said they already can&amp;#x27;t afford the welfare + pensions, it will just shrink till it gets too low to live then they will just kys as by now they are legit unable to live at all&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860723&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859099&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;this nigga thinks German economy circa 1988 is anything like today&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lol&lt;br&gt;Lmao even&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860724&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860401&lt;br&gt;a drooly retard eh? yeah that sounds just perfect for our new expanded military, the bundeswehr needs you to pick this uniform, this little sign and just stand there to block the evil russian drones with your face for us&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860758&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;tfw the only time in my life where I might receive neetbux for a few months is the exact time this happens&lt;br&gt;fucking lol my entire life is me getting fucked by the universe. Nothing good ever happens to me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860764&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860626&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;moat&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;he fell for Buffett boomer brain rot &lt;br&gt;The only moats Buffett had were his generous throat and his congressman daddy. And let&amp;#x27;s not forget about being lucky enough to be born in close proximity to swollen jewish nuts in Israel&amp;#x27;s 2nd state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860766&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860758&lt;br&gt;join a gang, sell weed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>[TICKER | 42.0/hr] Thread 61858027 — 62 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858027</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858027?lm=1771252418</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 14:33:38 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Thread 61858027&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858027'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 62 • Updated: 2026-02-16 14:33 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you had to place your entire life savings into ONE crypto currency or ONE single stock,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What would you bet your life savings on?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858042&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858027&lt;br&gt;I though it was a hot webm and feel deceived&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858046&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858027&lt;br&gt;AGNC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858053&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858027&lt;br&gt;Easy: CHAINLINK&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858623&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;That&lt;br&gt;Is&lt;br&gt;A&lt;br&gt;Man&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858805&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858027&lt;br&gt;@grok make her naked&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858806&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858027&lt;br&gt;At current prices? MSFT&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858813&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858027&lt;br&gt;Bitcoin, or if an ETF counts, VT&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858829&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why does she look like goddess happa? Forgot her name, the one that did the porn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858835&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;some stupid biotech gamble&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858899&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858829&lt;br&gt;mayli (i thought the same)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858912&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALL my savings? Bitcoin it is.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858932&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858156&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858166&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I&amp;#x27;ve been on the google + TQQQ train for many years now and have made bank. Was a very obvious play starting around 2015.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Concerned to see it getting shilled in more places lately, makes me think the dumb money has finally arrived and we are due for a reckoning&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859135&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858899&lt;br&gt;Based Mayli enjoyer&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859140&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858027&lt;br&gt;She&amp;#x27;s not that cute&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859288&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858027&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859415&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858027&lt;br&gt;Any of the Dividend King stocks. Can&amp;#x27;t go wrong. They&amp;#x27;re better than index funds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859487&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858027&lt;br&gt;whore fatigue. unless she has a shenis, than yum&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859871&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858616&lt;br&gt;Lol who the fuck uses unity, everyone is switching to godot and unreal lol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859921&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858616&lt;br&gt;It was down long before the software sell-off (probably a reason for that).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Also, they&amp;#x27;re not profitable lol. They&amp;#x27;re losing $100m per quarter. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your entire thesis is &amp;quot;it&amp;#x27;s gone down a lot, so it must go up&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860093&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858027&lt;br&gt;Anime dog crypto&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860101&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858027&lt;br&gt;I mean, what? Obviously some index ETF is the only safe bet.&lt;br&gt;But if I had to pick 1 stock...Walmart. I&amp;#x27;m already up 350% on my WMT and it pays a dividend. Walmart isn&amp;#x27;t going away any time this century.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860102&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858027&lt;br&gt;Paper silver in a few days when it gets a bit lower.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese markets are closed for a week because of Chinese new year and in the west there&amp;#x27;s big shorts on silver that need to be delivered so comex silver price will be manipulated down aggressively. It will jump back up as soon as Chinese new year is over because there&amp;#x27;s no change in supply and demand on their side. Basically a guaranteed &amp;gt;15% jump within a day or two.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860111&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860101&lt;br&gt;Walmart is very expensive at this P:E ratio so I wouldn&amp;#x27;t buy here but if I had to Yolo 1 stock that would be it because it is safe.&lt;br&gt;In the real world I&amp;#x27;m diversified into a dozen ETFs and stocks, real estate, physical silver etc.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860150&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858027&lt;br&gt;XMR because of its privacy feature, PLTR because evil has no limit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860205&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;hbar&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860217&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All world index fund.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860225&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860217&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;he thinks the world is going to get better&lt;br&gt;L&amp;#x27;Oréal m8. L&amp;#x27;Oréal.&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s the era of the byitch eurodollarpound.&lt;br&gt;Vest in byitches &amp;amp; hoes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860268&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858156&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;2x nasdaq&lt;br&gt;If that’s a long term hold you lose everything to decay&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860293&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Monero &amp;amp; xAI/SpaceX&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860302&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858027&lt;br&gt;ONE&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860596&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858027&lt;br&gt;XRP and it isn&amp;#x27;t even close.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860647&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;yoloing non disposable income on gamba&lt;br&gt;I wouldn&amp;#x27;t do anything like that because I&amp;#x27;m not a giga retard.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;hurr durr you&amp;#x27;ll never be heckin rich tho anon!&lt;br&gt;yeah no one on this miserable piece of shit board will be. and if they do/are they had disposable income to start with. gamba doesn&amp;#x27;t pay unless you can eat loss. period the end. dunno how many times we have to go over this before you shitters get that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860652&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858076&lt;br&gt;God bless you saar&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>[TICKER | 35.8/hr] My wife doesn’t appreciate long term investing — 52 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61853689</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61853689?lm=1771252495</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 14:34:55 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;My wife doesn’t appreciate long term investing&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61853689'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 52 • Updated: 2026-02-16 14:34 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;She doesn’t want to DCA, max out 401ks, max out Roth. She has her 20k savings before we married in a saving account getting 0.00% interest (sat there for like 5 years) I tried to explain a HYSA, money market, and VOO. What do I do?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853694&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;401k is for niggers though&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853699&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853689&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;What do I do?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Show her grocery store prices from 2019 and now. Show her prices from 2024 and now.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Show her how the government printed 4 trillion dollars from 2024 to now.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is a terrible time to invest though, there&amp;#x27;s only downside from here until you see trump on TV saying he needs to BRRRRR to save the nation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853700&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853689&lt;br&gt;Why should she waste her money investing when she could let you do it and simply take half of it whenever she wants?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854232&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853720&lt;br&gt;That sounds wonderful, but I can&amp;#x27;t seem to find an industrials-only ETF or mutual fund that would let me participate. Anybody want to recommend one?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854234&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853689&lt;br&gt;Why would your wife have any say over finances?&lt;br&gt;Get her preggers and put her to work in the kitchen&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854373&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854232&lt;br&gt;Google &amp;quot;DJIA index fund&amp;quot; and take your pick, or if that&amp;#x27;s too much work then &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;SPDR Dow Jones Industrial Average ETF Trust, ticker DIA&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854387&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854198&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854203&lt;br&gt;You can’t rape your wife dude.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854492&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853689&lt;br&gt;Women are fucking idiots and should be enslaved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855768&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853689&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Divorce her now. The marriage won&amp;#x27;t work long term, and if you have kids you&amp;#x27;ll lose them, too. This marriage was probably the worse decision you have ever made.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855836&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853689&lt;br&gt;buy a home? it&amp;#x27;s okay to have cash in the bank if you have lots of USD debt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61855863&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;people spend years on 4chins, learn nothing, and end up marrying the exact kind of dumb bitch multiple boards warned about &lt;br&gt;You deserve each other.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857234&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853689&lt;br&gt;if you&amp;#x27;re so smart, why aren&amp;#x27;t you rich (and so don&amp;#x27;t care about your wife&amp;#x27;s money)&lt;br&gt;turns out,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857329&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sure you can make a million if you dca and invest s thousand s month for 30 years. But in 30 years that&amp;#x27;d be worth 1000&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857335&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853925&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Too late to stack physical silver&lt;br&gt;If you can trade fiat for silver, it&amp;#x27;s not too late.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857348&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853689&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;She doesn’t want to DCA, max out 401ks, max out Roth&lt;br&gt;Good. She knows what she&amp;#x27;s doing&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857425&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854213&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I am a woman&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;writes like a man&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857474&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854213&lt;br&gt;I am also a woman.. tee hee silly anons don&amp;#x27;t hit on me &amp;lt;3&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857476&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854373&lt;br&gt;dow jones? more like down jones&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857589&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853689&lt;br&gt;Take an image of a shopping cart and show how every year it contains less items in exchange for the same money bill&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857596&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Im a man and I identify as a lesbian&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857600&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853689&lt;br&gt;You CANNOT fix low IQ. It’s her money anyway, let her having it erode there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858419&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853720&lt;br&gt;Now adjust for dxy, retard&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858459&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853689&lt;br&gt;I don&amp;#x27;t see the problem. You take her money and invest it for her. My wife was a bitch in the beginning, now when she questions my financial advice I just tell her to do what I say. And she does.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858474&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858419&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;reeee you can&amp;#x27;t fire all those DEI positions it makes me sad&lt;br&gt;I voted for this exact fucking thing&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858491&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853704&lt;br&gt;That&amp;#x27;s only because you&amp;#x27;re a poorfag in a lower tax bracket&lt;br&gt;(It&amp;#x27;s okay, I am too)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859752&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853848&lt;br&gt;Yeah, 100% this!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859980&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61855863&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Taking seriously the advice you receive on 4chan&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Uhhhh….&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859991&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;my wife&lt;br&gt;KYS in the most unimaginably painful way you redditor subhuman.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859998&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853689&lt;br&gt;Don&amp;#x27;t invest for other people unless you literally have complete power over them, they will resent you for them not having access to their money and will go out of their way to spend every penny of whatever allowance they get and test boundaries by overspending.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860464&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858419&lt;br&gt;Do you get payed for your diligent work?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860469&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;1pbitd&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;49 bot replies&lt;br&gt;This websites dead as fuck.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860480&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853689&lt;br&gt;Women are retards. My wife has brought me nothing but financial ruin. These hoes are out of control. If I didn’t have 3 kids I’d ghost this bitch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860658&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860464&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;payed&lt;br&gt;no and I believe your kind should be adressing me as &amp;quot;sir&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>[TICKER | 25.8/hr] $ICP just partnered with the government of Pakistan — 41 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61850558</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61850558?lm=1771252007</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 14:26:47 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;$ICP just partnered with the government of Pakistan&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61850558'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 41 • Updated: 2026-02-16 14:26 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=r-RmZyeuxzo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850566&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;ICY PEE PARTNERS WITH POO &lt;br&gt;so the prophecy was right icy pee poo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850573&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850566&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;WITH POO&lt;br&gt;You mean one of the most populated countries on planet Earth? Seethe more linky retard and kill yourself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850584&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850558&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I can tell this is hogwash because it&amp;#x27;s news anouncement via Youtube.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851040&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850566&lt;br&gt;The pee is icy but the poo/diarrhea is flaming hot. Together they make a super hero duo commanding the powers of ice cold piss and lava hot shit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851054&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850558&lt;br&gt;Won’t the Jews be upset with this?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851101&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850566&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851112&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850558&lt;br&gt;Holy fuck this is so BEARISH&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851240&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851054&lt;br&gt;Upset because of what? Because the icp devs bribes some pakistani to announce some bullshit on twitter?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851416&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851240&lt;br&gt;Why open your mouth when you don&amp;#x27;t know what you&amp;#x27;re saying?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851738&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850558&lt;br&gt;i&amp;#x27;ve been to the world computer summit in june last year and i&amp;#x27;ve talked to anyone in the team that i came across. let me tell you one thing; they&amp;#x27;re comfortable. they all get hundreds of thousands in salaries each year and could not care less about the price. at the event there were two very clear very seperate pockets. the VC&amp;#x27;s and the (((COMMUNITY))) and you could see the disgust in the eyes of the VC&amp;#x27;s for the community. any questions regarding tech or details to the team were answered dismissively, there is not an ounce of passion present in the entire team. i think all they care about is doing research on cryptography.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; i&amp;#x27;ve met the guy from openchat and he looked like he hadn&amp;#x27;t slept a full 8h in several weeks, he looked anxious and stressed.&lt;br&gt;when talking to the community members i&amp;#x27;ve probed for interesting projects, and literally the best project present was windoge98.&lt;br&gt;after that dominic played with an llm on stage for an hour straight everyone pretended it&amp;#x27;s the second coming of steve jobs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;they gave away bags of coffee because of caffeine.ai and it was unironically the best thing at the event. so good i even thought about licensing the coffee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851740&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851040&lt;br&gt;So Pakistanis are now jeets too?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851814&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850926&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;ppl&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851833&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851416&lt;br&gt;Im just guessing&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851740&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;So Pakistanis are now jeets too?&lt;br&gt;???? Always were. Bangladesh and Sri lanka too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61852144&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850558&lt;br&gt;The Saarnet&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61852793&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850584&lt;br&gt;Don&amp;#x27;t know about this one but poos did sign many crypto deals with trump. Ironically crypto has been dumping since&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853251&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851833&lt;br&gt;Pakistanis are white&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853281&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;61853251&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853296&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850611&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;AI licenses&lt;br&gt;So this is a thirdie government jumping the gun and getting in the way of something that people aren&amp;#x27;t doing yet to make sure that they don&amp;#x27;t start, just so they can take a cut if anyone dares to try. Classic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853824&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853296&lt;br&gt;Man shut the fuck up, you sound like a bitch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853832&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853281&lt;br&gt;racist&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853871&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850642&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850740&lt;br&gt;pakistans hate indians tho, its actually p based&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61853919&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853871&lt;br&gt;Only Indians can be jeets, end of&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854123&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851738&lt;br&gt;This checks out with my impression of DFINITY. They are extremely arrogant and have borderline disdain for their own users. And honestly the Pakistan news is demoralizing. Yes the tech is great but God damn I am down by about $50K. And mission 70 is not the solution -- gaining adoption is.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854128&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850558&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853824&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853832&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61853919&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;SARR PAKISTANIS ARE WHITE SARR&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854229&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For some reason I misread that as plundered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854266&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854128&lt;br&gt;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/India%E2%80%93Pakistan_relations&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854891&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854128&lt;br&gt;Pakistanis are more white than an average American lol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854914&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850566&lt;br&gt;holy kek..&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857209&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850566&lt;br&gt;witnessed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860272&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61854914&lt;br&gt;you kek at racism?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860593&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850558&lt;br&gt;ICPoo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860624&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850558&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;internet &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;computer&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;holy kek - only for Pookistani this might sound exotic and alluring&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>[TICKER | 21.9/hr] Oldfags I summon you — 32 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61856347</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61856347?lm=1771252456</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 14:34:16 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Oldfags I summon you&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61856347'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 32 • Updated: 2026-02-16 14:34 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oldfags I know you&amp;#x27;re still here. A lot of charts look like they&amp;#x27;ve bottomed. Tell me what to stack I have 3.8 BTC and looking to acquire alts as I think they will start pumping now the money printers returning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856352&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;looking to acquire alts&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856368&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856347&lt;br&gt;Took one of these Topgolf girls to a round of golf once and they were terrible lmao&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856433&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856368&lt;br&gt;What the fuck is a topgolf girl that girls swing is immaculate 99% of people at these ranges cannot hit a ball straight&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856470&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856433&lt;br&gt;Basically a topgolf girl is a girl who is only good at driving ranges and makes post on IG of their swings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856488&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856470&lt;br&gt;but why not hire a better looking whore? why take them golfing? you guys are weird&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856501&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856488&lt;br&gt;I didn&amp;#x27;t hire her. I just asked her out to go golfing with me&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856509&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856470&lt;br&gt;i looked her up that girl is a +2.1 handicap and would probably whoop both our asses&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856550&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856347&lt;br&gt;ethbtc is sus, I dont think cz is finished dumping on wintermute for now!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856551&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856347&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;looks like it bottomed&lt;br&gt;Holy shit I swear biz is full of handicapped newfags. Just check the previous cycles, the bear market started THREE MONTHS ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856682&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856347&lt;br&gt;how many bitcoin for a golf bunny like that?&lt;br&gt;also moar&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856732&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856347&lt;br&gt;old fags no longer hold crypto&lt;br&gt;t. old fag&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856793&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856732&lt;br&gt;this desu&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856797&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856347&lt;br&gt;we finna linu&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857022&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856488&lt;br&gt;The only weird guy are you assuming you have to hire a girl to go play golf with her&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857025&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856551&lt;br&gt;Nah everything was frontrunned, the alt bear market started more then a year ago&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857031&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;alts will never pump again&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;the only notable alt that pumped last cycle was xrp&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;unless you&amp;#x27;re counting like a 2-3x as pumping then goodluck, they can also fall 90% or more from here&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857237&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Binance coin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857946&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856509&lt;br&gt;You guys are faggots man&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857986&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61857025&lt;br&gt;this look to alts the bear market started in jan 2025&lt;br&gt;btc was just lucky some boomers pumped the etf to get a higher high in oct, but this market has been a ghost town for the past year&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858251&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856347&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;looking to acquire alts&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#x27;re doomed. Shitcoins aren&amp;#x27;t going to pump ever again. I sincerely doubt ETH will even survive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858300&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856347&lt;br&gt;Not an originalfag or a 2017 oldfag, but I am a 2019 unc. Get out now and for the love of God stay away from alts, not even memeing. The bear was confirmed the moment we closed under 100k.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I rotated to stocks back in November.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856551&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856732&lt;br&gt;this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858317&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856509&lt;br&gt;how&amp;#x27;d you find her name? also what is it? asking for a fren&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858346&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856732&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858300&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856551&lt;br&gt;jewish posts&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860179&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856433&lt;br&gt;I hit straight balls if you know what I mean :)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860219&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oldest fag possible. Migrated day one from /g/. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The real dumping hasn&amp;#x27;t started yet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860260&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856551&lt;br&gt;Looks ljke the next &amp;#x27;cycle&amp;#x27; is going to go alll the wayy to 155k.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860609&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meaningfully buying across any of these is extremely high confidence, with particular emphasis on the front end:&lt;br&gt;XRP, QNT, CC, XDC, ALGO, DAG, HBAR, XLM, SUI, SEI, APT, FLR, ONDO, NOM, ADA, HYPE, SOL, POL, ATOM, DAG, AAVE, DOT, VET, ZRO, RED.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860614&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ancientfag here (I used to mine btc on my gaming pc back in 2012)&lt;br&gt;why are faggots still falling for the jeetcoin rugpulls in &amp;lt;current year&amp;gt;?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860615&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Topgolf is retarded&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Everytime I went the place was filled with whores, niggers and trailer trash&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860630&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860615&lt;br&gt;this is everywhere except certain higher grocery stores.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860639&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856347&lt;br&gt;XRP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860653&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856347&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;a bitch like that will make more money in a year than 90% of normal men will make in a decade &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;women will still call this society a fucking patriarchy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>[TICKER | 15.2/hr] Thread 61858109 — 36 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858109</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858109?lm=1771249214</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 13:40:14 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Thread 61858109&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61858109'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 36 • Updated: 2026-02-16 13:40 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;Saylor will be liquida—ACK!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858119&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;So we have to short squeeze bitcoin until 8k? &lt;br&gt;Noted&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858128&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Challenge accepted&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858135&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858109&lt;br&gt;Hostile takeovers will take place long before that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858178&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858109&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;DUUUUDE YOU SHOULD TOTALLY TRUST WHAT SAYLOR SAYS BECAUSE....UH.....HE KNOWS WHAT HE&amp;#x27;S DOING!&lt;br&gt;holy shit OP you&amp;#x27;re a retard, he will be forced to resign if Bitcoin goes to 30k. He&amp;#x27;s already down -7 billion at this price&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858192&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858178&lt;br&gt;Were you born yesterday? Saylor wasn&amp;#x27;t liquidated through worse crashes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858216&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858109&lt;br&gt;Hes not going to sell&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858224&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858178&lt;br&gt;why does it matter if he&amp;#x27;s down 7 billion? the debt isn&amp;#x27;t due... seriously plz explain to me why it matters and why he can&amp;#x27;t just wait for the inevitable recovery?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858229&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858224&lt;br&gt;Explain how he repays creditors without diluting shareholders (baggies) to zero, if Bitcorn stays supressed for any significant period.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858234&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858229&lt;br&gt;the argument is that buttcorns stay at $8k for years? is that right?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858301&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858109&lt;br&gt;Im pretty sure a bank will call the loans long before it hits $8k because what the fuck would liquidating $6 billion of BTC do to the price even at todays levels?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858224&lt;br&gt;the banks will call in their loans if the collateral loses value long before $8k. retards like you dont understand that the bid/ask price is meaningless when you are trying to liquidate 715,000 btc. and that selling this in a short period of time would destroy order books and crash the market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858314&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858234&lt;br&gt;It doesn&amp;#x27;t need to, the stock is alreaady crashing because everyone knows he can;t keep up this scam for much longer. Even if the government is turning a blind eye now to his ponzi scheme.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858315&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Let&amp;#x27;s go 7.9k BTC!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858325&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858109&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;if Bitcoin falls to $8k, we have so much Bitcoin we could sell like you wouldn&amp;#x27;t even believe&lt;br&gt;Really confidence inspiring.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858370&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858128&lt;br&gt;CZ will either win or give us the greatest discount in history while he simultaneously send the whole crypto market to the brink of extinction&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858405&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858109&lt;br&gt;Btc to 7.9k confirmed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858418&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858109&lt;br&gt;So what happens when it drops to $7900?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858439&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858109&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858452&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858109&lt;br&gt;Anyone want to speculate what MSTR share price would be at BTC $8K …kek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858499&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858418&lt;br&gt;He just refinances with a finger snap. ezpz.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858501&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Don&amp;#x27;t they have to make payments on that debt though, which will draw down assets further&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858608&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858301&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; bank loans&lt;br&gt;Where did you even get this information from? Afaik he has only take one bank loan from SVB which was paid back a long time ago.&lt;br&gt;His debt comes from convertible notes which won&amp;#x27;t mature before the next cycle (not in this bear market unless it&amp;#x27;s a multi year bear).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; selling this in a short period of time would destroy order books&lt;br&gt;He would never sell on the open markets. He can sell it to OTC services which will be able to finance whatever amount he has to sell.&lt;br&gt;Some 2011 whale sold 80k BTCs to Galaxy Digital when BTC was trading at 110k.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858619&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This jew is a ponzi scam artist and crypto lards only support him because they think he is doing the work of finding greater fools which is what they need for their own bags to go up&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859185&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858171&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;price dumps to $8k in effort to liquidate saylor&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;unsuccessful&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;those sellers don&amp;#x27;t buy back in at giga-generational wealth creating dips&lt;br&gt;sounds like bitcoin ain&amp;#x27;t the one&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859214&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858501&lt;br&gt;bro they just refinance and roll it forward, its simple&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859218&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858171&lt;br&gt;Whales know it doesn&amp;#x27;t even have to go that low. Keeping it at 30-40k for a few years could be sufficient.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859228&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858234&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;$8k&lt;br&gt;Check MSTR&amp;#x27;s price action when bitcoin is around $70k right now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859235&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858178&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;lowering your DCA is le bad&lt;br&gt;Okay retard&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859963&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859228&lt;br&gt;what does that have to do with Strategy&amp;#x27;s obligation to sell BTC?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;did you even read the thread?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860237&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858501&lt;br&gt;lol no, their convertible notes have a 0% coupon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860245&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The jeet brain can&amp;#x27;t comprehend Strategy&amp;#x27;s business model.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860247&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858109&lt;br&gt;ChatGPT says ther total liabilities are actually 15BN as of q3 2025 filings, but that still gives them a 60BN net asset position. I guess they&amp;#x27;re actually in a pretty safe position in terms of debt/margin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860391&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858152&lt;br&gt;Too many other players with too much skin in the game for them to do this. Pension funds, corpos and governments are tied to bitcoin now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860465&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61860237&lt;br&gt;What about the coupé notes?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>[TICKER | 11.6/hr] Real Bitcoiners Don’t Flinch — 61 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61844089</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61844089?lm=1771238872</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 10:47:52 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Real Bitcoiners Don’t Flinch&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61844089'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 61 • Updated: 2026-02-16 10:47 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;If BTC dumps, you hold. If you’ve got conviction, volatility is just noise. You can even make it productive if you want, but that’s on you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61847281&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61844089&lt;br&gt;I want to buy more bitcoin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61847285&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61844089&lt;br&gt;Just bought ADA&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61847287&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61844089&lt;br&gt;Boy I&amp;#x27;m from Texas. We don&amp;#x27;t hedge, we double down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61848941&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61844089&lt;br&gt;This shit works on retarded new fags. We can tell that it&amp;#x27;s Bitcoin OGs that are selling. It&amp;#x27;s obvious they&amp;#x27;re pivoting to AI.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849001&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61848934&lt;br&gt;that still shows there’s room to grow anon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849022&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61848941&lt;br&gt;Rotation isn’t betrayal. OGs taking profit doesn’t mean BTC is dead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849056&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61844089&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;be a PROFESSIONAL bagholder&lt;br&gt;Lol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849078&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849056&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#x27;s just another hype ser&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849109&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849056&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Why represent Bitcoin coin with 1s and 0s, why not a golden coin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849190&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849109&lt;br&gt;Because BTC is code, not metal.&lt;br&gt;1s and 0s fits. A gold coin is just boomer cosplay.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849202&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849056&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;CENTRAL BANKING IS BAD!&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;But look, gold is good because central banks love it!&lt;br&gt;metalfags lol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849281&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849202&lt;br&gt;either you hate the system or you’re front-running it, not both.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849331&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61848266&lt;br&gt;BTC is only for store of value. Why saylor is into this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849336&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849109&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849190&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849360&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61847516&lt;br&gt;bring me back Celcius. I regret this platform&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849371&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849336&lt;br&gt;Why do you act like you know everything? We only want x100&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849378&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61848607&lt;br&gt;Is Bitcoin staking possible?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849429&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849371&lt;br&gt;I know enough to survive the fiat death fallout.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61849968&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849360&lt;br&gt;would love to have a porn actress managing my money&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850004&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849360&lt;br&gt;Celsius was “trust me bro” custody. That’s why it nuked. This is the opposite: your keys, no CeFi middleman, no backroom rehypothecation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850031&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849378&lt;br&gt;Yup, you can still earn yield on BTC in a few ways anon.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849968&lt;br&gt;Bro saw one selfie and decided she is a hedge fund manager.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850049&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849429&lt;br&gt;Just stay humble and keep stacking skills, not just coins.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850072&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850031&lt;br&gt;I saw her getting pounded, sucking a dick and she is talented&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61850114&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61850072&lt;br&gt;you must be satisfied with her kid&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851207&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849331&lt;br&gt;Because he’s not trying to trade. He wants to stack BTC and borrow against it like rich people do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61851807&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851207&lt;br&gt;I fucking hate people like that. This is literally what slumlords do. They buy and shit house at a foreclosure sale then rent it, then show the bank that they have income and get a loan for another house to do the same thing again. God damn parasites. I hope this mother fucker dies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61854185&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61851807&lt;br&gt;If you think the system is broken, focus on fixing the rules, not fantasizing about someone dying. That’s loser energy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856618&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849336&lt;br&gt;You really think so?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856674&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61847911&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61848277&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61848573&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61849022&lt;br&gt;kek baggies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858288&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61844089&lt;br&gt;real men never dump their wife&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858322&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856674&lt;br&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PSZxmZmBfnU&amp;amp;list=RDPSZxmZmBfnU&amp;amp;start_radio=1&lt;br&gt;Some where over the rainbow crypto gets up high. Over the other end of the rainbow crypto fags cry!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859775&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856674&lt;br&gt;Not convinced.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860139&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858288&lt;br&gt;Be a good man lol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>[TICKER | 9.7/hr] I think I accidentally built a chain that can’t stall — 52 replies</title><link>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61856571</link><guid>https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61856571?lm=1771238371</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 10:39:31 +0000</pubDate><description>Open</description><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;I think I accidentally built a chain that can’t stall&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://boards.4chan.org/biz/thread/61856571'&gt;Open thread&lt;/a&gt; • Replies: 52 • Updated: 2026-02-16 10:39 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OP&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Been working on a blockchain design alone for ~1 year. Not a fork. Not based on ETH or Cosmos. Entirely custom protocol.&lt;br&gt;noticed something strange while running validator simulations tonight.&lt;br&gt;Even when all validators go offline, the chain continues producing blocks.&lt;br&gt;Not fake blocks. Protocol-generated blocks. Deterministic. Verifiable. No consensus break.&lt;br&gt;This wasn’t originally the goal. It emerged from how ticket burning and slot timing interact.&lt;br&gt;Current properties:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; 3-second slots&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; leader selection via burned tickets (PoAsh)&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; protocol generates blocks if leader fails or no tickets eligible&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; chain never halts, even under 100% validator failure&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; validators can’t stall the chain intentionally or accidentally&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Still has bugs (pic related), but if this holds under edge cases, it removes one of the oldest failure modes in blockchain design: liveness collapse.&lt;br&gt;Still early. Still finding edge cases I didn’t anticipate.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Next test is validator rejoin after extended protocol-only operation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;posting devlogs elsewhere &amp;#x27;cause I kept losing simulation history when threads expire.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;devlogs: https://t [dot] me/+2SXaDc7CMYc4MTZh&lt;br&gt;posting validator logs, failures, and protocol behavior as they happen. easier than losing everything when threads expire.&lt;br&gt;can answer here too, but threads vanish.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Early replies (first 3)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856588&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Well have our boys in the lab run the data and get back to you when we have some results. Son, you might have just saved western civilization.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856601&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856588&lt;br&gt;current simulator shows protocol blocks advancing state root deterministically when no validator is eligible. still testing validator reintegration and fork resistance. bugs in pic related came from vault state transition edge case.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856604&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856571&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Not X, not Y, but Z.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;It&amp;#x27;s not X, it&amp;#x27;s Y&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thanks chatgpt, if I wanted to read ai gen shit, I would just message it myself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Latest replies (last 30, oldest → newest)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856983&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856955&lt;br&gt;probably.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61856989&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How do I track this obvious scam so I can buy some early and try to dump it ontop of someone else&amp;#x27;s head before it collapses and steals all of my money?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857011&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856989&lt;br&gt;no coin or market yet. still working on protocol and simulator. devlogs are here: https://t&lt;br&gt; [dot] me/+2SXaDc7CMYc4MTZh&lt;br&gt;github coming once core behavior is stable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857041&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856928&lt;br&gt;AIRDROPS ARE BACK ON THE MENU BOYS&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857393&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856571&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;accidentally&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857448&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856633&lt;br&gt;Absolute AI slop, anyone with any technical reasoning level above 0 IQ would understand u made like 3 logical mistakes there&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;node process same block independantly&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Resume ontop of that state&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;No validator proposal&lt;br&gt;And then ofc this doesnt stall? &lt;br&gt;Lol&lt;br&gt;Lmao even&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857466&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856604&lt;br&gt;Exactly my thoughts, chatgpt slop&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61857487&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856604&lt;br&gt;/thread&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61858876&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856712&lt;br&gt;Thank you. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Can you explain how this chain retains any sort of decentralization when validators are/were offline?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Can you walk me through the scenario when validators are offline but chain activity still occurs, and then one or more validators are brought back online? Give me the before, middle and end states&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859251&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61858876&lt;br&gt;good question. decentralization is preserved because protocol blocks are deterministic and computed independently by every node from prior state.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Timeline:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;before&lt;br&gt;validators are online and proposing normal blocks. chain advances normally. each block contains transactions, state transitions, and validator rewards.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;during validtor absence&lt;br&gt;if no validator proposes a block for a slot, the protocol generates one deterministically. this block contains no validator-driven economic activity, it just advances the chain state and slot number.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;every node computes the exact same protocol block independently from the previous state and slot number. no coordination or authority required, so no fork emerges.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;chain continuity is preserved, but no validator rewards or transaction selection occurs during this period.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;when validators return&lt;br&gt;validators sync to the latest chain state like normal. since protocol blocks are deterministic, all nodes converge on the same chain tip.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;validators then resume proposing normal blocks containing transactions and rewards. protocol blocks stop appearing as long as validators are active.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;so protocol blocks preserve continuity, but validators still control economic state transitions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859269&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859251&lt;br&gt;sorry if i&amp;#x27;m retarded but whats the point of validators if the chain just goes on by itself?&lt;br&gt;or did i misunderstand everything?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859282&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Selene&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Post adams apple and shoulder to hip ratio you abomination&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859286&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856571&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;tripfag&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;typical tranny-name&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;schizo programming ramble&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;still has bugs but&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859304&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859269&lt;br&gt;validators decide economic state. protocol blocks only preserve continuity.&lt;br&gt;protocol blocks don’t include validator rewards or transaction selection. they just advance the chain deterministically when nobody proposes a block.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;validators are still required for:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;including transactions&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;distributing rewards&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;performing meaningful state transitions&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;protocol blocks can&amp;#x27;t invent transactions or assign rewards. they only prevent the chain from stalling.&lt;br&gt;when validators return, they resume normal block production and economic activity continues as usual.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859307&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856571&lt;br&gt;Are you a tranny or vaxed?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859352&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As a validator, why should I accept blocks produced by other validators (granting them fee rewards and changing the state in ways that may be disadvantageous to me) rather than just letting empty blocks go by until it&amp;#x27;s my turn to validate? This would produce a bunch of forks, where every node has a separate chain with just empty blocks and their own validated blocks. Proof of work addresses this problem because the cost required to generate a single block is significant and roughly equivalent to just mining for the next one, so the right move is just to accept the latest block that&amp;#x27;s been mined and try again on the next. Proof of stake, or any similar mechanism where producing a block is low cost, doesn&amp;#x27;t result in this behavior.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859376&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;good question. the protocol still relies on fork choice rules and economic penalties to enforce convergence.&lt;br&gt;validators can’t safely ignore valid blocks from others because doing so puts their vault stake at risk. building on a fork that diverges from the canonical chain can result in slashing or loss of future eligibility.&lt;br&gt;protocol blocks don’t grant rewards and don’t create alternate economic history. they just advance the deterministic timeline when no validator proposes a block.&lt;br&gt;when a validator proposes a block, the fork choice rule makes the chain with the strongest economic backing (valid stake progression) the canonical one. rational validators follow that chain because diverging reduces their own expected rewards and risks penalties.&lt;br&gt;so protocol blocks preserve continuity, but economic consensus is still enforced through validator incentives and fork choice rules.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859380&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856571&lt;br&gt;Cool&lt;br&gt;How do I invest in your chain of the future and become rich from digital beans?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859388&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859380&lt;br&gt;there’s nothing to invest in yet. still working on protocol and simulator. no token, no market.&lt;br&gt;current focus is getting consensus and validator behavior stable first. testnet comes before any economic layer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859409&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thanks for the tip, I look forward to frontrunning the next /biz/ jeet scam&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859410&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859376&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;validators can’t safely ignore valid blocks from others because doing so puts their vault stake at risk.&lt;br&gt;But under the protocol, as you&amp;#x27;ve described it, there are K+1 valid blocks at any given slot: K for however many acceptable validators are allowed at that slot, plus the empty block. The empty block must be valid by virtue of the whole deterministic, non-stalling behavior you&amp;#x27;re trying to achieve. And there&amp;#x27;s no way to decide at a point in time *which* of those K+1 valid blocks is the canonical one. This would be equivalent to solving the race where two validators both propose a &amp;quot;real&amp;quot; block at the same time; you can&amp;#x27;t penalize a validator for accepting one valid block over another.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859444&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859410&lt;br&gt;you’re right if the protocol defines K+1 simultaneously-valid blocks for the same slot. that would be broken.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;in my design there isn’t “K acceptable validators per slot” — there’s a single slot leader chosen deterministically (ticket proof). so it’s 1 leader block max, not K.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;validity is:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;a “real” block is valid only if it includes the slot leader proof for that slot (ticket/VRF/etc)&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;if two different real blocks appear with the same leader proof, that’s equivocation slashable&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;the protocol/empty block is valid only if either (a) leader==None (no eligible ticket), or (b) the leader missed a hard deadline, after which any late leader block is invalid for that slot&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;so at any point in time there isn’t a set of K+1 valid candidates. either the leader block exists in-time and the empty block is invalid, or the deadline passes and the empty block is the only valid block for that slot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859479&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How is this different from the dozens/hundreds of other ETH killers that have emerged? Is it useful design and will I get rich if I buy?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859683&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61859479&lt;br&gt;not trying to be an “ETH killer.” different design focus.&lt;br&gt;main difference is deterministic liveness. chain advances even when no validator proposes a block. most chains implicitly depend on validator availability for forward progress.&lt;br&gt;protocol-generated blocks preserve continuity, while validators still control economic state transitions.&lt;br&gt;focus is on predictable long-term behavior and failure resistance, not maximum throughput or hype metrics.&lt;br&gt;there’s nothing to buy right now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859727&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Everyone in this thread literally needs to order a hooker and get laid.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859791&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The chain doesnt exist if no validator is running it retard&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In which process are said blocks supposedly be generated? Thin air? Ether?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859837&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856571&lt;br&gt;I dont believe in what you wrote here, but if in the few years in turns out to be true, ill find you and ill suck your dick.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859932&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856571&lt;br&gt;Do you have a telegram we can join to follow along? I want to secure an early bag. Please make us rich.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61859964&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856571&lt;br&gt;Oh stfu. You’re most likely a mid tier swe or a vibe coder who’s gotten too horny off of Claude &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Share your GitHub and I can validate this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;61860128&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;61856588&lt;br&gt;Fucking kek well done anon, I needed this today&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>